TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
JULY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1763	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Henry	B-pers
Buthurst	I-pers
+	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
J.	O
Eardly	O
Wilmot	O
||	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bredell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sydebottom	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodyer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Negus	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boorshere	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sherindine	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Juby	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beamont	I-pers
*	O
,	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Seaman	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beamont	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
ill.	O
John	B-pers
Makebridge	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crocket	I-pers
.	O
258	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
our	O
sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
secretary	B-place
's	I-place
office	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Custom-house	I-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
paper	O
lost	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
watched	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
concealed	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
seven	O
quires	O
of	O
printed	O
forms	O
,	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Attorney	O
General	O
's	O
opinion	O
on	O
duties	O
due	O
on	O
prize-goods	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
war	O
in	O
America	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
searching	O
her	O
basket	O
he	O
found	O
three	O
bundles	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
yearly	O
correspondence	O
from	O
three	O
different	O
parts	O
,	O
being	O
letters	O
from	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
business	O
of	O
merchants	O
from	O
the	O
out-ports	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
259	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilfully	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ortell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Prince's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
||	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
bed-curtains	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
a	O
window-curtain	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
poker	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen-fire	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
extinguished	O
by	O
timely	O
assistance	O
before	O
it	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
farther	O
damage	O
than	O
burning	O
the	O
curtain	O
and	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
wainscot	O
.	O
Diverse	O
persons	O
gave	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
insanity	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
account	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ortell	I-pers
.	O
Without	O
examining	O
the	O
evidences	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acq	O
.	O
260	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Ardesoif	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
Christian	B-pers
Ardesoif	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Stephen	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
toy-shop	O
at	O
Charing-cross	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
a	O
pair	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
weigh	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
up	O
another	O
pair	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
stopped	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beaver	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
this	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
call	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
where	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
buckles	O
into	O
a	O
hole	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
261	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
||	O
Charles	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
custody	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
another	O
lodger	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
any	O
body	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
strange	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
girl	O
,	O
named	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
drop	O
of	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
girl	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
262	O
,	O
263	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Alderton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Alderton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
major	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
service	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
passed	O
me	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
four	O
others	O
of	O
different	O
colours	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
seemingly	O
made	O
on	O
purpose	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
confessed	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Merryfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
prisoners	O
second	O
examination	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
themselves	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
pulled	O
them	O
half	O
way	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
after	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
quite	O
out	O
.	O
Price	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
and	O
Nichols	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackway	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
Price	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
his	O
behaviour	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Mouk	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
Nichols	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
within	O
a	O
week	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
extreamly	O
well	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
264	O
,	O
265	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
ruffled	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
all	O
fast	O
and	O
safe	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
night	O
the	O
family	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
his	O
daughter	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
cloaths	O
on	O
and	O
pursued	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
daughter	O
from	O
a	O
window	O
above	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
from	O
one	O
yard	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
alarmed	O
the	O
neighbours	O
from	O
his	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
die-house	O
concealed	O
between	O
two	O
water-tubs	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
what	O
business	O
,	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
following	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
ruffled	O
shirts	O
hanging	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Likess	I-pers
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
often	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
seeing	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Cope	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirts	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
daughter	O
that	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sheridan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
die-house	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Likess	I-pers
of	O
buying	O
the	O
shirts	O
of	O
Cope	O
.	O
Collins	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
and	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
carpenter	O
's	O
tools	O
,	O
No	O
246	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Cope	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
the	O
shirts	O
to	O
Likess	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Ann	B-pers
Blaney	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tragon	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Becher	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Meridey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Collins	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Cope	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
266	O
,	O
267	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
chrystal	O
sleeve-buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
Forrester	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
followed	O
immediately	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
shewed	O
some	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
being	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
denied	O
having	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
going	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
Morgan	O
delivered	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
two	O
pair	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Morgan	O
offered	O
him	O
his	O
silver	O
watch	O
to	O
indemnify	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
compounding	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
268	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
English	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
St.	I-place
Andrew-street	I-place
.	O
While	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
kitchen	O
to	O
dine	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
apprentice	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
which	O
before	O
were	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
his	O
relation	O
and	O
apprentice	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
often	O
walking	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
concealed	O
himself	O
and	O
watched	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
finding	O
she	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
throw	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wickin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
dresser	O
drawer	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
things	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
petticoat	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
fell	O
such	O
things	O
)	O
she	O
had	O
wore	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
but	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
she	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
charged	O
an	O
innocent	O
person	O
with	O
this	O
spoon	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
Jonas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Han	O
.	O
Bartholomew	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
270	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Blakey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tallon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Tallon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Blue	I-place
Ball	I-place
in	I-place
Poppin's-alley	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
four	O
hours	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
room-door	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
for	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
,	O
she	O
staid	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
bed	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
unlocked	O
my	O
buroe	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
wife	O
up	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
four	O
guineas	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tallon	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
wanted	O
a	O
pocket-handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
flew	O
and	O
tore	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
us	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
for	O
scandalizing	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
cried	O
murder	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
down	O
stairs	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
below	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
if	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
were	O
it	O
is	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
paper	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
six	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hollings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
has	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
master	O
gave	O
her	O
that	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
blow	O
her	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
mistress	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tawney	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hitson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
271	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
.	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
flaxen	O
Russia	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
manager	O
of	O
a	O
workhouse	O
in	O
Beech	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
ninety	O
or	O
an	O
hundred	O
ells	O
of	O
Russia	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
use	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
absconded	O
about	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
of	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
63	O
yards	O
at	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
justices	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Armonsteed	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
confession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
272	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
six	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
7	O
guineas	O
,	O
4	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Joseph	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Lamb-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spittle-fields	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
shoe	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nobody	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
shoe	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
into	O
your	O
cellar	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
sight	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
for	O
some	O
salmon	O
kits	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
by	O
groaping	O
about	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
your	O
money	O
lay	O
from	O
the	O
salmon	O
kits	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
quantity	O
and	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
money	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
!	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
salmon	O
kit	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
13	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
8	O
salmon	O
kits	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
fetched	O
them	O
away	O
by	O
two	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
kit	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
tubs	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
a	O
salmon	O
kit	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
necessary	O
being	O
so	O
near	O
,	O
somebody	O
that	O
went	O
there	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
a	O
kit	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
so	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
partners	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
blind	O
man	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
great	O
rogue	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
mother	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Quintam	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
bag	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
another	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Quintam	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Moon	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
use	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
dress	O
so	O
well	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
know	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
word	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shoe	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
ever	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
-	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
these	O
buckles	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
's	O
money	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
blast	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
black	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
under	O
salmon	O
kit	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
three	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Trueman	O
's	O
brew-house	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
prize	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
he	O
untied	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
he	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
rejoiced	O
his	O
heart	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
thirty	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
gold	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
George-Yard	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
it	O
all	O
into	O
gold	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
White	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
bag	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
black	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
black	O
by	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
as	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
me	O
but	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
273	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
linnen	O
purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
June	O
16	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Wilsdon	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
in	O
Hendon-wood-lane	B-place
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
horse	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
what	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pistol	O
tinder-box	O
)	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
that	O
minute	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
trifle	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
your	O
while	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
immediately	O
,	O
why	O
are	O
you	O
so	O
long	O
?	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
purse	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
let	O
my	O
horse	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Elstrey	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Plough	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
halfpence	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
many	O
shillings	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
three	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
purse	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
as	O
kind	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
just	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
law	O
will	O
allow	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nutkin	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
tinder-box	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
so	O
bright	O
?	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nutkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
joined	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
came	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
pistol	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
pulled	O
nothing	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
colard	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
called	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
halfpence	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
silver	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
purse	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
money	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
.	O
Nutkin	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
purse	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Nutkin	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
fright	O
I	O
owned	O
having	O
this	O
thing	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
tinder-box	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
274	O
,	O
275	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crosgall	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Crosgall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
Harvey	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
also	O
for	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
pillow	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
pillow	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
landlady	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnwell	I-pers
.	O
Dunn	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
30	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Harvey	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Harvey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
Dunn	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
lock	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
but	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
spouse	O
has	O
under	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
Harvey	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
276	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloath	O
coats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
plush	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
lace	O
hat-band	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
hole	O
broke	O
between	O
the	O
coach-house	O
and	O
stable	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
creep	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
intelligence	O
from	O
Christopher	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
box	O
coat	O
to	O
one	O
Powel	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
lost	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
footman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Felton	O
Harvey	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
coachman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
selling	O
the	O
coat	O
to	O
Powel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
27	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spence	O
,	O
near	O
Lewes	O
,	O
in	O
Sussex	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
his	O
things	O
found	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
at	O
Lewes	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
when	O
nor	O
where	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
brought	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
he	O
continued	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
with	O
this	O
difference	O
only	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
in	O
George-street	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
277	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
cloath	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buttons	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hickey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hickey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
brother	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
brother	O
there	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
cloaths	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
running	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
cloaths	O
,	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Finchley	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Steward	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Highgate	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
wig	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
at	O
Highgate	O
there	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
custody	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
wig	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
milk-woman	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
's	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
towards	O
White	O
Conduit-fields	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
1	O
or	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
from	O
Hornsey	O
going	O
towards	O
Holloway	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
wig	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
work	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
278	O
,	O
279	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bready	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Goldsbruf	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Goldsbruf	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Union	B-place
Court	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
two	O
penny	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
coat	O
in	O
pledge	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
for	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Petticoat-square	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3.	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
my	O
maid	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
this	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
.	O
(	O
Please	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
home	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
1	O
July	O
,	O
1763	O
.	O
The	O
Mark	O
of	O
X	O
Mary	O
Harris	O
.	O
)	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
name	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
then	O
;	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
concealed	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
and	O
bolster	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
.	O
Welch	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Bready	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
ignorant	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Cotton	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
below	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
walk	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
carrying	O
the	O
chest	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
Welch	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Wilson	O
,	O
No	O
166	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fludyer	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
money	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Castelli	I-pers
;	O
and	O
No	O
14	O
in	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Blackiston	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bourke	I-pers
.	O
280	O
,	O
281	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Emanuel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
shagreen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Goldring	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
March	O
24	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Goldring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
two	O
watches	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
M'Kenzie	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Robinson	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Pinchbeck	O
one	O
to	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
to	O
confirm	O
that	O
of	O
M'Kenzie	O
?	O
Goldring	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
282	O
,	O
283	O
,	O
284	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Myford	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
bullocks	O
livers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mathias	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Shortland	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
tripe-man	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Wood's-close	B-place
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
were	O
his	O
servants	O
;	O
a	O
liver	O
being	O
found	O
concealed	O
they	O
were	O
suspected	O
and	O
accused	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
livers	O
to	O
Shortland	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
that	O
Shortland	O
's	O
business	O
is	O
to	O
sell	O
tripe	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
selling	O
price	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
sell	O
again	O
is	O
6	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
Holmes	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
concerned	O
as	O
Myford	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Shortland	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Myford	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Holmes	O
and	O
Shortland	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Myford	O
tried	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
No	O
219	O
in	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
285	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Moses	B-pers
Geebens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
in	O
Brokers-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
pottage-pot	O
from	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
286	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lewis	B-pers
Mackely	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
did-break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
worsted	O
purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
15	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
de	I-pers
Magalin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
did	O
steal	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Jonas-Court	B-place
,	I-place
East-Smithfield	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Greek	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
twelve	O
after	O
having	O
fastened	O
the	O
house	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
being	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
Anthonis	O
Golsalvis	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
also	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Magalin	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
The	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
broke	O
from	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
latch	O
quite	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
6	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
his	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee	O
buckles	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
We	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
Golsalvis	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
money	O
all	O
safe	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
playing	O
the	O
rogue	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
knock	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
disturb	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
Golsalvis	O
and	O
Nesbit	O
to	O
guard	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
woman	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
another	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
she	O
produced	O
9	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
language	O
did	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
In	O
Spanish	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
De	I-pers
Magalin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Portugal	O
sailor	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Blenheim	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
together	O
in	O
Francis	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
near	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
ship-mate	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
we	O
received	O
our	O
money	O
at	O
Plymouth	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
7	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
breeches	O
knees	O
,	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
Golsolvis	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
awaked	O
me	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
and	O
said	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
?	O
I	O
awaked	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
shutters	O
broke	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Cole	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
from	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
joke	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
produce	O
the	O
9	O
half	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Joe	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
afraid	O
I	O
'll	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
that	O
I	O
spent	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swan-alley	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
with	O
2	O
Irish	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
tired	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
this	O
purse	O
and	O
10	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
nine	O
I	O
kept	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
of	O
2	O
guineas	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
buckles	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
insisted	O
upon	O
knowing	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Anthonio	O
Golsalvis	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
's	O
about	O
5	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sash	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
inquiring	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Cole	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
to	O
every	O
thing	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
mentioned	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
goes	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
287	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Kenzer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
canvas	O
tarpaulin	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
||	O
Mr.	O
Smart	O
's	O
barge	O
lay	O
at	O
anchor	O
in	O
Lime-house	B-place
hole	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
to	O
leave	O
the	O
tarpaulin	O
out	O
into	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
row	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
George	B-pers
Jerrard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
work	O
'd	O
the	O
barge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tarpaulin	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
boat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
288	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Pearcey	B-pers
Gouldin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Hanover	O
Packet	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
steerage	O
where	O
my	O
hammock	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
buckles	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat-pocket	O
in	O
my	O
hammock	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jerviso	O
's	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jervise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
Old	O
Stairs	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
these	O
buckles	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
weighed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
23	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jervise	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Jervise	O
bought	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
long	O
trowsers	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
289	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brinklow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elrington	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elrington	I-pers
.	O
This	O
note	O
was	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
405	O
l.	O
at	O
the	B-place
Horse	I-place
Guards	I-place
,	O
March	O
31	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
o'clock	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
H.	O
No	O
.	O
240	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Co.	O
dated	O
17	O
Feb.	O
1763	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
paid	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
tried	O
here	O
for	O
stealing	O
these	O
notes	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
174	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
)	O
And	O
one	O
thing	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
when	O
Clark	O
pressed	O
between	O
the	O
pillar	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
searching	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
two	O
women	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
those	O
two	O
women	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
dressed	O
in	O
black	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
tallish	O
man	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
very	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
shorter	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
confusion	O
upon	O
losing	O
my	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
eye	O
so	O
fixt	O
upon	O
Clark	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
suspected	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
that	O
notice	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
himself	O
Brown	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
plate	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
deep	O
mourning	O
;	O
Brown	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
settle	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
they	O
bought	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
27	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Brown	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
Bank	O
note	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Castles	O
and	O
Wheatley	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
very	O
few	O
tradesmen	O
kept	O
so	O
much	O
cash	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
have	O
you	O
no	O
smaller	O
notes	O
?	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
smaller	O
notes	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
smaller	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
Brown	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
this	O
25	O
l.	O
note	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
remainder	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
seemed	O
equally	O
concerned	O
in	O
buying	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
in	O
chusing	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
sleeve	O
mocha	O
buttons	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
one	O
looked	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
looked	O
out	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
also	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
salts	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
equally	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Brown	O
said	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Hector	O
,	O
Williams	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
India	O
trade	O
21	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
brown	O
,	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
considerably	O
shorter	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
always	O
putting	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
neck	O
below	O
his	O
ear	O
.	O
My	O
young	O
man	O
made	O
observation	O
on	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fear	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
observed	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
they	O
staid	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drank	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
little	O
negus	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
looking	O
over	O
a	O
warning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
such	O
a	O
note	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
``	O
No	O
.	O
H	B-pers
.	I-pers
240	O
,	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Henry	O
``	O
Hoare	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
upon	O
``	O
demand	O
,	O
25	O
l.	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
for	O
``	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Co.	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
''	O
John	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
last	O
Michaelmas	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
black	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reynold	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
plate	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
they	O
bought	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
salt-sellers	O
,	O
2	O
milk-pots	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
all	O
laid	O
out	O
27	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
man	O
looked	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
short	O
one	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Brown	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
my	O
master	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
master	O
a	O
large	O
note	O
,	O
master	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
smaller	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
smaller	O
;	O
then	O
Brown	O
gave	O
master	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
2	O
guineas	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
minded	O
a	O
scar	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
rubbing	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
goldsmith	O
and	O
jeweller	O
,	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
High	O
Street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
somebody	O
rang	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
tea	O
spoons	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
mistress	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
served	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
mistress	O
must	O
change	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
notes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
to	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
and	O
change	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
came	O
to	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
dressed	O
in	O
mourning	O
,	O
I	O
passed	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
hard	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
having	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
dubious	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
bundles	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
shorter	O
thick	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
since	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
now	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
talk	O
thin	O
man	O
pitted	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
brown	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
White-chapel-bars	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
whether	O
they	O
joyned	O
the	O
two	O
in	O
mourning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
and	O
late	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
10	O
years	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Garden-Court	O
,	O
Baldwin's-gardens	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
a	O
tin-man	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
years	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Bisset	I-pers
,	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tempkins	I-pers
,	O
an	O
edge-tool-maker	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
all	O
spoke	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
290	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
Patrick	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
three	O
India	O
bonds	O
,	O
value	O
105	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joachim	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Joachim	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
Bass	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
bankers	O
,	O
messrs.	O
Honeywood	O
and	O
Fuller	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
banker	O
's	O
book	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
accounts	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
India	O
bonds	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
coach	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
,	O
my	O
book	O
stood	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
broker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sivers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Change-alley	O
,	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
num-	O
numbers	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
Jonathan	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
advertized	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
first	O
20	O
,	O
then	O
30	O
,	O
then	O
40	O
guineas	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
examined	O
Steers	O
and	O
Stevens	O
who	O
had	O
offered	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
(	O
See	O
their	O
trials	O
,	O
No	O
19	O
and	O
20	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
)	O
by	O
proving	O
the	O
bonds	O
my	O
property	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
bonds	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
No	O
30623	O
,	O
and	O
30687	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
No	O
21077	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
more	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
;	O
near	O
the	O
Poultry	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
got	O
round	O
him	O
while	O
Casey	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
writing	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
soon	O
destroyed	O
that	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
bonds	O
for	O
an	O
100	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
numbers	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
21077	O
,	O
30623	O
,	O
30687	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
particular	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
payable	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
tavern	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bonds	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
tavern	O
now	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
coal	O
merchant	O
,	O
at	O
Shadwell-dock	O
,	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
buy	O
stolen	O
goods	O
of	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
that	O
money	O
shared	O
amongst	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
horses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
more	O
than	O
3	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Cock	O
Inn	O
that	O
morning	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
of	O
picking	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
also	O
many	O
other	O
days	O
besides	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Cock	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
evidence	O
Fuller	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Brinklow	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
drank	O
there	O
in	O
company	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
291	O
,	O
292	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
9203	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Brinklow	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
,	O
waiting	O
about	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
should	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
pocket-books	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
take	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
go	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
Change	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Lombard-street	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
as	O
near	O
him	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
Parsons	O
and	O
Hayes	O
stopped	O
or	O
interrupted	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
Cole	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right-side	O
pocket	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
rememberance	O
Brinklow	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
book	O
was	O
soon	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
Brinklow	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
near	O
us	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
by	O
London-Bridge	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
a	O
boat	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
another	O
;	O
the	O
boats	O
came	O
pretty	O
close	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
paid	O
the	O
waterman	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
us	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
Brinklow	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
I	O
went	O
below	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Lumbley	O
's	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Raven	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
expected	O
they	O
all	O
would	O
have	O
came	O
,	O
(	O
we	O
all	O
frequented	O
that	O
house	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
James	O
Hall	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
where	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
feed	O
my	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
Cole	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
James	O
Hall	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Brinklow	O
,	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Hayes	O
,	O
and	O
Watson	O
,	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
Parsons	O
produced	O
a	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
notes	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
payable	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
9203	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
other	O
notes	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
one	O
advertised	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
trust	O
my	O
companions	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
practice	O
that	O
we	O
all	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
cheat	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
We	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
Watson	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
but	O
13	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
at	O
15	O
l.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
suited	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
spare	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Lumbley	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
Watson	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
dined	O
off	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
lamb	O
and	O
cabbage	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
Watson	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
13	O
l.	O
Parsons	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
apprehend	O
went	O
to	O
Watson	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
brought	O
13	O
l.	O
we	O
equally	O
divided	O
it	O
among	O
us	O
5	O
,	O
taking	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
lost	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
remembered	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
trade	O
a	O
wheel-wright	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
an	O
inn	O
at	O
Reading	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
that	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dealt	O
in	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
traded	O
in	O
goods	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
thief	O
about	O
3	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
once	O
had	O
a	O
complaint	O
lodged	O
against	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
for	O
having	O
false	O
or	O
diminished	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
committed	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
after	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
this	O
discovery	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
of	O
other	O
facts	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
acknowledge	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Wilks	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Cockbourn	O
say	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Wilks	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Fuller	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tog	O
ether	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
drank	O
together	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
intimate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
may	O
they	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Wilks	O
.	O
May	O
be	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
times	O
;	O
sometimes	O
once	O
,	O
sometimes	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
times	O
,	O
40	O
times	O
.	O
Wilks	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
.	O
James	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat-sheaf	O
in	O
Purple-lane	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Fuller	O
drink	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
they	O
knew	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
never	O
but	O
three	O
times	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
but	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
293	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Lucy	B-pers
Bruguiere	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
knowingly	O
and	O
designedly	O
,	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
,	O
obtaining	O
from	O
Spencer	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
his	O
servant	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stellings	I-pers
,	O
five	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
three-quartered	O
mantua	O
,	O
by	O
pretending	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Minet	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Minet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stellings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
other	O
rich	O
goods	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
between	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
and	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stellings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
Morris	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
mercer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
come	O
often	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
she	O
came	O
for	O
5	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
3-quarter	O
'd	O
mantua	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Minet	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
white	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Minet	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary-Axe	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
are	O
mantua	O
makers	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Minet	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
for	O
5	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
another	O
petticoat	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Minet	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
suspect	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
imposition	O
?	O
Stellings	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
sent	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
that	O
day	O
been	O
and	O
had	O
22	O
yards	O
of	O
garnet	O
ground	O
brocade	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
brocade	O
of	O
me	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
skimming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
dressed	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
blind	O
me	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
brother	O
;	O
(	O
whispering	O
very	O
softly	O
)	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
can	O
I	O
have	O
2	O
yards	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
silk	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
carry	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
here	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
alarm	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
passed	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
goods	O
fairly	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
step	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
garnet	O
ground	O
brocade	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
this	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
silk	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Minet	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
servants	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
order	O
for	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
silks	O
from	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Steallings	O
.	O
The	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
5	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
mantua	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
alamode	O
.	O
The	O
18th	O
,	O
9	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
and	O
blue	O
3-quarter	O
'd	O
figur	O
'd	O
strip	O
'd	O
tobine	O
,	O
4	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
,	O
6	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
black	O
persian	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
green	O
half	O
ell	O
.	O
The	O
19th	O
,	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
half	O
ell	O
Persian	O
The	O
25th	O
,	O
10	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
white	O
3-quarter	O
'd	O
tobine	O
,	O
5	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
crimson	O
sattin	O
,	O
5	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
black	O
ditto	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
crimson	O
half	O
ell	O
Persian	O
The	O
17th	O
,	O
4	O
ells	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
blue	O
sattin	O
,	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
ditto	O
,	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
half	O
ell	O
sarsnet	O
,	O
6	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
black	O
half	O
ell	O
ditto	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
Italian	O
mantua	O
.	O
May	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
22	O
yards	O
of	O
garnet	O
ground	O
flower	O
'd	O
gimp	O
brocade	O
,	O
19	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
3	O
quarter	O
'd	O
Italian	O
mantua	O
,	O
10	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
half	O
ell	O
alamode	O
,	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
half	O
ell	O
sarsnet	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
yards	O
1-eight	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
.	O
This	O
closes	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
67	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
she	O
had	O
all	O
those	O
of	O
me	O
under	O
pretence	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Minet	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
punctual	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
every	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
general	O
bill	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Minet	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
ordered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
goods	O
for	O
her	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
's	O
for	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
silk	O
mentioned	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
ever	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
hands	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
working	O
for	O
her	O
was	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Humphry	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
them	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
her	O
mother	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Duniere	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
11	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
13	O
years	O
and	O
6	O
months	O
old	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
mother	O
and	O
sister	O
were	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
good	O
examples	O
set	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
out	O
of	O
compassion	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
obtaining	O
the	O
5	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
3-quarter	O
'd	O
mantua	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gilyard	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Gilyard	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
down	O
Hounsditch	B-place
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
lodgings	O
at	O
their	O
request	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
more	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
watchman	O
going	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
brought	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
all	O
about	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
snatched	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
named	O
Joe	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
this	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
hold	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
going	O
to	O
hit	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
offered	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
fell	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Gilyard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
disguised	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
money	O
last	O
?	O
Gilyard	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
punctually	O
say	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
295	O
,	O
296	O
,	O
297	O
,	O
298	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Foulder	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bond	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wybourn	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wybourn	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
value	O
400	O
l.	O
and	O
diverse	O
promissory	O
notes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	B-place
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
tavern	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
spending	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
my	O
attorney	O
;	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Vine-Office-Court	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wright	O
;	O
he	O
accosted	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
Holo	O
,	O
Brother	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
brother	O
.	O
What	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
brother	O
?	O
then	O
tip	O
us	O
your	O
Manus	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
upon	O
giving	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hearty	O
shakes	O
he	O
declared	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
Mason	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
none	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
brother	O
a	O
coming	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
examine	O
you	O
;	O
then	O
Foulder	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
Wright	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
pretends	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mason	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
examine	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
rascal	O
for	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
abuse	O
me	O
for	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
foul	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
words	O
proceeded	O
to	O
blows	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
I	O
believe	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
charge	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
unluckily	O
my	O
watchman	O
was	O
off	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
ill	O
using	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
Foulder	O
seized	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
then	O
Hicks	O
and	O
Cooper	O
came	O
up	O
(	O
all	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
)	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
got	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
Foulder	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
accuse	O
me	O
with	O
being	O
a	O
highwayman	O
or	O
street-robber	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
at	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
before	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Blackiston	I-pers
,	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
settling	O
my	O
affairs	O
with	O
my	O
attorney	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
were	O
these	O
notes	O
and	O
bond	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
I	I-pers
missed	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
searched	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wright	O
fumbled	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
all	O
among	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
could	O
stop	O
payment	O
when	O
I	O
pleased	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wondered	O
how	O
I	O
could	O
charge	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
book	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
before	O
Sir	O
Matthew	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
opened	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
indictment	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
evidences	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
book	O
produced	O
,	O
a	O
bond	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
dated	O
June	O
19	O
,	O
1761	O
,	O
for	O
400	O
l.	O
A	O
note	O
,	O
dated	O
June	O
27	O
,	O
1761	O
,	O
for	O
128	O
l.	O
Another	O
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
,	O
1762	O
,	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
Another	O
for	O
247	O
l.	O
Another	O
,	O
July	O
26	O
,	O
1761	O
,	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Another	O
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
,	O
1761	O
,	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
)	O
These	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
when	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wybourn	I-pers
,	O
son	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wybourn	I-pers
deceased	O
,	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
certifies	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
father	O
,	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
being	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
their	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
looks	O
at	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
declares	O
the	O
signing	O
his	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
questions	O
asked	O
how	O
Wright	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
began	O
begging	O
mercy	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
any	O
positive	O
answer	O
how	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
all	O
declared	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
Wright	O
himself	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Sir	O
Matthew	O
committed	O
two	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
,	O
all	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
seeing	O
Wright	O
pull	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
pocket-book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Blackiston	I-pers
.	O
Wright	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
was	O
excessively	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
and	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
book	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
merry	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
For	O
Wright	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marfleet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Wright	O
about	O
18	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
merchant	O
at	O
Boston	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
footman	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
industrious	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
8	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Countess	O
of	O
Orkney	O
's	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Obrien	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
2	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
could	O
do	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Norgrove	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
3	O
years	O
;	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Maud	I-pers
,	O
about	O
9	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
about	O
3	O
;	O
and	O
Americost	O
Backhurst	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Wright	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Foulder	O
,	O
Hicks	O
,	O
and	O
Cooper	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
299	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Beaton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Edward	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
in	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Kingsland	B-place
and	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Islington	B-place
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
chaise	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
their	O
faces	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
nor	O
buckles	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
it	O
advertized	O
a	O
gentleman	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
amongst	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
other	O
robberies	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
things	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
evidence	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
Stevenson	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Everard	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mossady	I-pers
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
unsupported	O
by	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
300	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
4	O
guineas	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
John	O
Smithson	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
4	O
guineas	O
near	O
the	B-place
Three	I-place
Mackerols	I-place
,	I-place
Mile-end-road	I-place
,	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
watch	O
was	O
advertised	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
301	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
on	O
the	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
tortoishell	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
moidore	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
from	O
Kingsland	B-place
turnpike	I-place
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
but	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
thought	O
it	O
needless	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
detained	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
in	O
Surry	O
and	O
Essex	O
.	O
302	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Russel-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
betwixt	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
coats	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
10	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
hung	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
coats	O
to	O
shew	O
among	O
the	O
salesmen	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
stop	O
the	O
coat	O
if	O
brought	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Arnold	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
stop	O
the	O
coat	O
if	O
brought	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
.	O
)	O
Brown	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Butterley	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
staid	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Pritchard	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
mentioned	O
a	O
woman	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pap-boat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Goodgar	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
Tower-hill	B-place
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
feeding	O
the	O
child	O
with	O
the	O
pap-boat	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
rang	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
she	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
