TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1763	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Sydney	O
Stafford	O
Smythe	O
+	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was-tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hazlefoot	I-pers
,	O
Coles	B-pers
Fortrice	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Trout	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Roberson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
,	O
Bullwin	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Treslove	I-pers
,	O
Collin	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Channon	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
141	O
,	O
142	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
bars	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Muleman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Muleman	I-pers
,	O
Esqrs	O
.	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
This	O
indictment	O
was	O
founded	O
upon	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
witness	O
to	O
support	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
other	O
bars	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Ross	O
and	O
Muleman	O
,	O
Esqrs	O
.	O
March	O
4th	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
one	O
Turner	O
,	O
a	O
waterman	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
dodged	O
three	O
soldiers	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
each	O
with	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
our	O
wharf	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
wharf	O
?	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
called	O
Dyers-hall	B-place
wharf	I-place
,	O
the	O
nearest	O
iron-wharf	O
to	O
London	O
bridge	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
twelve	O
bars	O
of	O
four	O
inches	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
broad	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
thick	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
feet	O
long	O
,	O
not	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
length	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Collins	B-pers
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
had	O
worked	O
at	O
our	O
wharf	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
three	O
bars	O
of	O
iron	O
were	O
also	O
there	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
twelve	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
hammer	O
when	O
the	O
iron	O
is	O
hot	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
sort	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
called	O
a	O
double	O
bullet	O
.	O
Bringing	O
them	O
to	O
Wood-street-Compter	O
,	O
Collins	O
began	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
three	O
other	O
bars	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
had	O
taken	O
these	O
three	O
bars	O
also	O
from	O
our	O
wharf	O
,	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
messrs.	O
Ross	O
,	O
and	O
Co	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
iron	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
with	O
each	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
coming	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
wharf	O
to	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
belongs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Jewry	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
pitched	O
the	O
bars	O
;	O
we	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
look	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
to	O
observe	O
whether	O
we	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
iron	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cart	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
sixpence	O
each	O
for	O
carrying	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
whom	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
?	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
pitched	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
met	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
paper	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
stampt	O
on	O
the	O
iron	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
White	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
's	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
each	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Lewis	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
followed	O
and	O
questioned	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
they	O
stopt	O
us	O
and	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
evidence	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
bars	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
seven	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Addison	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
Collins	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
where	O
the	O
bars	O
stood	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Lewis	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
.	O
Davis	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
his	O
first	O
cousin	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
143	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jenings	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
fowls	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Read	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Poulterer	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
market	I-place
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
six	O
minutes	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
missed	O
six	O
fowls	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
fowls	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
having	O
been	O
gnawed	O
by	O
mice	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
be	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
some	O
dead	O
fowls	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
four	O
dead	O
fowls	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
observing	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
fowls	O
down	O
upon	O
an	O
empty	O
cask	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
be	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
his	O
fowls	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
That	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
fowls	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
along	O
he	O
much	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
let	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Brewer-street	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Christopher	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Cross-street	O
,	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
144	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
separate	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
washed	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
chaired	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
facing	O
Hungerford	O
market	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
and	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
person	O
;	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
she	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
145	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
45	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
fixt	O
to	O
a	O
messuage	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Jonathan	B-pers
David	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
produced	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Parr	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
repairing	O
two	O
houses	O
belonging	O
to	O
Esquire	O
Norton	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
a	O
gutter	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
rambling	O
about	O
to	O
get	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
three	O
sailors	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Bell-yard	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
be	O
should	O
carry	O
that	O
lead	O
for	O
them	O
cross	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
146	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Gatfield	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
29	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
accomplice	O
and	O
evidence	O
against	O
James	O
Hardy	O
,	O
No	O
191	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fludyer	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
147	O
,	O
148	O
,	O
149	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Miles	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Bryan	B-pers
Donnelly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Owen	B-pers
Keney	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
twelve	O
silver	O
coat-buttons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
gilt	O
band	O
for	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
hat-buckle	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
gilt	O
,	O
one	O
ducat	O
,	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
eight	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	B-place
Drum	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Thomas's-street	I-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Donnelly	O
and	O
Cook	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
below	O
;	O
Cook	O
brought	O
me	O
up	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
cellar	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
to	O
take	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
gold	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
my	O
door	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
missing	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
who	O
was	O
last	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
Cook	O
,	O
Donnelly	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Donnelly	O
's	O
lodging	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
wife	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
Cook	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
sufficiency	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
make	O
money	O
of	O
.	O
(	O
Donnelly	O
is	O
a	O
seaman	O
lately	O
come	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Dragon	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
had	O
information	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
secured	O
at	O
the	O
Bull's-head	O
in	O
Stretton-street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
coat	O
buttons	O
,	O
my	O
hat-band	O
,	O
and	O
hat-buckle	O
taken	O
out	O
ofDonnelly	O
's	O
left	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Cook	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
dear	O
Cook	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
could	O
rob	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
us	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
proceeded	O
to	O
search	O
Cook	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
my	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
my	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
ducat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
ladle	O
,	O
a	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chain	O
washed	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
child	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
also	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
2	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
groat	O
,	O
a	O
king	O
James	O
's	O
groat	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
half	O
crowns	O
.	O
Keney	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
A	O
coach-man	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
all	O
this	O
morning	O
;	O
meaning	O
Keney	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Keney	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gay	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
Keney	O
to	O
stoop	O
back	O
and	O
drop	O
something	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
watches	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
case	O
flew	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
fall	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
thrust	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Keney	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Sprage	I-pers
,	O
a	O
headbrough	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
.	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
of	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
br	O
each	O
of	O
trust	O
;	O
he	O
trusted	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
cellar-door	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
money	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
chair	O
.	O
He	O
knocked	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
guinea	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
8	O
s.	O
He	O
had	O
every	O
farthing	O
again	O
.	O
Donnelly	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
knowed	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
your	O
Lordship	O
does	O
,	O
Cook	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
buttons	O
,	O
I	O
knowed	O
nothing	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Keney	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Cook	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
these	O
had	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
Keney	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fruiterer	O
opposite	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Keney	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
he	O
has	O
portered	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Cook	O
and	O
Donnelly	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Keney	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
150	O
,	O
151	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
money	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
a	O
fire	O
broke	O
out	O
near	O
Wapping	B-place
new	I-place
stairs	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
what	O
little	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
were	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
examined	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
the	O
boy	O
confessed	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
boy	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
d.	O
he	O
confessed	O
also	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
eight	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
mother	O
?	O
Montague	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
pretty	O
near	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
works	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
school	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
into	O
an	O
ill	O
habit	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Keney	I-pers
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
152	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Jefferyn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hibbins	I-pers
,	O
doctor	O
of	O
physic	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
;	O
one	O
blue	O
silk	O
and	O
silver	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
silver	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
brown	O
silk	O
and	O
gold	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
sattin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tissue	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
tissue	O
negligee	O
,	O
one	O
pompadour	O
silk	O
negligee	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
blue	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hibbins	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	B-pers
Hibbins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
advertised	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Hibbins	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
Miss	O
Hibbins	O
lies	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
before	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Hibbins	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
then	O
shut	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
sash	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
up	O
to	O
keep	O
open	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
put	O
up	O
of	O
itself	O
it	O
would	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
we	O
imagine	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
must	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
window	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murkwate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
sister	O
brought	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
silk	O
sack	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
negligee	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
Murkwate	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
ONeal	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
former	O
mistress	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
in	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
these	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
bring	O
them	O
?	O
Murkwate	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
pompadour	O
silk	O
sack	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Noakes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
doctor	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
duplicates	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
pawned	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
tickets	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
and	O
this	O
paper	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
paper	O
)	O
the	O
maid	O
declared	O
the	O
mistress	O
's	O
silver	O
cloaths	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
from	O
tarnishing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
lodging	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
named	O
Stoaks	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
this	O
key	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
in	O
their	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
liberty	O
to	O
try	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
opened	O
the	O
late	O
Lord	O
Warwick	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
Dr.	O
Hibbins	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
from	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
doctor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
walk	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
safety	O
to	O
the	O
doctor	O
's	O
garret	O
window	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
Stoaks	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stoaks	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
relation	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brockhurst	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brockburst	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
my	O
counting-house	O
was	O
privately	O
entered	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
desk	O
and	O
my	O
clerk	O
's	O
desk	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
few	O
halfpence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
discovered	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
of	O
her	O
son	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
threats	O
she	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
in	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Devoe	I-pers
through	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
counting-house	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
broke	O
both	O
the	O
desks	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
it	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
15	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
33	O
l.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
apprentice	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
charity-school	O
.	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
better	O
than	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
considerable	O
charges	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
wrong	O
me	O
before	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
lad	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
worth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
almost	O
drunk	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
154	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Burrel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Kenedy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
tugs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Julius	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
,	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
collarmaker	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
his	O
apprentice	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
tugs	O
to	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
155	O
,	O
156	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Paston	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
140	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
little	O
affair	O
at	O
Trig-stairs	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
repairing	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soil-pipe	O
that	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
remove	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
to	O
send	O
some	O
workmen	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
clerk	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
it	O
weighed	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
600	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
pounds	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
ill	O
practices	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
Messrs.	O
Wills	O
and	O
Mitchel	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Nightrider's-street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
measured	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
32	O
feet	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
measured	O
the	O
lead	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
none	O
diminished	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
into	O
many	O
pieces	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Woodby	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
lead	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
information	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	O
alehouse	O
on	O
Labour-in-vain-hill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
south-side	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
pitched	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
stones	O
by	O
the	O
rails	O
.	O
Paston	O
called	O
Tom	O
;	O
Tom	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
ale-house	O
up	O
Distaff-lane	O
into	O
Paul	O
's	O
church-yard	O
.	O
After	O
Waters	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
Paston	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
Waters	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Black-swan-alley	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
desired	O
a	O
young	O
lad	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
carried	O
one	O
piece	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
by	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Starling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Rummer	O
on	O
Labour-in-vain-hill	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
7	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Waters	O
came	O
through	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
lead	O
in	O
your	O
stable	O
,	O
will	O
it	O
be	O
safe	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
something	O
a	O
bar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
wat	O
e	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
carpenter	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
;	O
the	O
carpenter	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
stolen	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
in	O
so	O
careless	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
a	O
man	O
hanged	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
pipe	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
carpenter	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
works	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
desired	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
without	O
watching	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
receiver	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
at	O
noon	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
away	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
known	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
came	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
porter	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Plummer	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Deputy	O
Willis	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
sent	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
soil	O
pipe	O
taken	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
his	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
exceeding	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoners	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
pieces	O
on	O
their	O
shoulders	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
carpenter	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
such	O
lead	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	O
on	O
Labour-in-vain-hill	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
suspicion	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
appoint	O
somebody	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
receiver	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
known	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
away	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
porter	O
to	O
watch	O
where	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
night	O
two	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servants	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul's-church-yard	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
two	O
men	O
pitch	O
some	O
lead	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
porter	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
at	O
twice	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
soil	O
pipe	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
weight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
Paston	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Paston	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
fodder	O
up	O
a	O
coffin	O
,	O
the	O
nastiness	O
of	O
the	O
corps	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
Waters	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
ale-house	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Paston	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Blewet	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fellow-apprentice	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Sarah	O
Firmin	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Chidwick	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Tompson	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
;	O
Jer	O
.	O
Williamson	O
,	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Bassom	I-pers
,	O
about	O
ten	O
;	O
Robert	O
Hawl	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
;	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Paston	O
recommended	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
pairs	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
the	O
Barber	O
was	O
shaving	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
compting-house	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Holland	O
's	O
voice	O
call	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
13	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
people	O
's	O
houses	O
to	O
take	O
things	O
?	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
without	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Holland	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
take	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
down	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
left	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
impossible	O
to	O
see	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
steward	O
of	O
the	O
Hector	O
,	O
a	O
transport	O
ship	O
,	O
captain	O
Nichols	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
at	O
Lisbon	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
158	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
O	I-pers
Neal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
burglariously	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	B-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
smash	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
immediately	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
broke	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
my	O
course	O
towards	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pursuit	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
stop	O
watch	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hands	O
was	O
bloody	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
glove	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
cut	O
through	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
fact	O
in	O
stealing	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
interceeded	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
jumped	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
frame	O
,	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
Bell-yard	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
stop-watch	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
glass	O
his	O
glove	O
was	O
cut	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hand	O
bloody	O
:	O
(	O
the	O
glove	O
produced	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Temple-bar	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
and	O
up	O
Bell-yard	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
pretty	O
short	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
disturbance	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
along	O
very	O
fierce	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
glisten	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
like	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
strove	O
with	O
my	O
elbow	O
and	O
foot	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
between	O
the	O
people	O
's	O
feet	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
took	O
the	O
man	O
away	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
for	O
the	O
mob	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
in	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
something	O
of	O
consequence	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
watch	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
receipt	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
dropped	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Nathaniel	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
his	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hamersly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
(	O
by	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
chairmen	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
attempted	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
)	O
up	O
Bell-yard	O
,	O
he	O
forced	O
by	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
one	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
took	O
out	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
slipped	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
directly	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
Bell-yard	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
by	O
that	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
fell	O
I	O
hurt	O
my	O
hand	O
against	O
the	O
watch-glass	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
four	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kimson	I-pers
.	O
159	O
,	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gilstrop	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gunthorpe	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cowlas	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
M'Antires	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
161	O
,	O
162	O
,	O
163.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
24	O
bushels	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
barge	O
on	O
a	O
navigable	O
river	O
called	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
6	O
sacks	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
sacks	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
barge	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Graves	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
48	O
quarters	O
of	O
malt	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
barge	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
six	O
sacks	O
,	O
the	O
sacks	O
were	O
marked	O
W.	O
M.	O
Henley	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
stole	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
malt	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
public	O
brewer	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
the	O
sacks	O
marked	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
bought	O
it	O
so	O
cheap	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
West	O
,	O
Johnson	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
,	O
deal	O
in	O
malt	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
lie	O
constantly	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
sacks	O
the	O
28th	O
or	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
sacks	O
marked	O
with	O
different	O
marks	O
.	O
Johnson	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
concerning	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
this	O
malt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
hope	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
two	O
sacks	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
two	O
sacks	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
West	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
hopes	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
admitted	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
malt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
thirty	O
quarters	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
shewed	O
us	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
malt	O
was	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Lyon	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
two	O
sacks	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
Lyon	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
sacks	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
into	O
my	O
barge	O
from	O
the	O
wharf	O
in	O
Channel-row	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
sacks	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
hopper	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
six	O
together	O
under	O
some	O
barrels	O
joining	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
premises	O
,	O
where	O
people	O
may	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
yard	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dunkin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
malt	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
went	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
we	O
missed	O
seven	O
sacks	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
New-court	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
examining	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Johnson	O
.	O
One	O
Child	O
a	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
some	O
malt	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
confession	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
confession	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
that	O
stole	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
malt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
West	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
asleep	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
and	O
shew	O
us	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
pitched	O
the	O
malt	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sample	O
of	O
the	O
malt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
some	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
sort	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
six	O
sacks	O
of	O
mine	O
covered	O
up	O
under	O
some	O
bricks	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
by	O
Murray	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
to	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
customary	O
to	O
have	O
sacks	O
left	O
at	O
one	O
place	O
and	O
another	O
where	O
malt	O
is	O
delivered	O
?	O
Dunkin	O
.	O
Certainly	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
hid	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dolman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
requested	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ameck	O
and	O
Dunkin	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
malt	O
being	O
stolen	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Johnson	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
innocency	O
respecting	O
it	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
malt	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Doughty	O
and	O
West	O
;	O
his	O
confession	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
intricate	O
and	O
dark	O
;	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
put	O
him	O
by	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
they	O
sent	O
out	O
for	O
West	O
.	O
When	O
West	O
came	O
into	O
court	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
promise	O
,	O
voluntarily	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
with	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Doughty	O
of	O
stealing	O
those	O
different	O
malts	O
to	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Graves	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
away	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
craft	O
,	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
malt	O
be	O
worth	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Dolman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
it	O
went	O
at	O
33	O
s.	O
34	O
s.	O
and	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Dolman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ameck	O
and	O
Dunkin	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
times	O
see	O
their	O
books	O
.	O
West	O
turned	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
farther	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
got	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
transported	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
stolen	O
the	O
malt	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
than	O
Johnson	O
and	O
West	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
From	O
West	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
selling	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
malt	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
.	O
Dolman	O
.	O
The	O
malt	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
means	O
now	O
is	O
Ameck	O
and	O
Dunkin	O
's	O
malt	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
malt	O
now	O
in	O
question	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Graves	O
's	O
malt	O
;	O
a	O
distinct	O
affair	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
sacks	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
HENLEY	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
hopper	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dunkin	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
West	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
six	O
sacks	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
malt	O
worth	O
a	O
quarter	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
worth	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
customary	O
when	O
malt	O
is	O
sold	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
sacks	O
are	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
owners	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
The	O
owners	O
are	O
so	O
careful	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
a	O
sack	O
be	O
left	O
if	O
possible	O
.	O
West	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
concern	O
in	O
felling	O
a	O
grain	O
of	O
malt	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
defy	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
serjeant	O
here	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Murray	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
dealings	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
sacks	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
,	O
what	O
were	O
found	O
not	O
on	O
my	O
premises	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Dunkin	O
.	O
In	O
searching	O
Murray	O
's	O
houses	O
there	O
were	O
thirty	O
beds	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
bed	O
we	O
found	O
made	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
sacks	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
marks	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
west-country	O
sacks	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
some	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
inspect	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
For	O
West	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
West	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
For	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
Hurst	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Johnson	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
Murray	O
called	O
William	O
Beach	O
,	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
malt	O
,	O
near	O
Little	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
betwixt	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
brewer	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
malt	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
traded	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
character	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Lowery	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-way	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Wate	I-pers
of	O
Great	O
St.	O
Ann's-lane	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mearns	I-pers
,	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
David	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
,	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
West	B-pers
and	O
Johnson	B-pers
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Murray	B-pers
Guilty	O
T.	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
164	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rachael	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
dimmety	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
February	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Rachael	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
.	O
A	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
fell	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
her	O
business	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
linnen	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
Dyer	O
's	O
in	O
Knave's-acre	O
.	O
The	O
Dyer	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
orders	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
dye	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Spooner	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
last	O
?	O
Spooner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
shift	O
and	O
petticoat	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
black	O
silk	O
apron	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
warrant	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodging	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
shifts	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
black	O
silk	O
apron	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
,	O
the	O
Dyer	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
found	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	B-pers
This	O
silk	O
apron	O
and	O
shifts	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
humbly	O
implore	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
two	O
years	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seemed	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
condition	O
.	O
Howse	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Ferrers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
9	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
does	O
she	O
bear	O
?	O
Ferrers	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
6	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
5	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Pell	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
very	O
industrious	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
166	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Stair	B-pers
Burnett	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Bellie	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Philip	O
Bellie	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
2	O
months	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
being	O
almost	O
naked	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
buckles	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
weigh	O
two	O
ounces	O
,	O
iron	O
chapes	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
thing	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
down	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
cleaned	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
buckles	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
till	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
167	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawstone	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawstone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
stopt	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
iron	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
15	O
days	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
One	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
a	O
supporter	O
to	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
grinding	O
stone	O
center	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
fixed	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
manner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
crank	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
brew-house	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
since	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
as	O
old	O
iron	O
.	O
Laurence	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
after	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
of	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
Buckle-street	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
iron	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Buttall	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Gridiron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
's	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
night-house	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
it	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
bring	O
proof	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
got	O
quite	O
off	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Buttall	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
iron	O
?	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
till	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
17	O
days	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Buttall	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
iron	O
being	O
stopt	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
brought	O
him	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
twenty	O
my	O
workmen	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
pick	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
he	O
pitched	O
upon	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
within	O
these	O
9	O
months	O
of	O
about	O
fifty	O
100	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
iron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
men	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
nobody	O
else	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
168	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Paul	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
wilfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
made	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
an	O
ill-designed	O
and	O
disorderly	O
person	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
wicked	O
mind	O
and	O
disposition	O
,	O
not	O
regarding	O
the	O
laws	O
and	O
statutes	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
nor	O
pains	O
or	O
penalties	O
that	O
should	O
fall	O
thereon	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
pistol	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
loaded	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
bullet	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
did	O
wilfully	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
and	O
knowingly	O
shoot	O
at	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
he	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
sovereign	O
lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
to	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Wilsden	B-place
;	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
stop	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
intent	O
to	O
stop	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
neither	O
will	O
I	O
be	O
stopt	O
.	O
I	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shot	O
at	O
me	O
slap	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
horse	O
's	O
starting	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
upon	O
my	O
feet	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Pope	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
my	O
knee	O
on	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pursue	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
was	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
pursued	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
holding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
bred	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
wherever	O
I	O
desired	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
clapped	O
another	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
my	O
body	O
with	O
my	O
right-hand	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
pointed	O
to	O
my	O
thigh	O
,	O
he	O
snapt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
flash	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
kicked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
my	O
knee	O
upon	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
my	O
garters	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
pistols	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
ten	O
bullets	O
and	O
a	O
bullet-mold	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
pistol	O
that	O
he	O
snapt	O
at	O
me	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
powder	O
and	O
one	O
ball	O
.	O
(	O
Two	O
pocket	O
pistols	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
pistols	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
threatned	O
to	O
shoot	O
you	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
chariot	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
and	O
lady	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
horse	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
yes	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
highwaymen	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
waiting	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
you	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
pretty	O
fast	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
turning	O
a	O
short	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
sitting	O
on	O
their	O
horses	O
,	O
with	O
masks	O
on	O
their	O
faces	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
surprize	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
riding	O
on	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
might	O
release	O
the	O
man	O
they	O
then	O
attacked	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
discharged	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
off	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
shot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
aim	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
?	O
Pope	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
what	O
aim	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
smoak	O
pretty	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
clapt	O
spurs	O
to	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
his	O
partner	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
retreat	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
pursue	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
off	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
gathered	O
ground	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
quitted	O
his	O
horse	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
demand	O
any	O
money	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
let	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
is	O
an	O
atheist	O
;	O
he	O
gives	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
that	O
he	O
believes	O
there	O
is	O
neither	O
God	O
,	O
or	O
devil	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
oath	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
town	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
sun-set	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
masked	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
great	O
matter	O
of	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
this	O
discourse	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
go	O
stop	O
that	O
other	O
;	O
then	O
Lewis	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
staid	O
;	O
presently	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
stir	O
or	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
Lewis	O
fired	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
riding	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
assistance	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
assistance	O
came	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Brown	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
masked	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
you	O
to	O
stop	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
when	O
he	O
fired	O
his	O
pistol	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stoaker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
10	O
bullets	O
and	O
some	O
powder	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Seeing	O
the	O
evidence	O
is	O
so	O
plain	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
little	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
farmer	O
Cook	O
turn	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
I	O
did	O
fire	O
at	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
my	O
circumstances	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
declare	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
intention	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
.	O
This	O
thing	O
has	O
been	O
so	O
represented	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
hone	O
here	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
entirely	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stopping	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Worcester	O
stage	O
near	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
Bush	O
,	O
No	O
4	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
169	O
,	O
170	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linnen	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
worsted	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
M'Carty	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
M'Carty	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
I	O
lived	O
on	O
Little	B-place
Tower	I-place
hill	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
a	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
run	O
up	O
a	O
score	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
day	O
after	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
them	O
to	O
pay	O
and	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
begun	O
to	O
have	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
observing	O
pistols	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
pockets	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
secured	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
pistols	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Donaldson	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
two	O
neckcloths	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
there	O
is	O
C.	O
C.	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
M'Carty	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
seamen	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
India-house	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
advertised	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
again	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
marked	O
C.	O
C.	O
as	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
know	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Donaldson	O
's	O
pocket	O
sixty-five	O
bullets	O
and	O
some	O
gunpowder	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
three	O
pistols	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Donaldson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
we	O
lodged	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
quite	O
strangers	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Cotton	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
for	O
Liverpool	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
on	O
ship	O
board	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
:	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
watch	O
for	O
security	O
for	O
the	O
reckoning	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
us	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
saw	O
pistols	O
in	O
Robinson	O
's	O
pockets	O
.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ebden	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Ebden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bleeding	I-place
Heart	I-place
,	I-place
Cross-street	I-place
,	I-place
Hatton-garden	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
parcel	O
of	O
plate	O
seemingly	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
She	O
takes	O
up	O
the	O
lid	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
only	O
doubled	O
together	O
)	O
This	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
plain	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rankin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
Barnet	O
,	O
a	O
Broker	O
there	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
tankard	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
as	O
now	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winkley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mrs.	O
Ebden	O
's	O
son	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Barnet	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
tankard	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
five	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
hard	O
at	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
by	O
what	O
they	O
ever	O
knew	O
before	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
172	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Chippendale	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
court	O
called	O
Hammer-and-crown	O
court	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
isinglass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
stopped	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
in	O
Hammer-and-crown	B-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Ratcliff-cross	I-place
;	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
pockets	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
seeing	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
catched	O
the	O
isinglass	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
made	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
directly	O
.	O
Several	O
gentlemen	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
tavern	O
,	O
they	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
isinglass	O
cost	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
my	O
master	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
tavern	O
Ratcliff-cross	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
's	O
voice	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
isinglass	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
manner	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
live	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
this	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
ship	O
tavern	O
with	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
waiter	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
isinglass	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
tavern	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
failed	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
your	O
haunts	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
get	O
clear	O
of	O
this	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
isinglass	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
and	O
960	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Millard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Uxbridge	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen-window	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
locks	O
forced	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
sometime	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
bundle	O
was	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
lost	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
four	O
pints	O
of	O
ale	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
slip	O
away	O
without	O
paying	O
his	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
behaved	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
as	O
an	O
idiot	O
.	O
The	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
papers	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
slate	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
since	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
who	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
opportunity	O
to	O
observe	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
five	O
days	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Pain	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
mind	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
talked	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
question	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
sensible	O
when	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Clitherow	O
,	O
he	O
talked	O
very	O
well	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
very	O
sensible	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
questions	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
asked	O
several	O
questions	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
this	O
his	O
behaviour	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
ceiling	O
and	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
AmbroseTawney	B-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
;	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Prague	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Tawney	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Ealing	B-place
;	O
that	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
Peter	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
missing	O
next	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
horse-pistol	O
stand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
shoes	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Lynch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
M.	O
Kynch	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
held	O
his	O
arm	O
while	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
understanding	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
sensible	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
174	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bank-note	O
No	O
283	O
,	O
signed	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sabertine	I-pers
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
London	O
,	O
16	O
March	O
1763	O
,	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
one	O
ditto	O
No	O
21	O
,	O
signed	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
London	O
,	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
1763	O
,	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
one	O
ditto	O
No	O
240	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
17th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1763	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
one	O
ditto	O
No	O
82	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
21st	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1763	O
,	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
ditto	O
No	O
81	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
21st	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1763	O
,	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
8th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
1762	O
,	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
said	O
notes	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elrington	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
such	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elrington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
war-office	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
desirous	O
of	O
seeing	O
his	O
Majesty	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
passing	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
stept	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
people	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
;	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
charge	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
placed	O
themselves	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
button	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
myself	O
close	O
to	O
a	O
pillar	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
body	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
behind	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
took	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
push	O
me	O
now	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
crowd	O
here	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
His	O
Majesty	O
going	O
by	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
hand	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
cried	O
,	O
O	O
ra	O
!	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
immediately	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
pillar	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
shuffling	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
accuse	O
a	O
person	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
mind	O
me	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
running	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Iron-gate-way	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
crowded	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
through	O
very	O
cleverly	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
too	O
much	O
consequence	O
to	O
loose	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
crowd	O
made	O
way	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
or	O
two	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
near	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
coffee	O
house	O
window	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
seaman	O
very	O
officious	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
search	O
him	O
!	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
officious	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
search	O
the	O
gentleman	O
myself	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
leather	O
pocketbook	O
with	O
the	O
notes	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hands	O
by	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
carrying	O
you	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
guard-room	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
a	O
file	O
of	O
musqueteers	O
to	O
attend	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
seaman	O
,	O
whom	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
conceal	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
roguery	O
,	O
went	O
voluntarily	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strive	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seemed	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
confused	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
flutter	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
50	O
l.	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
any	O
honest	O
person	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
upon	O
getting	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
mentioned	O
the	O
several	O
numbers	O
names	O
and	O
sums	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
)	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
A	O
note	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
note	O
.	O
Elrington	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
No	O
82	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
signed	O
Edward	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
dated	O
21st	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1763	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
negociated	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
betwixt	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
Richard	B-pers
Devordack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Elrington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
coffee-house	O
when	O
the	O
King	O
went	O
by	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
captain	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
king	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
iron	O
gate	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
guard	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
captain	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
run	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
uneasy	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
security	O
for	O
ten	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
also	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
50	O
l.	O
that	O
the	O
captain	O
had	O
his	O
book	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
fell	O
into	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
's	O
hands	O
the	O
captain	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kirkland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
and	O
the	O
captain	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bobbed	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
run	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
guard-room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vandicom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Majesty	O
