TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
MAY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1763	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
Adams	O
*	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meller	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Healy	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bedell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Leaper	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Banner	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hoppey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cubbidge	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Nightingal	I-pers
*	O
,	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
for	O
Humphry	O
Nightingal	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramwell	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burgall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Christopher	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
undressed	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
where	O
I	O
usually	O
hang	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
bedside	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
quickly	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
fall	O
asleep	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
to	O
tie	O
about	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
four	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
supper	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
joking	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
may	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
mistaken	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Aldersgate	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
for	O
29	O
s.	O
in	O
whose	O
custody	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
a	O
turnkey	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
often	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
she	O
sell	O
a	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
cloaths	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
enable	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
service	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Blue	O
Balls	O
by	O
Aldersgate	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
interest	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
besides	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
distressed	O
widow	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
what	O
I	O
pleased	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lion	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
198	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gapper	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Gapper	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
Newgate	B-place
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
then	O
you	O
are	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
with	O
the	O
letters	O
C.	O
G.	O
upon	O
it	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gapper	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
started	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
pocked	O
was	O
picked	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
under	O
Newgate	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
momentary	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
hand	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
10	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Fountain	O
tavern	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
boys	O
ran	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
kinsman	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
through	O
Newgate	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
boys	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
did	O
me	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
throwing	O
my	O
hands	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
thrown	O
upon	O
the	O
cape	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
to	O
speak	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
boys	O
ran	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
you	O
are	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sparks	O
,	O
No	O
277.	O
in	O
the	O
mayoralty	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Janssen	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
pewter	O
.	O
199	O
,	O
200	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Rabson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Poulton	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
forty	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mariot	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mariot	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
secretly	O
in	O
their	O
warehouse	O
.	O
And	O
Samuel	B-pers
Beaden	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Mariot	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
.	O
My	O
uncle	O
John	B-pers
Mariot	I-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
some	O
warehouses	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Milford-lane	B-place
,	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
corn	O
trade	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Baylis	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
fields	O
,	O
I	O
attend	O
at	O
the	O
corn	O
market	O
Mondays	O
,	O
Wednesdays	O
,	O
and	O
Fridays	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
our	O
servant	O
,	O
comes	O
there	O
to	O
us	O
to	O
take	O
orders	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
warehouses	O
in	O
Milford-lane	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
ormed	O
by	O
Jones	O
there	O
had	O
len	B-pers
some	O
corn	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Burton	B-pers
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
malt	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
they	O
took	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
's	O
stable	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Howard-street	O
,	O
near	O
Norfolk-street	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
stables	O
in	O
Surry-street	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
stables	O
in	O
Surry-street	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
sack	O
marked	O
W.	O
H.	O
a	O
West	O
country	O
sack	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
in	O
our	O
warehouse	O
that	O
the	O
owner	O
has	O
not	O
fetched	O
away	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
sack	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
.	O
Beaden	O
hearing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
surrendered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
receiving	O
the	O
oats	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
grainery	O
keeper	O
to	O
messrs.	O
Mariots	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
corn	O
market	O
to	O
my	O
masters	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
the	O
warehouses	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Baylis	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Baylis	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
keys	O
were	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Burton	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
Burton	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Baylis	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
keys	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
which	O
was	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bushed	O
was	O
moved	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Burton	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
carrying	O
a	O
sack	O
for	O
old	O
Price	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Dowley	O
's	O
grainery	O
keeper	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
none	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Baylis	O
employed	O
by	O
you	O
that	O
Friday	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
for	O
us	O
when	O
we	O
wanted	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
because	O
at	O
times	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mariot	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
at	O
times	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Baylis	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
I	O
having	O
no	O
pockets	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
had	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Horseshoes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
Baylis	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
is	O
below	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rust	O
,	O
the	O
grainery	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
Rust	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
take	O
another	O
sack	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
)	O
we	O
will	O
share	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
Rust	O
put	O
up	O
another	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
Surry-street	O
,	O
and	O
pitched	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
which	O
Baylis	O
had	O
left	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
's	O
stable	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
'd	O
the	O
sack	O
that	O
Baylis	O
carried	O
by	O
the	O
red	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
those	O
sacks	O
again	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
burnt	O
at	O
Baylis	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Baylis	O
.	O
You	O
burnt	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
under	O
Baylis	O
's	O
arm	O
.	O
Jones	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
taking	O
malt	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
advantage	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
by	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
Rust	O
and	O
Baylis	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-shoes	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
5	O
s.	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
Baylis	O
had	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
Rust	O
kept	O
the	O
other	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
sacks	O
came	O
to	O
10	O
s.	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
farthing	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
received	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
5	O
s.	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
two	O
sacks	O
,	O
and	O
Rust	O
had	O
received	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
other	O
5	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Arundel-street	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
because	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
it	O
would	O
blast	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
ruin	O
him	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
stable	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
sack	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
when	O
Baylis	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
did	O
carry	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
grainery	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
's	O
stable	O
.	O
Mr	O
Beaden	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
word	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
graineries	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
heard	O
Baylis	O
confess	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
one	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
from	O
the	O
grainery	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
's	O
stable	O
in	O
Surry-street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barrot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Baylis	O
or	O
Burton	O
at	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
stables	O
?	O
Barrot	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
declare	O
to	O
one	O
Humphry	O
Evans	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
shot	O
the	O
oats	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
into	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
binn	O
?	O
Barrot	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
all	O
this	O
dispute	O
about	O
?	O
I	O
fancy	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
hole	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
shot	O
any	O
oats	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
weat	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Burton	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
received	O
any	O
money	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
receive	O
any	O
of	O
him	O
during	O
his	O
breath	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
want	O
corn	O
,	O
I	O
or	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dowley	O
's	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
trades	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
quarters	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
our	O
stable	O
in	O
Surry-street	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
.	O
Baylis	O
has	O
brought	O
sacks	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Dowley	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
porter	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
stable	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
upon	O
any	O
other	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
ordered	O
corn	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Dowley	O
's	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
always	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
,	O
his	O
foreman	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
oats	O
brought	O
in	O
in	O
secret	O
.	O
Baylis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
oats	O
,	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
John	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
employed	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Beaden	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
corn	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dowley	O
,	O
of	O
Milford-lane	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
give	O
orders	O
to	O
my	O
servants	O
when	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
account	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
For	O
Beaden	O
.	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
when	O
Burton	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
on	O
his	O
examination	O
gave	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
any	O
money	O
he	O
or	O
they	O
received	O
of	O
Beaden	O
?	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
ask	O
that	O
question	O
.	O
Baylis	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
carry	O
some	O
oats	O
to	O
Beaden	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
he	O
or	O
Burton	O
did	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
present	O
when	O
any	O
money	O
was	O
paid	O
;	O
neither	O
did	O
they	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
money	O
being	O
received	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dowley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
serve	O
Mr.	O
Beaden	O
with	O
corn	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
this	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
sometimes	O
seven	O
quarters	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
ten	O
,	O
sometimes	O
thirty	O
quarters	O
within	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
;	O
sometimes	O
I	O
send	O
the	O
oats	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
sacks	O
,	O
sometimes	O
in	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
sacks	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
west-country	O
sacks	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
of	O
this	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
evidences	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
court	O
thought	O
it	O
needless	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
.	O
Baylis	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Beaden	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Eagle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
12	O
hens	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
turkeys	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
my	O
hen-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
two	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
fowls	O
taken	O
away	O
then	O
are	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictments	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
garret	O
at	O
Wallam-green	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
picking	O
the	O
feathers	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
cock	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lamb	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
acknowledged	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
diverse	O
others	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
talking	O
any	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
while	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
dispute	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
denying	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
sorry	O
I	O
should	O
rob	O
such	O
a	O
worthy	O
gentleman	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
miser	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
minded	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
bad	O
enough	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
No	O
84	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Dickinson	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
weather	O
sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Maidenhead-bridge	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
twelve	O
weather-sheep	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
ground	O
joining	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sat	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
killing	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
John	B-pers
Portsmouth	I-pers
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
how	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Harcourt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
twelve	O
weather-sheep	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
tired	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
loss	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
price	O
to	O
ask	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
all	O
?	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
at	O
a	O
loss	O
what	O
to	O
ask	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
and	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
lives	O
at	O
Catridge-green	O
,	O
three	O
miles	O
beyond	O
Chesham	O
.	O
I	O
detained	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
sheep	O
appeared	O
dusty	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
come	O
some	O
distance	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
prison	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
John	B-pers
Portsmouth	I-pers
came	O
,	O
he	O
claimed	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
Marsh	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Portsmouth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
.	O
The	O
sheep	O
were	O
in	O
our	O
ground	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
fence	O
was	O
pulled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stakes	O
thrown	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sheep	O
had	O
been	O
drove	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
cross	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Harcote	O
's	O
grass	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
J.	O
M.	O
in	O
pitch	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
readle	O
mark	O
on	O
their	O
shoulders	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
drive	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
18	O
s.	O
each	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
204	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Copland	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Copland	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
Joseph	O
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
linnen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
Highgate	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
silk	O
and	O
ribbons	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
child	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
missed	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
,	O
in	O
searching	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
found	O
about	O
6	O
yards	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
her	O
niece	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
other	O
ribbons	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
ribbon	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
nor	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
Highgate	O
.	O
Edward	O
Jones	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
205	O
,	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Stainer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Grubstreet	B-place
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
a	O
fortnight	O
and	O
three	O
days	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
in	O
these	O
their	O
names	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
book-case	O
which	O
stood	O
on	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
their	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
use	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
warning	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
begged	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
confess	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Farmer	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Jewin-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moreland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Griffin	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
Stainer	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
with	O
three	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
;	O
one	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
ten	O
days	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
proper	O
in	O
his	O
condition	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
cannisters	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
capuchin	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
shift	O
and	O
capuchin	O
in	O
Chandois-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
tortoishell	O
snuff-box	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
rim	O
and	O
top	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shirt	O
buttons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Smith	O
on	O
Puddle-dock-hill	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
drawers	O
open	O
about	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
branch	O
of	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
Bowman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
engine	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
mend	O
locks	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
box	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rodbard	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
place	O
Black	O
Friars	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
paper	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
I	O
paid	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rodbard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
this	O
box	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Bowman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
rule	O
by	O
which	O
you	O
calculate	O
your	O
interest	O
?	O
Isaac	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
three	O
halfpence	O
a	O
month	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
halfpence	O
?	O
Isaac	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
day	O
past	O
after	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Somebody	O
that	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
spight	O
has	O
gone	O
and	O
taken	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blashfield	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Judith	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Garnon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
,	O
April	O
14	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Street	I-pers
.	O
My	O
brother	O
John	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
partners	O
,	O
linnen-drapers	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
printed	O
cotton	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
some	O
thing	O
We	O
told	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
searched	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
my	O
maid	O
down	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
some	O
little	O
pockets	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
southsea	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
gown	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
cotton	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
property	O
by	O
the	O
pattern	O
,	O
size	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sag	O
end	O
with	O
the	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
servant-maid	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
account	O
of	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
210	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Capel	O
in	O
Surry	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
from	O
my	O
other	O
farm	O
at	O
Wooton	B-place
last	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
My	O
servant	O
John	B-pers
Longley	I-pers
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Longley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
tenant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Palmer	O
at	O
Wooton	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
last	O
I	O
rack	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
horses	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
Wooton	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
let	O
my	O
mistress	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
John	B-pers
Dendy	I-pers
to	O
seek	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
gelding	O
back	O
again	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Longley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dendy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
this	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
leg	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
by	O
the	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
?	O
Dendy	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
horse	O
?	O
Dendy	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
made	O
another	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
story	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
story	O
?	O
Dendy	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
Epsom	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
to	O
market	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
horse	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
horse	O
coaser	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
about	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
never	O
gave	O
me	O
time	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
a	O
stranger	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
business	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hogan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Harmandsworth	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
carrying	O
news-papers	O
to	O
my	O
customers	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
bolt	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
double	O
spring-look	O
at	O
the	O
sore-door	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
great	O
board	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
window-shutter	O
and	O
fastened	O
it	O
with	O
two	O
broomsticks	O
a-cross	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
whole	O
frame	O
of	O
a	O
lower	O
window	O
was	O
beaten	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witnesses	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
white	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
John	O
Appleton	O
's	O
wife	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
constable	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
laid	O
upon	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
two	O
oilet-holes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
wife	O
make	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
value	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
gowns	O
and	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
linnen	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitmel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
lower	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Whitmel	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
day	O
light	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
will	O
and	O
power	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
clear	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
but	O
God	O
Almighty	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Whitmel	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
such	O
offer	O
made	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Whitmel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
answered	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Whitmel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
Whitmel	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
doors	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
April	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Harrington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
trunk-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Chancery-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shop	O
shut	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
trunk	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
by	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
the	O
trunk	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
knot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
walked	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
They	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
trunk	O
an	O
ell	O
long	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
stall-board	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
board	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
feet	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Our	O
apprentice	O
Samuel	B-pers
Little	I-pers
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
has	O
stole	O
a	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
Little	O
catch	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
that	O
and	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Little	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Hemmings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baskerville	O
at	O
the	O
bottle	O
warehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edmund	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Vigne	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Vigne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch	O
maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
towards	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
accosted	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
dressed	O
in	O
sailors	O
jackets	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
common	O
cloaths	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
near	O
York-buildings	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
mumbling	O
way	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
us	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
They	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
very	O
strongly	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
most	O
prudent	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
three	O
such	O
desperate	O
fellows	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
kept	O
very	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
)	O
to	O
pass	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
opposite	O
Northumberland-house	O
,	O
fearing	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
knock	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
it	O
opened	O
,	O
they	O
,	O
by	O
seeing	O
valuable	O
things	O
there	O
,	O
might	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
force	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
treat	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
to	O
run	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
fearing	O
they	O
would	O
follow	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
cellar	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
decent	O
appearance	O
;	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
treat	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
there	O
own	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
some	O
liquor	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
slip	O
:	O
they	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
there	O
,	O
coachmen	O
and	O
chairmen	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
night	O
house	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
my	O
head	O
leaning	O
on	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
home	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Panton-street	B-place
and	O
James-street	B-place
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
lamps	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
running	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
now	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
I	O
given	O
you	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
Said	O
they	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
chatter	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
deliver	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
my	O
thigh	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
on	O
my	O
hands	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
natured	O
fellow	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
G	O
d	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
my	O
glove	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
diamond	O
cluster	O
ring	O
,	O
9	O
large	O
and	O
8	O
small	O
ones	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
ring	O
was	O
worth	O
at	O
least	O
22	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pass	O
no	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Vigne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
nobody	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
shoulder	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Vigne	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
my	O
ring	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
only	O
the	O
setting	O
of	O
my	O
diamond	O
ring	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
hoop	O
and	O
setting	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
hoop	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
having	O
several	O
reasons	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
Mr	O
.	O
Le	O
Sage	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
get	O
protection	O
from	O
the	O
Landlord	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
?	O
Vigne	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
blamed	O
myself	O
since	O
for	O
not	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
this	O
hoop	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
.	O
This	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
diamonds	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
sent	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
5	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
ring	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
thousand	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
9	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
asked	O
10	O
guineas	O
James	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
a	O
ring	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
is	O
a	O
jeweller	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
James	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
give	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
to	O
Geary	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
diamonds	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
Warren	O
?	O
Thorp	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
cluster	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
what	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
he	O
tried	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
file	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
he	O
worth	O
10	O
guineas	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
Collins	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
Gutter-lane	O
first	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
brought	O
word	O
back	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
?	O
Geary	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Le	O
Sage	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
this	O
ring	O
(	O
taking	O
the	O
hoop	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
market	O
price	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
?	O
Le	O
Sage	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
16	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
boy	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
last	O
the	O
hoop	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
Geary	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
Geary	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
or	O
week	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
jacket	O
,	O
he	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
fighting	O
cobler	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
ring	O
that	O
is	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
common	O
paste	O
ring	O
to	O
Geary	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Plymouth	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
service	O
this	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Saltash	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pannel	O
saw	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
was	O
doing	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hand	O
saw	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
small	O
job	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
nobody	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
job	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
one	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
four	O
years	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
journeyman-carpenter	O
,	O
of	O
whose	O
character	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
complaint	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
inclinable	O
to	O
thing	O
favourable	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
a	O
peruks-maker	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
glass	O
cannisters	O
with	O
silver	O
tops	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
salt-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Burr	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Burr	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
breakfast	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
family	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
church	O
,	O
except	O
Mrs.	O
Burr	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maids	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
10	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
persons	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
some	O
plate	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bedington	I-pers
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
buffet	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Burr	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pasfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
punch-ladle	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
ladle	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Burr	O
.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Pasfield	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
murder	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
senses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
216	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Low	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
containing	O
450	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willan	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Willan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
some	O
body	O
taking	O
my	O
hay	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
trusses	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
hay	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
barn	O
at	O
Marybone	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Marybone	O
parish	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
with	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
the	O
hay	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
other	O
trusses	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
Before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
three	O
trusses	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
barn	O
at	O
Marybone	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
trusses	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
hay-binder	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
trusses	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
take	O
any	O
hay	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Walter	O
Holding	O
and	O
Richard	O
Rigby	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Keys	O
about	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
April	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
and	O
blacksmith	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
robbing	O
his	O
master	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
old	O
iron	O
lay	O
with	O
something	O
bulky	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
iron	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
more	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
upwards	O
of	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
mixed	O
together	O
only	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
it	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
5	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
two	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
daughter	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
boarding-school	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
her	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
school	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cap	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
tip	O
of	O
her	O
stay	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ruffles	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
replace	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
M'Millan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
William	O
.	O
We	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
snuff-box	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
settle	O
empty	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kilbourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
drop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
stoop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
fall	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
my	O
wig	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
3	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
only	O
getting-drunk	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
than	O
the	O
farthest	O
person	O
living	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
that	O
I	O
offered	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
offered	O
14	O
s.	O
for	O
things	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Young	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
how	O
could	O
I	O
buy	O
things	O
without	O
money	O
?	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
offer	O
14	O
s.	O
for	O
things	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
he	O
offered	O
her	O
that	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
money	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
woman	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
hats	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
farther	O
than	O
my	O
pocket	O
will	O
go	O
?	O
George	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
220	O
,	O
221	O
,	O
222	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lilley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Forsir	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Corin	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
buckles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Corin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
belonging	O
to	O
Marybone	O
gardens	O
.	O
Having	O
company	O
to	O
attend	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
stay	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
Tibbutts	O
,	O
Lambert	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
we	O
begged	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
link	O
of	O
the	O
landlord	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
to	O
light	O
us	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
posts	O
,	O
there	O
three	O
men	O
or	O
more	O
met	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
link	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
link	O
?	O
The	O
second	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
link	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
or	O
shoved	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
link	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Corin	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
know	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
striped	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
riffled	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
people	O
talk	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
cam	O
e	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
loose	O
?	O
Corin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
single	O
six-pences	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
again	O
.	O
Another	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
men	O
?	O
Corin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
confusion	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
seized	O
me	O
and	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
shoes	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
durst	O
not	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
companions	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Cavendish-square	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
light	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
two	O
watchmen	O
.	O
At	O
my	O
getting	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
light	O
horse-man	O
's	O
cap	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
with	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
Smith	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
link	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
had	O
a	O
striped	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
evidence	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
link	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Chapman	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Chapman	O
had	O
then	O
my	O
shoes	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Corin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
last	O
Christmas	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
became	O
first	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
sailors	O
;	O
we	O
just	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
a	O
frolick	O
together	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
there	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
19	O
accidentally	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
,	O
what	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Rob	O
the	O
first	O
we	O
came	O
a-thort	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
declared	O
this	O
.	O
Lilley	O
and	O
Forsit	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
stick	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
robbed	O
two	O
country-carts	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Church-street	O
,	O
near	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Marybone	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
these	O
three	O
waiters	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Lilley	O
was	O
the	O
foremost	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
link	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
link	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
link	O
?	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
link	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shove	O
and	O
hove	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Forsit	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sixpences	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
Lilley	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
both	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
busy	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
waiters	O
;	O
Forsit	O
took	O
his	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
too	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
Forsit	O
got	O
his	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
Lilley	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Holborn	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
a	O
night-house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
better	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Cowman	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
sign	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Tower-goal	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
pretty	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
Lilley	O
left	O
his	O
stick	O
behind	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
prison	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
who	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
drank	O
at	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
for	O
six	O
weeks	O
past	O
,	O
sometimes	O
they	O
have	O
drank	O
together	O
and	O
sometimes	O
at	O
separate	O
boxes	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
sailors	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
charge	O
my	O
memory	O
with	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
son-night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Ward	O
is	O
a	O
musician	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
on	O
the	O
violin	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
evidence	O
wore	O
a	O
striped	O
jacket	O
.	O
Chapman	O
and	O
Smith	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
often	O
together	O
.	O
Ward	O
lodged	O
facing	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
playing	O
them	O
a	O
tune	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cowman	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Horns	O
and	O
Horseshoe	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoners	O
and	O
evidence	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
Lilley	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
by	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
beer	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
Forsit	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
sat	O
together	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
gone	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
hat	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
purl	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
Smith	O
staid	O
alone	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
wrangling	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
me	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Forsit	O
hit	O
Smith	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
across	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
;	O
still	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
of	O
what	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
want	O
my	O
stick	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
revenge	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
charge	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
half	O
like	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
shov	O
'd	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
Lilley	O
left	O
his	O
stick	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
split	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
then	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
blood	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
large	O
stick	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
Smith	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
brick-field	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
bad	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
where	O
any	O
ill	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
admit	O
you	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Smith	O
began	O
to	O
open	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
left	O
Maynard-street	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o'clock	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
all	O
four	O
together	O
somewhere	O
by	O
Tyburn-road	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
three	O
men	O
with	O
two	O
carts	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
driving	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
one	O
3	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
another	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
three	O
men	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
link	O
in	O
his	O
han	O
,	O
they	O
looked	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
servants	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
link	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Lilley	O
come	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
about	O
noon	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tibbuts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Corin	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
coming	O
from	O
Marybone	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
I	O
lay	O
sometime	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
senseless	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
shewed	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
head	O
)	O
this	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
link	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
hat	O
,	O
wig	O
,	O
buckles	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
some	O
silver	O
and	O
halfpence	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
strip	O
me	O
naked	O
,	O
I	O
struggled	O
for	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
to	O
Lambert	O
and	O
Corin	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Zepheniah	O
Lambert	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
waiters	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
borrowed	O
a	O
link	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
got	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
met	O
us	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
link	O
,	O
to	O
Corin	O
;	O
then	O
another	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
striped	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
give	O
us	O
the	O
link	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
stick	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
being	O
busy	O
upon	O
my	O
other	O
two	O
companions	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
I	O
made	O
off	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
from	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
mens	O
names	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
Lilley	O
,	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
Forsit	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
Sir	O
John	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
the	O
waiters	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
sent	O
word	O
that	O
Ward	O
and	O
Forsit	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
or	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
Newton	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
waiters	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Ward	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
cloaths	O
on	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Lilley	O
,	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Forsit	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
Marybone	O
fields	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
three	O
men	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
cap	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
cap	O
was	O
not	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Lilley	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
knew	O
Forsit	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
resolute	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
will	O
and	O
powers	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
one	O
Williams	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
committed	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Clark	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grief	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
prisoner	O
detained	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
against	O
some	O
persons	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
after	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Chapman	O
by	O
a	O
mark	O
that	O
Smith	O
the	O
evidence	O
had	O
mentioned	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Chapman	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Forsit	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
;	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
swear	O
innocent	O
peoples	O
lives	O
away	O
.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
can	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Ward	O
better	O
than	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cavenaugh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	O
Johnson	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Pindor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Lynford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
also	O
had	O
known	O
Ward	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
New	B-place
Road	I-place
against	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
the	O
ditch	O
is	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
house	O
chaise	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
hollo	O
,	O
hollo	O
,	O
there	O
directly	O
came	O
two	O
more	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
they	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
stop	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
stopped	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
presented	O
a	O
horse	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
lowered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
shafts	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
one	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
the	O
lady	O
set	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
rifle	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
would	O
satisfy	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
'd	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
s.	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
risling	O
the	O
lady	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
her	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
coach	O
behind	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
employed	O
about	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
neither	O
can	O
I	O
describe	O
the	O
dress	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
presented	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
rifled	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
pretty	O
lusty	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
.	O
A	O
pawnbroker	O
had	O
given	O
information	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
that	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Publican	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
at	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
lads	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
perfect	O
in	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
perswade	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Dyer-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
delivered	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Hull	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
produce	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
skittle-ground	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
officers	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	O
Bolton-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
advertisement	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
watch	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
horse	O
chaise	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
bitterly	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
past	O
there	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
lately	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
drawed	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
friends	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
224	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Doolan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
shirt-buckle	O
set	O
with	O
garnet	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
shirt-buckle	O
set	O
with	O
glass	O
paste	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
comb-maker	O
and	O
hard	O
ware-man	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Lombard-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
shirt-buckle	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
conceal	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
garnet	O
one	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
so	O
close	O
after	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
without	O
my	O
seeing	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
at	O
home	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
exchange	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
17	O
s.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
to	O
the	O
Post-office	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
shirt-buckle	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
punish	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
constable	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
down	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
down	O
two	O
shirt-buckles	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
paste	O
one	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
garnet	O
one	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
no	O
means	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
may	O
get	O
off	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
5	O
guineas	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
secretary	O
's	O
office	O
at	O
the	O
Post-office	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
drink	O
three	O
glasses	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
fuddled	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Frances	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
-	O
Green	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Olton	I-pers
Vring	I-pers
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Oston	I-pers
Vring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
making	O
sailor	O
's	O
jackets	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
little	O
child	O
with	O
a	O
farthing	O
worth	O
of	O
gingerbread	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
and	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
and	O
the	O
cloak	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
gown	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
blue	O
Balls	O
,	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Frances	O
Green	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
8	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Lovechild	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confessing	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
cloak	O
called	O
a	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
she	O
did	O
in	O
Poor	B-place
Jewry-lane	I-place
;	O
that	O
she	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
that	O
by	O
enquiring	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
at	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
man	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Hibbot	I-pers
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledge	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
ever	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
replace	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
227	O
,	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
houshold	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrold	I-pers
.	O
For	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
M'Carty	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
191	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
sessions	O
paper	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
229	O
,	O
230	O
,	O
231	O
,	O
232	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
lined	O
with	O
beaver-skin	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
Dresden	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
double-laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
round	O
robbins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
Mechlin	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
Holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
point	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
set	O
with	O
paste	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
fancy	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
bag	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
lutestring	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
printed	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
black	O
laced	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gittoes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
Moring	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
