TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEPHENSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Eardley	I-pers
Wilmot	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Overlove	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cawthorne	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Osmond	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Fanicourt	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Childs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hagarth	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Harden	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brougham	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Farrer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
William	O
Wallis	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
Newgate	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
meddle	O
,	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
myself	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
obstinate	O
resistance	O
;	O
either	O
he	O
or	O
an	O
accomplice	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
:	O
with	O
assistance	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
Woodstreet	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
again	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hand-cuffs	O
;	O
he	O
again	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Pulling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Pye-Corner	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
struck	O
the	O
gentleman	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
assistance	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
soon	O
secured	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
any	O
where	O
:	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
and	O
Magpye	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogan	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
pounds	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
horse-hair	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Slim	I-pers
,	O
October	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hansley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Slim	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Golden	B-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
horse-hair	O
weaver	O
;	O
the	O
warehouse	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
goods	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
apprentice	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
way	O
through	O
that	O
cellar	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
step	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
18	O
pounds	O
of	O
horse-hair	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
lately	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
only	O
see	O
her	O
upper	O
part	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hair	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
trod	O
upon	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
lap	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
E.	O
Hansley	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Slim	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
work	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
weave	O
girth	O
web	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
long	O
hair	O
,	O
not	O
proper	O
for	O
that	O
work	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
forging	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
words	O
and	O
figures	O
following	O
:	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
Aug.	O
16	O
.	O
1764	O
.	O
At	O
one	O
month	O
pay	O
this	O
first	O
of	O
exchange	O
:	O
to	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
value	O
receiv	O
'd	O
in	O
Cash	O
,	O
which	O
place	O
to	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
per	O
advice	O
.	O
To	O
Mesrs	O
.	O
Thomas	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
,	O
merchants	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Rich	O
.	O
Scott	O
.	O
Accepted	O
Sept.	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
John	O
Hall	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sconswer	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
1543.	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Ralph	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
September	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Ralph	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
anchor	O
smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
an	O
anchor	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
one	O
that	O
weighed	O
500	O
3	O
qrs	O
.	O
and	O
26	O
pounds	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
per	O
hundred	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
bill	O
,	O
drawn	O
from	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
;	O
my	O
anchor	O
came	O
to	O
8	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
bought	O
four	O
irons	O
for	O
caulking	O
ships	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
ballance	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
15	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
sum	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
so	O
much	O
cash	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
the	O
anchor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
another	O
such	O
affair	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
indorsement	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sconswer	I-pers
,	O
is	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Vickerton	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
owner	O
of	O
several	O
ships	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
mistrust	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
no	O
questions	O
concerning	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
or	O
Croft	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
ship	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Maylin	O
of	O
Scarborough	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
know	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
some	O
connections	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
brother-in-law	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
bills	O
,	O
were	O
forged	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Turn-wheel	O
Lane	O
,	O
Cannon-street	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
such	O
persons	O
as	O
Thomas	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
,	O
partners	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Titteley	O
,	O
the	O
brother-in-law	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
of	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Quaker	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
Newsham	O
Hodges	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
each	O
bills	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
convinced	O
were	O
forged	O
.	O
Richard	O
Heklin	O
,	O
who	O
transacts	O
business	O
for	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
refused	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
such	O
bills	O
,	O
suspecting	O
them	O
since	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
has	O
no	O
correspondence	O
with	O
any	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
defect	O
in	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
present	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
handwriting	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
or	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
but	O
detained	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
for	O
such	O
an	O
offence	O
in	O
Surrey	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Cremain	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sidera	I-pers
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
plush	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Fliggart	I-pers
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fliggart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Fliggart	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
formerly	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Cable-street	B-place
,	I-place
Rosemary	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
set	O
himself	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
my	O
curtain	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
some	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
:	O
he	O
stuck	O
his	O
knife	O
in	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
spoke	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
their	O
butcher	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
my	O
child	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
contradict	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Clare-market	B-place
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
meat	O
hanging	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
air	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
watch	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
mutton	O
mentioned	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
,	O
by	O
Holborn	O
Bars	O
,	O
very	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
journeyman	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
78	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
maker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
clerk	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
some	O
spoons	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
business	O
:	O
Levi	O
soon	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
my	O
clerk	O
traded	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
spoons	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Levi	O
's	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
staid	O
till	O
Levi	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
Adams	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
these	O
spoons	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
78	O
tea-spoons	O
)	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
sell	O
my	O
spoons	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
distressed	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
on	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
Jew	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
these	O
very	O
spoons	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
blind	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
bespeak	O
goods	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
spoons	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
appointment	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Myer	O
's	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
bargained	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
shamoy	O
skin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
brass	O
pins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Yendle	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowring	I-pers
,	O
September	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ashwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Mrs.	O
Hodgson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
;	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
died	O
since	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
stolen	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
by	O
the	O
shirt	O
that	O
is	O
lost	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
turn	O
round	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
hung	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
view	O
of	O
a	O
Jobb	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
shirt	O
to	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
dry	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
slip	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
of	O
Cloth-workers	O
;	O
Mrs	O
Ringrose	O
washes	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
neighbours	O
;	O
she	O
takes	O
the	O
things	O
one	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
brings	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
some	O
marked	O
with	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
with	O
red	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ringrose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Billiter	O
Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
cobler	O
's	O
stall	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
at	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
which	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
some	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
particularly	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
advertised	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
's	O
paper	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
James	B-pers
Grief	I-pers
came	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
safe	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
all	O
safe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
la	O
ndlord	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grief	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
keys	O
from	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Salway	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
were	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
on	O
Little	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
Ellis	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
it	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
tied	O
one	O
over	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
round	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
one	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
Bond	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
his	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
goods	O
?	O
Grief	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Bond	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
Sliford	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
September	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Ellis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Going	O
through	O
Fenchurch-street	O
to	O
the	O
'Change	O
,	O
this	O
bundle	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
post	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
some	O
coachmen	O
if	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
a	O
reward	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
'Change	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Captain	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
;	O
then	O
going	O
over	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
us	O
up	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
separate	O
bundles	O
were	O
tied	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
cord	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
fits	O
in	O
the	O
bulk	O
used	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
Bond	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
India-House	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Ellis	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
tie	O
round	O
the	O
bundle	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
with	O
certain	O
stones	O
set	O
therein	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
October	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Minories	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
he	O
draw	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
steal	O
above	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
show	O
him	O
the	O
glass	O
:	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
guinea	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
that	O
for	O
one	O
)	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
hands	O
over	O
them	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
servant	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
to-morrow	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
turning	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Harkee	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
two	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
ring	O
out	O
of	O
each	O
hand	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
stuck	O
there	O
with	O
something	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
also	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
cane	O
.	O
After	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
The	O
rings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
wife	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
the	O
daughter	O
,	O
confirmed	O
her	O
testimony	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
grand	O
jury	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
dinner	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
detected	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
home	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
cane	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
forty-doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
durst	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
steal	O
rings	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sheriff	O
's	O
officer	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
but	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
fivepence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
farthings	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Horn-fair	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
up	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
ring	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
s.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
one	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
one	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
she	O
snatched	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
;	O
my	O
cane	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
she	O
seized	O
that	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
flurry	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
guinea	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
for	O
my	O
cane	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
your	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
Silver-smith	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
that	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
mell	O
you	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
hear	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
:	O
he	O
demanded	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
White-Horse-Yard	O
,	O
Catherine-street	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
:	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Harding	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Say	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
:	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
acknowledge	O
myself	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
my	O
cane	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harding	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
show	O
'd	O
any	O
money	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
ring	O
on	O
his	O
finger	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
come	O
back	O
for	O
his	O
cane	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
again	O
before	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Nunn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pewter	O
mustard-pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pewter	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
November	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shoe-lane	I-place
;	O
my	O
apprentice	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
pewter	O
plates	O
secreted	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
staying	O
till	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
breakfast	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
plates	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
street	O
near	O
Break-neck	O
stairs	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Harris	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
seven	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
mustard	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
pepper	O
caster	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
plates	O
we	O
had	O
missed	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
;	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
plates	O
were	O
marked	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
apprentice	O
mark	O
them	O
:	O
upon	O
my	O
shewing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knee	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
five	O
plater	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
nine	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
a	O
wheel	O
,	O
and	O
portered	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
submit	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Petit	I-pers
,	O
December	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Petit	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
six	O
,	O
coming	O
along	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
tugging	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
about	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
hit	O
my	O
elbow	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
perhaps	O
I	O
had	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
tug	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
chaps	O
turn	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
something	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
fall	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
in	O
Bunhill-Row	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Fulham	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pints	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
glass	O
quart	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bowstrell	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cost	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
brandy	O
and	O
bottles	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Fulham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
declaring	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
besides	O
what	O
Fulham	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
betwixt	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
:	O
he	O
sat	O
and	O
drank	O
till	O
about	O
six	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
:	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Worster	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
off	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
missed	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
still	O
,	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
back	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
scuffle	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
dropt	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Worster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
the	O
tankard	O
fell	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intoxicated	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
defrauding	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
farthest	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
Birmingham	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Manby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Manby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
near	O
Burntwood	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
there	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
17th	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
her	O
last	O
?	O
Manby	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
the	O
Mare	O
.	O
Manby	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
dark	O
brown	O
saddle	O
mare	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
bought	O
her	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Staines	O
(	O
he	O
drives	O
the	O
Staines	O
stage-coach	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
mare	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Manby	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Manby	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
brown	O
mare	O
that	O
I	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Manby	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
Guildford	O
assize	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Bradley	B-pers
That	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Manby	O
had	O
her	O
again	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
her	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
her	O
at	O
Turnham-green	O
;	O
she	O
stood	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
call	O
to	O
water	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
farther	O
Pack-horse	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
there	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
her	O
on	O
trial	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
again	O
to	O
Turnham-green	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
to	O
Turnham-green	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
whether	O
he	O
asked	O
eight	O
guineas	O
or	O
seven	O
:	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
the	O
mare	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
Staines	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
mare	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
mare	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
over	O
age	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
mare	O
worth	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
never	O
set	O
a	O
price	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
can	O
be	O
worth	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
16	O
or	O
18	O
guineas	O
.	O
Bradley	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Turnham-green	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Grinstead	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mare	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Manby	O
's	O
field	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Manby	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
delivered	O
the	O
mare	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Stallard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Bethnal-green	B-place
parish	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
half-penny-worth	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back-kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
over	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
shoulder	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
immediately	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
bidding	O
a	O
gentleman	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
two	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
spoon	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
fumbling	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
another	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
again	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
the	O
spoon	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jenkinson	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
fellow	O
spoon	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
,	O
being	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
at	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
against	O
the	O
spoon	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
challenged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Anne	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Job	O
Field	O
two	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
August	B-pers
(	O
a	O
Negroman	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lionel	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
November	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Lionel	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
has	O
my	O
first	O
floor	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
silver	O
buckles	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
laid	O
two	O
guineas	O
(	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
property	O
)	O
into	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
drawer	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
knees	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saved	O
that	O
money	O
up	O
,	O
by	O
dressing	O
people	O
's	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
finishing	O
coffins	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coffin-maker	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
employed	O
August	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
things	O
of	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
abroad	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
things	O
of	O
great	O
Value	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
several	O
times	O
brought	O
my	O
purse	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
's	O
sister	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
'	O
with	O
messages	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
hours	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Moses	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
November	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
at	O
Ratcliff-cross	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
company	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
:	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
)	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Cable-street	B-place
;	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
they	O
got	O
some	O
beer	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
lodger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
all	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
sat	O
close	O
by	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
blasted	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
never	O
wore	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Butler	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
he	O
would	O
look	O
into	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
right	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
Butler	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
?	O
Howell	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
find	O
that	O
house	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
going	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
the	O
expence	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
agreeable	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
justice	O
was	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
was	O
present	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
leave	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Low	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
Butler	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
.	O
My	O
landlord	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
your	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
return	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
his	O
watch	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sitting	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wear	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
staid	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cable-street	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Siseham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
give	O
the	O
man	O
his	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
than	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
seeing	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Howell	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
:	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
woman	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Butler	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
here	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bell	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Howell	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discharge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
without	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
justice	O
if	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
bring	O
him	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sent	O
his	O
wife	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crump	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
master	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Butler	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
doors	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Howell	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Antigallican-arms	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
where	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pay	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
into	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
heave	O
money	O
about	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Butler	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
he	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
six-pence	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
roguishness	O
in	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
sold	O
or	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
of	O
keeping	O
it	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
may	O
die	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
stand	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belee	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Phebea	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	O
:	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Ratcliff	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Monk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
then	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
;	O
I	O
reached	O
down	O
twenty-two	O
,	O
linked	O
together	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
knobs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
only	O
wires	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
weigh	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
reached	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
whole	O
link	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
weigh	O
another	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
link	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
down	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
pair	O
:	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
link	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
she	O
went	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
link	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
18	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
where	O
every	O
body	O
lives	O
that	O
use	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
Monk	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Kingstreet	O
,	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
our	O
little	O
boy	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
enquiring	O
at	O
the	O
third	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
herself	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
jade	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
;	O
her	O
mother	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
vile	O
jade	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
hold	O
my	O
child	O
:	O
she	O
tore	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
manner	O
:	O
she	O
shoved	O
her	O
daughter	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
the	O
girl	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
ear-rings	O
:	O
both	O
the	O
mother	O
and	O
daughter	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
any	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
mother	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
daughter	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-two	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
on	O
a	O
link	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
pair	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
mother	O
offer	O
to	O
pay	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
take	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
?	O
R.	O
Audley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Legroves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
given	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
people	O
have	O
their	O
things	O
again	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
wracked	O
to	O
death	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
any	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
father-in-law	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
;	O
what	O
I	O
pledged	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Audley	B-pers
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
6	O
s.	O
then	O
she	O
weighed	O
a	O
pair	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
said	O
5	O
s.	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
she	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
guilty	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
worth	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
her	O
father-in-law	O
,	O
Wm	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Anne	O
Hunter	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Watson	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Phebea	O
Audley	O
.	O
This	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
comes	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
held	O
both	O
my	O
arms	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanfield	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ogden	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
orchard-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
happend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
's	O
labourer	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Ambury	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
They	O
say	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
water	O
for	O
tea	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
the	O
20th	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
before	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
quitted	O
her	O
lodgings	O
on	O
that	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
light	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
and	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
she	O
leave	O
her	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
removed	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Duck-lane	O
,	O
within	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Crofts	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
indifferent	O
:	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
as	O
hearty	O
as	O
a	O
buck	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
your	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
disadvantage	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
another	O
woman	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
at	O
Manchester	O
or	O
Birmingham	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
dinner	O
with	O
us	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
lodgings	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
owe	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
She	O
owed	O
me	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
:	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
consequence	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
13	O
guineas	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
kept	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
box	O
before	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
breast	O
of	O
mutton	O
and	O
turnips	O
,	O
and	O
dined	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
that	O
young	O
woman	O
stay	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
your	O
husband	O
stay	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
no	O
longer	O
than	O
his	O
dinner	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
woman	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
agree	O
that	O
woman	O
should	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
woman	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
,	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Their	O
house	O
was	O
open	O
to	O
all	O
comers	O
and	O
goers	O
:	O
that	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
got	O
all	O
drunk	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
me	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
pawn	O
her	O
gown	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
your	O
gown	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
your	O
money	O
last	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
hit	O
the	O
chamber-pot	O
against	O
the	O
box	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
out	O
on	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
from	O
year	O
's	O
end	O
to	O
years	O
end	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
that	O
Sunday	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Monday	O
neither	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
to	O
Tothill-street	O
,	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
feet	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
foot	O
wide	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Tothill-street	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
your	O
room	O
door	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
back-door	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
only	O
a	O
button	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
know	O
of	O
your	O
going	O
out	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
her	O
any	O
time	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
frequently	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
our	O
room	O
,	O
pretending	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
back	O
door	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
unbuttoned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
room	O
by	O
that	O
door	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
sometimes	O
by	O
one	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
easy	O
to	O
open	O
that	O
door	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
The	O
button	O
is	O
withinside	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
very	O
easily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
buttoned	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
S.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
button	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Heaton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
and	O
leather-cutter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
work	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
granted	O
him	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
understand	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
allowed	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
week	O
:	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
little	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
work	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
detected	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
usual	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
horn	O
to	O
pull	O
up	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
before	O
that	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
any	O
shoes	O
out	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
two	O
different	O
pairs	O
of	O
shoes	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
two	O
different	O
workmen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Samuel	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
,	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
without	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
rather	O
after	O
seven	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Friday	O
:	O
at	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
last	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
somebody	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
servant	O
not	O
to	O
unlock	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
press	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
all	O
was	O
right	O
,	O
as	O
left	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
ten	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
customer	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
as	O
customary	O
,	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
shoes	O
about	O
his	O
heels	O
;	O
followed	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
shoe-shop	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
shop	O
:	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
the	O
press	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
served	O
a	O
customer	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
heel-pieces	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
shutters	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
shoe-shop	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
press	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
seemingly	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
side-pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
skirts	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
open	O
the	O
sash	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
.	O
After	O
my	O
servant	O
had	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sam	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
;	O
he	O
moved	O
his	O
hat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
show	O
?	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
you	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
leather-shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
good	O
morning	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
man	O
open	O
the	O
press	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
pair	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
about	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
from	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
below	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
:	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
shoes	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
goods	O
being	O
at	O
four	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
many	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hagan	I-pers
,	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
produced	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
deposed	O
they	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
unfortunate	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
limbs	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
cruelty	O
of	O
a	O
master	O
at	O
a	O
boarding-school	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
rich	O
relations	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
spent	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
fortune	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
brought	O
myself	O
to	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
disgrace	O
upon	O
my	O
family	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Randall	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
deny	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
once	O
could	O
have	O
brought	O
many	O
credible	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
case	O
now	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
coach-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
November	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holt	O
,	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
chamberlain	O
at	O
the	O
Pyed	O
Bull	O
:	O
our	O
coach-house	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
cold	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
late	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
carriage	O
up	O
at	O
almost	O
eleven	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
here	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
country	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
lodge	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
so	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Get	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
you	O
a	O
lodging	O
:	O
he	O
walked	O
off	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
chariot	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
drawn	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
would	O
not	O
shut	O
to	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
out-side	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
coach-house	O
was	O
undone	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
other	O
stables	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
at	O
Islington	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
before	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
The	O
confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
.	O
The	O
confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
near	O
the	O
Gully-hole	O
,	O
in	O
Chick	O
lane	O
,	O
for	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
confession	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Coffey	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Rotherhithe	O
.	O
Three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Denmark-street	B-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff-highway	I-place
(	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
)	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
enough	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
this	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
pay	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
for	O
us	O
both	O
:	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
as	O
mentioned	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
about	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
three	O
guineas	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
two	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
:	O
the	O
shilling	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
pocket	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
guinea	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
lie	O
with	O
you	O
all	O
night	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
concealed	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
must	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
all	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
lie	O
upon	O
her	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Magnab	I-pers
the	O
maid-servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
I	O
that	O
lay	O
together	O
:	O
Ward	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
Magnab	O
lay	O
all	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
bedside	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
:	O
Ward	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Deptford	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Magnab	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
persuaded	O
me	O
that	O
Magnab	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
sent	O
one	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
why	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
acknowledge	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Magnab	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
himself	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
lie	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bed	O
if	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
slip	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
his	O
bed	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
?	O
I	O
fetched	O
him	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
by	O
his	O
bedside	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
he	O
quarrelled	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
her	O
staying	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
bed	O
but	O
my	O
own	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
slip	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
serge	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
gingham	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
November	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
,	O
and	O
this	O
black	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
lodged	O
there	O
also	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
my	O
cloaths	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
black	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
recommended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
by	O
enquiring	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-cross	O
,	O
by	O
Charing-cross	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
pawned	O
opposite	O
Durham-yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
,	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Black	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
let	O
another	O
Black	O
have	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
to	O
Ireland	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
waistcoat	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
Pepper	O
and	O
Salt	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
wore	O
it	O
above	O
four	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
accidentally	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
coat	O
worth	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
coat	O
cost	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Noise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
at	O
Cock-hill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
Captain	O
Oliver	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
bound	O
for	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Sunday	O
night	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
late	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
room	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
his	O
clothes	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
coat	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Half-moon-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
John	O
Peters	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
Captain	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Woolwich	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
another	O
man	O
conveyed	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
halves	O
in	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Heather	B-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
right	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Peters	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
letter	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blacket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Noise	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
:	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
near	O
Exeter	O
'Change	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
pawned	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sold	O
it	O
out	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
,	O
Charing-Cross	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
some	O
people	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
best	O
confess	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
a	O
girl	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
27	O
,	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
leaden	O
pound	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
2	O
pound	O
brass	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
leaden	O
weight	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Martin	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Marlock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
December	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
betwixt	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
conducted	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
his	O
candle	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Hollo	O
,	O
who	O
calls	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
stick	O
out	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
before	O
Justice	O
Scott	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
and	O
Lewis	B-pers
Udale	I-pers
were	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
testimony	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ashmore	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
a	O
nonplus	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Tophurst	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
27	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discharged	O
last	O
week	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Jersey	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
furlough	O
,	O
to	O
Newcastle	O
upon	O
Tyne	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
in	O
Church-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sight	O
being	O
bad	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Milbank	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
lain	O
two	O
nights	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
Head	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
soldier	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
private	O
house	O
alone	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
moidore	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
six-pence	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
drank	O
twice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
pence	O
for	O
her	O
trouble	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
pull	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
breeches	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
awaked	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
seven	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
woman	O
and	O
her	O
companion	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
was	O
still	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
companion	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
woman	O
up	O
,	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
name	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
18th	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
information	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
near	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
is	O
named	O
Davidson	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
set	O
Ann	B-pers
Tophurst	I-pers
at	O
liberty	O
:	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
this	O
watch	O
produced	O
here	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
,	O
a	O
Fishmonger	O
,	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
27	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
:	O
they	O
described	O
it	O
both	O
by	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
thief	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
sells	O
things	O
by	O
Auction	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
was	O
to	O
advance	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
where	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
:	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Dark-house	O
lane	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
brought	O
and	O
examined	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
separately	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Maccall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
November	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Upper	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
stalls	O
in	O
the	O
steel-yard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
;	O
the	O
iron	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
deemed	O
our	O
property	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
is	O
landed	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stubley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
of	O
the	O
steel-yard	O
:	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
hall	O
where	O
this	O
iron	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
near	O
where	O
such	O
pieces	O
of	O
iron	O
lay	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
pissing	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
into	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
stole	O
some	O
iron	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
kneeled	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l	O
was	O
in	O
him	O
for	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
pile	O
of	O
iron	O
marked	O
P.	O
R.	O
M.	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Patrick	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
thoroughfare	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lockey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
quartered	O
upon	O
me	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
lately	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
abroad	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
when	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Laughlin	O
Goff	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
a	O
fair	O
,	O
just	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
man	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
is	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
clothes	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
gone	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
court	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baudouin	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
October	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Baudouin	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
is	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
order	O
four	O
bottles	O
of	O
cappillaire	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crisp	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Catherine	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Baudouin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perfumer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Seething-lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
four	O
bottles	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
his	O
mistress	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
send	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
send	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Baudouin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
Mary	B-pers
Colwell	I-pers
with	O
the	O
cappillaire	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
five	O
and	O
three-penny	O
piece	O
:	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
six-pence	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
crying	O
,	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
people	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pierpoint	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
girl	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
quarter-guineas	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
did	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shillings	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
cross	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
Bell	O
,	O
a	O
lifeguard	O
man	O
,	O
