TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
of	O
JUNE	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGEN	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Eardley	I-pers
Wilmot	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Rice	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cancellor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carmichael	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reader	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carrock	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cubbidge	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Dick	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Scuder	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hathwell	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
.	O
319	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Dollard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
behind	O
me	O
of	O
,	O
Stop	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
pick-pocket	O
,	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
:	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
same	O
voice	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
your	O
pocket	O
has	O
been	O
picked	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
court	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
ran	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
making	O
water	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
dropped	O
any	O
thing	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Drawwater	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
nothing	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Drawwater	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Ludgate-hill	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
apprized	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
a	O
court	O
:	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
appearance	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
public-house	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Drawwater	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
is	O
that	O
court	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
?	O
Gordon	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
doors	O
distant	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
immediately	O
made	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
Gordon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Drawwater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
tavern	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
whether	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
?	O
Drawwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
man	O
run	O
down	O
that	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
Drawwater	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
spout	O
;	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
tucked	O
in	O
:	O
this	O
spout	O
is	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
to	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
maker	O
,	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
bread	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
320	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Conrad	B-pers
Mazaret	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Vidal	I-pers
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Lamatte	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
interpreter	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Vidal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine-merchant	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
seven	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chamber	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Mentioning	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Notley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
two	O
table	O
spoons	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
produced	O
two	O
table	O
spoons	O
:	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
gentleman	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dubrce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
redeem	O
these	O
two	O
spoons	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Vidal	O
sent	O
the	O
money	O
by	O
me	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
shirts	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Chevalier	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Demateer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
ill	O
:	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
)	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
gaol	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Demateer	O
.	O
He	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
and	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
spoon	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
he	O
dined	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Natley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
pawn	O
it	O
with	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Notley	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
owned	O
that	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
321	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
sixteen	O
iron	O
bitts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
sink	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
iron	O
drill	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
wooden	O
plough	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
eight	O
plough-irons	O
,	O
fourteen	O
chissels	O
,	O
twelve	O
gages	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
carpenters	O
tools	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
at	O
Tottenham-high	B-place
cross	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chest	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
locked	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
person	O
get	O
to	O
your	O
chest	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
that	O
was	O
screwed	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
pursuit	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
suspected	O
another	O
person	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
tools	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hodge	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
tools	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
322	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Alderton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Alderton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
Cecil-street	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
jirk	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
third	O
person	O
;	O
having	O
nobody	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
catch	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
waiter	O
to	O
search	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
them	O
both	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
another	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
appeared	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Nelson	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
this	O
winter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
transported	O
three	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
intend	O
never	O
to	O
forgive	O
any	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
catch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
lad	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
both	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
into	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
us	O
go	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
since	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Bristol	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
spinner	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
he	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
Fleetstreet	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
between	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
turned	O
about	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
hit	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
gentleman	O
picked	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cloaths	O
,	O
not	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
405	O
,	O
406	O
,	O
407	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
323	O
,	O
324	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
May	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixty	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wiggett	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
;	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
assisting	O
,	O
and	O
commanding	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
to	O
do	O
and	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
felony	O
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wiggett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Turnstile	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gagnon	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
there	O
before	O
:	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
some	O
ribbons	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
ribbons	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
Three	O
rolls	O
of	O
ribbon	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wiggett	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
opened	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
show	O
them	O
some	O
ribbons	O
:	O
I	O
handed	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
ribbons	O
down	O
.	O
May	O
agreed	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
:	O
I	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
box	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
colour	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
have	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
measuring	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gagnon	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
May	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
more	O
ribbons	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
May	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ribbons	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
May	O
's	O
pockets	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
when	O
I	O
set	O
it	O
before	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
?	O
M.	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gagnon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Turnstile	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
look	O
sharp	O
after	O
them	O
fellows	O
,	O
they	O
look	O
more	O
like	O
thieves	O
than	O
horses	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
opinion	O
they	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
something	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apprentice	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
ribbons	O
;	O
presently	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
!	O
they	O
have	O
put	O
some	O
in	O
their	O
pockets	O
now	O
:	O
presently	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
,	O
there	O
!	O
they	O
have	O
taken	O
some	O
more	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
come	O
over	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
carpenter	O
followed	O
us	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
May	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
you	O
put	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
friend	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shuffled	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
rolls	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
slipped	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
up	O
two	O
rolls	O
,	O
one	O
purple	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
)	O
:	O
these	O
are	O
they	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
other	O
roll	O
of	O
green	O
ribbon	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
Stanley	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
carpenter	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
,	O
the	O
high-constable	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
pulling	O
their	O
hats	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
we	O
:	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
may	O
come	O
to	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Stanley	O
say	O
?	O
Gagnon	O
.	O
Stanley	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
th	O
at	O
ever	O
we	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
these	O
actions	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
whose	O
property	O
the	O
ribbons	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
begged	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
My	O
master	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
,	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
go	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Wiggett	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
watch	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
May	O
put	O
some	O
ribbons	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
separate	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
these	O
ribbons	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
begged	O
we	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
no	O
ways	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
May	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
plead	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Stanley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
otherwise	O
than	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Magenis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
May	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
workedin	O
the	O
watch	O
way	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Walworth	O
,	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
watch-movement-maker	O
.	O
May	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
:	O
he	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
steel-work	O
part	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
diligent	O
man	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
May	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Stanley	O
about	O
Newington	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
tinkering	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
goes	O
with	O
a	O
barrow	O
,	O
grinding	O
of	O
knives	O
.	O
May	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
325	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
leaden	O
glue-pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
;	O
one	O
leaden	O
glue-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tunbridge	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
leaden	O
glue-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
in	O
building	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Mercer's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Long-acre	I-place
:	O
these	O
four	O
pots	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
building	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mullings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Four	O
pots	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
prosecutors	O
depose	O
to	O
their	O
respective	O
pots	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
two	O
of	O
these	O
pots	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
bag	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pots	O
,	O
with	O
nails	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
things	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
came	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
workhouse	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
326	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
plane	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
sash	O
sillaster	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
's	O
and	O
one	O
oil-stone	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Marychurch	B-pers
Callin	I-pers
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
Stephen	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Marybone	B-place
.	O
This	O
day	O
month	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sash	O
sillaster	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
buildings	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
us	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
missed	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
)	O
:	O
we	O
suspected	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
offered	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
another	O
by	O
.	O
Marychurch	O
Callin	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
oil-stone	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
plane	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bench	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
questioned	O
him	O
about	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
l	O
was	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
These	O
tools	O
were	O
missed	O
this	O
day	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
oil-stone	O
on	O
his	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
sillaster	O
behind	O
the	O
bench	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
sillaster	O
was	O
Brown	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
one	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
the	O
oil-stone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
sash	O
sillaster	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
327	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
ax	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
wheel-wright	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
this	O
ax	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
ax	O
from	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
within	O
the	O
gateway	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
ax	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
victuals	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
starve	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
seeing	O
it	O
lying	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
yards	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
328	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cannell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
Recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
329	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hester	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farrard	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cosins	I-pers
,	O
February	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farrard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Spittal	O
Fields	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
four	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Cosins	I-pers
,	O
to	O
weave	O
:	O
on	O
his	O
bringing	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
wanting	O
one	O
pound	O
two	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
Cosins	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Hick's-Hall	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
seven	O
ounces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
ounces	O
to	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Levins	I-pers
:	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cosins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
wound	O
silk	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
to	O
her	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
knot	O
of	O
silk	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
may	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
skains	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
near	O
Shoreditch	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Eight	O
Bells	O
,	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
Spittal	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
:	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
to	O
four	O
ounces	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
sitting	O
justices	O
,	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
one	O
silk	O
to	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Levins	I-pers
.	O
She	O
owned	O
to	O
taking	O
seven	O
ounces	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Hick's-hall	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
Anne	B-pers
Levins	I-pers
;	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
to	O
taking	O
between	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
ounces	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Roloe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
headborough	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
confession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
At	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
silk	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
one	O
word	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
330	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
tin	O
lanthorns	O
,	O
glazed	O
with	O
crown	O
glass	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wesley	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
repairing	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Wesley	I-pers
's	O
,	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
Windmill-hill	B-place
,	I-place
called	I-place
the	I-place
Foundery	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Upper	I-place
Moor-fields	I-place
;	O
these	O
lanthorns	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
separate	O
times	O
;	O
one	O
hung	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
preaching	O
place	O
,	O
on	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
lanthorn	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
,	O
exactly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
creature	O
,	O
lying	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
asking	O
charity	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
hardly	O
keep	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
something	O
for	O
herself	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
by	O
London-wall	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
eight-pence	O
on	O
one	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
gone	O
on	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lost	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
fatherless	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
followed	O
these	O
people	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
utter	O
destruction	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
destruction	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
pawn	O
my	O
cloths	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wesley	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
recover	O
my	O
cloths	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
cloths	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
on	O
for	O
about	O
12	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
my	O
living	O
,	O
being	O
let	O
to	O
perish	O
without	O
mercy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
day	O
walking	O
very	O
solitary	O
in	O
the	O
Foundery	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
these	O
lanthorns	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
one	O
for	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
but	O
who	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
recover	O
my	O
cloths	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
drove	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wesley	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
require	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
cloths	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
upon	O
a	O
poor	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
water	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
account	O
she	O
has	O
given	O
,	O
true	O
or	O
false	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
false	O
story	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
believed	O
the	O
poor	O
creature	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mind	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
331	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vaugh	I-pers
.	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Vaugh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
distiller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Wapping-street	B-place
.	O
Last	O
saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
somebody	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cask	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
stocking	O
officer	O
,	O
who	O
gauged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
gallons	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
at	O
a	O
cask	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
Vaugh	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
empty	O
ones	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
cellar	O
.	O
At	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
some	O
neighbours	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pipe-maker	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
gallons	O
of	O
your	O
brandy	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
by	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
common	O
necessary	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
brandy	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
last	O
monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
:	O
he	O
there	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
confederate	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
:	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Vaugh	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
the	O
flap	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
little	O
cellar	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
little	O
casks	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
empty	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
brandy	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pipe	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Vaugh	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hulme	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
work	O
:	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pipe-maker	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
opened	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
yard	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
common	O
necessary	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
kagg	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
gallons	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
kagg	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
seen	O
,	O
followed	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
soon	O
see	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
gimlet	O
,	O
and	O
bored	O
down	O
the	O
bung	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bung	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
French	O
brandy	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
mate	O
of	O
ship	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
belonged	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
two	O
gallons	O
of	O
the	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
remainder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
kagg	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
Wapping-stairs	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
protecutor	O
's	O
cellar	O
is	O
?	O
Hulme	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
400	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Bridge	O
Maryot	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Greenwood-court	O
,	O
Nightingale-lane	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
brandy	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
would	O
be	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
gallon	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
if	O
his	O
master	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
brandy	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
that	O
Friday	O
night	O
late	O
,	O
drinking	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
12	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
this	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
332	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Medley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mealey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
James	I-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blewet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
February	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Blewet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gun-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel-road	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
Mount	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
witness	O
and	O
another	O
sailor	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
alehouse	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
difference	O
between	O
a	O
gun	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
last	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
without	O
With-your-leave	O
,	O
or	O
By-your-leave	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
for	O
an	O
old	O
gun	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
brings	O
a	O
pistol	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
in	O
exchange	O
?	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
pistol	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
an	O
Indiaman	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
expect	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
captains	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Dinner	O
was	O
getting	O
ready	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
sailor	O
staid	O
and	O
dined	O
:	O
at	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
sailor	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Harding	O
whom	O
they	O
hired	O
for	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
Harding	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
gun	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
:	O
Harding	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
would	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
orders	O
from	O
the	O
Justices	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
gun	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
table	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
flung	O
upon	O
poor	O
Will	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gun	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
gun	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spittal-fields	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
goods	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
safe	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
careful	O
how	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
:	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
regi	O
mentals	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
mentioned	O
so	O
many	O
dozen	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
many	O
dozen	O
of	O
china	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
waterman	O
had	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
slip	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
a	O
token	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
right	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
lower	O
water-gate	O
,	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
a	O
gun	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
gun	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
gun	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
gun	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
captain	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Indies	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
Deptford	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
make	O
all	O
the	O
speed	O
you	O
can	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
none	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Baptist-Head	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Lower	O
Water-gate	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
expecting	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fraud	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
porter	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
with	O
such	O
notes	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
my	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
back	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
gun	O
coming	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Greenland-dock	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
demanded	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
gun	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
's	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
owned	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
4	O
s.	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
gun	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
gun	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Harding	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
agreement	O
between	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
gun	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
a	O
flint	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
stood	O
with	O
this	O
gun	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
talked	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
333	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpkin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
London-wall	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lodged	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
by	B-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
kettle	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
pretty	O
backward	O
in	O
her	O
rent	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
last	O
sessions	O
ended	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
used	O
generally	O
to	O
lock	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
kettle	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
the	O
kettle	O
was	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
another	O
woman	O
carried	O
that	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
the	O
bed	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
who	O
vouched	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
within	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
bed	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Simpkin	O
.	O
Ross	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
husband	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
she	O
calls	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witness	O
here	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bilingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Simpkin	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
rogue	O
of	O
a	O
husband	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
raise	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
family	O
:	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Bilingham	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Stepney	O
parish	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-court	O
,	O
Winford-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
bad	O
character	O
;	O
she	O
once	O
lived	O
facing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
propose	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
gentlewoman	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
they	O
begged	O
very	O
hard	O
;	O
something	O
was	O
talked	O
of	O
about	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
consent	O
of	O
the	O
grand	O
jury	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
334	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Steping	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Steping	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
le	O
Grand	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
inst	O
.	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
convicts	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
crowd	O
,	O
within	O
about	B-place
twenty	I-place
yards	I-place
of	I-place
Newgate	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Magpye	I-place
;	O
the	O
blow	O
occasioned	O
my	O
reeling	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
almost	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
left	O
hand	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
lose	O
your	O
hat	O
.	O
Directly	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pocket-handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
or	O
less	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
putting	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Radman	I-pers
;	O
I	O
gave	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
somebody	O
at	O
my	O
fob	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
short	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rogue	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
there	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
snatch	O
at	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
arm	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
move	O
it	O
forwards	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
just	O
about	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
into	O
somebody	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
is	O
handed	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
take	O
and	O
lick	O
you	O
well	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
but	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
box	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
several	O
voices	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Magpy	O
say	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
an	O
errant	O
pick-pocket	O
:	O
I	O
shoved	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Magpye	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
sheriff	O
's	O
officer	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
some	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
assist	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
dismounted	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hoey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
spectators	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
criminals	O
go	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
loading	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
gentleman	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
:	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
chink	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
second	O
cart	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
loaded	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
foot	O
upon	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
serve	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
,	O
in	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
about	O
it	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
:	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
l.	O
Name	O
,	O
Brital	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
at	O
Newgate	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
nuts	O
,	O
and	O
leaned	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
both	O
my	O
hands	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Sea-coal-lane	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
,	O
map	O
and	O
printseller	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
bed-joyner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
behaved	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
earned	O
22	O
s.	O
or	O
23	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
weeks	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
335	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Humphry	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Andrew	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Newgate	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
seeing	O
my	O
eye	O
was	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
dropped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
His	O
mother	O
appeared	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
sworn	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
ten	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
336	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Hugh	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
under	O
journeyman	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
three	O
separate	O
times	O
;	O
once	O
of	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
of	O
this	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
attending	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
at	O
breakfast	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
canister	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
served	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
weigh	O
her	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
canister	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
sugar	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tray	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
;	O
I	O
imagine	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
six-pence	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
change	O
:	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
shillings	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
known	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
attended	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
examined	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charlton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
lying	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
tea	O
table	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
till	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
servant	O
's	O
saying	O
he	O
suspected	O
he	O
once	O
stole	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
at	O
separate	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
three	O
shillings	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
change	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
well	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
friends	O
to	O
remit	O
money	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
had	O
he	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
ten	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
be	O
discharged	O
,	O
or	O
receive	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
service	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
337	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ridgment	O
,	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
.	O
Being	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
,	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
North-Audley-street	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
house	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
court-road	O
;	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Warren	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
easing	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
rifle	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Oxford	O
road	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
kicking	O
up	O
my	O
heels	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
ran	O
along	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
weapon	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
Warren	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hollowed	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
much	O
noise	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
throtled	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Warren	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
so	O
sharp	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
purse	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Warren	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
six-pence	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
neck	O
:	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
suppose	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
if	O
help	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Earp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
crying	O
out	O
in	O
Soho-square	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
seemingly	O
;	O
I	O
darkened	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
;	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
charge	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
aggressor	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bettoe	I-pers
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
taking	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
?	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
slip	O
off	O
his	O
frock	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
knocked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
master	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
:	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
his	O
hands	O
as	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
seeing	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
his	O
was	O
a	O
six-pence	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
attack	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Betton	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Bettoe	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
Soho-square	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
expecting	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
staff	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
box	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
into	O
the	O
square	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
running	O
?	O
Bettoe	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
.	O
Kelly	O
seemed	O
to	O
talk	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
quarrel	O
betwixt	O
them	O
:	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
ado	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
struggling	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
slipped	O
off	O
his	O
neck	O
.	O
Matthew	O
Green	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
the	O
watchmen	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
338	O
,	O
339	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
eleven	O
pound	O
of	O
pork	O
,	O
called	O
ham	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Duncan	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Saviour	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Bolt	O
and	O
Tun	O
Inn	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
box	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
down	O
into	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cuthbert	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Bolt	O
and	O
Tun	O
for	O
a	O
box	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cuthbert	O
:	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hambleton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
it	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
rest	O
myself	O
:	O
a	O
woman	O
asked	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
to	O
help	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
(	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
questions	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
spell	O
;	O
so	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
turned	O
into	O
Pater-noster-row	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
slip	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Canes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Plough-street	O
,	O
Goodman's-fields	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
coat	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
pledged	O
before	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Jacob	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
Jews	O
would	O
not	O
touch	O
money	O
on	O
your	O
sabbath	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
As	O
to	O
money	O
and	O
a	O
pretty	O
girl	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
touched	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
Sharp	O
,	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
340	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Park-place	O
by	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Philip	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
with	O
some	O
relations	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
in	O
Cockspur-street	B-place
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
paving	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
stones	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
directly	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
chair	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
named	O
Harrington	O
,	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
round-house	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
watch	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
you	O
felt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
my	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
quitted	O
his	O
hold	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
again	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
round	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
as	O
the	O
watch	O
were	O
going	O
ten	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
were	O
advising	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
to	O
speak	O
very	O
reasonably	O
and	O
sensibly	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
wall	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
which	O
knocked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
running	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
towards	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
round-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Brentford	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Joyner's-street	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
father-in-law	O
's	O
.	O
Just	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Pall-mall	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
fall	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
paving	O
stones	O
:	O
another	O
man	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
341	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dagon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vaux	I-pers
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vaux	I-pers
.	O
On	O
May	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
we	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
her	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
serving	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
hustling	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
stirred	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
fell	O
down	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
possessed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
342.	O
(	O
L	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
room	O
even	O
to	O
that	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
seemed	O
a	O
little	O
frighted	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
frighted	O
at	O
,	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Nurse	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
a-jar	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
kitchen	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
spoons	O
(	O
mentioned	O
)	O
and	O
apron	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
between	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
shop	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
apron	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitton	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
having	O
first	O
seen	O
her	O
;	O
his	O
window	O
looks	O
into	O
our	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitton	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Blake	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
saw	O
her	O
peeping	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
kitchen	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
nurse-keeping	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
a	O
chairing	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reyner	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
nurse	O
that	O
nursed	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
lying	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
nursing	O
in	O
Alders-gate-street	O
,	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
doors	O
up	O
an	O
entry	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
frighted	O
:	O
I	O
wanted	O
only	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
the	O
nurse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Rachael	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
18	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Lythan	I-pers
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
343	O
.	O
344	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ricketts	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
walking-canes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Worster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
vessel	O
called	O
a	O
hoy	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Dagenart	I-pers
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
the	O
canes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
in	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
secreted	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
King	O
took	O
them	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
Abe	O
Jacobs	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
King	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
His	O
evidence	O
not	O
being	O
supported	O
by	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
345	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooksbank	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooksbank	I-pers
.	O
Yesterday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
my	O
son	O
said	O
,	O
Papa	O
,	O
Papa	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
(	O
pointing	O
towards	O
Newgate-street	O
)	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
gathered	O
together	O
:	O
a	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
just	O
within	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
tea-board	O
cutter	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
since	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooksbank	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
15th	O
year	O
of	O
my	O
age	O
;	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Newgate	O
with	O
my	O
papa	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
us	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
us	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
fellows	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
hustled	O
me	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
papa	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
papa	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
linen	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Newgate-street	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
came	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
346	O
,	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Arabella	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Pentycross	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Pentycross	I-pers
,	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
through	O
Black-boy-alley	B-place
;	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Pentycross	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Cow-Cross	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
trifling	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
neck	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
five-pence	O
halfpenny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
six-pence	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
along	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
Portugal	O
piece	O
of	O
copper	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
much	O
like	O
that	O
woman	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
lusty	O
fat	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
turned	O
herself	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Pentycross	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
speaking	O
of	O
this	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
houses	O
in	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
West-Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
:	O
I	O
challenged	O
her	O
about	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
Pentycross	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
?	O
Pentycross	O
.	O
With	O
having	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
robbing	O
me	O
in	O
Black-boy-alley	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
Edwards	O
might	O
be	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
use	O
her	O
ill	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
Edwards	O
lived	O
?	O
Pentycross	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
Pentycross	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Arabella	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Pentycross	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
347	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Chantry	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Chantry	I-pers
,	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
the	B-place
Cheshire	I-place
Cheese	I-place
in	I-place
Parker's-lane	I-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
:	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
lodging	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
that	O
lodging-room	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
whether	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
all	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Chantry	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
the	O
17th	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Chantry	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
brewer	O
,	O
or	O
cooper	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
50	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
need	O
,	O
wanting	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
cloaths	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
348	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Newgent	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
hampers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pryor	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pryor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
turner	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
an	O
easy	O
chair	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
back-shop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
basket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Craven-street	O
,	O
with	O
6	O
hampers	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
warehouse-door	O
,	O
and	O
tumble	O
the	O
baskets	O
about	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
these	O
hampers	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
these	O
six	O
hampers	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse-door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
standing	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate-market	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
again	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
job	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
job	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
Go	O
down	O
to	O
Hungerford-market	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
four	O
baskets	O
packed	O
up	O
;	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
349	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
wooden	O
block	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
card	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
screws	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pressing	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
covenant	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
bound	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
missing	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Legroves	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
confession	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
try	O
how	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
or	O
alter	O
a	O
wig	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
thing	O
to	O
lend	O
a	O
covenant	O
servant	O
a	O
block	O
and	O
card	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
350	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Botham	I-pers
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Botham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Surry-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
the	O
coal-trade	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
barber	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
shave	O
me	O
and	O
fetch	O
my	O
wigs	O
.	O
Things	O
being	O
missing	O
at	O
sunday	O
times	O
,	O
we	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Maxfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
we	O
first	O
missed	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
We	O
knowing	O
nobody	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
laid	O
a	O
shirt	O
to	O
trap	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Two	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
shirts	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lockbard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Arundel-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
the	O
shirts	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
when	O
a	O
shirt	O
was	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
fear	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frighted	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Wyate	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
351	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
shoe-buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ditto	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
German	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
was	O
s	O
worn	O
interpreter	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
who	O
they	O
