TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGEN	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brigs	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hurles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sabe	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Vardy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Aires	I-pers
.	O
476	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Hockerday	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	B-place
16	I-place
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gang's-man	O
on	O
Fresh-wharf-key	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
several	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
hogs-heads	O
;	O
on	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
staid	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
hoop	O
stuck	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
of	O
a	O
hogshead	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
puddling	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
his	O
pocket	O
heavy	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
other	O
people	O
had	O
taken	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
sugar	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
lost	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
477	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
one	O
Germain	O
.	O
who	O
had	O
an	O
adze	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
cooper	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
an	O
adze	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
about	O
the	O
tobacco	O
hogshead	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pull	O
out	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
tobacco	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
difficulty	O
,	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tobacco	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
threw	O
some	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
Germain	O
threatened	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
business	O
they	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
of	O
pilfering	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
observed	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
heading	O
up	O
a	O
hogshead	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
for	O
a	O
chew	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Burch	O
had	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
tobacco	O
.	O
Burch	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
true	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
478	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Bellis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brigstock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brigstock	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brigstock	I-pers
(	O
the	O
younger	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
barber	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
shave	O
me	O
)	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
servants	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
watch	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Winman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brigstock	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
479	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
New	B-place
Brentford	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
several	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
would	O
suit	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
stair	O
foot	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
bring	O
down	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
earnest	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
absolutely	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
a	O
tobacco-box	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
taking	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
getting	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
key	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shotter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
in	O
going	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Old	O
Brentford	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
and	O
enquired	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
his	O
neighbours	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
favour	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
480	O
,	O
481	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Owen	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harmer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Spender	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Spender	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Dragon	I-place
at	I-place
Stepney	I-place
;	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Rope	I-place
walk	I-place
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
under	O
a	O
boarded	O
fence	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
cross	O
the	O
eyes	O
with	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
,	O
which	O
set	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
stagger	O
.	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
from	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
face	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
another	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
struggled	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
under	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
heavy	O
;	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
lusty	O
fat	O
man	O
)	O
:	O
we	O
tumbled	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
nimbler	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
times	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
fist	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
blow	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
left	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
about	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
heat	O
of	O
my	O
passion	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
before	O
then	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
blind	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
blows	O
on	O
my	O
upper	O
lip	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
gushed	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
nose	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
turned	O
partly	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
2	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
from	O
my	O
left	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
from	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
money	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Spender	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
moidore	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
buckles	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
papers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
rope-maker	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
found	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
confined	O
within	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
bruises	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
teeth	O
were	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
message	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
usage	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
word	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
Monday	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
hat	O
(	O
taking	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
;	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
burnt-in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
maker	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
lining	O
was	O
cut	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
sware	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
wig	O
,	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
,	O
has	O
swore	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
path-way	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
mentioned	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
two	O
people	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
gold	O
loop	O
and	O
button	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
cover	O
to	O
the	O
button	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owns	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Bow	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
parted	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
,	O
that	O
goes	O
down	O
to	O
Bow-common	O
;	O
if	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
very	O
bad	O
fields	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
church-yard	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
frequent	O
robberies	O
committed	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Glass-house-fields	O
,	O
near	O
Stepney-fields	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
on	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
screamed	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
this	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
she	O
live	O
at	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
she	O
does	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
not	O
;	O
sometimes	O
at	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
just	O
where	O
she	O
pleased	O
:	O
her	O
father	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
by	O
night	O
or	O
day	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
this	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
Whether	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
captain	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
collier	O
.	O
Her	O
mother	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
out	O
about	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Bow	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
Robinson	O
and	O
she	O
parted	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
within	O
300	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Robinson	O
keeps	O
her	O
company	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Galton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
,	O
in	O
Glass-house-yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Smith	O
could	O
inform	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
now	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Captain	O
Spender	B-pers
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
girl	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
was	O
?	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
heard	O
Capt	O
.	O
Spender	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
Robinson	O
was	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
hat	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
Why	O
not	O
beat	O
Dragon	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
482	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Paul	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
New-gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Lomax	O
,	O
in	O
Blue-coat-fields	B-place
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
chew	O
of	O
tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pouch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
coming	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
missed	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
:	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
her	O
confess	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Garaway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
:	O
she	O
strongly	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
both	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
:	O
she	O
wished	O
her	O
eyes	O
might	O
roll	O
about	O
the	O
floor	O
like	O
two	O
marbles	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
1	O
s	O
5	O
d.	O
farthing	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
half	O
guinea	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
sailed	O
away	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
483	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
September	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sun-alehouse	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Devereux-court	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
for	O
about	O
ten	O
weeks	O
:	O
I	O
often	O
missed	O
money	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
till	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
inst	O
.	O
then	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
cross	O
and	O
a	O
B.	O
and	O
one	O
sixpence	O
marked	O
F.	O
B.	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
money	O
,	O
that	O
amounted	O
to	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
buying	O
herself	O
new	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
marked	O
six-pence	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
paid	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
named	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Inspected	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
jury	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
till	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
pardon	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
484	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Barney	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Middle-row	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
my	O
half-pence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
till	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
ten	O
shillings	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
lay	O
loose	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
two-penny	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
:	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
loose	O
parcel	O
:	O
the	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
their	O
beer	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three-halfpence	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Rositer	I-pers
,	O
the	O
servant	O
girl	O
,	O
of	O
near	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
stood	O
near	O
the	O
money	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
any	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
485	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Henry	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sheriff	O
's	O
officer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clare	I-place
market	I-place
,	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
,	O
lost	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
gold	O
chain	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
a	O
reward	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wytick	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
,	O
at	O
Charing	O
cross	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
necessity	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
take	O
25	O
guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
after	O
my	O
brother	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
?	O
Ferguson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
by	O
his	O
desire	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
his	O
brother	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
about	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
:	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
to	O
give	O
;	O
his	O
brother	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
uttermost	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
not	O
received	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
from	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
grandfather	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
this	O
prosecution	O
.	O
Ferguson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
relations	O
but	O
his	O
brother	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
some	O
expectations	O
from	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
relations	O
for	O
carrying	O
on	O
this	O
prosecution	O
?	O
Ferguson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Curtoes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
gold	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
ten	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
a	O
book	O
that	O
I	O
keep	O
for	O
advertised	O
watches	O
lost	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
reward	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wytick	O
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
at	O
Charing	O
cross	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
for	O
twelve	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
watch	O
is	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
stop	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
too	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wytick	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ferguson	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wytick	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Ferguson	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
which	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
nobody	O
could	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
prisoner	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
officious	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
up	O
the	O
advertisement	O
and	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
hall	O
;	O
the	O
chain	O
cost	O
nine	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
owned	O
he	O
sold	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
38	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
hid	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
pocket	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
knows	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
prosecution	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
sole	O
expence	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
grandfather	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
I	O
married	O
a	O
young	O
lady	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
inclination	O
of	O
her	O
parents	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
every	O
method	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
separated	O
from	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
soon	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
custody	O
:	O
after	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
prevail	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
friendship	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
be	O
reconciled	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
goods	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
their	O
intention	O
to	O
part	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
offered	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
France	O
;	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
the	O
influence	O
of	O
her	O
relations	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
friends	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
decline	O
and	O
leave	O
it	O
:	O
my	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
cruelty	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
relations	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
learned	O
music	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
harpsichord	O
brought	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
bill	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
her	O
friends	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
get	O
released	O
out	O
of	O
custody	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
:	O
he	O
soon	O
got	O
released	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
lieutenant	O
in	O
the	O
sea-service	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Buckinghamshire	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
486	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Slifford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Brian	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Brian	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Stepney	B-place
:	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
hardly	O
said	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
when	O
three	O
fellows	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
flashed	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
more	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
the	O
bank	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
hat	O
away	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
your	O
companion	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
led	O
you	O
to	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
suppose	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
frighted	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
it	O
hung	O
over	O
his	O
shoulders	O
;	O
his	O
arms	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
fellow	O
had	O
a	O
hair	O
cap	O
on	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Daies	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
over	O
Stepney	O
fields	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
hail	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
yo	O
ho	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yo	O
ho	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
said	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
came	O
and	O
ran	O
his	O
hand	O
by	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frighted	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
s.	O
he	O
retreated	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
half	O
done	O
with	O
you	O
yet	O
:	O
he	O
rifted	O
all	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
receive	O
some	O
hurt	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
thumb	O
and	O
finger	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
threatening	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
heels	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
home	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
standing	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
rifling	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
over	O
his	O
shoulders	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
?	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
detain	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
fetch	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
could	O
ascertain	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
lived	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
Green	O
Cannister	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
bring	O
their	O
landlady	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
was	O
their	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
pretending	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
London	O
Hospital	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
boy	O
by	O
Whitechapel	O
church	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
going	O
towards	O
Blue-coat-fields	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
I	O
could	O
after	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
to	O
go	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
boy	O
again	O
by	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
Fields	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
expecting	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
dressed	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
a	O
pretty	O
long	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
round	O
his	O
neck	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
evidence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Galton	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bottom	I-pers
were	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
drew	O
him	O
into	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
seven-pence	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
information	O
of	O
him	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Galton	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
,	O
upon	O
Bottom	O
's	O
information	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nailer	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bottom	I-pers
lodged	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
coming	O
together	O
along	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
facing	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Bottom	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
Bottom	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
whispered	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bottom	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
lay	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
this	O
way	O
a	O
robbing	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
Stepney	O
fields	O
:	O
Bond	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
stand	O
;	O
we	O
flashed	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
missed	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
seven-pence	O
half	O
penny	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nailer	I-pers
was	O
with	O
us	O
when	O
we	O
drank	O
the	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
?	O
Bottom	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
fired	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Bottom	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
did	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
this	O
?	O
Bottom	O
.	O
I	O
discovered	O
it	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wallis	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
this	O
evidence	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
more	O
inclined	O
to	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
clear	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bottom	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dressed	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Wallis	O
's	O
?	O
Bottom	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
stock	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
on	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
;	O
but	O
as	O
no	O
farther	O
evidence	O
could	O
be	O
given	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
on	O
that	O
.	O
487	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Frederick	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
reading	O
an	O
advertisement	O
at	O
the	O
register-office	B-place
window	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
:	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
pocket	O
moving	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
(	O
a	O
linen	O
one	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
I	O
directly	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
me	O
resolute	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
charged	O
Mr.	O
Charlton	B-pers
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
488	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Fish-Street	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
pull	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
clear	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
that	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
holding	O
him	O
last	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Mills	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
live	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Samphire	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
was	O
at	O
harvest	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
a	O
Gravesend	O
boat	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
going	O
after	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
throwed	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
t	O
o	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
a	O
lad	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
down	O
at	O
that	O
corner	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
another	O
lad	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
boy	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
489	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Derbin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
,	O
June	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
,	O
record	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
December	O
1762	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Bell-Court	O
,	O
near	O
Abchurch	O
Lane	O
;	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
who	O
proves	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
identical	O
person	O
mentioned	O
in	O
this	O
Record	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
,	O
the	O
Short	O
Hand	O
writer	O
,	O
must	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
tried	O
here	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
mentioned	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
Considering	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
was	O
I	O
never	O
to	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
on	O
such	O
an	O
affair	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
tried	O
here	O
before	O
?	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
prepared	O
with	O
my	O
book	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
well	O
remember	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
in	O
December	O
sessions	O
1762	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
dwelling	O
house	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
Abchurch	O
Lane	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
name	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sabbath	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
people	O
were	O
at	O
church	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
mentioned	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
from	O
once	O
seeing	O
him	O
?	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Gurney	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
four	O
times	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
tried	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
I	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
from	O
a	O
near	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
near	O
Christ-church	O
,	O
Surry	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
at	O
Croydon	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
account	O
he	O
severely	O
threatened	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
where-ever	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
petitioned	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
excused	O
giving	O
evidence	O
on	O
his	O
trial	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
met	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
on	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
doubt	O
by	O
his	O
eye	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
returned	O
from	O
transportation	O
.	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
houshold	O
;	O
my	O
business	O
here	O
is	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
nobody	O
incommodes	O
the	O
worthy	O
Aldermen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
turn	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Walbrook	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Derbin	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
seen	O
you	O
without	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
you	O
are	O
got	O
to	O
your	O
old	O
trade	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
stop	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
bag	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
White	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
searched	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
clothes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
him	O
tried	O
here	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
bag	O
a	O
mettle	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
tortoise	O
shell	O
case	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
lac	O
'd	O
hats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
one	O
;	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
jacket	O
.	O
Twelve	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gimblet	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
lac	O
'd	O
hats	O
,	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
,	O
are	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
bills	O
found	O
here	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
:	O
the	O
question	O
is	O
,	O
Whether	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
lose	O
my	O
freedom	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
free	O
subject	O
of	O
either	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
plantations	O
.	O
In	O
purchasing	O
my	O
freedom	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
;	O
my	O
friends	O
paid	O
my	O
passage	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
they	O
granted	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
delivers	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
``	O
On	O
Board	O
the	O
Neptune	O
,	O
Captain	O
Somervell	B-pers
,	O
``	O
June	O
17th	O
,	O
1763.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Derbin	I-pers
is	O
a	O
freeman	O
.	O
``	O
Any	O
Magistrate	O
may	O
grant	O
him	O
a	O
``	O
pass	O
by	O
destroying	O
this	O
.	O
Witness	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
``	O
David	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Dr.	O
David	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
is	O
the	O
person	O
the	O
people	O
are	O
consigned	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Bladensburg	O
in	O
Maryland	O
:	O
and	O
Colonel	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
granted	O
me	O
a	O
pass	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
for	O
Charles	O
county	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
weak	O
as	O
to	O
imagine	O
they	O
have	O
power	O
to	O
reverse	O
the	O
sentence	O
you	O
received	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
No	O
.	O
93.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Matthew	O
Blackision	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
159.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fludyer	I-pers
's	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
convicted	O
and	O
branded	O
at	O
Croydon	O
,	O
August	O
3	O
,	O
1761.	O
and	O
tried	O
by	O
four	O
prosecutors	O
on	O
four	O
several	O
indictments	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Beckford	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
see	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
that	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
490	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Jebb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
Scupple	O
Hunter	O
,	O
that	O
haunts	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
hogsheads	O
of	O
tobacco	O
cut	O
open	O
on	O
Galley-key	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
of	O
62	O
hogsheads	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
going	O
with	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
betwixt	O
the	O
casks	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
tobacco	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
some	O
)	O
which	O
was	O
placed	O
all	O
round	O
his	O
body	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
between	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
waked	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
tobacco	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
491	O
,	O
492	O
,	O
493	O
,	O
494	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Nathan	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
hat	O
lac	O
'd	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
August	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Nathan	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Short	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shipman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
Lombard-street	B-place
:	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shipman	O
,	O
and	O
insulted	O
him	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Cook	O
and	O
Miller	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
Beadle	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
:	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
knocked	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
Cook	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Shipman	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
insulted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
without	O
speaking	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
hat	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
were	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Shipman	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
Beadle	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Short	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
ask	O
for	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Short	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
Beadle	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
their	O
intentions	O
were	O
to	O
rob	O
some	O
body	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
know	O
nothing	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
insulted	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
stand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
path	O
;	O
then	O
Cook	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shipman	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
shove	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
he	O
began	O
damning	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shoving	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
Beadle	O
quitted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
scuffle	O
began	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
watch	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
They	O
lost	O
both	O
their	O
hats	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
nothing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
's	O
lodgings	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
reply	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
this	O
hat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
gold	O
lac	O
'd	O
hat	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Spencer	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
desired	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
place	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
:	O
Miller	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
while	O
we	O
went	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
more	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
up	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Carey	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Three	O
Herrings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Spencer	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
dirty	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
secured	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
came	O
from	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
to	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
those	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
against	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
round	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
blows	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
tumbled	O
off	O
;	O
Miller	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
upon	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
some	O
body	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
demand	O
their	O
money	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
We	O
intended	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Miller	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
brazier	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Cook	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-case	O
maker	O
.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
Lombard-street	O
;	O
we	O
brushed	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
elbows	O
;	O
Beadle	O
ran	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
came	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
what	O
Beadle	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
beat	O
Beadle	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lift	O
Beadle	O
upon	O
his	O
legs	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Miller	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Cook	O
and	O
Beadle	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Cook	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Beadle	O
home	O
to	O
Newington	O
:	O
going	O
up	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
gold	O
lac	O
'd	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
;	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Carey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
lac	O
'd	O
hat	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
them	O
any	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
:	O
then	O
Poll	O
Spencer	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
hat	O
may	O
be	O
worth	O
a	O
guinea	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
should	O
buy	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
runners	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
hiked	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
He	O
called	O
Margaret	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
at	O
sea	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
let	O
in	O
Miller	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
accidentally	O
:	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
Carey	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
hat	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Cook	O
and	O
Miller	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Carey	O
and	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
indictment	O
against	O
Cook	O
and	O
Miller	O
for	O
robbing	O
Hugh	B-pers
Short	I-pers
of	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
495	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sanney	I-pers
,	O
August	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
account	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
496	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lavess	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
August	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Francis	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
soldiers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy-barracks	B-place
,	O
and	O
laid	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
lie	O
two	O
in	O
a	O
cabin	O
;	O
one	O
Wybourn	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
my	O
barrack	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
corporals	O
finding	O
in	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
a	O
blue	O
rag	O
,	O
and	O
seven-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
key	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
necessary	O
further	O
,	O
my	O
breeches	O
were	O
found	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
military	O
law	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
try	O
him	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
disorderly	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
Ambury	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
or	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
about	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
sat	O
upright	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
breeches	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
till	O
day-light	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
to	O
taking	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
they	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
false	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
James	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
16	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oxley	I-pers
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
know	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
497	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Fairwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver-print	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Black	B-place
boy	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
mug	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
tap	O
room	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
were	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pint	O
mug	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
he	O
ever	O
did	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
this	O
mug	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
inscription	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
necessity	O
obliged	O
them	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
inscription	O
is	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
putting	O
a	O
crown	O
into	O
your	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
inscription	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
woman	O
how	O
long	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
alive	O
and	O
well	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
your	O
mug	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
there	O
three	O
of	O
four	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
almost	O
done	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
your	O
mug	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
rest	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
step	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
my	O
wife	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
step	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
round	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
as	O
I	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
slipped	O
out	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
person	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Florida	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
backwards	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
coat	O
open	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
:	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
coat	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
or	O
pewter	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
some	O
money	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
me	O
fell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
6	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
me	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frighted	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
buried	O
it	O
two	O
feet	O
deep	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
sold	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
mug	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
have	O
his	O
mug	O
again	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
innocent	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
weighed	O
it	O
:	O
it	O
weighed	O
14	O
ounces	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
right	O
way	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
blind	O
as	O
a	O
beetle	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
my	O
way	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
If	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
mug	O
go	O
home	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
her	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
silversmith	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
done	O
for	O
you	O
almost	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
finished	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
498	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
two	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pewter	O
bottom	O
to	O
a	O
scale	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
alarmed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
somebody	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
shutter	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Whittle	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
nails	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
fast	O
bolted	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
the	O
nails	O
were	O
drawn	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
few	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
pewter	O
scale	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
hear	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
scale	O
bottom	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bareav	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
directions	O
where	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
hampers	O
loaded	O
with	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
away	O
pretty	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
bit	O
of	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Joseph	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Boad	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
499	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Dover	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
callimancoe	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
holland	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Element	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Susannah	B-pers
Element	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
top	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
after	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
little	O
reply	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
and	O
sleepy	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
cloaths	O
that	O
I	O
wear	O
,	O
were	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
presently	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
crack	O
,	O
and	O
looking-round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
cloaths	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
people	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
her	O
father	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
on	O
my	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
shift	O
and	O
stays	O
:	O
she	O
pulled	O
them	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
:	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Fra	O
.	O
Hardey	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
500	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Macrin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goad	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Goad	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
backwards	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
generally	O
shut	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
with	O
written	O
papers	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
Mr.	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
of	O
Bridgewater	O
Gardens	O
came	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bridgewater	O
Gardens	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Pollock	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Pollock	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pledged	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
raise	O
money	O
to	O
bury	O
a	O
child	O
that	O
lay	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
them	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Pollock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go-along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
eighteen-pence	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Pollock	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
spite	O
and	O
malice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
501	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
ready-furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
502	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jourdan	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jefferey	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jefferey	O
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Jefferey	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
New	B-place
North-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
our	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
purse	O
that	O
had	O
several	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
crooked	O
guinea	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
mourning	O
buckles	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
:	O
before	O
twelve	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
standing	O
out	O
,	O
not	O
locked	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
buckles	O
,	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
bank	O
note	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
note	O
is	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
things-mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
facing	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
entry	O
directly	O
,	O
without	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
four	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
twice	O
,	O
which	O
lead	O
me	O
to	O
observe	O
him	O
particularly	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
coat-pocket	O
:	O
it	O
seemed	O
difficult	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Broughton	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
stirred	O
from	O
my	O
window	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
till	O
Mrs.	O
Knight	O
's	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
remark	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
?	O
Broughton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
his	O
back	O
part	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
go	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
that	O
street	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
bid	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
go	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
something	O
,	O
putting	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Noy	I-pers
,	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
describe	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
:	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
Tavistock-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
Bridges	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Drury-lane	O
:	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
seen	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
pretty	O
near	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Noy	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
assistance	O
:	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
bringing	O
him	O
along	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
papers	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Noy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
step	O
light	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
without	O
knocking	O
or	O
scraping	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Noy	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
loose	O
papers	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
very	O
slowly	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
observed	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
crossed	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
towards	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
use	O
some	O
ill	O
language	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Boswell-court	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Knight	O
I	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
best	O
manner	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
Bridges	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
plainly	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Tavistock-street	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
into	O
King-street	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
two	O
soldiers	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
fellow	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
apiece	O
;	O
they	O
immediately	O
ran	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
wants	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
impudent	O
thing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
cleared	O
himself	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
soldiers	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Wild-street	O
:	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Noy	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
pursued	O
him	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
James-street	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
into	O
Hart-street	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
catched	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
again	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mob	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
Great	O
Wild-street	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
bailiffs	O
:	O
the	O
mob	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
believed	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
assistance	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
assisted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
,	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
guinea	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
swore	O
to	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
large	O
crooked-guinea	O
,	O
with	O
dents	O
in	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
correspond	O
with	O
his	O
description	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
,	O
exactly	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
guinea	O
inspected	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
jury	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seventeen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
pocketed	O
two	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
half-pence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
none	O
to	O
myself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
purses	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
crooked	O
guinea	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
nine	O
guineas	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
purse	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
money	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
father	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
by	O
appointment	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Noy	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
:	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
between	O
Wild-street	O
and	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
into	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
knowing	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
into	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
loose	O
again	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
Devil's-gap	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
:	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
described	O
a	O
crooked	O
guinea	O
,	O
with	O
particular	O
dents	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
purse	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
sometime	O
without	O
a	O
companion	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
never	O
to	O
touch	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pockets	O
:	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
's	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
glance	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
this	O
crooked	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
eating	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
eating	O
that	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
eating	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
his	O
mouth	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
white	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Seven-dials	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
the	O
advertisement	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
effect	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
where	O
them	O
cloaths	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
whom	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
spoons	O
and	O
buckles	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Povey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
King-street	O
,	O
Seven-Dials	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
,	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
bairy	O
trunk	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
spoons	O
and	O
buckles	O
:	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
there	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
two	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
;	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
flung	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
husband	O
goes	O
for	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
woman	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
three	O
words	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
particularly	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
M.	O
Mark	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
there	O
?	O
M.	O
Mark	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
longer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
M.	O
Mark	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
there	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Morning	O
?	O
M.	O
Mark	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
bee	O
n	O
three	O
Weeks	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
that	O
woman	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Glascow	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
breakfast	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
proof	O
enough	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
Sir	O
John	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
frighted	O
every	O
body	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
died	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
forty	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
twenty-three	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
have	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
named	O
Mark	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
that	O
can	O
prove	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Munster	O
,	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
silver	O
and	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
over	O
to	O
get	O
