TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
of	O
MAY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGEN	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mansfield	O
*	O
;	O
Baron	B-pers
Smythe	I-pers
+	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sowerby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fasson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Houston	I-pers
,	O
Theomartyr	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Briant	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Briant	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lightwood	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Richard	O
Beal	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Sharpley	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Surity	I-pers
.	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
little	I-place
above	I-place
Mr.	I-place
Ashley	I-place
's	I-place
punch-house	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
drawing	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
person	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
less	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
punch	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
just	O
behind	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
punch-house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
in	O
the	O
punch-house	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
222	O
,	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
linen	O
huckaback	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
wrappers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
four	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
three	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
with	O
wine	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
other	O
glass	O
bottle	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
mountain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
three	O
bottles	O
,	O
with	O
red	O
port	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
madera	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
claret	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
claret	O
and	O
burgundy	O
,	O
mixed	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
rum	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
arrack	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
ditto	O
,	O
filled	O
with	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Mitre	I-place
tavern	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
waiters	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
preceding	O
day	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
other	O
servants	O
had	O
complained	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
of	O
linen	O
and	O
things	O
:	O
I	O
ordered	O
every	O
man	O
's	O
box	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
in	O
his	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
variety	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
poor	O
sister	O
in	O
my	O
neighbourhood	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
used	O
often	O
to	O
resort	O
,	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
abundance	O
of	O
napkins	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
marked	O
R.	O
A.	O
and	O
some	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
and	O
wine	O
of	O
sundry	O
sorts	O
in	O
bottles	O
;	O
on	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
my	O
mark	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
napkins	O
were	O
sewed	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
sister	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
herself	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
mark	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
brother	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
The	O
brother	O
said	O
,	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
napkins	O
there	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
washed	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
a	O
great	O
regard	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
takes	O
the	O
wine	O
left	O
by	O
customers	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
leave	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
waiters	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
generally	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
)	O
if	O
they	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
the	O
master	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
is	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
bottles	O
,	O
and	O
apply	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
use	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
never	O
countenanced	O
their	O
taking	O
such	O
wine	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
alehouses	O
,	O
but	O
should	O
not	O
deny	O
their	O
drinking	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
the	O
waiters	O
boxes	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
taking	O
something	O
from	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
concealing	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
bed-cloths	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
cloaths	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
three	O
glass	O
cloths	O
and	O
ten	O
napkins	O
.	O
My	O
method	O
is	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
waiters	O
a	O
certain	O
number	O
of	O
glass	O
cloths	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
give	O
me	O
back	O
a	O
dirty	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
deliver	O
them	O
a	O
clean	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
expect	O
the	O
waiters	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
cloths	O
clean	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
things	O
behind	O
the	O
bed-cloths	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
mistress	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
some	O
napkins	O
and	O
cloths	O
from	O
the	O
bed-cloths	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
executed	O
the	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
twelve	O
damask	O
napkins	O
and	O
glass	O
cloths	O
,	O
two	O
rubbers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
were	O
found	O
when	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
's	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
washed	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
sister	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
them	O
.	O
James	O
Cowen	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
usual	O
for	O
all	O
waiters	O
in	O
town	O
to	O
carry	O
napkins	O
in	O
their	O
pockets	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
wine	O
that	O
gentlemen	O
leave	O
in	O
bottles	O
,	O
that	O
lies	O
among	O
the	O
waiters	O
;	O
sometimes	O
on	O
an	O
evening	O
we	O
save	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
bottles	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
carried	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
fowl	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
left	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
napkin	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
;	O
the	O
wine	O
that	O
is	O
left	O
we	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
it	O
among	O
ourselves	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Rum	O
and	O
Arrack	O
.	O
Mary	O
Cowen	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
accident	O
one	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
business	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
many	O
dirty	O
napkins	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Trufsen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bignal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
all	O
waiters	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
customary	O
with	O
waiters	O
,	O
when	O
any	O
ullage	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
to	O
eat	O
what	O
they	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
the	O
wins	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
man	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
years	O
;	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
about	O
14	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Duglass	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Lawrance	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Grenley	O
,	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Carnaby	I-pers
,	O
about	O
12	O
years	O
;	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Burch	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
Mary	O
Cowen	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Shore	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Elsley	O
,	O
Walter	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
224	O
,	O
225.	O
Edward	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cunnigham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
outside	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dalmada	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
To	O
which	O
they	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Radman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Rockett	I-pers
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
alley	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
metal	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
watch	O
brass	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Lowther	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
evidences	O
,	O
deposed	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Rockett	O
and	O
Steward	O
,	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
executed	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
206	O
,	O
and	O
207	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
paper	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
room	O
the	O
reader	O
is	O
referred	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
227	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Court	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Lawford	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
sixpence	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Lawford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
cart	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
Little	I-place
Stanmore	I-place
:	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hollo	O
,	O
stop	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
indeed	O
:	O
He	O
returned	O
me	O
the	O
three	O
farthings	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
put	O
the	O
sixpence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
who	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
?	O
Lawford	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
buttoned	O
up	O
almost	O
to	O
his	O
nose	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mare	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
looking	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
man	O
rode	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
and	O
size	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
horse	O
or	O
a	O
mare	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Paternoster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
under	O
the	O
manger	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
horse	O
stood	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
man	O
offer	O
any	O
pistol	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
highwayman	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
guard	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
arms	O
or	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
Paternoster	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
returned	O
with	O
this	O
pistol	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
stall	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
horse	O
stood	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
recommend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hire	O
my	O
mare	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
eight	O
shillings	O
for	O
her	O
for	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
staid	O
three	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
three	O
days	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
longest	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
my	O
mare	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
your	O
mare	O
?	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
Mine	O
is	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
let	O
him	O
your	O
mare	O
before	O
?	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
twenty	O
miles	O
down	O
into	O
Kent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joannah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joannah	O
.	O
*	O
Joannah	O
Holmes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
42	O
guineas	O
;	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
king	O
's	O
coin	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
cabinet	O
;	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
missed	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
king	O
's	O
coin	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
likewise	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Manley	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
granted	O
her	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
found	O
eight	O
guineas	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
for	O
23	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
at	O
first	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
cabinet	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
seven	O
guineas	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Manley	O
when	O
he	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
knowledge	O
afterwards	O
that	O
the	O
night	O
that	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cat	O
's	O
Opera	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
my	O
mistres	O
's	O
cabinet	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
examination	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
has	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
scored	O
beer	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
229	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Sidnell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
shoe	O
buckeles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee	O
buckcles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
cloaths	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
buckles	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Liney	I-pers
,	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
produced	O
each	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
deposed	O
they	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
half	O
his	O
passage	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Holland	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
foot-guards	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
regiment	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
Christmas	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
she	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
waterman	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
Allice	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
hard	O
times	O
and	O
cold	O
weather	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
had	O
no	O
work	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
pledge	O
them	O
with	O
no	O
other	O
intention	O
but	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
places	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
231	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
crown	O
,	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
tissue	O
cloke	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
roller	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
curtain	O
,	O
with	O
gold	O
fringe	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Solomons	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gompertz	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
overseer	O
of	O
the	O
poor	O
in	O
our	O
synagogue	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
clerk	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
our	O
synagogue	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmith's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
these	O
goods	O
advertised	O
,	O
ten	O
guineas	O
reward	O
.	O
The	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
synagogue	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
locked	O
into	O
the	O
synagogue	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hannah	O
Solomons	O
:	O
the	O
clerk	O
brings	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
our	O
sabbath	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
horse	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
horse	O
some	O
corn	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
seeing	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
these	O
things	O
here	O
produced	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ritherdson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Stay	O
here	O
till	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ritherdon	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ritherdon	O
shot	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
the	O
synagogue	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Emanuel	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
of	O
?	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ritherdon	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
synagogue	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
spring	O
lock	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
within	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
without	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
himself	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
nobody	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
's	O
:	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
it	O
before	O
us	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
's	O
two	O
sons	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Though	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
was	O
accused	O
by	O
the	O
Jews	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
party	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
synagogue	O
(	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
)	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
gold	O
fringe	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plunk	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ritherdon	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
came	O
running	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
customer	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
presently	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
locked	O
at	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
synagogue	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Jew	O
boy	O
that	O
looks	O
after	O
my	O
horse	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
boy	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
something	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
no	O
lock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
nobody	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
could	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
questions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
he	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
the	O
Jews	O
charge	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Ritherdon	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
young	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Solomons	O
was	O
very	O
earnest	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
boy	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Smithson	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sight	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
plump	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ritherdon	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
is	O
concerned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
a	O
Jew	O
?	O
Ritherdon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
Solomons	O
is	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
synagogue	O
.	O
Coleman	B-pers
Solomons	I-pers
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
rash	O
action	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
had	O
learned	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
the	O
ornament	O
to	O
the	O
cloke	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
is	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
tell	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
then	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ritherdon	O
.	O
Solomons	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gompertz	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
Peter	B-pers
Feather	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Alice	B-pers
M'Clalin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Lilley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Carnes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilsber	I-pers
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Plank	O
of	O
Long-acre	O
here	O
?	O
Ritherdon	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
should	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
232	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
gallons	O
of	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sabe	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sabe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
anonymous	O
letter	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Collins	O
had	O
behaved	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
in	O
concealing	O
oil	O
that	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
lamps	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
gallons	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
oil	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
tin	O
cannister	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
oil	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
general	O
complaint	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
allowed	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
extraordinary	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
work	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
oil	O
from	O
?	O
Sabe	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
served	O
with	O
oil	O
every	O
day	O
at	O
my	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
oil	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
pots	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
oil	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
saved	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
quantity	O
that	O
I	O
allowed	O
him	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
lamps	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
oil	O
than	O
was	O
wanted	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
never	O
brought	O
any	O
;	O
only	O
the	O
empty	O
pots	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
quarts	O
of	O
lamp	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sabe	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sabe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
church-warden	O
of	O
our	O
parish	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
our	O
workhouse	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
against	O
his	O
pot	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
oath	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
Joe	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
his	O
pot	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
reel	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
spill	O
the	O
oil	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
carrying	O
the	O
pot	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
quarts	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
oil	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
perceive	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
day	O
's	O
theft	O
;	O
thus	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
injured	O
in	O
my	O
property	O
and	O
reputation	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lighted	O
the	O
lamps	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
general	O
complaint	O
in	O
his	O
walk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
impossible	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
knew	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
oil	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
saved	O
out	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
oil	O
home	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
left	O
,	O
after	O
serving	O
the	O
lamps	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Flaun	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sabe	O
:	O
I	O
deliver	O
the	O
oil	O
out	O
every	O
morning	O
.	O
That	O
morning	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
gallons	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
measured	O
the	O
oil	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
quarts	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
considerable	O
saving	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
early	O
with	O
the	O
oil	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
234	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
by	O
Lord	O
Adam	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Adam	O
Gordon	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Adair	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
32	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
an	O
acceptance	O
thereto	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Henry	B-pers
Baldero	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
235	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Maer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
37	O
yards	O
of	O
linen-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
damask	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Tisdell	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
January	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Tisdell	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
's	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Wm	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
Saturday	O
in	O
Dec.	O
Mr.	O
Sampson	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
stock	O
:	O
we	O
left	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
holland	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
warehouses	O
,	O
intending	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
particular	O
use	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
inward	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
holland	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
greatly	O
alarmed	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
crimson	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
damask	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
presently	O
missing	O
:	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
nurse	O
,	O
and	O
footman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
thief	O
:	O
I	O
discharged	O
an	O
innocent	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
own	O
stockings	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
word	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
cloth	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pen	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
absconded	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
his	O
friends	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
sorry	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
crime	O
:	O
he	O
in	O
my	O
counting-house	O
owned	O
,	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
cloth	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
whole	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
damask	O
,	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
things	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
indictment	O
favourable	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
,	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
young	O
,	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
;	O
by	O
giving	O
security	O
,	O
of	O
sending	O
him	O
abroad	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
understand	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
plead	O
guilty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
His	O
master	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sing	O
,	O
works	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
in	O
making	O
up	O
furniture	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back-warehouse	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
holland	O
lying	O
convenient	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wrapped	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
wrapper	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
things	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
holland	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pen	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
workwoman	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Sing	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
here	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sing	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
concealed	O
behind	O
a	O
board	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fellow-apprentice	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
has	O
since	O
absconded	O
;	O
he	O
frequently	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
stealing	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Axby	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
holland	O
and	O
the	O
worsted	O
damask	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
fellow-apprentice	O
lay	O
:	O
the	O
plaister	O
was	O
pulled	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
board	O
nailed	O
tight	O
over	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
damask	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sing	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Axley	O
brought	O
me	O
word	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
concealed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
mentioned	O
:	O
but	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
He	O
served	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
so	O
good	O
an	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
natural	O
inclinations	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
seduced	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
woman	O
seduced	O
him	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
intimate	O
with	O
Brown	O
,	O
my	O
other	O
apprentice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
where	O
Brown	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
dropt	O
my	O
knee-buckle	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
looking	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
moving	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
holland	O
stuck	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Brown	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
shirt	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
keep	O
the	O
remainder	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
reputable	O
tradesmen	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
236	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Christian	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Trail	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
of	O
robbing	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
gaol	O
five	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
Groves	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
watch	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
named	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
David	B-pers
Mure	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
lived	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
237	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
Hindon	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Anne	O
Hindon	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Joannah	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
Hyde-Park-Corner	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
we	O
hunted	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
James-street	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
your	O
head	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
(	O
she	O
produced	O
a	O
rag	O
)	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
before	O
judge	O
and	O
jury	O
twenty	O
times	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
amongst	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
J.	O
Roach	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
linen-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Charles-street	B-place
,	I-place
Grosvenor-square	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen-cloth	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
what	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
linen	O
:	O
my	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
guards	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
quartered	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
there	O
for	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
nights	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
7th	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
consulting	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
leering	O
about	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
partner	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
notice	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fling	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
One	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
setting	O
things	O
to	O
rights	O
in	O
the	O
club-room	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Daniel	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
half-penny	O
:	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
nuts	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
half-penny	O
:	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
daughter	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
then	O
master	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
partner	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
knapsack	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
sticking	O
about	O
three	O
inches	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
light	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
linen	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
bed	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
More	O
's	O
assistance	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
help	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
pencil-mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
knapsack	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
Bethway	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
battalion	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
for	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
marching	O
regiment	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
:	O
he	O
never	O
missed	O
his	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
came	O
clean	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
stall	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
spend	O
per	O
day	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
his	O
pay	O
could	O
support	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
married	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
some	O
fortune	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
following	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
cloth	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
cloth	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
:	O
all	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
239	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rachael	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Cobane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
a	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
upon	O
Mill-bank	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
warm	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
tied	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
drunk	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
watch-house	O
candles	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
tied	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Polly	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
she	O
directed	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Nanny	O
Wilson	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
worked	O
at	O
weeding	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
maiden	O
name	O
is	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
240	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Purdey	I-pers
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Purdey	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Purdey	I-pers
is	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lime-house	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
A.	O
Purdey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Purdey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boyadell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
my	O
dinner-hour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
very	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
bed-gowns	O
;	O
six	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
besides	O
,	O
all	O
wet	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Segwick	I-pers
(	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
her	O
daughter	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
exchange	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
my	O
gown	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
garters	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
garters	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
,	O
one	O
canvass	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
February	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Holborn-bars	I-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
with	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
garters	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
fell	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Philips	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
to	O
lie	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
George	O
at	O
Holborn-bars	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
night-house	O
:	O
we	O
sit	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
for	O
the	O
reception	O
of	O
watchmen	O
and	O
coachmen	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
come	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
neckcloth	O
tied	O
about	O
his	O
jaw	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
the	O
tooth-ach	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
holding	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
jaw	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
pain	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
perceived	O
by	O
his	O
pushing	O
so	O
hastily	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
making	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
stepped	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
friend	O
,	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
all	O
is	O
well	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
described	O
the	O
purse	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
pardon	O
.	O
Gascoyne	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
searching	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shirt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
callicoe	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
lodge	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
tooth-ach	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
garters	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
having	O
dropped	O
mine	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
asked	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
ask	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
more	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
the	O
pillow	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
purse	O
fell	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
garters	O
were	O
in	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
242	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
camblet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Farnham	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Farnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bethnal-green	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
camblet	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
a-	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Widow	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Farnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wise	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
my	O
husband	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
,	O
were	O
called	O
on	O
their	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Their	O
recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
243	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lisk	I-pers
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Lisk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
milk-cellar	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
also	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
had	O
my	O
cardinal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
catch	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
never	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
244	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Deprose	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	B-place
Cock	I-place
,	I-place
Cock-hill	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Steven	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
said	O
his	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
summons	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
to	O
appear	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
tankard	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
the	O
alderman	O
directed	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
in	O
my	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
call	O
for	O
her	O
that	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
tankard	O
last	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
It	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Dial	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
high-street	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
business	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
break	O
his	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
drove	O
to	O
necessity	O
;	O
telling	O
me	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
rather	O
out	O
of	O
pity	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
profit	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
dressed	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
30	O
ounces	O
,	O
7	O
pennyweights	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
new	O
silver	O
now	O
,	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
window	O
for	O
sale	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
coming	O
by	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
see	O
the	O
tankard	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
tankard	O
:	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
,	O
came	O
at	O
night	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
they	O
would	O
prosecute	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
described	O
the	O
woman	O
they	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
tallied	O
exactly	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
tankard	O
of	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
,	O
who	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
ing	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
dress	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
in	O
the	O
cloaths	O
that	O
she	O
dresses	O
in	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
we	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
looked	O
more	O
like	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
before	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
some	O
work	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
had	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
received	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
five	O
and	O
threepenny-piece	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
tankard	O
standing	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
whether	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
describe	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
they	O
suspected	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
his	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
all	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sign	O
her	O
name	O
while	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
she	O
made	O
the	O
letter	O
M	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
making	O
the	O
W	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
some	O
scruple	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
write	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
pen	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
such	O
an	O
M	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
W	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
words	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
letters	O
very	O
much	O
resembled	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
wrote	O
before	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
errand-boy	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
together	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
exactly	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Carrington	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
forsook	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
before	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
No	O
.	O
312	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
245	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
till	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Jane	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
delivered	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
without	O
being	O
asked	O
.	O
Charles	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Marshall	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
pu	O
nd	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
ho	O
d	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
which	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
he	O
till	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
J.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
246	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
poker	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
quilt	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bady	I-pers
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
February	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
247	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
stairs	O
when	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
these	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
say	O
a	O
man	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Hollo	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
pumps	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	B-place
of	I-place
Lincoln	I-place
's	I-place
inn-fields	I-place
,	I-place
going	I-place
into	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
pegs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
pegs	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
into	O
Lincoln's-inn-fields	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
directed	O
the	O
apprentice	O
which	O
way	O
to	O
run	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
248	O
,	O
249	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
planes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
iron	O
chissels	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
pincers	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
knife	O
,	O
one	O
rasp	O
,	O
one	O
wooden	O
bevil	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
awl	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Darling	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Ramsey	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
denied	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
Darling	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
concealed	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Ramsey	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
tools	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
building	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
value	O
mine	O
at	O
12	O
s.	O
William	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
house-broker	O
.	O
Darling	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Man-in-the-Moon	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
all	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ramsey	O
's	O
.	O
and	O
be	O
bound	O
every	O
man	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
tools	O
again	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
granted	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Ramsey	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
said	O
Ramsey	O
to	O
Darling	O
,	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
great	O
rogue	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
Ramsey	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
Darling	O
says	O
he	O
has	O
sold	O
things	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
see	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
smoothing	O
planes	O
,	O
hammers	O
,	O
saws	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
tools	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
thousand	O
nails	O
,	O
which	O
Darling	O
made	O
information	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
Ramsey	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Ramsey	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
officer	O
speaks	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
;	O
seeing	O
some	O
old	O
tools	O
lying	O
,	O
and	O
Ramsey	O
's	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
carpenter	O
's	O
tools	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ramsey	O
's	O
denying	O
it	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
to	O
search	O
.	O
After	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
saws	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
conceal	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
more	O
saws	O
found	O
concealed	O
.	O
Marks	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ramsey	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
this	O
drawer	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
tool	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
opened	O
two	O
drawers	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
fourteen	O
saws	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
thirty-eight	O
saws	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
thirty	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
owned	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
were	O
divers	O
people	O
swore	O
to	O
their	O
tools	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
Dearing	O
's	O
confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
before	O
justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
several	O
indictments	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Ramsey	O
encouraged	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
purchase	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
not	O
obliterated	O
when	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Ramsey	O
.	O
Marks	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
account	O
that	O
Ramsey	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
book	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
goods	O
:	O
It	O
runs	O
in	O
this	O
form	O
:	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
mention	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
general	O
he	O
has	O
put	O
it	O
goods	O
:	O
Laid	O
out	O
on	O
goods	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
Darling	O
was	O
only	O
from	O
the	O
18th	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
tools	O
bought	O
of	O
Darling	B-pers
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Laid	O
out	O
upon	O
goods	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
Darling	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Ramsey	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
17	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Darling	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Ramsey	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
carpenter	O
's	O
tools	O
.	O
250	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cow	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
John	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
field	O
butts	O
down	O
to	O
Cambridge	B-place
heath	I-place
,	I-place
just	I-place
at	I-place
Hackney	I-place
turnpike	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
cow	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
well	O
all	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
where	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
where	O
she	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
jump	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
hide	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
market	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
cow	O
:	O
were	O
there	O
a	O
thousand	O
hides	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
know	O
her	O
hide	O
from	O
all	O
,	O
mine	O
was	O
so	O
particular	O
:	O
my	O
son-in-law	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
salesman	O
that	O
sells	O
the	O
hides	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
hide	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
Leaden-hall	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
brought	O
many	O
a	O
beast	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Smithfield	O
and	O
Islington	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
William	O
,	O
you	O
knew	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
beasts	O
when	O
I	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
cow	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
poor	O
middling	O
sort	O
of	O
meat	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
five	O
guineas	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
bid	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
then	O
up	O
to	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
half	O
way	O
over	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
luck	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
slaughter-house	O
,	O
in	O
Wheat-sheaf	O
yard	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
43	O
s.	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
remainder	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
hide	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
a	O
hide	O
salesman	O
,	O
at	O
Leaden-hall	O
market	O
;	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
brown	O
mottle	O
;	O
pretty	O
much	O
mottled	O
:	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
cow	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
son	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
cow	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leaning	O
upon	O
a	O
post	O
at	O
the	O
Crown-tavern	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
,	O
Leaden-hall	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hide	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
owned	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
hide	O
of	O
the	O
cow	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
cow	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
just	O
at	O
Shoreditch	O
church	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
knew	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
how	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
her	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
Islington	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
there	O
by	O
accident	O
:	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
alehouse	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
selling	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Harlow	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
you	O
bought	O
the	O
cow	O
?	O
Harlow	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
cow	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
a	O
cow	O
and	O
calf	O
at	O
Lewisham	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Leighton	O
,	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
lad	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
last	O
years	O
at	O
times	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
banker	O
:	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
ofen	O
sold	O
beasts	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Wheat-sheafs	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
received	O
money	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Procter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
use	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
calves	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
honestly	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
251	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Hoff	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Hoff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
linen	O
stocks	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Watford	B-pers
Runnet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barear	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Watford	O
Runnet	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black-fryars	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Furrier	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
:	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
old	O
hat	O
in	O
my	O
hat-box	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
new	O
one	O
:	O
after	O
seeking	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
people	O
found	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
and	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
the	O
Jews	O
;	O
some	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
:	O
them	O
I	O
got	O
back	O
again	O
:	O
the	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
he	O
mentioned	O
at	O
one	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
silk	O
stockings	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
at	O
another	O
:	O
the	O
justice	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
?	O
Runnet	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
bed-fellow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Runnet	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
from	O
Dantzick	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
hat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
he	O
pledged	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Hoff	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoff	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Puddle-dock	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
delivered	O
this	O
shirt	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
broke	O
the	O
chest	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
nail	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
High	O
German	O
taylor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
252	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chpaman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
sick	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
and	O
carry	O
out	O
work	O
.	O
When	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
shirt	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
delivered	O
the	O
shirt	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
neckcloth	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
my	O
nurse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
in	O
the	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
sheet	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
:	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
delivered	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
to	O
her	O
pawning	O
them	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ewers	I-pers
.	O
This	O
sheet	O
,	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Betty	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
baptized	O
so	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
got	O
me	O
fourteen	O
days	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
bridewell	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
swore	O
this	O
robbery	O
against	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
253	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
this	O
day	O
sennight	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Conner	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
green	O
shop	O
in	O
Covent-garden	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Reynold	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
she	O
did	O
pawn	O
these	O
teaspoons	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
to	O
taking	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
gold	O
ring	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
254	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Barrot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crang	I-pers
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Crang	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
organ-maker	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
chains	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
chain	O
advertised	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Briant	O
,	O
a	O
Blacksmith	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
bought	O
old	O
iron	O
:	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
chain	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
My	O
Mrs.	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
weighed	O
8	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
8	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Crang	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
kingdom	O
but	O
mine	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
chain	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Morris	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
master	O
live	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Briant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
this	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
under	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
s.	O
Had	O
I	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
should	O
have	O
stopped	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
chain	O
in	O
a	O
yard	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crang	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
255	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Dyot-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
got	O
very	O
drunk	O
there	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
My	O
pot	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cowlen	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cowlen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
copper	O
pot	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
last	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
:	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
:	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
256	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Abraham	B-pers
Torrince	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
planes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
four	O
planes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
257	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
William	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
cardinals	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
wooden	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
tin	O
canisters	O
;	O
one	O
wooden	O
tea-board	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hendon	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
called	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
window	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
the	O
wooden	O
bar	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
two	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
ground	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
five	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
some	O
tea	O
in	O
a	O
cannister	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea-board	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
carpenter	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
last	O
Michaelmas	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
stopt	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
advertised	O
them	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
at	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
all	O
your	O
goods	O
at	O
that	O
brokers	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Upon	O
seeing	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
tea-board	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
cardinals	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
rattle	O
in	O
the	O
tea-box	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
instead	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
strange	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
penny	O
of	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
salesman	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
19	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
abroad	O
in	O
Germany	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
battalion	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
258	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Boyland	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
At	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
