TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
E.	O
DILLY	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGEN	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Eardley	I-pers
Wilmot	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
+	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Percy	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Simkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Huckell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Abdy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kippax	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dayly	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brookshead	I-pers
.	O
67	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francois	B-pers
Jaume	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stafford	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Stafford	O
Briscoe	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
diamond	O
rings	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
without	O
buying	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
pattern	O
,	O
worth	O
8	O
guineas	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Townsend	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Churchyard	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ring	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
this	O
ring	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
16	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
half	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morrison	O
came	O
in	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
ring	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
one	O
upon	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
bought	O
some	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
ring	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Townsend	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
?	O
Townsend	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
friend	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
68	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Priggs	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Priggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Spital-fields	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
after	O
:	O
the	O
people	O
where	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
spending	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
asking	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
spent	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Woodyer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pawn	O
'd	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Power	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Another	O
girl	O
enticed	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
69	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Munday	B-pers
Musturs	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pawlet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
thirteen	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Oake	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gundery	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Oake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brudenell	B-place
's	I-place
Meuse	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gundery	O
:	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gundery	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
to	O
Knights-bridge	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
dinner	O
of	O
cod-fish	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
cloaths	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
out-patient	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Chandler-street	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
whip	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
for	O
a	O
lawyer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
with	O
others	O
for	O
a	O
doctor	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
lodging	O
at	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Oake	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
(	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
every	O
day	O
)	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hungry	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
rabbet	O
,	O
and	O
fry	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
rabbet	O
,	O
and	O
fry	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
frying	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
10	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
ten	O
thousand	O
pardons	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
sweat	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
confus	O
'd	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
eat	O
the	O
rabbet	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
cloaths	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
court	O
:	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
13	O
plate	O
buttons	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Oake	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
12th	O
or	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
lawyer	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
North-Audley-street	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
advertised	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
you	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Oake	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
change	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
(	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
owe	O
him	O
his	O
change	O
now	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
stopt	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
13	O
plate	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pawlet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
name	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
,	O
in	O
Brudenell	O
's	O
Meuse	O
;	O
(	O
The	O
cloaths	O
and	O
buttons	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
there	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
till	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
place	O
buttons	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
others	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
deposited	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
butler	O
to	O
some	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
square	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
cash	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
bound	O
himself	O
by	O
the	O
most	O
horrid	O
imprecations	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
will	O
stick	O
at	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
life	O
if	O
possible	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
70	O
,	O
71	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bosell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
by	O
ripping	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
palace	O
,	O
called	O
Somerset	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Beauclerc	I-pers
,	O
Oct	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Latimore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
board	O
of	O
works	O
,	O
and	O
reside	O
at	O
Somerset-house	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
Lady	O
Beauclerc	O
's	O
apartment	O
there	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
repaired	O
by	O
the	O
board	O
of	O
works	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
attempt	O
made	O
at	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
fast	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
more	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
building	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
palace	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
more	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
attempt	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
succeed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Couse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Somerset-house	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
board	O
of	O
works	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
Mr.	O
Latimore	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
lead	O
stolen	O
from	O
Lady	O
Beauclerc	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
replaced	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
attempt	O
again	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
then	O
I	O
ordered	O
watchmen	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
alarmed	O
the	O
whole	O
yard	O
,	O
so	O
nothing	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
3d	O
or	O
4th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
place	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
majesty	O
there	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
lead	O
;	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Boswell	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
upon	O
guard	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
some	O
from	O
over	O
Lady	O
Beauclerc	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
wash-house	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Cold-bath	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
we	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
amongst	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
some	O
from	O
the	O
barracks	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
time	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
about	O
200	O
weight	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
watermen	O
stand	O
under	O
,	O
at	O
Somerset-stairs	O
,	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Somerset-house	O
;	O
then	O
Hains	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Boswell	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
carried	O
some	O
in	O
bags	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
sold	O
that	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
s.	O
that	O
we	O
divided	O
amongst	O
us	O
three	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
cloak	O
stolen	O
from	O
Powell	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
that	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
lead	O
there	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Fountain	O
court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Boswell	O
and	O
Lee	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
lead	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
wash-house	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
place	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
sheet	O
lead	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
lead	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
have	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
lost	O
her	O
cardinal	O
,	O
either	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
.	O
Lee	O
and	O
Boswell	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
lead	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
sheet	O
lead	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
wash-house	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
grease	O
.	O
Mistress	O
lost	O
her	O
cloak	O
much	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
sheet	O
lead	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
Boswell	O
and	O
Lee	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
changed	O
with	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
72	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Esther	B-pers
Leesome	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
January	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Esther	B-pers
Leesome	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
us	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
plough	O
tug	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
half-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Leesome	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
11	O
years	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
do	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
she	O
says	O
is	O
false	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
two-pence	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
silver	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
and	O
met	O
us	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
us	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
our	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
gave	O
him	O
our	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
abuse	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
of	O
my	O
daughter	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
our	O
rings	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Anderson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
run	O
and	O
fright	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
hollow	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
wood	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
.	O
The	O
woman	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
wood	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
this	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
dash	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
near	O
two	O
feet	O
long	O
)	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
almost	O
to	O
Marybone	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Primrose-hill	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Belsize-house	O
,	O
below	O
Hampstead	O
church	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
over	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
iron	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
arm	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
iron	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
weapon	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
with	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
ran	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
civilly	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Holdway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
noted	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
long	O
looked	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
hand-cuffed	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
several	O
robberies	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
groat	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
two-pence	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
taking	O
any	O
silver	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
silver	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
groat	O
from	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
two-pence	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
any	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
capital	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
73	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Paldock	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Balldock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
7	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
somebody	O
wanted	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lying	O
cross	O
my	O
counter	O
:	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
my	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gold	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
the	O
following	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
stopt	O
till	O
his	O
mother	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
talked	O
together	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
tree	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
a	O
hollow	O
place	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
bottom	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
owning	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
committed	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
young	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
consider	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
2	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
hollow	O
tree	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
promise	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
favour	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
74	O
,	O
75	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
three	O
woollen	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
stuff	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
eight	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
eight	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
cap	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
four	O
flannel	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
Persian	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
silk	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Biass	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
woollen	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
stuff	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
Margaret	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
below	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
windows	O
,	O
a	O
whole	O
partition	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
Hermitage-bridge	O
:	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
many	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
sattin	O
cap	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Scott	O
,	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
Christmas	O
;	O
there	O
James	B-pers
Grief	I-pers
produced	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
coats	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
rats	O
having	O
knawed	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
cape	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
I	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
five	O
weeks	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Under	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
whole	O
pannel	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
four	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
eight	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linnen	O
,	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
one	O
about	O
8	O
yards	O
long	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
cardinal	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
gloves	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
we	O
dropt	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
hauled	O
down	O
a	O
blanket	O
from	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
we	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
,	O
to	O
Thompson	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
distributed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
three	O
:	O
we	O
sent	O
our	O
wives	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Biass	I-pers
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
hole	O
in	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
cape	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
plaid	O
waistcoat	O
:	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
tied	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
walked	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
Mulberry-garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Biass	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Branch	O
.	O
He	O
heard	O
us	O
talk	O
how	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
piece	O
put	O
in	O
where	O
the	O
hole	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
expence	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
M.	O
Forbes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
these	O
goods	O
the	O
evidence	O
has	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
?	O
M.	O
Forbes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sackfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
business	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Forbes	O
(	O
she	O
takes	O
a	O
plaid	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
with	O
certainty	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Forbes	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Galton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
Branch	O
from	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Saltpetre	O
bank	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
his	O
information	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
:	O
he	O
impeached	O
Thompson	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Biass	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
other	O
robberies	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Thompson	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
his	O
bed	O
;	O
we	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
pray	O
is	O
Branch	O
turned	O
informer	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
an	O
information	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
doubt	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
deceive	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
admitted	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
on	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
owns	O
this	O
coat	O
,	O
shall	O
die	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
die	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
them	O
shall	O
die	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
will	O
admit	O
me	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
Thompson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
Biass	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
cards	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grief	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
did	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
and	O
Holly-bush	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Biass	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
evidence	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
shot	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
lad	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
?	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
untying	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
this	O
plaid	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
Biass	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Grief	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
the	O
news-paper	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
justices	O
;	O
there	O
Branch	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Forbes	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
there	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Thompson	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
is	O
any	O
body	O
sworn	O
in	O
as	O
evidence	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
deceive	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
evidence	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
Biass	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
lodging	O
,	O
at	O
cards	O
.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Branch	O
stole	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Biass	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Biass	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
76	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Millicent	B-pers
Spratley	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Featherstone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Berry	B-pers
Rosewell	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
My	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Berry	O
Rosewell	O
:	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
the	B-place
Crown	I-place
and	I-place
Cushion	I-place
at	I-place
Uxbridge	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
notice	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
:	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
shewed	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
figure	O
9	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
twelve	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
all	O
numbered	O
numerically	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
ends	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
engraved	O
,	O
Sergant	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
inn	O
before	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
produced	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
end	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
name	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
mist	O
the	O
number	O
9	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
:	O
this	O
spoon	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
streets	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
's	O
of	O
hers	O
:	O
it	O
being	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
suspecting	O
it	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
just	O
in	O
the	O
condition	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
advertise	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
woman	O
:	O
she	O
stood	O
in	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
had	O
it	O
advertised	O
;	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
information	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
hearsay	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
77	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
long-lawn	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
December	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-yard	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
mob	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Medowall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
betwixt	O
14	O
and	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Parkinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Cursitor-street	O
,	O
when	O
our	O
maid	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knowing	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
confusion	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
there	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
barber	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
shave	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
forget	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
down	O
Cursitor-street	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
:	O
seeing	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
sight	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
They	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
gown	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
stair-head	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
follow	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
wig-maker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
78	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
January	O
4	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gentleman	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Temple-Exchange	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
looking	O
on	O
a	O
show-glass	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	B-place
lottery-office	I-place
,	I-place
under	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
at	O
Clifford's-Inn	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
Sir	O
!	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
leave	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
mentioned	O
the	O
word	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
coffee	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Webster	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
bring	O
any	O
substantial	O
tradesman	O
that	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Temple-bar	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
persons	O
lived	O
in	O
Old-street	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
any	O
body	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
then	O
be	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
after	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
other	O
dirty	O
people	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
)	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
79	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
January	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
going	O
into	O
the	B-place
watch-house	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Fleet-ditch	I-place
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
tug	O
at	O
my	O
fob	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
crowd	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
cleverly	O
get	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
his	O
hand	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
side	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
watch	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
boy	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
quitted	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
assistance	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Search	O
me	O
:	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cockayne	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Butcher	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
lighted	O
lamp	O
just	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
struggled	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
's	O
boy	O
stood	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
imagined	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
Levi	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
December	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Levi	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoemaker-row	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
cloaths-shop	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
London-wall	B-place
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dropt	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
violence	O
of	O
the	O
blow	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
:	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
happened	O
after	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
blow	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
slapt	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout-coat	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
brass	O
buttons	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
evening	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
carry	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
?	O
Benjamin	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
that	O
struck	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnivell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
27	O
s.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
near	O
the	O
Harrow	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
:	O
Two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
with	O
directions	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sai	O
d	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
pick	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
500	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
describe	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
clerk	O
,	O
the	O
description	O
answers	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
occasion	O
:	O
Upon	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Public-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
no	O
sooner	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Saffron-hill	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
business	O
here	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
pawned	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
business	O
was	O
about	O
that	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
office	O
was	O
so	O
full	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
when	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
ill	O
;	O
but	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
he	O
did	O
attend	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
pledged	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Saffron-hill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
London-prentice	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
a	O
sea-faring	O
man	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
36	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
remainder	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
without	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
than	O
any	O
gentleman	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Barnivell	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
80	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk-handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Moncrieff	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Alexander	B-pers
Moncrieff	I-pers
.	O
About	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
Freeman's-court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Swithin's-alley	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
'Change	O
,	O
coming	O
along	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
suddenly	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
struggled	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
an	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
towards	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
'Change	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
stood	O
very	O
still	O
;	O
the	O
mob	O
gathered	O
round	O
;	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
jirk	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
catch	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
hold	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
over	O
to	O
'Change-alley	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
stroke	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hit	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
passage	O
going	O
into	O
'Change-alley	O
,	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
the	O
keeper	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cockayne	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
last	O
?	O
Moncrieff	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Aldgateward	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
York	O
Coffee	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
but	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
faint	O
away	O
when	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
your	O
Lordship	O
does	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
recommendation	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
Dublin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
letter	O
will	O
come	O
from	O
Dublin	O
,	O
from	O
some	O
very	O
good	O
gentleman	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
81	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
and	O
Egleborth	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
December	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Barnard	B-pers
Shemedes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
on	O
Gally-key	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
very	O
narrowly	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
somebody	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
cloth	O
lay	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
somebody	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bread	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Schemedes	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Hill	O
and	O
Hague	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
says	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
open	O
Key	O
,	O
before	O
a	O
thousand	O
men	O
that	O
might	O
all	O
see	O
me	O
it	O
:	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
carmen	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
lunch	O
of	O
bread	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Dass	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Grenaway	I-pers
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
82	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Capel	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
and	O
Osgood	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
,	O
December	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
,	O
the	O
tobacco	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Day	O
and	O
son	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
83	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
printed	O
book	O
,	O
called	O
,	O
The	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Telemachus	O
,	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Book	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
Testament	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
and	O
English	O
Dictionary	O
,	O
the	O
Universal	O
Gazetteer	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
books	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilkie	I-pers
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkie	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
left	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sallicoffer	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
had	O
neglected	O
to	O
bolt	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
box	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baillie	I-pers
.	O
About	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
this	O
Lady	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
:	O
he	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
immediately	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
feloniously	O
by	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
assisted	O
to	O
hoist	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
confederacy	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
box	O
?	O
upon	O
my	O
second	O
application	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Miss	O
Ramsay	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
pretty	O
weighty	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Miss	O
Ramsay	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
knowing	O
her	O
before	O
that	O
circumstance	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
knowing	O
him	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
sufficiently	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
her	O
shop	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
Michael	O
's	O
Alley	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
nearer	O
to	O
him	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
door-way	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
drop	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
Not	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
distance	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Baillie	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stationer	O
under	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Miss	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
box	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wilkie	O
:	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
Miss	O
Ramsay	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
this	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
nailed	O
up	O
again	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
one	O
word	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
answer	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
asked	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
day	O
's	O
holiday	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
hanged	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
several	O
questions	O
there	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
opened	O
his	O
mouth	O
to	O
speak	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
questions	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
answer	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
getting	O
my	O
brains	O
knock	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
afraid	O
to	O
speak	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
,	O
about	O
something	O
being	O
lost	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
slipt	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
mob	O
that	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
shop	O
to	O
Miss	O
Ramsay	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
having	O
some	O
jeweller	O
's	O
work	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
slapt	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
unbuttoned	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
was	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
mob	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
some	O
gentleman	O
was	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
his	O
toes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
run	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
again	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
taller	O
than	O
this	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unbutton	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
button	O
the	O
door	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
:	O
that	O
man	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
this	O
man	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
run	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
when	O
Stop	O
thief	O
was	O
cried	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
stands	O
up	O
.	O
)	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
among	O
the	O
crowd	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Stop	O
thief	O
was	O
first	O
called	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
had	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
ran	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
then	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
ran	O
immediately	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Stop	O
thief	O
was	O
cried	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
here	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
among	O
the	O
Jews	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
generally	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
on	O
a	O
night	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
story	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Jews	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
shop	O
you	O
was	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
That	O
shop	O
was	O
shut	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
.	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
7	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fix	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
venture	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
or	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Ramsay	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
your	O
sister	O
's	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
another	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
directly	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Baillie	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Ramsay	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hatton	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wormwood-street	O
,	O
two	O
doors	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
from	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
by	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
filagree	O
way	O
,	O
making	O
things	O
for	O
ladies	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
dress	O
caps	O
in	O
the	O
fancy	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
shop	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
indeed	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Baillie	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
that	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Baillie	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
shop	O
open	O
was	O
Miss	O
Ramsay	O
's	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hatton	O
.	O
Where	O
abouts	O
is	O
this	O
shop	O
you	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eleven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Rose	O
Solomon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
farthing	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
clear	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
staymaker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
his	O
daughter	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
money	O
,	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
would	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
clear	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Hatton	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
perjury	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
.	O
84	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
45	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
43	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
lodge	O
,	O
in	O
Wood	B-place
's	I-place
Close	I-place
,	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
45	O
guineas	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
43	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
by	O
my	O
bedside	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milk-woman	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
gravel-pits	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
counted	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
:	O
upon	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
five	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
mends	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
prisoner	O
does	O
;	O
going	O
by	O
his	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
counting	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
half	O
crowns	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
wanting	O
money	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
often	O
lent	O
him	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
most	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
was	O
13	O
s.	O
he	O
owned	O
us	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
me	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
days	O
after	O
our	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
recollecting	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
table	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
lock	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
key	O
to	O
be	O
fitted	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
not	O
altered	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
cloaths	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
:	O
these	O
things	O
together	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
the	O
Chester	O
stage	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
Ireland	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
warrant	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
coach	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
drove	O
on	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Culpeper	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
him	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Come	O
along	O
,	O
my	O
boys	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
spend	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
now	O
.	O
His	O
trunk	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
direction	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
George-Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
bookkeeper	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
trunk	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
ready	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
trunk	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
17	O
half	O
crowns	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
small	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
described	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
like	O
sand	O
holes	O
on	O
the	O
tail	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
this	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
amongst	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
George-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
,	O
that	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
describing	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
before	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
jury	O
inspect	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
Richard	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
Towel	O
Gallagan	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
taylor	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
85	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Beals	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cheque	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
December	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
suspect	O
,	O
I	O
concluded	O
it	O
was	O
likely	O
she	O
might	O
cut	O
it	O
into	O
pieces	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
sale	O
,	O
or	O
pawn	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
first	O
pawnbroker	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
my	O
cheque	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
court	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
live	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
my	O
cloth	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
ordered	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
her	O
lodging	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
her	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
:	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warr	O
ant	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
admitted	O
us	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
room	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
about	O
4	O
yards	O
and	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
cheque	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Siers	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
on	O
Clerkenwell-Green	O
,	O
7	O
yards	O
pledged	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
6	O
yards	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
near	O
20	O
yards	O
.	O
Returning	O
home	O
,	O
by	O
Hatton-wall	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
Anne	B-pers
Stowe	I-pers
's	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
where	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
yards	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
off	O
before	O
the	O
cheque	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
pieces	O
all	O
correspond	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
circumstances	O
agree	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loitered	O
about	O
my	O
shop	O
that	O
night	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
:	O
what	O
were	O
pledged	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
5	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
about	O
7	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
pledge	O
something	O
;	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
proffered	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
still	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
when	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
hat	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
denied	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
drink	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
cheque	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
person	O
but	O
she	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
place	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Stow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
,	O
at	O
Hatton-wall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
cheque	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
in	O
necessity	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
16	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Wosley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
4	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bolster	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
6	O
yards	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bowyer	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
about	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
cheque	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
cheque	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
divers	O
pieces	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
cheque	O
from	O
Scotland	O
,	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
Captain	O
Gordon	O
's	O
ship	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goram	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Tottenham-court	B-place
road	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
:	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
lodgings	O
this	O
day	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
away	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
feather-bed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
26	O
s.	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
those	O
things	O
for	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
87	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
December	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
88	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cherry-tree	B-place
alley	I-place
,	I-place
Bunhill-row	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
leather	O
case-maker	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
lost	O
6	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
long	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
bedchamber	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
four	O
years	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
from	O
her	O
master	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lain	O
out	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
master	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
fearing	O
she	O
should	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
:	O
I	O
enquired	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Norwich	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
weaver	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
Norton-Falgate	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
home	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
alehouse	O
;	O
her	O
master	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
had	O
confess	O
'd	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
encouraged	O
her	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
cards	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
in	O
prison	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
once	O
seen	O
her	O
head	O
peep	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
Garland	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
neighbour	O
,	O
lifted	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
frequently	O
used	O
to	O
lift	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Garner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
treated	O
this	O
neighbour	O
Garland	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
l.	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
list	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Laney	I-pers
.	O
This	O
unhappy	O
girl	O
is	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
suspect	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
some	O
very	O
bad	O
company	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
things	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
ribbons	O
,	O
necklaces	O
,	O
and	O
cloaths	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
silver	O
orris	O
weaver	O
,	O
was	O
fearful	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Laney	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
unhappy	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
no	O
friends	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
very	O
bad	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
set	O
me	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
89	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
coach	O
wheel	O
harness	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hebberden	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Physic	O
,	O
December	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
coach	O
wheel	O
harness	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Lady	O
Betty	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
's	O
coachman	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roote	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Hebberden	O
.	O
This	O
harness	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
named	O
Riley	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
90	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cheque	O
bed-curtain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
,	O
December	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Adam	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
King's-head-court	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
near	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
two	O
small	O
children	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
somebody	O
to	O
assist	O
;	O
so	O
my	O
wife	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
weekly	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
7	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
:	O
by	O
enquiring	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
91	O
,	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Billet	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Bevas	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
four	O
sattin	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
five	O
cotton	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
nine	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
four	O
other	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
red	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Union-stairs	B-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
my	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
that	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
:	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
within	O
twelve	O
hours	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
committed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Galton	I-pers
.	O
Those	O
things	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
,	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
stripping	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
2	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
3	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
printed	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
of	O
the	O
printed	O
one	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Galton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
people	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
those	O
shirts	O
are	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Macknealer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
neither	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
nor	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
little	O
dog	O
upon	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
gloves	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
stitch	O
'd	O
together	O
by	O
the	O
tops	O
.	O
About	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
yards	O
farther	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
other	O
gloves	O
without	O
thumbs	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
wrong	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Molton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
,	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
a	O
deplorable	O
condition	O
for	O
cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
time	O
,	O
being	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
Samuel	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
dressed	O
in	O
these	O
things	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
their	O
shirts	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
their	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
moment	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
!	O
poor	O
creatures	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
:	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
up	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
)	O
these	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Billet	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
off	O
Bevas	O
,	O
(	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
2	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
officer	O
in	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Billet	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
his	O
soul	O
and	O
body	O
and	O
all	O
for	O
a	O
groat	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
care	O
if	O
his	O
body	O
was	O
thrown	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
the	O
dogs	O
.	O
Billet	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
fitted	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
the	O
bomb-boats	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
Bevas	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
my	O
river	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
2	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
For	O
Billet	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
Billet	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
fitted	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Billet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Billet	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
eight	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
?	O
J.	O
Billet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
him	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
2	O
jackets	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
cheque	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
shirts	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
J.	O
Billet	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
not	O
cheque	O
,	O
but	O
striped	O
.	O
)	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Salloway	I-pers
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Salloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
coals	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
chargeable	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
we	O
sent	O
twenty-eight	O
sacks	O
of	O
coals	O
to	O
Esq	O
;	O
Leak	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
of	O
that	O
quantity	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
drove	O
the	O
waggon	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
mentioned	O
a	O
word	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
misunderstanding	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
cart	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Leak	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
sacks	O
wanting	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Salloway	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
)	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mere	O
mistake	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Leak	O
's	O
boy	O
,	O
that	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
his	O
playing	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
with	O
the	O
girls	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
twenty-eight	O
sacks	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jagoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Leak	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
waggon	O
with	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
a	O
ticket	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
twenty-eight	O
sacks	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
but	O
twenty-four	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Leak	O
and	O
I	O
chalked	O
them	O
down	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
four	O
sacks	O
:	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
twenty-eight	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
might	O
come	O
and	O
count	O
the	O
sacks	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
parlour-window	O
,	O
and	O
chalked	O
down	O
as	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
many	O
I	O
had	O
chalked	O
down	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
might	O
come	O
and	O
tell	O
the	O
sacks	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
very	O
likely	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
twenty-eight	O
empty	O
sacks	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
but	O
twenty-four	O
with	O
coals	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
a	O
paper	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
next	O
cart	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
load	O
that	O
waggon	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-eight	O
sacks	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
note	O
from	O
Esq	O
;	O
Leak	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
waggon	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
note	O
for	O
twenty-eight	O
sacks	O
,	O
brought	O
but	O
twenty-four	O
sacks	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	B-pers
the	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sad	O
dispute	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
:	O
you	O
delivered	O
but	O
twenty-four	O
sacks	O
instead	O
of	O
twenty-eight	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
mistake	O
of	O
the	O
footman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Anderson	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
sack	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
give	O
a	O
note	O
with	O
that	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
deliver	O
a	O
ticket	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
ten	O
chaldron	O
of	O
coals	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Leak	O
's	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
half	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
waggon	O
side	O
:	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
gentleman	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
coals	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
him	O
a	O
sack	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
pay	O
your	O
servant	O
that	O
brings	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
please	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Salloway	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
load	O
twenty-nine	O
sacks	O
;	O
I	O
loaded	O
twenty-nine	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
horses	O
too	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
followed	O
me	O
into	O
Fox	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
chalked	O
the	O
sacks	O
,	O
that	O
nobody	O
might	O
have	O
any	O
suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
sacks	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
the	O
sack	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
I	O
shot	O
the	O
coals	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
pay	O
your	O
master	O
for	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
coals	O
?	O
yes	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
sack	O
upon	O
the	O
wharf	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
shooting	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
threepence	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
empty	O
sack	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
:	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
chalk	O
the	O
other	O
sacks	O
,	O
that	O
nobody	O
shall	O
have	O
any	O
mistrust	O
of	O
these	O
other	O
sacks	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
sacks	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
two	O
sacks	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
hair-merchant	O
