TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
of	O
JULY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGEN	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clive	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Perrott	I-pers
;	O
||	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bumpus	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibs	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Cannan	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hitchins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bruin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sherridon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Makebridge	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dakin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
.	O
388	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
John	O
Bridge	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
woollen-draper	O
without	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
at	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
doors	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
rolled	O
up	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
hip-bone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
but	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
389	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-one	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dupuis	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dupuis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
pigeon-house	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
pigeons	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
thirty-six	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
called	O
Toy	O
pigeons	O
:	O
the	O
pigeon-house	O
is	O
over	O
a	O
coach-house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Fulham	O
.	O
By	O
searching	O
,	O
my	O
servants	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
one	O
Reeves	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
lost	O
again	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
own	O
places	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cuff	I-pers
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dupuis	O
:	O
the	O
pigeons	O
were	O
stolen	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Whitsunday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
James	O
Reeves	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
safely	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
objection	O
to	O
our	O
seeing	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
we	O
questioned	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
21	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
New-Way	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
pigeons	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
along	O
with	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
pair	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
pigeons	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
390	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
leather	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
night-gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vass	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bushrod	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
trunk	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Horse	I-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
;	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
porter	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
missed	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Maidenhead	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
found	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
on	O
hearing	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
nor	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
forbid	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
employed	O
there	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
391	O
,	O
392	O
,	O
393	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Sedro	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Ode	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
tankards	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Patton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Patton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
cellar	O
,	O
the	B-place
Thistle	I-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Great	I-place
Suffolk-street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
inst	O
.	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
six-pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
six-pennyworths	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
bowl	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
to	O
stir	O
the	O
liquor	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
little	O
cupboard	O
,	O
where	O
stood	O
two	O
silver	O
tankards	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
tankards	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
towards	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Farthing-fields	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pilmore	I-pers
.	O
Sedro	O
brought	O
this	O
lump	O
of	O
silver	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rands	O
,	O
in	O
Cary-lane	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
assayer	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
about	O
36	O
ounces	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenning	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
's	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
china	O
bason	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
silver	O
tankards	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
:	O
Morris	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
designed	O
by	O
us	O
four	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
melted	O
them	O
at	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
worked	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
hammered	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
melting	O
pot	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
lump	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
produced	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
by	O
Sedro	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
assayed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Ode	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
May	O
Sessions	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
six	O
livre	O
piece	O
,	O
80	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phoenix	I-pers
Sarrant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
December	O
29	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
267.	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
394	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Loveland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
doe-skins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
395	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mackdaniel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
O'Neal	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Owen	B-pers
O'Neal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
.	O
I	O
failed	O
eight	O
years	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lodges	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
ill	O
on	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
Hick's-Hall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
396	O
,	O
397	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
120	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brick-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Brentford	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
iron	O
from	O
the	O
ferry-wharf	O
there	O
;	O
(	O
A	O
piece	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
is	O
barge	O
dron	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Powell	O
confessed	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Pool	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
this	O
iron	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Murford	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Murford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Old	O
Brentford	O
.	O
Pool	O
brought	O
this	O
iron	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
some	O
for	O
three	O
farthings	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Powell	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Murford	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Powell	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Pool	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
iron	O
of	O
Powell	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
their	O
master	O
gave	O
it	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
beer	O
.	O
For	O
Pool	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Powell	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Pool	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
398	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Ann	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
M'Creary	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
my	O
mother	O
put	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
for	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
veal	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
A.	O
Peirce	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Dorathy	O
M'Creary	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
last	O
Saturday	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
;	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
4	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
cook	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
girl	O
with	O
the	O
veal	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
girl	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
child	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
dress	O
and	O
size	O
in	O
writing	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
hands	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
:	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Anne	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
girl	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
in	O
a	O
tray	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sharper	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
stood	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
the	O
woman	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sharper	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
woman	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
sware	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
till	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridge's-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
dragoons	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
from	O
twelve	O
till	O
after	O
two	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
cleaning	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
before	O
twelve	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
tea	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
almost	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridge's-street	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
our	O
door	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
lost	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
on	O
her	O
cap	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
wanted	O
ten	O
minutes	O
of	O
eleven	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
filled	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
water-tub	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
cream-pot	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
full	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
clock	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Captain	O
Whitehead	B-pers
is	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
she	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
from	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
over	O
or	O
under	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swan-yard	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
many	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
such	O
another	O
offence	O
.	O
399	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
woman	O
's	O
sattin	O
shoe	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Turnstile	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shutter	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
one	O
sattin	O
shoe	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
this	O
shoe	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
shop	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
:	O
(	O
Producing	O
the	O
shoe	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
i	O
t	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
names	O
within	O
were	O
alike	O
:	O
and	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Whitaker	O
's	O
sister	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
nine-pence	O
for	O
the	O
shoe	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Newmarket	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
saw	O
me	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
400	O
,	O
401	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
night-caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
one	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
glass	O
quart	O
bottles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Leak	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
physician	O
and	O
man-midwife	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Craven-street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
Hinds	O
was	O
my	O
foot-boy	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
A	O
parcel	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
livery	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
blanket	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
were	O
making	O
an	O
agreement	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
bundle	O
to	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
corner	O
,	O
for	O
2	O
d.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Shields	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Hinds	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
afterwards	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doland	I-pers
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
is	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Another	O
watchman	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Bevan	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
402	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
January	O
,	O
1763	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wound	O
up	O
my	O
watch	O
(	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
)	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shirts	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
almost	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Collier	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
403	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Arthur	B-pers
Kane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
razor-case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
)	O
in	O
Banbury-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	I-place
he	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
good	O
wig	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
my	O
lad	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
shaved	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
razor-case	O
and	O
some	O
razors	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
razors	O
away	O
?	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
be	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
fighting	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
got	O
clear	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
hell	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Culymore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
wig	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
take	O
for	O
service	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
razors	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
razors	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Charles	O
-	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
shaved	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
razors	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
shaving	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
razors	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
senses	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
cuts	O
I	O
received	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
wars	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
404	O
,	O
405	O
,	O
406	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
walking	O
canes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Worster	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
hoy	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
same	O
persons	O
gave	O
evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Ricketts	O
,	O
in	O
No	O
.	O
343.	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
407	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loseby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Asterly	I-pers
.	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Asterly	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
have	O
I	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
fall	O
from	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
his	O
jacket	O
on	O
his	O
shoe	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Asterley	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
kick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
that	O
kick	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
determined	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
seize	O
my	O
cane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
kick	O
on	O
the	O
arse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
:	O
I	O
knowing	O
myself	O
innocent	O
,	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
kicked	O
right	O
under	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
followed	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
minute	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bruncell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
408	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Isaac	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Levingstone	I-pers
,	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Levingstone	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
is	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
concealed	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
receive	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
picked	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Going	O
up	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
went	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
409	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
porcelain	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
nine	O
British	O
basons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
tea	O
pots	O
,	O
fourteen	O
tea-cups	O
,	O
twenty	O
saucers	O
,	O
two	O
tumblers	O
,	O
two	O
milk	O
juggs	O
,	O
a	O
mustard	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sauce-boat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
June	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
presents	O
of	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
manufacturing	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sold	O
large	O
quantities	O
of	O
such	O
daily	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
certify	O
these	O
were	O
not	O
such	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
410	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Barnaby	I-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
fifteen	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
sessions	O
,	O
1759	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
only	O
evidences	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Appleton	O
and	O
Bransfield	O
,	O
which	O
no	O
ways	O
affected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Numbers	O
69	O
,	O
70	O
,	O
71	O
,	O
72.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
411	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Beaden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
John	I-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Middleditch	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Middleditch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Budge-row	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
:	O
we	O
are	O
grocers	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deficiency	O
in	O
our	O
tea	O
;	O
the	O
excise-officer	O
makes	O
us	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
stock	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
this	O
decrease	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
supposed	O
by	O
our	O
book	O
,	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
of	O
tea	O
were	O
deficient	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
connection	O
with	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
entertained	O
a	O
bad	O
opinion	O
of	O
honest	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
determined	O
to	O
turn	O
them	O
all	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
ours	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
earlier	O
than	O
common	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
mercy	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cannister	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
paper	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
might	O
hold	O
about	O
eight	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
frightened	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
cannister	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
us	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
canvas	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
fellow	O
,	O
somewhere	O
near	O
Ipswich	O
;	O
we	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
blown	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
young	O
offender	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
Middleditch	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
had	O
two	O
capital	O
bolts	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
breach	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lath	O
and	O
plaister	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
could	O
undo	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
fasten	O
again	O
the	O
bolts	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
confession	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
penitence	O
,	O
I	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
Slack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
upon	O
unlocking	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
a	O
cannister	O
,	O
emptying	O
tea	O
into	O
a	O
paper	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
;	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
you	O
must	O
do	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
suspected	O
in	O
taking	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
masters	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
from	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
paper	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
the	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
cannister	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
having	O
then	O
on	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
shirt	O
.	O
In	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Middleditch	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
his	O
cloaths	O
on	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Middleditch	O
said	O
,	O
Young	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
your	O
taking	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
:	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Middleditch	O
said	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
tea	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
taking	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
into	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Smallwood	O
,	O
a	O
smuggler	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
this	O
he	O
also	O
confessed	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
take	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
other	O
servants	O
do	O
so	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
a	O
confession	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
whatever	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
412	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hempen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
hundred	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Menetone	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Menetone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ship-builder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
burnt	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
New-crane-stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
nails	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boat	O
lying	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
nails	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
nails	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
nails	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
counting-house	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Onslow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
stealing	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
barge	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
of	O
nails	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
a	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
boat	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
a-drift	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
nails	O
from	O
another	O
man	O
:	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
nails	O
were	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
by	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
under	O
shore	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
so	O
wet	O
by	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
an	O
our	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
413	O
,	O
414	O
,	O
415	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Robert	B-pers
Wittingdale	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Wittingdale	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
near	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
More	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
together	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
public-house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
drank	O
till	O
pretty	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
Saltpetre-bank	B-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
Cornish	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
More	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
their	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
to	O
be	O
Cornish	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
upon	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
:	O
Robinson	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
moving	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
the	O
cloth	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
about	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
Robinson	O
returned	O
,	O
snatched	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
sorry	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
all	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Robinson	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
cock	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
man	O
what	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Robinson	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
beckon	O
to	O
Robinson	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
slipped	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Robert	B-pers
Wittingdale	I-pers
.	O
Never	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
as	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
Robert	B-pers
Wittingdale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
of	O
Robinson	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
cloaths	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
at	O
this	O
minute	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
More	O
bring	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
down	O
to	O
Saltpetre	O
bank	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
Cornish	O
:	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
More	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
nobody	O
will	O
hurt	O
you	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
Black-boy-alley	O
,	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
;	O
then	O
Robinson	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
went	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
Robinson	O
before	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Cornish	O
were	O
sitting	O
together	O
;	O
Jane	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
More	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
;	O
Robinson	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
women	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Robinson	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
a	O
smith	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
O'Harra	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
afterwards	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
thing	O
done	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
walking	O
about	O
all	O
night	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
watch	O
there	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
and	O
alarm	O
them	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sick	O
of	O
an	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
seeing	O
this	O
evidence	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Martin	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
by	O
business	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
cart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
Cornish	O
's	O
face	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
More	O
tie	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
with	O
Robinson	O
at	O
the	O
Black-boy	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
pass	O
time	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
and	O
Robinson	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
alley	O
together	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
More	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
old	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
8	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
spent	O
seven	O
farthings	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
people	O
he	O
pleased	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
lodging	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
my	O
endeavour	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
two-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
that	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Charles	B-pers
Orr	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Rotherey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cowman	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Cornish	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
More	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
but	O
two-pence	O
half-penny	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
living	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
that	O
witness	O
,	O
More	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
)	O
on	O
Saltpetre	O
bank	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
robbed	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
then	O
coming	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Robinson	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
you	O
were	O
robbed	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gang-porter	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
sugar	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
gateway	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
Ralph	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
pockets	O
full	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
The	O
sugar	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
pockets	O
,	O
some	O
was	O
spilt	O
:	O
it	O
weighed	O
seventeen	O
pounds	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
all	O
clean	O
sugar	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
hogshead	O
with	O
the	O
head	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
plundered	O
:	O
we	O
weighed	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
wanted	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
loophole	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
fall	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
out	O
some	O
sugar	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
story	O
high	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
feet	O
high	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
gang's-men	O
came	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
,	O
in	O
landing	O
some	O
rum	O
and	O
brandy	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
being	O
drunk	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
417	O
,	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
betwixt	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
below	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
by	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
Wilkinson	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
down	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Wilkinson	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
minute	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
through	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
that	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
following	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
after	O
him	O
at	O
Temple-bar	O
:	O
he	O
there	O
met	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
no	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
Curtis	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
gentleman	O
:	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
at	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
we	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Wilkinson	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
shuffle	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
by	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
their	O
trial	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
so	O
soon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
their	O
witnesses	O
ready	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
419	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caffry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Peter	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
:	O
a	O
gentleman	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
bacon	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
where	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
:	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
what	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
bacon	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
Whitsun-Monday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drunk	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
420	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
eleven-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Ld	O
.	O
Mayor	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
flounders	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
cod	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
advantage	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
two	O
crooked	O
shillings	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
crooked	O
shillings	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
shillings	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
half-penny	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
twelve	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
tells	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
the	O
minute	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
38.	O
and	O
135.	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coff	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jervis	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Jervis	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
:	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
goods	O
taken	O
away	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
My	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
repairing	O
:	O
I	O
kneeled	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
young	O
master	O
to	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
ladder	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
journeyman	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
,	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
his	O
business	O
was	O
to	O
cut	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
young	O
master	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Bulimore	O
Francis	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
in	O
two	O
hours	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Windmill-court	O
,	O
Pye	O
Corner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
call	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
at	O
all	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
here	O
they	O
be	O
.	O
(	O
Two	O
pair	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fellow	O
journeyman	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
19th	O
instant	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
before	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
two	O
pair	O
instead	O
of	O
one	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
maid	O
charged	O
him	O
but	O
with	O
one	O
pair	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
shew	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Adamson	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Penton	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
seaman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
enquiring	O
about	O
,	O
got	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
prosecute	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
law	O
directs	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
spoons	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
betwixt	O
twelve	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
423	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Walter	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
'	O
Change-gate	B-place
:	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lucy	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
one	O
box-iron	O
,	O
two	O
heaters	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
wooden	O
pail	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
David	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
twelve	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
paid	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
threaten	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
exasperated	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
give	O
her	O
authority	O
to	O
pawn	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
near	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
discovered	O
every	O
article	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
wrote	O
the	O
particulars	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
warrant	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Legoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
confess	O
I	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
sick	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
support	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
425	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
,	O
for	O
boiling	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Esther	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
copper	O
that	O
was	O
fixed	O
in	O
a	O
washhouse	O
,	O
in	O
brick	O
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
waterman	O
's	O
arms	O
,	O
at	O
Islleworth	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
copper	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
little	O
brazier	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
your	O
copper	O
since	O
?	O
Esther	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
:	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Godman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
.	O
Millicent	B-pers
Godman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
goods	O
,	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
wheelbarrow	O
full	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
waterman	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
goods	O
:	O
the	O
waterman	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
waterman	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
Richardson	O
,	O
another	O
brazier	O
,	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Godman	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
things	O
come	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
down	O
to	O
Brentford	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
wheel-barrow	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
,	O
wheel-barrow	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
boat	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
divers	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
in	O
particular	O
see	O
any	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
word	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
wait	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
copper	O
in	O
my	O
boat	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
426	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
Pitney	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Shambrooke	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Shambrooke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Windmill	B-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Rosemary-lane	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
her	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
mug	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
mug	O
and	O
prisoner	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
servants	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
moved	O
the	O
mug	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
her	O
friend	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
presently	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
trifle	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
mug	O
.	O
Then	O
Alice	O
Gaul	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Alice	B-pers
Gaul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
deliver	O
back	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
customer	O
before	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
this	O
mug	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Solomon	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Philipson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
his	O
service	O
was	O
she	O
cleared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
427	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Neptune	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank-note	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
,	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Benj	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
of	O
Lord	O
Ligonier	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
295	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
date	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Bare	O
Key	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
desk	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
note	O
lost	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
laid	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
on	O
two	O
examinations	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
Toby	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
examination	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
out	O
:	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
eight	O
months	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
brought	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
we	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
date	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
two	O
blacks	O
came	O
and	O
changed	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Lord	O
Ligonier	O
's	O
house-keeper	O
here	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
paid	O
the	O
note	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
order	O
you	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
produce	O
it	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
note	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
produced	O
,	O
to	O
identify	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
described	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
428	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Grace	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Russel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Anne	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Francis	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
more	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lodgers	O
had	O
called	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
describing	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
:	O
we	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
now	O
on	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
at	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
we	O
found	O
my	O
petticoat	O
and	O
daughter	O
's	O
stays	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
petticoat	O
and	O
stays	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
last	O
Friday	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Milavay	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
chamber	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
midwife	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
higher	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
but	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
midwife	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
go	O
away	O
:	O
whether	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
petticoat	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
429	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Ooler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
quarts	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hutchinson	B-pers
Mure	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
||	O
Henry	B-pers
Dominy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
excise	O
officer	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stationed	O
in	O
the	O
Blessing	O
,	O
Captain	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
se'ennight	O
we	O
were	O
delivering	O
rums	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
lighters	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
waterman	O
at	O
Ratcliff-Cross	B-place
:	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
bored	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
a	O
puncheon	O
,	O
and	O
drawed	O
off	O
some	O
rum	O
in	O
a	O
bladder	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bladder	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
trowsers	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
quarts	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
his	O
confession	O
,	O
the	O
lightermen	O
were	O
all	O
concerned	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
large	O
gimlet	O
,	O
and	O
small	O
tap	O
and	O
faucet	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
tasted	O
the	O
rum	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
hold	O
,	O
doing	O
my	O
duty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
was	O
the	O
cargo	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
It	O
all	O
belonged	O
to	O
Hutchinson	B-pers
Mure	I-pers
.	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drawing	O
of	O
rum	O
into	O
a	O
bladder	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
quarts	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
on	O
shore	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
sculler	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
liquor	O
or	O
bladder	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lucy	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
3	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
in	O
Clement's-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Trumpet	O
,	O
Sheer-lane	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
ch	O
urch-yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
chair	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
woman	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
negus	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Crane	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
fire	O
shovel	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
nose	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
murdered	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
expect	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
They	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
used	O
me	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
murdered	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
detained	O
,	O
being	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
431	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harbin	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
||	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harbin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
being	O
sick	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
one	O
week	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harbin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
bed	O
afterwards	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
cardinal	O
,	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
petticoat	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
pulled	O
off	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
buckles	O
and	O
cloaths	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
,	O
A	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
cloaths	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
carrying	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
432	O
,	O
433	O
,	O
434	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pullein	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
and	O
Pullein	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
Pullein	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
buys	O
and	O
sells	O
old	O
cloaths	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
105	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
pinned	O
up	O
hanging	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
search	O
?	O
Barrow	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
from	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
Hussey	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
lads	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pullein	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
silk	O
ones	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
?	O
Hussey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
curtain	O
divides	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
behind	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
sold	O
him	O
any	O
before	O
?	O
Hussey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
no	O
scruple	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Hussey	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
gentlemens	O
pockets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
in	O
getting	O
these	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
?	O
Hussey	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
lads	O
?	O
Hussey	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Hussey	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Clarkenwell	O
bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Hilliard	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
:	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
admitted	O
me	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pullein	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
these	O
boys	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
sell	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
handkerchiefs	O
might	O
they	O
sell	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Fross	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
twelve	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
while	O
the	O
boys	O
were	O
selling	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
minded	O
my	O
seeing	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
silk	O
ones	O
,	O
some	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
these	O
boys	O
several	O
times	O
come	O
on	O
nights	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
refused	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
may	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
these	O
boys	O
with	O
handkerchiefs	O
there	O
?	O
Fross	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
ten	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
till	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Pullein	O
was	O
a	O
staymaker	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
looked	O
after	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
understood	O
the	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
linen	O
for	O
shirts	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
this	O
discovery	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
bring	O
Pullein	O
into	O
trouble	O
:	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
Pullein	O
:	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
words	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
This	O
woman	O
lodges	O
in	O
Pullein	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
5	O
or	O
600	O
handkerchiefs	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
here	O
produced	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
his	O
wife	O
separate	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-one	O
silk	O
ones	O
,	O
sixty-nine	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
fifty	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
ones	O
.	O
When	O
Fross	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Pullein	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
buy	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
these	O
boys	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Smith	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
frighted	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
next	O
.	O
Hilliard	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Hussey	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
Smith	O
;	O
they	O
stopped	O
us	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
picking	O
pockets	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
lad	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Pullein	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
Fross	O
,	O
(	O
upon	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
having	O
a	O
summons	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
buying	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
)	O
offered	O
her	O
service	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
affidavit	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
connection	O
with	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
What	O
handkerchiefs	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
among	O
64	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
For	O
Pullein	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Fross	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
either	O
transport	O
her	O
master	O
,	O
or	O
be	O
transported	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Pullein	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
doing	O
needle	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pullein	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
almost	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Fross	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
mending	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
see	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
:	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
curtain	O
goes	O
a-cross	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
curtain	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bracy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Frankline	O
,	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pullein	O
bought	O
as	O
many	O
goods	O
there	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
64	O
l.	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
pawned	O
and	O
not	O
redeemed	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
handkerchiefs	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
silk	O
,	O
some	O
cotton	O
,	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
any	O
shop-book	O
?	O
Bracy	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
put	O
down	O
what	O
things	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
that	O
64	O
l.	O
in	O
that	O
book	O
?	O
Bracy	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
:	O
we	O
book	O
them	O
when	O
we	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Commery	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Prescot	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hawst	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cluton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Hilliard	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
Pullein	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
,	O
1761	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
full	O
life	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
book	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
original	O
register-book	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
parish	O
;	O
it	O
appears	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
That	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1758	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
witnessed	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
another	O
woman	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
ceremony	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
wedding	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
Mary	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
?	O
Bowyer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
to	O
a	O
year	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Wapping-chapel	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
clerk	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
witness	O
here	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
inst	O
.	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
licence	O
at	O
the	O
Commons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
former	O
wife	O
?	O
M.	O
Howell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
about	O
eighteen	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
register-book	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
``	O
No	O
.	O
57.	O
James	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
this	O
parish	O
,	O
batchelor	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
married	O
by	O
``	O
licence	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
,	O
1761	O
,	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Deverdoe	I-pers
,	O
``	O
curate	O
.	O
''	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
married	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
my	O
first	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
two	O
other	O
voyages	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
436	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ilive	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
two	O
copper	O
tea-kettles	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
pail	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
six	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
Henry	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
17th	O
year	O
of	O
her	O
age	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
pewter	O
pots	O
down	O
the	O
bog-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
this	O
we	O
supposed	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
scouring	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
chastise	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
told	O
us	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
taking	O
a	O
copper	O
teakettle	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
;	O
named	O
Aspinell	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
grey-peas	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
mother	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
chare	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
they	O
drew	O
her	O
into	O
this	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
T.	O
437	O
,	O
438	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Philip	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Philip	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Sadler's-wells	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
:	O
on	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
,	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
up	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
:	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
have	O
patience	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
foot-pad	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
he	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
denying	O
it	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
chased	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
ladies	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
purse	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
one	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
trouble	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shew	O
you	O
my	O
pockets	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
pocket	O
two	O
penknives	O
and	O
two	O
keys	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
surrendered	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
keys	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
the	O
gentleman	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Drive	O
on	O
,	O
coachman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
describe	O
the	O
two	O
penknives	O
?	O
Roper	O
.	O
One	O
is	O
a	O
buck-horn	O
handle	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
broken	O
point	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
tortoise-shell	O
handle	O
.	O
When	O
Lacey	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
penknives	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
(	O
The	O
knives	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Povey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
clerk	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
drive	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
the	O
two	O
Bareav	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
two	O
brothers	O
)	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
horse	O
patrole	O
upon	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
to	O
Marybone	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
pistols	O
and	O
hangers	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
beyond	O
the	O
Farthing-pye	O
