TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGEN	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
Sidney	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Smythe	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
||	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Colebatch	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomlinson	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Astie	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Nichol	I-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kennier	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rabbit	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gary	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pinkard	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Richard	O
Pinkard	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
ill.	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
544	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gang's-man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
last	O
Saturday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
at	O
Smart	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
capstan-garret	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
break	O
into	O
a	O
hogshead	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
and	O
take	O
sugar	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
within	O
his	O
shirt	O
and	O
trowsers	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
seven	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jebb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
keys	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
seven	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
trowsers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
picked	O
up	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
lumps	O
of	O
sugar	O
under	O
the	O
wheel	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
all	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
none	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
little	O
holes	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
545	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Luke	O
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Luke	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
hole	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Stepney	I-place
.	O
I	O
missed	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
bedroom	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
?	O
Paine	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
blue-anchor	O
alehouse	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
changed	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
drinking	O
bumbo	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
more	O
gold	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
shewed	O
a	O
key	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
house	O
all	O
over	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
this	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
money	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
redeeming	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
46	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
?	O
Paine	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
from	O
what	O
place	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Paine	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Horns	O
,	O
at	O
Limehouse-hole	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
missed	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
fellows	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
two	O
women	O
two	O
penny	O
drams	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
we	O
changed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
quarter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
's	O
apprentice	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
shut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Garret	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
noon	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
changed	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
also	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
this	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
's	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
?	O
Garret	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
way	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
deliver	O
back	O
such	O
a	O
key	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
proper	O
pick-lock	O
key	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
from	O
what	O
place	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Garret	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
confederates	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
key	O
himself	O
,	O
by	O
filing	O
the	O
wards	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Garret	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
shipwright	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
46	O
s.	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
key	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
546	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
,	O
October	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-end	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Redcow	I-place
lane	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
twenty	O
geese	O
,	O
two	O
turkeys	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
fowls	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
of	O
my	O
loss	O
at	O
Leaden-hall	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
goose	O
sold	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
upwards	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
goose	O
worth	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
Leaden-hall	O
market	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
town-fed	O
goose	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
foul	O
killed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Laycock	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
person	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
being	O
foul	O
killed	O
?	O
Laycock	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
had	O
its	O
throat	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
a	O
sack	O
;	O
the	O
blood	O
was	O
congealed	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
it	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
stolen	O
goose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Laycock	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goose-seeder	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
ends	O
of	O
goose	O
wings	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
:	O
they	O
exactly	O
fit	O
to	O
the	O
wings	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
that	O
goose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
goose	O
in	O
its	O
feathers	O
?	O
Laycock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
feathers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
distinguish	O
with	O
certainty	O
between	O
a	O
country	O
goose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
town	O
fed	O
goose	O
.	O
Laycock	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
difference	O
between	O
the	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
as	O
between	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
superfine	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
common	O
cloth	O
;	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
feed	O
a	O
goose	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
here	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
geese	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
goose	O
which	O
I	O
asked	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
better	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
complained	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
town	O
fed	O
goose	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
sold	O
that	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
each	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
here	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
geese	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
hoy	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
;	O
I	O
gave	O
2	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Cook	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
547	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Slee	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Slee	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
country	O
friend	O
that	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Majesty	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
crowd	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
advertised	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
clerk	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ashbener	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lower	O
Featherstone-buildings	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
A	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
such	O
a	O
watch	O
advertised	O
,	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
offence	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
nature	O
:	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
keep	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Butcher	O
row	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Thatch'd-house	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
being	O
afraid	O
to	O
trust	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
knows	O
I	O
offered	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
shows	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
Ashbener	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
months	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
some	O
months	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Proudfoot	I-pers
,	O
September	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Proudfoot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Blue-coat-school	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Christ-church	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
people	O
assembled	O
together	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stood	O
there	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
somebody	O
taking	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
left	O
I	O
should	O
accuse	O
him	O
wrongfully	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
could	O
possibly	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
their	O
backs	O
were	O
towards	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
seeing	O
me	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
turned	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
stood	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
notion	O
he	O
would	O
attempt	O
it	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desirous	O
of	O
detecting	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
stood	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
down	O
just	O
by	O
my	O
fob	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
move	O
again	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shove	O
with	O
his	O
arm	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
stood	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fearful	O
he	O
should	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
my	O
watch	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
foot	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
constable	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Proudfoot	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
Proudfoot	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
moving	O
just	O
at	O
his	O
toe	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
fall	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
it	O
should	O
fall	O
from	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
548	O
,	O
549	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
;	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pinches	I-pers
;	O
September	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
Powell	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
breeches	O
on	O
when	O
taken	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
confederate	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
taken	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Rice	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
Powell	O
said	O
.	O
Powell	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
meaning	O
Rice	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Powell	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Rice	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
shoebuckles	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
;	O
September	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
Powell	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
confessed	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Rice	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
For	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Rice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Powell	O
confess	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
my	O
shoes	O
are	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Rice	O
.	O
Powell	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Rice	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
550	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
deal	O
scaffolding	O
poles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Corser	I-pers
,	O
September	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
found	O
the	O
said	O
poles	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Cavener	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Cross-street	O
;	O
but	O
Cavener	O
not	O
coming	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
551	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Squires	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
old	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
September	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
old	O
iron	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
41	O
pounds	O
weight	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
old	O
iron	O
in	O
a	O
scale	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
iron	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
told	O
,	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
enquiring	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
iron	O
at	O
Kentish-Town	O
;	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
near	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
iron	O
,	O
with	O
Napper	O
and	O
Pelham	O
,	O
12	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
old	O
iron	O
,	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hardacre	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
morning	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
death	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
552	O
,	O
553	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Carlow	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
called	O
long-ell	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
September	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
at	O
Old	B-place
Ford	I-place
:	O
we	O
are	O
scarlet	O
dyers	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
our	O
warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hand-bills	O
printed	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
I	O
heard	O
Spence	O
say	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Goad	O
the	O
Evidence	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Carlow	O
staid	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Goad	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
Carlow	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goad	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
;	O
we	O
proceeded	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Mile-End	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Bow	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
warehouse	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
warehouse	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
two	O
long-ells	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
window	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
;	O
thinking	O
it	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
town	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Rosemary	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Islington	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
by	O
the	O
cloth	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
purl	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
near	O
White-conduit	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
afterwards	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Roe-buck	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Carlow	O
's	O
mother	O
;	O
they	O
there	O
took	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
custody	O
.	O
Two	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harriat	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
cloth	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
:	O
Spence	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
both	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
:	O
Spence	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
besides	O
what	O
you	O
took	O
?	O
Goad	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
took	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Spence	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
extravagant	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
money	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
long-ell	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
up	O
the	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harriat	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Spence	O
and	O
Carlow	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mallot	O
,	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
)	O
.	O
Mallot	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
Mallot	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
or	O
he	O
must	O
find	O
the	O
lining	O
?	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
sitting	O
drinking	O
,	O
Spence	O
produced	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
taylor	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
work	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
wrapper	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Spence	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
cloth	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
get	O
what	O
you	O
can	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
six	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
measured	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
cloth	O
into	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Ned	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
Spence	O
came	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Carlow	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
night	O
Spence	O
delivered	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Harriat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
answer	O
,	O
when	O
Spence	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
six	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Spence	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
dispense	O
with	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
yes	O
?	O
Harriat	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
witnesses	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
applied	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
some	O
people	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
cloth	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
was	O
stole	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
or	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
so	O
Spence	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
own	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
stopped	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
afterwards	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
piece	O
)	O
:	O
this	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Huston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Crane	O
's	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
their	O
warehouse	O
had	O
been	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
cloth	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Spence	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
cloth	O
)	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
promiscuously	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
information	O
brought	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
cloth	O
.	O
Crane	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
our	O
property	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
orange	O
colour	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
thing	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
)	O
This	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Ludlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
such	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
Crane	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
produced	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
take	O
these	O
men	O
;	O
Carlow	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
and	O
Spence	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
Spence	O
gave	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
Harriat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Wright	O
;	O
that	O
Harriat	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
broker	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
Carlow	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
is	O
turned	O
broker	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
people	O
.	O
Alexander	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Crane	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
Spence	O
was	O
for	O
being	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
touch	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Carlow	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Spence	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
fellow	O
that	O
is	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
foreman	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Crane	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
cloth	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
any	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
safely	O
swear	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
again	O
.	O
Carlow	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
repeated	O
them	O
words	O
as	O
David	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
has	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
evidence	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
554	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
quarts	O
of	O
red	O
port	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Brannan	I-pers
,	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Brannan	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Owen	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
the	O
George	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
facing	I-place
the	I-place
dead	I-place
wall	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
notice	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
that	O
somebody	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
our	O
warehouse	O
;	O
while	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
neighbour	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
cocks	O
was	O
left	O
running	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
red	O
wine	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Spelman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
candle-light	O
and	O
day-light	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
safe	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l	O
had	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
into	O
a	O
corn-chandler	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
you	O
?	O
Spelman	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
accord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
bottle	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
:	O
(	O
producing	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
glass	O
bottle	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
two	O
other	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
full	O
of	O
red	O
port	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
a	O
light	O
place	O
?	O
Spelman	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
rails	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
is	O
very	O
open	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kenney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Spelman	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
billetted	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Godwin	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
spite	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
denied	O
me	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
for	O
denying	O
me	O
small-beer	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brannan	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
greater	O
guard	O
concerning	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
555	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bath	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
September	O
17	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
at	I-place
Old	I-place
Brentford	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
2	O
Bath	O
metal	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Still	O
at	O
New	O
Brentford	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
I	O
drive	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
tap-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
,	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Still	O
at	O
New	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
556	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
;	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
:	O
last	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
stood	O
by	O
my	O
bed-side	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
locked	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
lock	O
forced	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
The	O
Bolt	O
was	O
put	O
back	O
some	O
how	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
by	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
cutting	O
down	O
leaden	O
spouts	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
order	O
,	O
that	O
are	O
paving	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
advised	O
with	O
him	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
granted	O
me	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
Going	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
me	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
he	O
called	O
sister	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
other	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
stock	O
and	O
bits	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
:	O
he	O
delivered	O
up	O
his	O
tools	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
Sir	O
John	O
said	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
.	O
He	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
warrant	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
granted	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
sister	O
's	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
tool-box	O
he	O
took	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
in	O
tools	O
,	O
which	O
tools	O
he	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
18	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
opening	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
box	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
whether	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
people	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Holding	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
557	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
,	O
October	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
plate	O
for	O
the	O
poor	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Portuguese-chapel	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
chapel	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
gallery	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
Mount	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
steps	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
church	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
558	O
,	O
559	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Stannynought	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Squires	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gang's-man	O
,	O
at	O
Buttle-wharf	B-place
;	O
Stannynought	O
is	O
a	O
cooper	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
buildings	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
board	O
of	O
sugar	O
drawn	O
in	O
samples	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
King's-head	O
,	O
in	O
Love-lane	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
Warren	O
part	O
the	O
sugar	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
Warren	O
had	O
his	O
share	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
forced	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
before	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
letter	O
they	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Warren	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
;	O
directed	O
to	O
James	O
and	O
Squires	O
,	O
ascribing	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
to	O
drunkenness	O
,	O
and	O
begging	O
mercy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
a	O
gang's-man	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
wharf	O
,	O
being	O
with	O
Squires	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
.	O
Stannynought	O
's	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
inspecting	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
of	O
one	O
sort	O
.	O
Stannynought	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Warren	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
sugar	O
:	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Squires	O
and	O
Mr.	O
James	O
came	O
in	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
have	O
we	O
catched	O
you	O
?	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
what	O
?	O
in	O
taking	O
sugar	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
sugar	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Warren	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
waited	O
my	O
coming	O
out	O
:	O
this	O
sugar	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
wondered	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
suffer	O
the	O
law	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
can	O
swear	O
I	O
brought	O
any	O
sugar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
buildings	O
:	O
he	O
says	O
I	O
threw	O
my	O
share	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Squires	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Warren	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
Stannynought	O
carrying	O
a	O
board	O
of	O
sugar	O
?	O
Squires	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Stannynought	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hatt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
Winifred	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Comings	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Lucy	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Comberlidge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Warren	O
called	O
James	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
,	O
Dennis	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fullerton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
560	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
M'Cartney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
walking-canes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
eleven	O
other	O
walking-canes	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
;	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
home	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
walking-canes	O
from	O
India	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
reposited	O
in	O
a	O
warehouse	B-place
at	I-place
Blackwall	I-place
,	O
till	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
sale	O
came	O
on	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
lock	O
,	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
lock	O
upon	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
warehouse	O
was	O
after	O
that	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
some	O
canes	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
did	O
you	O
deposit	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
delivered	O
in	O
about	O
thirtyfive	O
thousand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wagg	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
porters	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
overseers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
private	O
trade	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
staples	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
holes	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
400	O
of	O
the	O
fine	O
walking-canes	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
marked	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
fifteen	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
mark	O
?	O
Wagg	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
letter	O
G.	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
cane	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
others	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
parcel	O
,	O
not	O
marked	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
'Change	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forset	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
cane-shop	O
,	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
I	O
acquainted	O
his	O
journeyman	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
were	O
brought	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
with	O
two	O
canes	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
twenty	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
word	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Horshoe	O
and	O
Magpye	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
canes	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
two	O
canes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
the	O
canes	O
at	O
any	O
rate	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
cane	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
ready	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
canes	O
and	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
canes	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
.	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
neither	O
he	O
nor	O
the	O
canes	O
should	O
go	O
back	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
24	O
canes	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
sister	O
kept	O
one	O
.	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
lodged	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Here	O
are	O
fifteen	O
of	O
them	O
have	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lumpers	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Blacks	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
's	O
wharf	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
these	O
canes	O
are	O
Captain	O
Cotton	B-pers
's	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
canes	O
that	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
canes	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shipwright	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
.	O
Captain	O
Cotton	B-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
Cox	O
and	O
Martin	O
(	O
two	O
other	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
)	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
the	O
Captain	O
they	O
should	O
attend	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
their	O
innocence	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
we	O
launched	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
hearing	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
were	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
knowing	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
things	O
these	O
are	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
have	O
warehouses	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
canes	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
watchmen	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
men	O
that	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
trusted	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
years	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Samvell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
farther	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
impeached	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
the	O
canes	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Luck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
a	O
well-behaved	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Luck	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
ever	O
man	O
bore	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
worth	O
almost	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
I	O
am	O
worth	O
,	O
set	O
aside	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
561	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Foulger	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
near	O
us	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Felton	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
seven	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
resign	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
about	O
a	O
pick-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bundle	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
ten	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gauze-weaver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
deal	O
in	O
handkerchiefs	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
:	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
562	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dowle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	I-place
above	I-place
the	I-place
'Change	I-place
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
picture-shop	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Decoster	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Decoster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
directly	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
Decoster	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
he	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
founder	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
picture	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
under	O
my	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
steps	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
gentleman	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fanstick-maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dowle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
blind	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
sold	O
gingerbread	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
this	O
twenty-eight	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
suppose	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
?	O
Dowle	O
.	O
Nature	O
binds	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
fault	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fish-woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
563	O
,	O
564	O
,	O
565	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Shadwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
86	O
pieces	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
cut	O
for	O
heels	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
53	O
pieces	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
cut	O
for	O
soles	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
his	O
son	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Daniel	B-pers
Waldron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	B-place
.	O
Shadwell	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
four	O
months	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
quantities	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
M'Cloud	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Ross	O
's	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
absent	O
ever	O
since	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
bound	O
over	O
?	O
Waldron	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
quantities	O
of	O
soles	O
and	O
top	O
leather	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ross	O
;	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
leather	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
their	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
bought	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Prince	O
,	O
in	O
Old	O
Bedlam	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
leather	O
secreted	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
,	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
;	O
they	O
work	O
below	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
chamber-masters	O
and	O
coblers	O
:	O
they	O
make	O
and	O
mend	O
shoes	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
parcel	O
of	O
leather	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
leather	O
?	O
Waldron	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
to-day	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
apprentice	O
neither	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
this	O
leather	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
top-pieces	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
handwriting	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
was	O
taxed	O
with	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
?	O
Waldron	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
said	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
boy	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
soles	O
that	O
have	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
made	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
when	O
Shadwell	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
this	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holder	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sign	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
freely	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Ross	O
's	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pieces	O
had	O
your	O
mark	O
?	O
Waldron	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
deal	O
in	O
leather	O
?	O
Waldron	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
cut	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
leather	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
two	O
Ross	O
's	O
deny	O
the	O
fact	O
?	O
Waldron	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
man	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
with	O
his	O
confession	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thing	O
not	O
desired	O
of	O
a	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
Shadwell	O
should	O
have	O
mercy	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
?	O
Waldron	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
nor	O
nobody	O
else	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holder	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
confession	O
of	O
Shadwell	O
's	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Alderman	O
Kite	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
signed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
sign	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
also	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Ross	O
's	O
were	O
asked	O
some	O
questions	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
alderman	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
that	O
would	O
clear	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
accuse	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
leather	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
connections	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
frequently	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
frequently	O
called	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
alderman	O
thought	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
's	O
confession	O
might	O
proceed	O
from	O
ignorance	O
,	O
so	O
gave	O
him	O
warning	O
.	O
The	O
confession	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
gives	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
some	O
top-pieces	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
several	O
quantities	O
,	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
fifty-three	O
for	O
soles	O
;	O
and	O
divers	O
top-pieces	O
,	O
not	O
less	O
than	O
an	O
hundred	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
they	O
living	O
and	O
working	O
together	O
:	O
that	O
some	O
were	O
delivered	O
when	O
one	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
said	O
leather	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
constantly	O
gave	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ross	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
fortnight	O
,	O
at	O
almost	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
leather	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Andrew	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
leather	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
there	O
below	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
several	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
above	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
concealed	O
any	O
where	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
of	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
William	O
lies	O
;	O
after	O
seeing	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
trunks	O
that	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
?	O
William	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Scotland	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
farther	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
warrant	O
expressed	O
to	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
are	O
you	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
any	O
magistrate	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
examination	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
enticed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
son	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
dissatisfied	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
thinking	O
I	O
was	O
against	O
doing	O
my	O
duty	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fludyer	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Andrew	O
's	O
wife	O
we	O
were	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
search	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
search	O
where	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
welcome	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
young	O
Ross	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
partly	O
undressed	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
)	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
procure	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
those	O
trunks	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
closet	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
wrenched	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
53	O
pair	O
of	O
soles	O
,	O
and	O
76	O
or	O
86	O
fore-pieces	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
put	O
your	O
things	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
the	O
shoe-making	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
followed	O
portering	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
shops	O
for	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
put	O
the	O
leather	O
into	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Wood-street-compter	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry-compter	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
examination	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Kite	O
:	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
began	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
faultering	O
in	O
his	O
speech	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
's	O
leather	O
,	O
only	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
William	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
leather	O
was	O
what	O
the	O
boy	O
brought	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
own	O
shoes	O
.	O
When	O
Shadwell	O
was	O
giving	O
the	O
account	O
,	O
Andrew	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
so	O
softly	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
magistrate	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
deny	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Potter	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Potter	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
first	O
having	O
communication	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
M'Cloud	O
was	O
called	O
on	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
His	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Shadwell	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
carry	O
work	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
by	O
Ross	O
's	O
stall	O
to	O
the	O
chief	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
pay	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
never	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
have	O
any	O
leather	O
but	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
leather	O
of	O
this	O
boy	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
make	O
soles	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
mend	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
gave	O
any	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
M'Cloud	O
has	O
done	O
all	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
.	O
William	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
falsity	O
in	O
saying	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
leather	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
brought	O
some	O
once	O
to	O
mend	O
his	O
own	O
shoes	O
.	O
For	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Shadwell	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Rooks	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
Ask	O
my	O
master	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Waldron	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
;	O
he	O
certainly	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
married	O
Shadwell	O
's	O
mother	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
careful	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
his	O
mother	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
bestowed	O
learning	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Ross	O
's	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fowell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
father	O
by	O
fight	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
son	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
soberly	O
and	O
honestly	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
bills	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
account	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
received	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
very	O
honestly	O
and	O
faithfully	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Fuller	O
and	O
Cope	O
,	O
bankers	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
and	O
shut	O
people	O
's	O
shops	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
William	O
the	O
son	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
exceedingly	O
good	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
and	O
pay	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
above	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
value	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Fuller	O
and	O
Cope	O
,	O
bankers	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
account	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
father	O
and	O
son	O
;	O
the	O
father	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
son	O
about	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
esteemed	O
them	O
both	O
as	O
honest	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
done	O
business	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
James	O
and	O
Jeffreys	O
,	O
brokers	O
in	O
'Change-Alley	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
father	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
tenant	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
son	O
from	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
so	O
has	O
the	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Eldridge	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surveyor	O
to	O
the	O
wharfingers	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Petoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
exceeding	O
good	O
characters	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
tenants	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
always	O
paid	O
their	O
rent	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
;	O
no	O
people	O
can	O
bear	O
better	O
characters	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
bear	O
good	O
characters	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stationer	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
post-office	O
,	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mackintosh	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
woollen	O
draper	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
father	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
son	O
from	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
exceeding	O
good	O
characters	O
:	O
was	O
any	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
one	O
would	O
give	O
either	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
exceeding	O
good	O
characters	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
people	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
setting	O
aside	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
warder	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
ward	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
upwards	O
of	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
very	O
faithful	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
employed	O
by	O
'Squire	O
Fuller	O
and	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
under	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
in	O
these	O
houses	O
in	O
my	O
absence	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taft	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
very	O
honest	O
men	O
both	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
persons	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
endeavouring	O
honest	O
men	O
both	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
father	O
twenty-four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
son	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
very	O
honest	O
characters	O
.	O
Shadwell	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Andrew	O
and	O
William	O
Ross	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
566	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
seals	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
||	O
At	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
sometimes	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
daughter	O
sometimes	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
always	O
;	O
I	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
company	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
mother	O
goes	O
out	O
a	O
nurse-keeping	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
again	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Seven	O
Stars	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
Nan	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
my	O
watch	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
:	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
fast	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
past	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Lemon-street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Harry	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
Nan	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
about	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
staid	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
perhaps	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
lain	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offer	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
publicly	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Davis	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Davis	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
Chapman	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
sit	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
arm-chair	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
chair	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
himself	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
doors	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
then	O
:	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
raised	O
my	O
head	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
dose	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rustle	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Chapman	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
my	O
candle	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
always	O
leave	O
a	O
good	O
fire	O
a-light	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
joke	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
my	O
Harry	O
's	O
watch	O
:	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
fright	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
Harry	O
's	O
watch	O
away	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
look	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
and	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
?	O
if	O
Harry	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fetched	O
some	O
anniseed	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
Davis	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
was	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
your	O
life	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
resolutely	O
bent	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
awake	O
Davis	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
murdered	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
nurse-keeping	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
my	O
windows	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
say	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Chapman	O
had	O
stole	O
Davis	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
Davis	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
Davis	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
escaped	O
with	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
Harry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Seven	O
Stars	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Nan	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
fellow	O
there	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
fellow	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
d	O
-	O
g	O
and	O
swearing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
than	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
anniseed	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
play	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
in	O
an	O
arm-chair	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
lie	O
down	O
and	O
rest	O
myself	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
come	O
and	O
lie	O
by	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
twelve	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Fortune	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Ann	O
Wright	O
from	O
a	O
baby	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Harry	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
so	O
stupified	O
with	O
drink	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
you	O
keep	O
such	O
bad	O
company	O
when	O
your	O
mother	O
is	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
wonder	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
killed	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Chapman	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
her	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
hussey	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
such	O
a	O
brazen	O
face	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
frighten	O
Chapman	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
wits	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Harry	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Chapman	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
after	O
it	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
has	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
so	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
in	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
six	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Nan	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
window	O
is	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
thing	O
uncommon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Harry	O
has	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
Chapman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
frighten	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Harry	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Magee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Davis	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
had	O
given	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
keeping	O
company	O
with	O
other	O
men	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mading	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Maclainer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
waterman	O
and	O
lighterman	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
industrious	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
567	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Ann	O
Fowler	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lemonere	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lemonere	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fighting	O
;	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
signs	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
understand	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
wash	O
my	O
shirts	O
for	O
threepence	O
each	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back-room	O
:	O
presently	O
came	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
hit	O
me	O
two	O
blows	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
soldier	O
ill-used	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
escaped	O
from	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
closely	O
pursued	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
;	O
a	O
watchman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
watch	O
might	O
be	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
very	O
strongly	O
having	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
soldier	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
soldier	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
keys	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
some	O
consideration	O
?	O
Lemonere	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
understand	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
flurry	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Hedge-Lane	O
;	O
a	O
watchman	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
woman	O
that	O
now	O
interprets	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
house	O
out	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
beadle	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
conducted	O
us	O
into	O
Swan	O
Yard	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
some	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
violent	O
raps	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
soldier	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
beat	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
examined	O
below	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
watch	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
there	O
stood	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
soldier	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
we	O
talked	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
night	O
I	O
ever	O
watched	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
discharge	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
soldier	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
or	O
third	O
drawer	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
discharged	O
the	O
soldier	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
and	O
thirsty	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
Tavern	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
gill	O
of	O
wine	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
tucking	O
my	O
gown	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
cushee	O
?	O
[	O
to	O
bed	O
]	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Star-Inn	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
drink	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
other	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
drink	O
any	O
spirituous	O
liquors	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
wine	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
the	O
waiter	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
pay	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
,	O
Nancy	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
go	O
home	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
and	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
stay	O
here	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
you	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
his	O
watch	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
hearing	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
put	O
us	O
both	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
together	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sociable	O
again	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
constable	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
soldier	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
soldier	O
owned	O
de	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
568	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Pinchin	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
iron	O
hammer	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
33	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
September	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
pease	O
and	O
beans	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
cart	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
Bow	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
drive	O
the	O
cart	O
home	O
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
fresh	O
sack	O
of	O
pease	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
sell	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
sleep	O
in	O
my	O
arm	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
my	O
husband	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
swore	O
by	O
his	O
eyes	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
pocket-apron	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
nurse	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
do	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
thirty-four	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
past	O
that	O
by	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carnon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
between	O
