TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1764	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
E.	O
DILLY	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIDGEN	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Perrott	I-pers
+	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Furman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lear	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hannam	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shackle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Loton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibart	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Lloyde	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gibart	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Godard	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rush	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
126	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Dennis	B-pers
O'Brien	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
cardinal	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
eleven	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hulme	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
February	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Hulme	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Fleet-street	B-place
towards	O
Temple-bar	O
;	O
betwixt	O
Crane-court	O
and	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
lad	O
rub	O
against	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
the	O
opposite	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Crane	O
court	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
under	O
a	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
strip	O
and	O
shew	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
followed	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
first	O
stopt	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
man	O
here	O
?	O
Hulme	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
turn	O
up	O
that	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
he	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
:	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cover-lid	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
plate	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Aris	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
Couchart	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
January	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
not	O
let	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
turnpike-keeper	O
,	O
at	O
Marybone	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
428.	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
Her	O
behaviour	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
on	O
her	O
former	O
trial	O
,	O
discovered	O
her	O
insanity	O
of	O
mind	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Governors	O
of	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
proper	O
object	O
of	O
that	O
charity	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
,	O
January	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
David	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catharines	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
house-carpenter	O
and	O
ship-joyner	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
sister	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
creature	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
privately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
to	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
but	O
19	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
bundle	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
back	O
window	O
broke	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
concluded	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
shoes	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
gown	O
,	O
cap	O
and	O
shift	O
,	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bedrey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
coloured	O
apron	O
,	O
pledged	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
wife	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
worsted	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Cleland	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Cleland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
at	O
Windmill-hill	B-place
,	I-place
Moor-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
curtain-rings	O
to	O
my	O
bed	O
rattle	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
curtain	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
substance	O
by	O
my	O
bedside	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
gold	O
rattle	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
iron	O
box	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
keep	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
lay	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
anybody	O
stir	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
move	O
(	O
I	O
burn	O
a	O
lamp	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
opening	O
,	O
the	O
dog	O
barked	O
below	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
called	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
purse	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
below	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
my	O
purse	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
drummer	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
quartered	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
since	O
Christmas	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
I	O
bewitched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
rob	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Comings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
She	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
:	O
when	O
my	O
mistress	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
her	O
purse	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
purse	O
from	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
dog	O
bark	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mastiff	O
dog	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Upon	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
crept	O
under	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
quartered	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
finding	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
lodging	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
at	O
all	O
I	O
lay	O
till	O
almost	O
day-light	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
dog	O
barked	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
servant	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
drum	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
131	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
January	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Matthew	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	B-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
then	O
picked	O
,	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
arm-in-arm	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
tap	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
when	O
near	O
the	O
Horn-Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
by	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pump	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
right	O
understanding	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
resolute	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
submit	O
quietly	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
pump	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pint	O
pewter	O
mugs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Best	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
pint	O
pewter	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bennit	I-pers
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
Alderwick	O
,	O
a	O
pewterer	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
three	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pots	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
stopt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
whose	O
names	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
pots	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pots	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bennit	I-pers
,	O
victuallers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
got	O
my	O
bread	O
honestly	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
pots	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
harm	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Connaway	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Maubart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gang-porters	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Porter's-key	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Dutton	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
lanthorn	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
above	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
capsen	O
rope	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
load	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
we	O
concluded	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
must	O
have	O
gone	O
down	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
knew	O
they	O
must	O
then	O
be	O
safe	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
vault	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
sugar	O
mentioned	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
alehouse	O
:	O
his	O
apron	O
was	O
all	O
daubed	O
with	O
sugar	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
this	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
land	O
some	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
sugar	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
dirt	O
and	O
tar	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
fish	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sugar	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
clear	O
from	O
dirt	O
or	O
tar	O
)	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
134	O
,	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sausages	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
September	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Isabella	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Aldgate-high-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
pork-shop	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
on	O
St.	O
Matthew	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
they	O
;	O
then	O
Dalton	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
Driver	O
:	O
Driver	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
paused	O
a	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
nothing	O
.	O
Dalton	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
disputed	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
then	O
Dalton	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
expected	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
clean	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
concluded	O
my	O
sausages	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Dalton	O
,	O
Good	O
woman	O
,	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
sausages	O
:	O
she	O
opened	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
sausages	O
of	O
yours	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
fell	O
to	O
beating	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
street	O
;	O
Driver	O
said	O
,	O
roll	O
the	O
old	O
bitch	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
there	O
that	O
prevented	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
farewell	O
women	O
,	O
farewell	O
sausages	O
:	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
notoriously	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
robbery	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
neither	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
own	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
136	O
,	O
137	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lot	B-pers
Lash	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
trunk	O
with	O
goods	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
repeating	O
watch	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
630	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
jewels	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
1020	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
upon	O
a	O
certain	O
key	O
,	O
adjacent	O
to	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
caused	O
to	O
be	O
loaded	O
on	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
three	O
cases	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
matted	O
trunks	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
trunks	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
trust	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
myself	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
got	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
key	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
our	O
waterman	O
which	O
we	O
employ	O
,	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
accompanied	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
trunks	O
and	O
cases	O
unloaded	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
safely	O
under	O
the	O
crane	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
merchants	O
use	O
for	O
shipping	O
goods	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
water-side	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
orders	O
care	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
waterman	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
ship	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
wait	O
a	O
little	O
:	O
the	O
thing	O
in	O
dispute	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
ships	O
we	O
should	O
ship	O
them	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
discharged	O
the	O
carman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Turpin	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
particular	O
directions	O
concerning	O
shipping	O
those	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
shipped	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Turpin	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
receipt	O
for	O
only	O
four	O
out	O
of	O
five	O
of	O
these	O
cases	O
.	O
The	O
ship	O
is	O
a	O
Spanish	O
ship	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
St.	O
Michael	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Turpin	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
trunk	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
it	O
was	O
wrong	O
shipped	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
anxious	O
of	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
richest	O
of	O
the	O
trunks	O
,	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
Heart	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crow-foot	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
divided	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
with	O
three	O
letters	O
,	O
J.	O
G.	O
C.	O
in	O
Roman	O
capitals	O
,	O
with	O
No	O
.	O
15.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
were	O
different	O
marks	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
flat	O
trunk	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
feet	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
22	O
inches	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
20	O
deep	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Turpin	O
upon	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
enquiry	O
we	O
could	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
shipping	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
must	O
produce	O
this	O
trunk	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
871	O
fans	O
,	O
value	O
164	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
trinkets	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
guineas	O
;	O
a	O
gold	O
repeating	O
watch	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
precious	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
630	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
toilet	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
l.	O
a	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
necklace	O
and	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
were	O
from	O
1000	O
to	O
1100	O
l.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
matted	O
and	O
corded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sealed	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
wax	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
matting	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
diligent	O
enquiry	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
could	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
to	O
the	O
custom-house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
parcels	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
by	O
themselves	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
crane	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
only	O
four	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
into	O
the	O
long	O
room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
Henson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
Henson	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
l.	O
He	O
is	O
sworn	O
.	O
Henson	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
pastry-cooks	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
the	O
custom-house	O
key	O
with	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
shipped	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
Errand	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Burr-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
clock	O
at	O
the	O
custom-house	O
key	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Brewer	O
's	O
key	O
I	O
saw	O
Lot	O
Lash	O
standing	O
under	O
the	O
crane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
flat	O
parcel	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
matted	O
and	O
corded	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
officers	O
would	O
seize	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
proceeded	O
on	O
my	O
other	O
Errand	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Tower	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
coming	O
along	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
describe	O
the	O
shape	O
or	O
size	O
of	O
that	O
parcel	O
?	O
Henson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
directly	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
heavy	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
over	O
Tower-wharf	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
what	O
purpose	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
farthest	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
wharf	O
he	O
turned	O
towards	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
of	O
my	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
recollect	O
this	O
?	O
Henson	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
warning	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
trunk	O
stolen	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Brewer	O
's	O
Key	O
?	O
Henson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
keys	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
key	O
,	O
towards	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Lot	O
Lash	O
before	O
?	O
Henson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Henson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Lot	O
Lash	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
James	B-pers
Charnieck	I-pers
,	O
Kennit	O
Dixon	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blakistons	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
138	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Livery	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
near	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
(	O
a	O
very	O
moon-light	O
night	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Grace-church	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
questions	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
room	O
enough	O
for	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
walk	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
keep	O
at	O
a	O
proper	O
distance	O
and	O
not	O
come	O
nigh	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
got	O
near	O
Lime-street	B-place
in	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
she	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
waist	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
mistook	O
my	O
way	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
catch	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
watch	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
almost	O
every	O
night	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
coming	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
charged	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
without	O
my	O
answering	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
stealing	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
am	O
looking	O
for	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
such	O
a	O
little	O
woman	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
15	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tryal	O
,	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
324	O
,	O
)	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
goods	O
stolen	O
by	O
Adwell	O
and	O
Madin	O
.	O
139	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Macdougall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
soles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
ten	O
wooden	O
lasts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Skene	I-pers
,	O
January	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
Finleson	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Skene	I-pers
is	O
now	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
assignees	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
leather	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
bankrupt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
soles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
bankrupt	O
says	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
bankrupt	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
information	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
leather	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Finleson	O
who	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
inward	O
sole	O
leather	O
,	O
fifteen	O
lasts	O
,	O
(	O
all	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
bankrupt	O
's	O
name	O
)	O
and	O
fifty	O
pair	O
of	O
soles	O
,	O
ten	O
dozen	O
welts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
parcels	O
of	O
leather	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
soles	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Marshman	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
out	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pair	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
bankrupt	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
method	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
worse	O
leather	O
at	O
the	O
leather-cutters	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
and	O
kept	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
soles	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
clicker	O
brought	O
the	O
lasts	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
Mr.	O
Skene	O
been	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
?	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
ever	O
since	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
few	O
shoes	O
out	O
among	O
the	O
workmen	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
carried	O
on	O
this	O
scene	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Levistone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
upwards	O
of	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
inward	O
sole	O
leather	O
found	O
,	O
fifteen	O
lasts	O
or	O
upwards	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
the	O
bankrupt	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
each	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
found	O
fifty	O
soles	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
dozen	O
of	O
Welts	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
worser	O
soles	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
bad	O
one	O
's	O
in	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Levistone	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
currier	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
of	O
Journeymen	O
doing	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
?	O
Levistone	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Finleson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
creditor	O
to	O
the	O
bankrupt	O
of	O
21	O
l.	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
think	O
this	O
prosecution	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
malice	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Skene	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
might	O
you	O
deliver	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
?	O
Skene	O
.	O
About	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
pair	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
Materials	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
out	O
lasts	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
lasts	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
were	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
army	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
were	O
customers	O
lasts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
kept	O
your	O
leather	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
worse	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
have	O
discovered	O
it	O
?	O
Skene	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
thinking	O
of	O
any	O
fault	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
creditor	O
under	O
the	O
commission	O
?	O
Skene	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
of	O
21	O
l.	O
I	O
borrowed	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
two	O
guineas	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
become	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
?	O
Skene	O
.	O
I	O
became	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
in	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
likely	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
?	O
Skene	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
pressed	O
me	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
security	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Skene	O
.	O
The	O
lasts	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
soles	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
the	O
cutting	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
cutting	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
my	O
leather	O
to	O
Scotland	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
welts	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
journeymen	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
home	O
their	O
lasts	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
soles	O
of	O
journeymen	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
leather-cutter	O
shops	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
out	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
140	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Howland	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
,	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
an	O
assistant	O
to	O
a	O
new	O
servant	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
:	O
Some	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
two	O
table-cloths	O
and	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
discharged	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
nine	O
weeks	O
;	O
not	O
on	O
any	O
suspicion	O
,	O
having	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
her	O
mother	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
for	O
her	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
cloaths	O
there	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
mother	O
inquiring	O
after	O
her	O
things	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
things	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
evidence	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
two	O
shirts	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Milbourne	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
shirt	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
table-cloths	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
the	O
shirts	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirts	O
and	O
tablecloths	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Abel	B-pers
Boykett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
pledged	O
those	O
shirts	O
and	O
table-cloths	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
141	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sowdon	I-pers
,	O
January	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Sowdon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Edward	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
apartment	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
among	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
petticoat	O
pawned	O
in	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
name	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
cleared	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
himself	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
some	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
142	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Comings	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
January	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Margaret	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Russel-court	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eleven	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
just	O
before	O
had	O
been	O
lying	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
A	O
little	O
girl	O
came	O
running	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
her	O
shop	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
in	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
window	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
take	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
ran	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
morning	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
gave	O
me	O
six	O
shillings	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
bear	O
my	O
expences	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
at	O
Kensington	O
and	O
drank	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
London	O
I	O
met	O
more	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merriday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
better	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
baker	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
143	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
post-chariot	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Traverse	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
February	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Bright	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stable	O
keeper	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Traverse	O
's	O
post-chariot	O
stood	O
in	O
my	O
coach-house	O
,	O
in	O
Curson-street	B-place
,	I-place
May-fair	I-place
;	O
the	O
two	O
side	O
glasses	O
were	O
stolen	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
coach-glass	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths-man	O
this	O
day	O
fortnight	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
frame	O
that	O
would	O
near	O
sit	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
for	O
half-a-crown	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
news-paper	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
read	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
glass	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
master	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Hay-hill	O
,	O
by	O
Brudenell	O
's	O
muse	O
:	O
After	O
dinner	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
forbid	O
him	O
coming	O
there	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
there	O
came	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
he	O
measured	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
evening	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
slip	O
from	O
us	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
glass	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Bright	O
Hemmings	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
just	O
the	O
size	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
144	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
flint-glass	O
,	O
called	O
cullet	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
warehouse	O
,	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
My	O
father	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
in	O
the	O
china	O
and	O
glass	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
men	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
hit	O
my	O
elbow	O
against	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
body	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
yearly	O
servant	O
in	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
)	O
to	O
porter	O
out	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
at	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
keep	O
our	O
cullet	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
broken	O
glass	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
other	O
servants	O
had	O
left	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hollo	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
I	O
,	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
an	O
old	O
shoe	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
your	O
candle	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
dropt	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
bin	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
int	O
o	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
position	O
;	O
and	O
opposite	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
stood	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
;	O
we	O
sell	O
it	O
at	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
sack	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
chalk	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
stuck	O
a	O
pin	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sack	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
hunted	O
about	O
for	O
the	O
sack	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
cellar-stairs	O
;	O
the	O
chalk	O
mark	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
part	O
rubbed	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
pin	O
remained	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
putting	O
that	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
us	O
221	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
cullet	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
declared	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
their	O
lives	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bin	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
stable	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
square	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
that	O
quantity	O
.	O
He	O
sold	O
us	O
three	O
parcels	O
more	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
December	O
:	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
our	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
sell	O
goods	O
in	O
your	O
warehouse	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
We	O
do	O
daily	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
shop	O
is	O
forwards	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
to	O
clean	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
finding	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
cullet	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
candle	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
candlestick	O
;	O
master	O
coming	O
and	O
finding	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
suspected	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
:	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
sack	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
that	O
:	O
What	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
for	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
to	O
tap	O
the	O
beer	O
just	O
before	O
supper	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
145	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
gown	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
inquiring	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
pawned	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sell	O
,	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
through	O
mistake	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
neither	O
has	O
she	O
one	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pledged	O
this	O
gown	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
146	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Coff	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
medals	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
crystal	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Holiland	I-pers
,	O
February	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Christopher	B-pers
Holiland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Half-moon	B-place
tavern	I-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stopt	O
my	O
porter	O
with	O
a	O
medal	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
ill	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
medals	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
association	O
of	O
Antigallicans	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
be	O
answerable	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
both	O
the	O
medals	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
medal	O
that	O
I	O
stopt	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
old	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
thing	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
16	O
or	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
became	O
broke	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
had	O
broke	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
first	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
false	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mitchel	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-and-gate	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
Mitchel	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
upon	O
farther	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
tavern	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
Mitchel	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
dancing	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
in	O
this	O
condition	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
medal	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holiland	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
over	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
trusted	O
these	O
medals	O
to	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
other	O
medal	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
he	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
For	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Holiland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
extreme	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
B	O
.	O
147	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Just	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Addle	B-place
hill	I-place
,	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
pocket-piece	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
familiar	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
declined	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
coming	O
in	O
with	O
what	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
what	O
spoiled	O
your	O
familiarity	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
spent	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
my	O
Brother	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
Esquire	O
Castle	O
in	O
Spring-gardens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
only	O
one	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
half-a-guinea	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
brass	O
piece	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
stript	O
off	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
cloaths	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
bed	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
till	O
10	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
her	O
half-a-guinea	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Rawlinson	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
148	O
,	O
149	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bunyard	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Price	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Harbin	O
Elderton	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Harbin	B-pers
Elderton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
February	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Harbin	O
Elderton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
and	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopgate-street	B-place
.	O
Yesterday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
thieves	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
(	O
we	O
suspected	O
some	O
fellows	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
)	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
look	O
,	O
being	O
within	O
a	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Bunyard	O
take	O
some	O
goods	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
candles	O
were	O
lighted	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
goods	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
apprentice	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
thieves	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
they	O
should	O
return	O
.	O
In	O
less	O
than	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
Bunyard	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
residue	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
move	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
:	O
he	O
ran	O
against	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
over	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
conveyed	O
the	O
goods	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
goods	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
man	O
running	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
glass	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
engraver	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Price	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
rails	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
together	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
Price	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
with	O
Bunyard	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
particularly	O
to	O
Bunyard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
Price	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
other	O
say	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
to	O
be	O
Bunyard	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Joe	O
?	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Elbone	I-pers
.	O
Yesterday	O
fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Bunyard	O
,	O
hallow	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
giving	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
a	O
thief	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
?	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
fall	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
stranger	O
.	O
Bunyard	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
gentleman	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
myself	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
ran	O
down	O
Spittal-square	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
,	O
High-Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
earn	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
meet	O
one	O
James	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
.	O
Bunyard	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Price	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Bunyard	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
366.	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
150	O
,	O
151	O
,	O
152	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Galliher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
salver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
apple	O
scoop	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
dessert	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
canvas-bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christian	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
Christain	O
Watts	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Staines	B-place
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
deaf	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
imagined	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
high	O
wind	O
had	O
thrown	O
down	O
the	O
bricks	O
of	O
my	O
chimney	O
:	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
sufficiently	O
fastened	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
tobed	O
.	O
I	O
lie	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
unscrewed	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
below	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
pockets	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
my	O
chamber	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
lock	O
and	O
bar	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
an	O
apple-scoop	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
pockets	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
to	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
locks	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
a	O
silver	O
salver	O
,	O
two	O
small	O
silver	O
dessert	O
forks	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
trifling	O
to	O
mention	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
damage	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Bolt	O
to	O
advertise	O
my	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
my	O
silver	O
salver	O
was	O
there	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
constables	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
salver	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
Sheffield	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
my	O
neighbour	O
Mr.	O
Hebbleswate	O
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
in	O
New-street	O
:	O
he	O
stept	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
that	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Peter	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
strip	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
required	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
very	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
family	O
piece	O
of	O
plate	O
of	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
he	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
that	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
thrown	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
riding	O
by	O
,	O
full	O
gallop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
(	O
some	O
where	O
at	O
or	O
near	O
Stains	O
)	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
buried	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
neighbours	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
hired	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
the	O
plate	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
12	O
o'clock	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Robin	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
to	O
mend	O
her	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glazier	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
on	O
the	O
stair-case	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
new	O
glass	O
in	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hebbleswate	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Robins	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
up	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
plate	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
inform	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
I	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
privately	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
me	O
a	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
him	O
any	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
salver	O
was	O
a	O
family-piece	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
constable	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bolt	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
what	O
condition	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
glazier	O
was	O
just	O
putting	O
in	O
a	O
quarey	O
;	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
is	O
produced	O
here	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
I	O
not	O
seeing	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
condition	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
)	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
leading	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
her	O
chamber	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
kitchen	O
poker	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
lying	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
rumaged	O
.	O
Several	O
boxes	O
were	O
broke	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
locks	O
lying	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
bed	O
on	O
a	O
bedstead	O
;	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
cupboards	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
till	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
some	O
hand-bills	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
order	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
buried	O
a	O
silver	O
salver	O
behind	O
a	O
hay-rick	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bannister	O
's	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
an	O
inn	O
at	O
Stains	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
Robins	O
lives	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
advised	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
the	O
ricks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Robins	O
lived	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
hole	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
fresh	O
dug	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
rick	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
Madam	O
Watts	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
her	O
salver	O
;	O
then	O
Robins	O
declared	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
on	O
the	O
cellar-door	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
water	O
was	O
so	O
deep	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
,	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
cherry-nursery	O
and	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
round	O
or	O
two	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
Galliher	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
unscrewed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
ladder	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
said	O
that	O
Galliher	O
and	O
Godfrey	B-pers
both	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
thumping	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
heard	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Turk's-Head	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
200	O
yards	O
distance	O
)	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
consulted	O
who	O
should	O
sell	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
pitched	O
upon	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
cleanest	O
dressed	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
small	O
plate	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
mentioned	O
,	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
,	O
in	O
Coventry-street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
applescoop	O
,	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
forks	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Galliher	I-pers
and	O
Robins	O
offered	O
her	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
gate	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
or	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
stands	O
upon	O
Hamptoncourt	O
road	O
,	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
any	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
Davis	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
Galliher	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
Godfrey	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
all	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
than	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Galliher	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
at	O
Egham	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
nor	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
Before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
Godfrey	O
said	O
,	O
another	O
person	O
was	O
concerned	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
swearing	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
set	O
him	O
at	O
liberty	O
Sir	O
John	O
would	O
have	O
admitted	O
her	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
evidence	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
Robin	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Jane	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Fanny	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Galliher	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
Charles	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
poor	O
and	O
pert	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
you	O
are	O
like	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
alike	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
and	O
rob	O
somebody	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
:	O
Who	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
?	O
that	O
old	O
D	O
-	O
l	O
,	O
Madam	O
Watts	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
besides	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
Robins	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Galliher	O
and	O
Godfrey	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Griffith	B-pers
Merridith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Aleppo	O
Gauls	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Maidwell	I-pers
,	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
154	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
Burchall	I-pers
.	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
Burchall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cutler	O
and	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
odd	O
things	O
:	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
29	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
earnest	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
quick	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
fronting	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
moment	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
running	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
through	O
several	O
streets	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
in	O
your	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
put	O
your	O
hand	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
this	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
sware	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
just	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
that	O
made	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
by	O
mistake	O
:	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
stock-buckle	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
agreed	O
for	O
?	O
Burchall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
stock-buckle	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea-tongs	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
at	O
half-a-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
then	O
I	O
wanted	O
three	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
he	O
weighed	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
came	O
to	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
came	O
to	O
twenty-nine	O
or	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
stock-buckle	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
earnest	O
;	O
business	O
interfereing	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
stockbuckle	O
,	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cheapen	O
any	O
stock-buckle	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
155	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
March	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carren	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Carren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
journey-work	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
among	O
my	O
customers	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
recollect	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
cupboard	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
twelve	O
guineas	O
which	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Manley	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
in	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
:	O
The	O
constable	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
directly	O
to	O
justice	O
Manley	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Step	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
presently	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
arose	O
from	O
his	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
adjacent	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
expose	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Ben	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
very	O
well	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
this	O
morning	O
of	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
creature	O
shall	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
There	O
;	O
It	O
is	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
untied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
four	O
guineas	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
necessity	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
His	O
landlady	O
threatened	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
bed	O
from	O
under	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
promised	O
not	O
to	O
expose	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
execute	O
my	O
warrant	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
left	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
interrupted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
confessed	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
begged	O
of	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
As	O
his	O
confession	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
forgiveness	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
156	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Denham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
Crimer	I-pers
,	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Crimer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Peter	O
Fink	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
lodge	O
there	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Milner	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Denham	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Milner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Mansfield-street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
these	O
buckles	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Fink	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sick	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
shoes	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
buckles	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
took	O
these	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pledge	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
workmates	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Fink	O
.	O
Is	O
her	O
husband	O
gone	O
away	O
?	O
Fink	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
glass-case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
almonds	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
January	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
158	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Dugdall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
,	O
January	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Hendrick	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
Black	I-place
horse	I-place
in	I-place
Shug-lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
up	O
but	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
his	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
also	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
chimney	O
corner	O
,	O
that	O
cost	O
16	O
s.	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
for	O
his	O
beer	O
:	O
That	O
very	O
day	O
sennight	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
kettle	O
by	O
his	O
telling	O
us	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
week	O
after	O
the	O
kettle	O
was	O
lost	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Wright	O
for	O
his	O
advice	O
;	O
he	O
granted	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
stiffly	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kettle	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Coming	O
down	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Coachmaker's-arms	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
desired	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
or	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
flatly	O
denied	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
him	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
will	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
past	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lidard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
there	O
:	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
him	O
down	O
Great	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Galley	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
something	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Galley	O
's	O
taproom	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
broker	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
kettle	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Rayment	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
morning	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
opening	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
;	O
my	O
Mrs.	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Half-a-crown	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
without	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
to	O
some	O
brokers	O
;	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
brother	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
wants	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
buy	O
it	O
I	O
'll	O
sell	O
it	O
you	O
cheap	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Half-a-crown	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
18	O
d.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
18	O
d.	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
for	O
Half	O
a-crown	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Spital-fields	O
market	O
upwards	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
pursued	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
I	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
had	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
cloak	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
never	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
cloak	O
of	O
a	O
stranger	O
for	O
9	O
d	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	O
:	O
We	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Castle	I-place
and	I-place
Falcon	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
it	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
lighted	O
up	O
candles	O
he	O
moved	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
near	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
hot	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
moved	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
seat	O
overagainst	O
the	O
fire	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
against	O
the	O
middle	O
seat	O
where	O
the	O
pots	O
lay	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
called	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
pots	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
writing	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
chalk	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
pots	O
that	O
were	O
here	O
?	O
I	O
touched	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
heavy	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
've	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
quart	O
pots	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
quart	O
pots	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
Here	O
are	O
our	O
names	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
among	O
more	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
some	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
possible	O
that	O
his	O
pockets	O
could	O
contain	O
two	O
quarts	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
pot	O
each	O
?	O
M.	O
Flood	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
his	O
coat	O
was	O
almost	O
all	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
company	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
M.	O
Flood	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
sitting	O
in	O
that	O
seat	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
161	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Hermitage-street	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
till	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
inches	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
leaned	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
concealed	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Eaton	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
,	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
ore	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
,	O
January	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wharfinger	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
pigs	O
or	O
cakes	O
of	O
copper	O
ore	O
from	O
Ralph	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
imported	O
from	O
Spain	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
60	O
,	O
from	O
200	O
weight	O
to	O
25	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pig	O
of	O
copper	O
ore	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
foolish	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
copper	O
ore	O
;	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
taking	O
so	O
much	O
away	O
,	O
being	O
told	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
pigs	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bring	O
the	O
pig	O
of	O
copper	O
ore	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
copper	O
ore	O
lay	O
;	O
the	O
gates	O
were	O
shut	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
about	O
dusk	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gateways	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
pigs	O
were	O
lying	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
in	O
