TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Over	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
MAY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1765	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEPHENSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Eardley	I-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gubbins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Buller	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Percival	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bardwell	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickles	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Barford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brazier	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Peele	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
.	O
+	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Mussen	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	O
Keene	O
.	O
292	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Fleece	I-place
and	I-place
Sun	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
Threadneedle-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
my	O
coal-merchant	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
tea-kettle	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
back	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lewin	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
kettle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
293	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
steel-mounted	O
sword	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Boland	I-pers
,	O
April	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Boland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
;	O
so	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Elder-street	B-place
Norton	I-place
Falgate	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
footman	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
New-prison	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
there	O
by	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
letter	O
:	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
chose	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
abroad	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Glass-house-street	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
sword	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
velvet	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Denison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths-man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
velvet	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
(	O
producing	O
another	O
piece	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
there	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Another	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
three	O
shirts	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
Christmas	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
three	O
shirts	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
:	O
the	O
velvet	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
a	O
pound	O
or	O
guinea	O
for	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
velvet	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
velvet	O
also	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
velvet	O
and	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
sword	O
as	O
this	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
for	O
his	O
health	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
and	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
boat	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Denison	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
Seeing	O
a	O
crest	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Denison	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
two	O
shirts	O
and	O
the	O
sword	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
money	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
through	O
necessity	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen's-square	O
,	O
Bartholomew	O
Close	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Long	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
a	O
millener	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
before	O
this	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Sharborn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Harmonworth	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
Colebrook	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
myself	O
,	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
children	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
back-side	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
plaister	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
near	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
,	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
cannisters	O
with	O
about	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
tea	O
in	O
each	O
cannister	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
in	O
Longford	O
,	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sawyer	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
I	O
found	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
cannisters	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
boot-legs	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
and	O
cannisters	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
one	O
by	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
rim	O
being	O
unsoldered	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Cranford	O
park	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
what	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
?	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
goods	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
receipt	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
cannisters	O
at	O
Staines	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
sugar	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
bill	O
left	O
behind	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
hole	O
was	O
broke	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
whose	O
property	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
here	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cannisters	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot-legs	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
Scotch	O
pedlar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
cloth	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
or	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
agree	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
pack	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
the	O
pedlar	O
's	O
writing	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
paper	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
for	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
of	O
my	O
tenant	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
295	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	I-pers
Spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Hinch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
smoothing	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Banbury-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hinch	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
she	O
says	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
King	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hinch	I-pers
:	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bed	O
looked	O
very	O
queer	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
blanket	O
,	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
bolster	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
returned	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
(	O
Two	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
bolster	O
,	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
again	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
drank	O
the	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
nothing	O
home	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hants	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
blanket	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
sheet	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
the	O
15th	O
;	O
the	O
bolster	O
the	O
26th	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
:	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
nam	O
'd	O
Ingham	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
with	O
things	O
as	O
from	O
her	O
mistress	O
:	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'ennight	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
nurse	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ingham	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
lame	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
miss	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
words	O
about	O
the	O
work	O
;	O
she	O
worked	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
in	O
the	O
making	O
of	O
soldiers	O
clothes	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
words	O
about	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
took	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
work	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
they	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
after	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
would	O
work	O
for	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
mistress	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
knew	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
sell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
soon	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
expected	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
abused	O
me	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
Ingham	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
She	O
knew	O
of	O
my	O
pawning	O
the	O
things	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
consented	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
quarrel	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
charged	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
owed	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
pawning	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
made	O
but	O
one	O
coat	O
for	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
296	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Monkhouse	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jane	I-pers
Murry	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Jane	O
Murry	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Eleanor	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
green-stall	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
owned	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
named	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
gone	O
backwards	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
bed	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
beds	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
and	O
Hutchinson	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Cotterell	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
almost	O
always	O
first	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
my	O
hand	O
over	O
my	O
eyes	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
lay	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
cloak	O
under	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
pillow	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
cloak	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
turn	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pin	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
:	O
Hutchinson	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
pinning	O
her	O
shift	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
at	O
her	O
:	O
then	O
Jane	O
Gray	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
cloak	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
my	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
eight-pence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
is	O
since	O
dead	O
and	O
baried	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
last	O
Thursday	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
backwards	O
for	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
's	O
cloak	O
lay	O
under	O
her	O
head	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sticking	O
a	O
pin	O
in	O
her	O
coats	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
's	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
pinning	O
her	O
shift	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
going	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
eight-pence	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
,	O
make	O
yourself	O
easy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
pawned	O
the	O
cloak	O
for	O
eight-pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
poor	O
woman	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
work-house	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
burying	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back-door	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
eight-pence	O
for	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
her	O
lodging	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
297	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Swede	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Tuns	I-place
in	I-place
Cable-Street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
sober	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
a	O
public	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
beer	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
overtook	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
speak	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
some	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
sleeves	O
,	O
some	O
pushed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
partly	O
frighting	O
me	O
,	O
got	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
some	O
room	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
almost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
.	O
They	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
staying	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
:	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
come	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
some	O
halfpence	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
another	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
all	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
getting	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
wanted	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
:	O
they	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
staying	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
fight	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
my	O
ship-mates	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pulling	O
me	O
about	O
for	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
God	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
wished	O
I	O
was	O
below	O
.	O
Presently	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
welcome	O
to	O
go	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
buckles	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
drink	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
without	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
help	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
saucy	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
my	O
cloaths	O
off	O
against	O
my	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
whom	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
with	O
three	O
women	O
,	O
two	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
took	O
your	O
buckles	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
most	O
liberty	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
:	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
this	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
women	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
her	O
that	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
borrow	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
offered	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Oliver	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
ale-house	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
night-house	O
,	O
where	O
hundreds	O
of	O
unfortunate	O
girls	O
resort	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
brandy	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
girls	O
which	O
he	O
liked	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
girls	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Elstone	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Elstone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grosvenor-square	B-place
:	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Lord	O
Fortescue	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walking	O
before	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
the	O
pantry	O
door	O
opens	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
had	O
called	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
down	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
that	O
person	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
do	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
that	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
laid	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
nights	O
;	O
he	O
once	O
owed	O
me	O
twenty-pence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
299	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Walter	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
three-penny	O
loaves	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
two-penny	O
loaves	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
,	O
Long-acre	O
:	O
my	O
man	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
bread	O
according	O
to	O
custom	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
basket	O
and	O
bread	O
were	O
stole	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
bread	O
advertised	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
go	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
advertisement	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
bread	O
were	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
bread	O
,	O
six	O
quarterns	O
,	O
three	O
three	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
two-penny	O
loaves	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bushey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
pitched	O
my	O
basket	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
window	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Fetter-lane	I-place
,	O
according	O
to	O
custom	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
bread	O
were	O
stole	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
two	O
notches	O
on	O
the	O
handle	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
bread	O
had	O
the	O
Roman	O
W	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
:	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
bread	O
are	O
here	O
now	O
:	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
bread	O
correspond	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
man	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
bread	O
;	O
he	O
soon	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
basket	O
was	O
gone	O
again	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
disguise	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
a	O
brother	O
baker	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chick-lane	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
baker	O
there	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
such	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
baker	O
that	O
has	O
almost	O
ruined	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
selling	O
bread	O
cheaper	O
than	O
the	O
standard	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pitch	O
a	O
basket	O
and	O
take	O
six	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
,	O
two	O
under	O
each	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
baker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
named	O
Becket	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
took	O
the	O
bread	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
the	O
baker	O
's	O
man	O
went	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
towards	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
owns	O
this	O
basket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
began	O
to	O
swear	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
:	O
we	O
never	O
got	O
back	O
the	O
six	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
but	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
400	O
baskets	O
lost	O
within	O
sixteen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
months	O
,	O
with	O
bread	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
accuse	O
me	O
wrongfully	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
them	O
that	O
live	O
at	O
Jerusalem	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
300	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Dennis	B-pers
M'Guire	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sherridon	I-pers
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Sherridon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
last	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Poppin's-alley	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milkman	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
customers	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	B-place
alehouse	I-place
;	O
there	O
he	O
borrowed	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
hauled	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
three-pence	O
half-penny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
other	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
capable	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
myself	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
workman	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
M'Guire	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
watch	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
home	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
you	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Blackistone	O
in	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
a	O
trial	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Blackistone	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
acquitted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
an	O
evidence	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
out	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
drunken	O
sit	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
laughed	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
intimate	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
twice	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
time	O
he	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Red-Lion-court	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
passing	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
deliver	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
your	O
assistance	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
demanded	O
for	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
Since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
confinement	O
he	O
has	O
sent	O
his	O
friends	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Richard	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
mention	O
would	O
satisfy	O
you	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
lent	O
money	O
came	O
to	O
8	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
expence	O
and	O
costs	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
and	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
that	O
money	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
law	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Charles	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
stuff	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
With	O
proviso	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
He	O
forced	O
it	O
away	O
without	O
my	O
inclination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Sherridon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pavior	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Poppin	O
's	O
alley	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
alley	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
M'Guire	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
M'Guire	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
about	O
?	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
watch	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
hearing	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
found	O
some	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
counted	O
fifteen-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
fearing	O
the	O
man	O
should	O
go	O
into	O
any	O
company	O
he	O
returned	O
him	O
them	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
Dailey	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
man	O
home	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
yourself	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
four	O
nights	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
supper	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
M'Guire	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
milkman	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
trial	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
that	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
return	O
the	O
man	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Sherridon	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
M'Guire	O
?	O
Dailey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
months	O
:	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Plumbtree-court	O
,	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
one	O
that	O
went	O
as	O
a	O
guard	O
with	O
Sherridon	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Dailey	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
trouble	O
?	O
Dailey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
farthing	O
;	O
I	O
borrowed	O
six-pence	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
got	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
and	O
silver	O
seal	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
they	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Sherridon	O
and	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
removed	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
,	O
in	O
Black	O
Horse	O
alley	O
;	O
he	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
cow-keeper	O
for	O
my	O
monthly	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
we	O
shook	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
I	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
paid	O
my	O
cow-keeper	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
;	O
she	O
demanded	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
catched	O
him	O
asleep	O
with	O
his	O
breeches	O
about	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
neither	O
stand	O
nor	O
go	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
watch	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
was	O
joking	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
owe	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
summons	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
answered	O
to	O
it	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Blackistone	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
acquitted	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
this	O
Dailey	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
served	O
with	O
another	O
summons	O
:	O
Dailey	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
for	O
milk	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Sherridon	O
never	O
owned	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
Dailey	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
:	O
since	O
that	O
Sherridon	O
swears	O
point	O
blank	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Dailey	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
speak	O
of	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
quite	O
drunk	O
;	O
M'Guire	O
was	O
pretty	O
sober	O
:	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
Sherridon	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
good	O
woman	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
your	O
husband	O
is	O
worth	O
a	O
watch	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
one	O
:	O
his	O
wife	O
abused	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
she	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
three	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Sherridon	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
watch	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Dailey	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
Dailey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
go	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
character	O
he	O
bears	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Sherridon	O
say	O
,	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
or	O
when	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Collin	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
telling	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
M'Guire	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mathematical	O
instrument	O
maker	O
;	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wyn	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milkman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
by	O
the	O
Temple-gate	O
,	O
White-friars	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sherridon	O
about	O
18	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
stain	O
his	O
character	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
credited	O
upon	O
oath	O
?	O
Moran	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
or	O
not	O
:	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
before	O
we	O
drank	O
it	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
:	O
and	O
nobody	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Sherridon	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
line	O
with	O
M'Guire	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
off	O
my	O
cloaths	O
and	O
be	O
searched	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
within	O
the	O
knee	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Moran	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Sherridon	O
;	O
I	O
drink	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
pity	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
to	O
trouble	O
and	O
expence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
M'Guire	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
trifle	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
account	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
:	O
but	O
M'Guire	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
my	O
proposal	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
perfect	O
charity	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
Leeson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drunken	O
frolick	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
M'Guire	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
milked	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
yard	O
for	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
anything	O
by	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lenard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
M'Guire	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
in	O
Ireland	O
and	O
England	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
careful	O
,	O
industrious	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
M'Guire	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milk-man	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
M'Guire	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Sherridon	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
really	O
believed	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
through	O
a	O
drunken	O
fit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
doubtful	O
whether	O
M'Guire	O
had	O
took	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
,	O
a	O
brewer	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Derham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
months	O
and	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
301	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
spatterdashes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
McPearson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
McPearson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Boot	I-place
on	I-place
Snow	I-place
Hill	I-place
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
:	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
long-quarter	O
'd	O
pumps	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Houscombe	O
trying	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spatterdashes	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
we	O
always	O
lay	O
a	O
pair	O
to	O
each	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spatterdashes	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
buck	O
's	O
horn	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
shoes	O
:	O
as	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
coat	O
the	O
spatterdashes	O
fell	O
down	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
hook	O
as	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
gentleman	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
hook	O
or	O
buck	O
horn	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Houscombe	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
spatterdashes	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
a	O
neat	O
fashion	O
;	O
having	O
an	O
occasion	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
bespoke	O
a	O
pair	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
brought	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
night	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
woman	O
:	O
I	O
tried	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
on	O
without	O
assistance	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
hinder	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
one	O
spatterdash	O
half	O
on	O
and	O
half	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
thinking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
trifling	O
customer	O
,	O
as	O
none	O
would	O
please	O
him	O
.	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
again	O
in	O
trying	O
the	O
spatterdash	O
on	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
woman	O
being	O
unhandy	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
on	O
.	O
Seeing	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
being	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
business	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
another	O
trial	O
:	O
then	O
her	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
half	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spatterdashes	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
husband	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
another	O
pair	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
his	O
answer	O
before	O
this	O
:	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
lad	O
,	O
Leave	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
.	O
She	O
turned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
has	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
:	O
he	O
threw	O
both	O
of	O
his	O
arms	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
spatterdash	O
that	O
turns	O
down	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
tan-colour	O
,	O
fall	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spatterdashes	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
.	O
I	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
accomplices	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
necessary	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
money	O
enough	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
two	O
six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
tin	O
bent	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
appear	O
like	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spatterdashes	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
chuse	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
after	O
you	O
have	O
tried	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
on	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
on	O
with	O
the	O
spatterdashes	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
more	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
proper	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
threw	O
my	O
arms	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
the	O
spatterdashes	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Houscombe	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
being	O
both	O
asked	O
again	O
,	O
declared	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
spatterdashes	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
fall	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Houscombe	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
hung	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Edward	B-pers
Bolter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Longstaff	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cosey	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Victoire	B-pers
Donvilla	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rickaby	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
French	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shelfe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
week	O
's	O
warning	O
;	O
she	O
only	O
staid	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
where	O
the	O
five	O
gowns	O
lay	O
,	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Rickaby	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
ready	O
done	O
up	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
missed	O
the	O
five	O
gowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
French	O
?	O
S.	O
Shelfe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
spoke	O
English	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
understand	O
her	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
the	O
morning	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
went	O
about	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
gowns	O
at	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
produced	O
five	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Shelfe	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Rickaby	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
parlour	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Rickaby	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Warwickshire	O
.	O
]	O
These	O
five	O
gowns	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
before	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
gowns	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Shelfe	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Frances	B-pers
Bolioe	I-pers
,	O
a	O
milliner	O
in	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
John	B-pers
L'Esperance	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Brumley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
303.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
sattin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Catherine	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Eagle-court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
petticoat	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
nail	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
absent	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Bell	O
in	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
liquor	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
(	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	O
steel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
gown	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
petticoat	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
named	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
kept	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
in	O
Eagle-court	O
;	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
one	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
better	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Cut	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
304.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
blank	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
clasps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Newport-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
workshop	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
above	O
;	O
she	O
knocked	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buttons	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
blank	O
seal	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
clasps	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
seal	O
to	O
shine	O
between	O
his	O
fingers	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
palm	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
broken	O
English	O
I	O
a	O
rogue	O
!	O
I	O
punish	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
a	O
rogue	O
;	O
and	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
be	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
305	O
,	O
306	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Kinnaston	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
bunches	O
of	O
mock	O
garnets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
mock	O
garnet	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
ear-ring	O
set	O
with	O
garnets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
bead-collars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ranale	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Ranale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
working	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
.	O
This	O
day	O
week	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
girls	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
things	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
home	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
a	O
single	O
halfpeny	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ranale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
wax	O
necklace	O
;	O
I	O
reached	O
some	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
shewing	O
them	O
to	O
Arthur	O
,	O
Kinnaston	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
drawer	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
mock-garnet	O
necklaces	O
lying	O
in	O
that	O
drawer	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
minutes	O
;	O
they	O
bought	O
nothing	O
:	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
looked	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
mock-garnet	O
necklace	O
which	O
Arthur	O
had	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
bead-collars	O
,	O
three	O
bunches	O
of	O
mock-garnets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
garnet	O
knob	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
three	O
drop	O
ear-ring	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
alley	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
William	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
our	O
boy	O
,	O
after	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Bunches	O
of	O
mock-garnets	O
all	O
dirty	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
.	O
and	O
but	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
intelligence	O
,	O
nor	O
him	O
that	O
met	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
mock-garnets	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Bringing	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
Kinnaston	O
made	O
a	O
sham	O
to	O
tie	O
up	O
her	O
garter	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
before	O
her	O
to	O
hide	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Kennaston	O
drop	O
something	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
foot	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
tuck	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
russles	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
these	O
bunches	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dirt	O
.	O
Arthur	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
necklace	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
ask	O
'd	O
fourteen	O
pence	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
Kinnaston	O
's	O
Defence	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
buckle	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Jewin-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
Midwife	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Kinnaston	O
form	O
an	O
infant	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
fifteen	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
307	O
,	O
308	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rosa	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abigal	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masset	I-pers
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cohan	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
last	O
assizes	O
at	O
Rygate	O
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cohan	I-pers
was	O
read	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Bird	O
and	O
Co	O
's	O
.	O
yard	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
ship-wrights	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
spoons	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Strange	O
,	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
in	O
Surry	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Regan	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cohan	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Horan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
steal	O
:	O
Cohan	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Masset	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Deptford	O
and	O
stole	O
some	O
stockings	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catherine's-court	I-place
,	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
the	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
stockings	O
.	O
First	O
we	O
met	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
mistress	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
out	O
a	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
word	O
her	O
mistress	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
but	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
but	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
that	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cohan	I-pers
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
stolen	O
goods	O
of	O
other	O
boys	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
times	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
her	O
daughter	O
about	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
was	O
Cohan	O
?	O
Regan	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
seventeen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
boys	O
had	O
some	O
spoons	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
but	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
stockings	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
these	O
boys	O
there	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
?	O
S.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
them	O
there	O
twice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gilham	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
these	O
spoons	O
:	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
any	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
our	O
meaning	O
in	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
went	O
to	O
searching	O
her	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
these	O
five	O
spoons	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
boy	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
yes	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
other	O
spoon	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
that	O
Regan	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
look	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
five	O
out	O
herself	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
boy	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
spoons	O
he	O
sold	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
backs	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
marks	O
had	O
been	O
filed	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
file	O
the	O
letters	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
information	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
boy	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
Regan	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
letters	O
T.	O
M.	O
E.	O
upon	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
spoons	O
inspected	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
jury	O
)	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
letter	O
T.	O
not	O
quite	O
filed	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
another	O
by	O
a	O
dent	O
in	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
bowl	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
before	O
.	O
Rosa	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
spoons	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
that	O
girl	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
sent	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
Good	O
Friday	O
,	O
this	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
me	O
cheap	O
:	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
five	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
thing	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
mentioned	O
the	O
spoons	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
five	O
,	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
spoons	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
old	O
silver	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Phebe	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
15	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
bread	O
by	O
captains	O
of	O
foreign	O
ships	O
;	O
Spanish	O
,	O
and	O
Portugal	O
captains	O
:	O
she	O
speaks	O
French	O
and	O
Spanish	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
with	O
boxes	O
of	O
hardware	O
;	O
she	O
maintained	O
herself	O
and	O
children	O
very	O
handsomely	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
309	O
,	O
310	O
,	O
311	O
,	O
312	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Gammon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Magennes	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
48	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
60	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Russia	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
gloves	O
,	O
3	O
worsted	O
caps	O
.	O
and	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
gause	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Short	I-pers
:	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Truby	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
16	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
48	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
56	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
gloves	O
,	O
3	O
worsted	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
gauze	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ablet	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
4	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
;	O
each	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
24	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
linen	O
and	O
haberdashery	O
way	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
shutters	O
were	O
shut	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
laying	O
ill	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
were	O
stolen	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
hand	O
bills	O
delivered	O
about	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
odd	O
stockings	O
in	O
Field	O
lane	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Norfolk	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
lawn	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
23	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
two	O
parcels	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Brown	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
by	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
also	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Wilder	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gammon	I-pers
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Magennes	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Gammon	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eleven	O
months	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Penyman	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
sadler	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
errand	O
boy	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Gammon	O
in	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
church-yard	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
18	O
:	O
Magennes	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
skittles	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
dusk	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
came	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
,	O
down	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Magennes	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
Gammon	O
stood	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
Magennes	O
once	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
behind	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
tember	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
Magennes	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
Gammon	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
near	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
street	O
;	O
but	O
Gammon	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
timber	O
again	O
;	O
Magennes	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Magennes	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
pitcher	O
never	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
well	O
so	O
often	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
comes	O
home	O
broke	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
Gammon	O
watching	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
each	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Holmes	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Russia	O
cloth	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
four	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
linen	O
ones	O
,	O
about	O
50	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
or	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
childrens	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
all	O
there	O
were	O
60	O
pair	O
;	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
plain	O
lawn	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
three	O
other	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
caps	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
figured	O
gauzes	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
buys	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Monmouth-street	O
and	O
Rag-fair	O
:	O
it	O
might	O
want	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
10	O
o'clock	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
:	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
for	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
small	O
children	O
's	O
pocket	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
for	O
her	O
maid	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
ribb	O
'd	O
,	O
four	O
thread	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
crimson	O
coloured	O
:	O
we	O
left	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
others	O
that	O
had	O
employed	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
more	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
:	O
Magennes	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Wilder	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Black	O
Boy-alley	O
:	O
Gammon	O
lived	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
directly	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Wilder	O
was	O
suspicious	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Wilder	O
there	O
were	O
constables	O
about	O
near	O
her	O
lodging	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
searched	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
constables	O
had	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
thieves	O
lived	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
and	O
Magennes	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Wilder	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
search	O
about	O
here	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
wheel	O
barrow	O
,	O
and	O
wheeled	O
it	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
dunghill	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
two	O
other	O
barrows	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
search	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
then	O
sold	O
Holmes	O
a	O
few	O
stockings	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
for	O
another	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
trusted	O
to	O
her	O
honour	O
:	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
we	O
wheeled	O
the	O
barrow	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lawn	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
six	O
small	O
pieces	O
and	O
some	O
gauze	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
lawn	O
but	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Norfolk	O
had	O
:	O
after	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
16	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
8	O
s.	O
Mrs.	O
Wilder	O
saw	O
her	O
buy	O
all	O
these	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
we	O
disposed	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
that	O
are	O
produced	O
here	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
met	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
St.	O
Giles	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
us	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
we	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
things	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
if	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
schoolmaster	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
safe	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
washed	O
,	O
ironed	O
,	O
and	O
hemmed	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Wilder	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
stay	O
at	O
her	O
apartment	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
gauze	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
caps	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
she	O
would	O
throw	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Norfolk	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
leave	O
them	O
there	O
till	O
night	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
gave	O
them	O
us	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
Gammon	O
's	O
:	O
Gammon	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
out	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
:	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
her	O
bed	O
and	O
sowed	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
,	O
at	O
Black	O
Friars	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
lodging	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Hounds	O
,	O
in	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
half-and-half	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Then	O
Ablet	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
were	O
after	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
named	O
Jenny	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
;	O
we	O
all	O
ran	O
down	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
Magennes	O
and	O
Gammon	O
staid	O
in	O
Union-court	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
and	O
salmon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
Jenny	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
for	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
16	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
16	O
s.	O
also	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
us	O
the	O
other	O
8	O
s.	O
she	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
under	O
pretence	O
they	O
were	O
foul	O
linen	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
blind	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
us	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
Union-court	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
us	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
to	O
keep	O
from	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
fearing	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
again	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
Saturday	O
night	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Magennes	O
and	O
Gammon	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
fearing	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
afraid	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
it	O
all	O
upon	O
myself	O
,	O
let	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
do	O
what	O
he	O
will	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
milk-man	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
some	O
milk	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
shook	O
hands	O
and	O
parted	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
:	O
then	O
Ablet	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
thing	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
denied	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
first	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
to-morrow	O
;	O
he	O
trusted	O
to	O
my	O
honour	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
want	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
Magennes	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
evidence	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
admitted	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Ablet	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
that	O
keeps	O
me	O
without	O
business	O
:	O
Magennes	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
Parker	O
and	O
Gammon	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
;	O
Gammon	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
leave	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
Magennes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Hounds	O
in	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Magennes	O
,	O
Parker	O
,	O
and	O
Gammon	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
wait	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
by	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Hounds	O
along	O
with	O
Ablet	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
seeing	O
some	O
of	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
send	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
about	O
the	O
hand	O
bills	O
being	O
given	O
about	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
word	O
where	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
:	O
Ablet	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Frick	I-pers
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
:	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
Ablet	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
down	O
Holbourn	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
:	O
We	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
;	O
there	O
Ablet	O
cut	O
off	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
each	O
piece	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
met	O
Parker	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
in	O
Union-court	O
;	O
Parker	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Magennes	O
and	O
Gammon	O
waiting	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Magennes	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
Magennes	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
mind	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
shirt	O
and	O
stockings	O
clean	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
should	O
not	O
suspect	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
pay	O
Parker	B-pers
some	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
;	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
what	O
;	O
her	O
maid	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Porter	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Parker	O
,	O
Gammon	O
,	O
and	O
Holmes	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
also	O
seen	O
Jane	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
drinking	O
there	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
other	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Ablet	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
particular	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dupree	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Gammon	O
but	O
once	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
:	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
either	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
or	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
this	O
week	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
money	O
she	O
might	O
get	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
things	O
cheap	O
:	O
Magennes	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
things	O
opened	O
;	O
cotton	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
quantity	O
there	O
was	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
wear	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ask	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Dupree	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pay	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
also	O
gave	O
six-pence	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
two	O
small	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
Parker	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
left	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
lie	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
fearing	O
the	O
house	O
should	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
stay	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
purple	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
little	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
apartment	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
where	O
Parker	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
Mrs.	O
Holmes	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
to	O
where	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
Gardens	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
brought	O
me	O
under	O
an	O
obligation	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
speak	O
one	O
word	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
goods	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
hanging	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
promise	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
:	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Norfolk	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Parker	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
life	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
;	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
manage	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
proper	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Brewick-street	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
and	O
repass	O
'd	O
my	O
cellar	O
with	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
lying	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
resembling	O
these	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
one	O
's	O
here	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
in	O
their	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
or	O
a	O
woman	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
so	O
little	O
notice	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Goldsborough	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
in	O
Union-court	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
Jane	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
;	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
salmon	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
about	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
half-and-half	O
:	O
they	O
swore	O
so	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
