TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
II	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1765	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
duffil	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Juckson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Juckson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
cloaks	O
,	O
and	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	B-place
Cloysters	I-place
,	I-place
West-Smithfield	I-place
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Purple-Lane	O
,	O
stopt	O
the	O
cloak	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
here	O
is	O
an	O
evidence	O
that	O
can	O
.	O
John	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
cloak	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
read	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
stopt	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
this	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waklin	I-pers
.	O
(	O
She	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
cloak	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Juckson	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
several	O
days	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
West	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
this	O
yong	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Hussey	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
cardinal	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
Hussey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
saw	O
this	O
lie	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Allwin	I-pers
,	O
January	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Allwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bexley	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Kent	I-place
;	O
last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
the	B-place
common	I-place
:	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
fettered	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
mare	O
:	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
mare	O
and	O
the	O
fetter	O
on	O
the	O
horse	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
fetter	O
to	O
her	O
leg	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
used	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
not	O
been	O
incumbered	O
:	O
we	O
could	O
track	O
the	O
horse	O
down	O
a	O
lane	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
at	O
New-Cross	O
turnpike	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
horse	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
through	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
my	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
horse	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
George-yard	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
eight	O
pounds	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Get	O
down	O
,	O
friend	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
sleeve	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
stole	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
bought	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Allwin	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
known	O
in	O
my	O
country	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
thrashing	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
horse	O
last	O
?	O
Allwin	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
him	O
.	O
Allwin	O
.	O
A	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
,	O
three	O
white	O
feet	O
,	O
a	O
swelling	O
on	O
the	O
withers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
saddle-spot	O
on	O
the	O
off-side	O
:	O
I	O
bred	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
foal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Bexley-Common	O
from	O
London	O
?	O
Allwin	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
eleven	O
miles	O
from	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Allwin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
gelding	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
:	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
gelding	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
eight	O
guineas	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
gelding	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
swapped	O
a	O
little	O
poney	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
that	O
morning	O
:	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
at	O
what	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
at	O
Queenhithe	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
sometimes	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
foal	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
horse	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
:	O
I	O
seeing	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
this	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
swap	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
horse	O
and	O
mine	O
were	O
both	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
there	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Margaret's-hill	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
tail	O
being	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
mine	O
for	O
the	O
gelding	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
lain	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen's-head	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
horse	O
was	O
there	O
also	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
changed	O
with	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Epsom	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen's-head	O
sent	O
for	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Court	O
pleases	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
John	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
other	O
name	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Tison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen's-head	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Tison	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
sight	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
nights	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Tison	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
days	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
justly	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Tison	O
.	O
A	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
;	O
a	O
star	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
between	O
a	O
black	O
and	O
a	O
brown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
?	O
Tison	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
high	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
call	O
that	O
a	O
poney	O
?	O
Tison	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
above	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
poney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Tison	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
rightly	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
above	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
last	O
Thursday	O
?	O
Tison	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
last	O
Thursday	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
'till	O
this	O
moment	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
94	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
,	O
November	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
Christopher	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
name	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
sit	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
ring	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
ring	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
ring	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
three	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
ring	O
on	O
the	O
stair-head	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
in	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
cloak	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
shoulders	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
ring	O
from	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Pray	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
character	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
95	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
December	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forrester	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
our	O
stable	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bull-and-Gate	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
:	O
the	O
things	O
missing	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
there	O
safe	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
advertised	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wadley	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wadley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
:	O
I	O
seeing	O
they	O
were	O
livery	O
cloaths	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
:	O
that	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
a	O
livery	O
servant	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fleetwood	O
,	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
red	O
shag	O
breeches	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
bring	O
me	O
some	O
body	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
hesitate	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
my	O
brother	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
room	O
to	O
suspect	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
advertised	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Forrester	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
those	O
cloaths	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
96	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
yards	O
of	O
stuff-gartering	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
January	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
shop	O
:	O
coming	O
home	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
before	O
lost	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
I	O
passed	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
convenient	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
observe	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
another	O
fellow	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
stood	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
gartering	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
on	O
board	O
an	O
East-Indiaman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
97	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Moses	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
December	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Crow	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
:	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crow	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
98	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
stuff	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cosoy	O
seat	O
to	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dunnavan	I-pers
,	O
December	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
Jerrard	O
Bourn	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dunnavan	I-pers
are	O
chairmen	O
,	O
and	O
partners	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out-of	O
our	O
chair	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
inn-lane	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
curtains	O
and	O
seat	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
found	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
six-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
99	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
sattin	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Hannah	B-pers
Waites	I-pers
.	O
My	O
name	O
was	O
Hall	O
:	O
I	O
married	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
in	O
Field-lane	B-place
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
not	O
glaz	O
'd	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
line	O
break	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
cap	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
candle	O
at	O
my	O
neighbour	O
's	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
ribbon	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
cap	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
white	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
something	O
glittered	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
cap	O
and	O
ribbon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
examining	O
them	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
line	O
break	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Isaac	B-pers
Stoddard	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Studderd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
buckles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
December	O
29	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
John	O
Miller	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
last	O
Christmas-day	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
my	O
trade	O
,	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
master	O
turned	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
:	O
his	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
101	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Amelia	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
six	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
china	O
punch-bowl	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
two	O
ells	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
feathers	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Guy	B-pers
Winnick	I-pers
,	O
November	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Winnick	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Guy	B-pers
Winnick	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Sun	B-place
Tavern	I-place
fields	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
china	O
,	O
and	O
feathers	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shirt	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Pearce	B-pers
Money	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
stone	O
jars	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
quart	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
quart	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pearce	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
Pearce	B-pers
Money	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
:	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
house	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Money	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
jars	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
pales	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Money	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Money	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Atoway	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
January	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
perriwig-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
near	O
Fenchurch-street	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
relation	O
's	O
:	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bunhill-row	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Atoway	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
persons	O
singing	O
:	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
a	O
knack	O
of	O
trundling	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
almost	O
one	O
o'clock	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
offered	O
their	O
service	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
by	O
Fenchurch	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Filpot-lane	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
uncle	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
walked	O
down	O
Bunhill-row	O
,	O
talking	O
about	O
this	O
knack	O
of	O
the	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chiswell-street	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
which	O
opens	O
into	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
turned	O
and	O
gone	O
by	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
to	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
safe	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
talking	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
walk	O
;	O
when	O
,	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
most	O
violent	O
motion	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lay	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
drew	O
my	O
watch	O
(	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
which	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
hat	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
no	O
creature	O
was	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
them	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
that	O
alehouse	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
landlord	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
knew	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
By	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
by	O
Old-street-square	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
likewise	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Angler	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Old-street-square	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
security	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
heard	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
On	O
taking	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
warrant	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
Sunday	O
,	O
after	O
church	O
time	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
Puddle-dock-hill	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bruiser	O
:	O
there	O
they	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
cord	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
or	O
hat	O
again	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
identical	O
person	O
that	O
knocked	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
learned	O
since	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Francis	B-pers
Atoway	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
alehouse	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Filpot-lane	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
going	O
along	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
gentleman	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
go	O
cross	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
danger	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
and	O
hit	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
towards	O
Chiswell	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
acted	O
in	O
any	O
case	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
or	O
hear	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
speak	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
creature	O
near	O
us	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
suddenly	O
knocked	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
about	O
?	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
murder	O
;	O
they	O
held	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
beat	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walsham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
coach-harness-maker	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Walsham	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
gause-weaver	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
to	O
maintain	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
lived	O
this	O
last	O
twelvemonth	O
?	O
Walsham	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
same	O
public-house	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Walsham	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
?	O
Walsingham	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
a	O
good	O
or	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
?	O
Walsingham	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
robbing	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Theircher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
December	O
26	O
,	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Theircher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Theircher	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
David	B-place
(	I-place
Dove	I-place
)	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Berkley-square	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
perfumer	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
no	O
customer	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
till	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
shut	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
?	O
Theircher	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
shut	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
turning	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
from	O
towards	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
till	O
drawer	O
pulled	O
quite	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
my	O
till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Theircher	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
robbed	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
another	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
another	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Theircher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
before	O
?	O
Theircher	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
shop	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Theircher	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Micah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mrs.	O
Theircher	O
of	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
One	O
there	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
that	O
out	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
likewise	O
;	O
that	O
also	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
young	O
fellows	O
followed	O
the	O
coach	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suspected	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
impeach	O
his	O
gang	O
:	O
he	O
owned	O
there	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
followed	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
named	O
Dragon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Downs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
care	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
people	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
About	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
court-yard	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
that	O
money	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
fact	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
baise	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
two	O
laced	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
plain	O
caps	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
December	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Margaret	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bluecoat-boy	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
in	I-place
Duck-lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
:	O
some	O
I	O
missed	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
from	O
other	O
rooms	O
:	O
my	O
own	O
daughter	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
was	O
missing	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
your	O
daughter	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Upon	O
advertising	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
child	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
cap	O
on	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
as	O
willing	O
as	O
she	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
threw	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
herself	O
from	O
a	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
some	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Fosset	O
's	O
;	O
some	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
George-yard	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
;	O
some	O
at	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Slee	I-pers
's	O
,	O
Cox's-square	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
very	O
near	O
all	O
my	O
goods	O
again	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
directions	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Slee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cox's-square	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
two	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
George-yard	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
pledged	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
:	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Newman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pledged	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Box-tree	O
,	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
worth	O
my	O
while	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
serve	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
of	O
her	O
also	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
produced	O
here	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Newman	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
by	O
robbing	O
her	O
mother	O
;	O
her	O
father-in-law	O
having	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
ill	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
box	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
grandmother	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine-cooper	O
,	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
:	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
girl	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
master	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
left	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
service	O
?	O
Willson	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
virtuous	O
girl	O
then	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
her	O
lately	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
106	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miln	I-pers
,	O
January	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Miln	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Moor-fields	I-place
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
livery-stable	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
this	O
day	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
house	O
that	O
we	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
fort	O
of	O
a	O
counting-house	O
:	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
assistance	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
owed	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
cloaths	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
hanging	O
.	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
partly	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Miln	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
cloaths	O
and	O
bag	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
cloaths	O
or	O
b	O
ag	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
moon	O
.	O
I	O
owed	O
a	O
man	O
23	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
writ	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Chequers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
chastised	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
is	O
this	O
little	O
room	O
to	O
the	O
outward	O
gate	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
January	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Worlings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Bear	I-place
and	I-place
Raged-staff	I-place
inn	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
told	O
me	O
his	O
saddle	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
ostler	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
saddle	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
my	O
ostler	O
,	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
saddle	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
,	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
saddle	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
saddle	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
for	O
this	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged-staff	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
this	O
saddle	O
and	O
saddle-cloth	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Real	O
necessity	O
drove	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
crown	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
without	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
her	O
cardinal	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
saddle	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
finding	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
prosecute	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
lived	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ten	O
shillings	O
back	O
this	O
day	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
had	O
been	O
owned	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
this	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
family	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
family	O
he	O
has	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
108	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
salmon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Grinoway	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
December	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Grinoway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
fish-shop	O
;	O
the	O
salmon	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Manlove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
fresh	O
salmon	O
lay	O
upon	O
a	O
board	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
somebody	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
salmon	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
salmon	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
our	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
salmon	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Cheshire	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
salmon	O
weighed	O
about	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
head	O
part	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
tail	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
salmon	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
?	O
A.	O
Manlove	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
above	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Seven-Stars	O
,	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
Tower-street	O
:	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
just	O
opposite	O
the	O
Hamborough	O
Coffee-house	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
but	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
just	O
at	O
his	O
heels	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
salmon	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
thoughts	O
of	O
the	O
salmon	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
young	O
fellows	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
up	O
Thames-street	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mittens	O
on	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
smelt	O
at	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
smell	O
of	O
salmon	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
A.	O
Manlove	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
smell	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hands	O
?	O
A.	O
Manlove	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
smell	O
of	O
salmon	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
salmon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
back	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sight	O
'till	O
taken	O
?	O
A.	O
Manlove	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
salmon	O
fall	O
,	O
'then	O
he	O
ran	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
turning	O
?	O
A.	O
Manlove	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
109	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
puporting	O
to	O
bear	O
date	O
at	O
Hull	O
,	O
September	O
15	O
,	O
1764	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
drawn	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
merchants	O
and	O
partners	O
;	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Rumbolt	O
and	O
Walker	O
,	O
merchants	O
,	O
in	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
to	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
;	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
falsely	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
to	O
defraud	O
Messrs.	O
Thorleys	O
and	O
King	O
,	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
come	O
from	O
Nottingham	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
manufacturing	O
ware-house	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two-necks	O
,	O
Land-lane	O
:	O
my	O
servant	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
September	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
ordinary	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
:	O
after	O
the	O
ordinary	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
lend	O
a	O
gentleman	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
collect	O
some	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
stay	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
rained	O
hard	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
warehouse	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
washing	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
talking	O
you	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
40	O
l.	O
draught	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Dover	O
coach	O
comes	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
might	O
do	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Dover	O
coach	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
draught	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
Dover	O
coach	O
inn	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
inns	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two-necks	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
draught	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
indorsed	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
my	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
indorse	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
desk	O
and	O
indorsed	O
it	O
;	O
both	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Northage	I-pers
:	O
upon	O
examining	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
from	O
Hull	O
,	O
by	O
Messrs.	O
Thorleys	O
and	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
Rumbolt	O
and	O
Walker	O
,	O
of	O
Liverpool	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
upon	O
London	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
want	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
way	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
stocking	O
way	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
Sir	O
Wynn	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Golitteley	O
,	O
both	O
from	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
bill	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
Sir	O
Wynn	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
if	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
convenient	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
lodged	O
all	O
their	O
money	O
at	O
bankers	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
drew	O
upon	O
when	O
it	O
became	O
due	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hanford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
connections	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
it	O
for	O
acceptance	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
cash	O
;	O
I	O
concluded	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
little	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
suppose	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
accepted	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
accepted	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
proposed	O
giving	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hanford	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
an	O
utter	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Hull	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
Wrights	O
of	O
Nottingham	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
gentlemen	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
;	O
he	O
clap	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
fresh	O
air	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
forged	O
several	O
bills	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
this	O
bill	O
:	O
he	O
looked	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forged	O
bill	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
Liverpool	O
:	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
to	O
present	O
to	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
answer	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
Hull	O
,	O
September	O
15	O
,	O
1764	O
,	O
at	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
``	O
pay	O
this	O
first	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
order	O
``	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
``	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
in	O
freight	O
;	O
which	O
place	O
to	O
``	O
account	O
of	O
,	O
``	O
Yours	O
,	O
Thorsleys	O
and	O
King	O
.	O
``	O
To	O
Messrs.	O
Rumbolt	O
and	O
Walker	O
,	O
merchants	O
in	O
Liverpool	O
.	O
''	O
No	O
.	O
538.	O
William	B-pers
Northage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
indorse	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Northage	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
:	O
he	O
indorsed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two-necks	O
,	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
he	O
first	O
wrote	O
James	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
wrote	O
Holmes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hull	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
;	O
they	O
are	O
merchants	O
and	O
partners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
all	O
their	O
hand-writings	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
particularly	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
all	O
write	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
they	O
keep	O
any	O
clerk	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
)	O
whose	O
hand-writing	O
is	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
neither	O
of	O
their	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
names	O
Thorleys	O
and	O
King	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
these	O
names	O
are	O
not	O
their	O
hand-writing	O
:	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
in	O
partnership	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
upon	O
him	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
of	O
these	O
checks	O
*	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
and	O
two	O
bills	O
ready	O
filled	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
:	O
I	O
seeing	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two-necks	O
,	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
to	O
understand	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
*	O
Note	O
,	O
A	O
check	O
is	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
draught	O
,	O
marbled	O
or	O
flourished	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
totally	O
with	O
the	O
book	O
it	O
is	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
that	O
bill	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
or	O
saw	O
the	O
bill	O
:	O
if	O
Messrs.	O
Thorleys	O
and	O
King	O
were	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
their	O
hand-writing	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3.	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions-Paper	O
.	O
110	O
,	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hockley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridstone	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
thirteen	O
deal	O
boards	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Dingley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jeffrey	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
December	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Osboldiston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Dingley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
deals	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Dingley	O
?	O
Osboldeston	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
merchant	O
;	O
the	O
deals	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
barges	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
care	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
in	O
marking	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
chalked	O
them	O
all	O
a-cross	O
the	O
boards	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
barges	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
thirteen	O
deal	O
boards	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Osboldeston	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
worth	O
28	O
s.	O
as	O
we	O
sell	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Osboldeston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
some	O
timber	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
Hockley	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
bring	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
barge	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pursue	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
Hockley	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Jeffrey	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Jeffrey	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
chalk-marks	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Jeffrey	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Dingley	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hockley	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridstone	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Hockley	O
confess	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
deals	O
from	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Jeffrey	B-pers
the	O
sawyer	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
the	O
lighter	O
lay	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
lay	O
just	O
by	O
Limehouse-bridge	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
My	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
making	O
the	O
timber	O
fast	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Hockley	O
and	O
Ridstone	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
lighter	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
their	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
they	O
carried	O
away	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
deals	O
.	O
Hockley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
hand	O
with	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
deals	O
:	O
the	O
tide	O
ran	O
very	O
strong	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Lime-house-bridge	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Jeffrey	O
would	O
get	O
them	O
sawed	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
slip	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Jeffrey	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
For	O
Hockley	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hockley	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
general	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
Jeffrey	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jeffrey	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
worthy	O
man	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
sawyer	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
least	O
blemish	O
in	O
his	O
character	O
:	O
I	O
deal	O
for	O
5	O
or	O
600	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
for	O
deals	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
above	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
the	O
thirteen	O
deals	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
Jeffrey	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
fetched	O
to	O
value	O
the	O
goods	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
thirteen	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
above	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
single	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
double	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
three	O
inch	O
deal	O
.	O
The	O
intrinsic	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
3	O
s.	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
coarse	O
sappy	O
stuff	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
to	O
buy	O
deals	O
by	O
candle-light	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
young	O
fellows	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
Mr.	O
Jeffrey	B-pers
a	O
good	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blyth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Dingley	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
a	O
price	O
on	O
the	O
thirteen	O
deals	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Jeffrey	O
's	O
yard	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
the	O
price	O
he	O
sells	O
deals	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
1	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
judgement	O
.	O
Hockley	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Jeffrey	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
112	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Vander	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Mary	O
Stone	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cowdell	I-pers
,	O
January	O
6	O
.	O
||	O
George	B-pers
Cowdell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
in	O
New	B-place
Bond-street	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
servant	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Cowdell	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
gowns	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
gown	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
one	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
not	O
well	O
)	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
pledging	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Stone	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
gown	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
three	O
gowns	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
113	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Morris	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Morris	O
,	O
October	O
28	O
++	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
St.	I-place
Andrew-street	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
forwards	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
let	O
with	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
months	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
absconded	O
a	O
fortnight	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
husband	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
did	O
he	O
abscond	O
?	O
S.	O
Burford	O
.	O
He	O
absconded	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
no	O
notice	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
Little	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
two	O
sauce-pans	O
,	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Belton-street	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
,	O
had	O
pawned	O
another	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Hull	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
sauce-pans	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
flat	O
irons	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
saucepans	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
cohabited	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
pledged	O
this	O
sheet	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Murry	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
rakish	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
like	O
others	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
customer	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cripple	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
place	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
deserved	O
no	O
pity	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
in	O
unmarried	O
people	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
Rosa	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
some	O
cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
our	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mamma	O
,	O
mamma	O
,	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
Rosa	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
murder	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
drawn	O
his	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
play	O
his	O
pranks	O
,	O
abusing	O
and	O
rioting	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
father	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
drawing	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
:	O
I	O
begged	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
consider	O
the	O
condition	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
(	O
being	O
with	O
child	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
my	O
mother	O
down	O
also	O
.	O
This	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
violent	O
assault	O
only	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
detained	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
skellet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bridget	O
,	O
December	O
12	O
.	O
||	O
Bridget	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
iron	O
bars	O
forced	O
off	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
iron	O
bars	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
shutter	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
button	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
scullery	O
:	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
brass	O
kettle	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
room	O
joining	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
was	O
published	O
abroad	O
,	O
Mr.	O
West	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
kettle	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
On	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
)	O
in	O
Norton-falgate	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brass	O
kettle	O
,	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
flag	O
basket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
the	O
rim	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
size	O
and	O
shape	O
of	O
her	O
kettle	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
kettle	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
kettle	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
kettle	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
coppersmith	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
there	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
carried	O
kettles	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
200	O
weight	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
coachman	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
copper-smith	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
There	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
copper-smith	O
?	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
here	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
where	O
;	O
sometimes	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
second	O
examination	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
an	O
almanack	O
in	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
kettle	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
main	O
road	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
week	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Saverin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
January	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
June	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
silver	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
travel	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
small	O
quantity	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
;	O
I	O
usually	O
missed	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
brushed	O
my	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
twenty-one	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
distinctly	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
scratch	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
each	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
cloaths	O
out	O
to	O
brush	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
counted	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
my	O
two	O
shillings	O
marked	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
:	O
also	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
compare	O
;	O
they	O
exactly	O
corresponded	O
.	O
Captain	O
Templer	B-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
Colonel	O
Scott	B-pers
a	O
visit	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
the	O
Colonel	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
sealed	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
somebody	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
117	O
,	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
M'Farley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Barney	B-pers
Flyn	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown-piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Barney	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
Mrs.	O
Flyn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Barney	B-pers
Flyn	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Green-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bedchamber	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Flyn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
a	O
basket	O
full	O
of	O
half-pence	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
an	O
odd	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
four	O
coloured	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
laced	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
plain	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
caps	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
nine	O
.	O
When	O
Clark	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
step	O
ladder	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
between	O
my	O
neighbour	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
shed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
(	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
put	O
up	O
)	O
;	O
this	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dridal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
up	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
had	O
on	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
M'Farley	O
sent	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
round-house	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
also	O
owned	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Catharine	B-pers
M'Farley	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
Catharine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
told	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
this	O
she	O
also	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
commit	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
on	O
account	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
promised	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
such	O
promise	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dridal	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
such	O
a	O
promise	O
made	O
?	O
Dridal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Flyn	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
holland	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
eight	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
September	O
30	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Argyle	B-place
Buildings	I-place
:	O
her	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
September	O
,	O
of	O
some	O
linen	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
locks	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
forced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
marble	O
polisher	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
some	O
work	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
work	O
alone	O
there	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
more	O
men	O
at	O
work	O
besides	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
four	O
months	O
before	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
mistress	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
London	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Povey	O
.	O
Justice	O
Spinnage	O
sent	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
a	O
gold	O
snuff-box	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
eight	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
four	O
sheets	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
ones	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
drawers	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
M.	O
Fry	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
120	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Judith	B-pers
Barden	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
January	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
principal	O
evidence	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
121	O
:	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Saintree	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
odd	O
ones	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Marr	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
December	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Archibald	B-pers
Marr	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
coat	O
he	O
had	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
on	O
my	O
counter	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
sprung	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
only	O
leaned	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
an	O
ugly	O
look	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
challenge	O
him	O
then	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
shoes	O
were	O
called	O
for	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
:	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
these	O
pumps	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
would	O
pledge	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
customer	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
odd	O
ones	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
these	O
pumps	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
pledged	O
these	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
bundle	O
lie	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
halfpence	O
about	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
trifle	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
them	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
two	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
but	O
eighteen-pence	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
custom	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
two	O
shillings	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
road	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
E.	O
Obrian	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Saturday	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Yorkshire-Gray	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Saintree	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
you	O
stop	O
?	O
he	O
kicked	O
something	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Obrian	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
well	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
halves	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
shoes	O
?	O
E.	O
Obrian	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
,	O
when	O
he	O
kicked	O
this	O
bundle	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
rag	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
black	O
stuff	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
some	O
neighbour	O
about	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
us	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
122	O
,	O
123	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Cowel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
flock-bed	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
woolen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
woollen	O
coverlid	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
wooden	O
tub	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
drawers	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
January	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Maiden-head-court	B-place
,	I-place
Chiswell-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
watch-finisher	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
jacket	O
and	O
drawers	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
:	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
blanket	O
and	O
coverlid	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Turner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
last	O
Monday	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
after	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Turner	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Whitehart-yard	O
,	O
near	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
washing	O
tub	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Turner	O
,	O
sold	O
this	O
tub	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
brought	O
flocks	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
linnen	O
and	O
woolen	O
rags	O
:	O
I	O
buy	O
old	O
rags	O
,	O
old	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
not	O
bring	O
you	O
sheets	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
brought	O
nothing	O
but	O
rags	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
pillow	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
as	O
rags	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
as	O
rags	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
tub	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
groat	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
rags	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
opened	O
the	O
parcel	O
she	O
brought	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
them	O
amongst	O
rags	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
rags	O
brought	O
into	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
are	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mason	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
bringing	O
that	O
parcal	O
here	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
bring	O
a	O
flock	O
bed	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
a	O
tick	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
flocks	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
brought	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
flocks	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
weighed	O
but	O
twenty	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
mine	O
:	O
mine	O
were	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
snow	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
dirty	O
things	O
.	O
Turner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
partner	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
:	O
my	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
.	O
Turner	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
tub	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Cowell	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
124	O
,	O
125	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Langham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
December	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
John	O
Todd	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Susannah	O
Johnson	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
slop-seller	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Little-East-Cheap	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
December	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
bundles	O
of	O
bedding	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green-Man	O
and	O
Bell	O
,	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
,	O
by	O
our	O
porter	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
shipped	O
for	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
's	O
service	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
since	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
porter	O
returned	O
with	O
other	O
bundles	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
bundles	O
were	O
stolen	O
away	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
slop-seller	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
hill	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
:	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
word	O
from	O
Gravesend	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
parcels	O
deficient	O
:	O
the	O
gentleman	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
our	O
hedding	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Godsby	O
's	O
,	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
them	O
two	O
bundles	O
?	O
Todd	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Godsby	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bedding	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
two	O
beds	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
two	O
coverlids	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
hammocks	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
either	O
the	O
Saturday	O
or	O
Sunday	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
check	O
skirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
canvas	O
trowsers	O
on	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parcels	O
for	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
soldiers	O
:	O
he	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bundles	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Timothy	O
Murphy	O
stole	O
the	O
bedding	O
,	O
in	O
Dark-house-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Godsby	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
lodgings	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
confessed	O
,	O
one	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
Godsby	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
jacket	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brockholt	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dennison	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
)	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brockholt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
jacket	O
of	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Todd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
greatly	O
to	O
blame	O
:	O
you	O
should	O
take	O
care	O
never	O
to	O
buy	O
new	O
things	O
of	O
people	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
such	O
as	O
you	O
that	O
give	O
encouragement	O
to	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
:	O
you	O
may	O
think	O
