TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
MARCH	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1765	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEPHENSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Perrott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
+	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Tyrell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Charteer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Benwell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Snape	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burrell	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Collin	B-pers
Dollinson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Crace	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bickham	I-pers
,	O
Adam	B-pers
Dunkley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Portius	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Turing	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Vale	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
.	O
150	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
cod	O
fish	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
twelve	O
haddocks	O
,	O
seventeen	O
flounders	O
,	O
ten	O
lobsters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wicker-basket	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Simon	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kingstone	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
fish	O
;	O
I	O
use	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
under	I-place
the	I-place
Piazzas	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
basket	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
fish	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Going	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
:	O
my	O
name	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
villain	O
and	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
my	O
fish	O
?	O
he	O
stood	O
like	O
a	O
saint	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
obstropulous	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
A	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
fish	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
but	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
aye	O
my	O
cock	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
151	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crumholt	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
December	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crumholt	I-pers
being	O
but	O
ten	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crumholt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
King	O
's	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
my	O
daughter	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Mr.	O
King	O
live	O
?	O
E.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
'Change-court	O
,	O
Exeter	O
'Change	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
E.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Christopher	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
that	O
afternoon	O
my	O
child	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
to	O
give	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
child	O
went	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
lodge	O
?	O
E.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
On	O
Saffron-hill	O
:	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
darns	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
shirts	O
?	O
E.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
?	O
E.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
damaged	O
places	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
I	O
darned	O
up	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
shirt	O
still	O
continues	O
a	O
hole	O
.	O
She	O
shewed	O
the	O
places	O
on	O
each	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
Blakeney	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
near	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
shirts	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
woman	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
from	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
darn	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
and	O
shewed	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Miss	O
Conoway	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
windows	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
acquaint	O
Sir	O
John	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Arnold	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
shirts	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tagg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Conoway	O
,	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
three	O
shirts	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
did	O
he	O
bring	O
them	O
home	O
on	O
?	O
M.	O
Tagg	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
152	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Welstead	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Eleaner	O
Welstead	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Rowland	B-pers
Welstead	I-pers
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Queen	I-place
Charlotte	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Knaves-Acre	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
six-pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
which	O
weighed	O
28	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
some	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
missing	O
after	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
other	O
persons	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
the	O
mug	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
we	O
missed	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
people	O
are	O
of	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
,	O
a	O
relation	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
since	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Knaves-Acre	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
that	O
evening	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
six-penny	O
worth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
three	O
men	O
coming	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
first	O
about	O
four	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
six-pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
our	O
back	O
room	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
company	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fire	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Then	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
meaning	O
some	O
other	O
house	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
will	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
much	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
six-pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
six-pennyworth	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
china	O
bowl	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
spoons	O
in	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
made	O
them	O
six-pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
in	O
the	O
china	O
bowl	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
nephew	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Hickle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
related	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
when	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
down	O
till	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
men	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
nor	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
above	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
came	O
into	O
that	O
back	O
room	O
after	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
one	O
of	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
had	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
above	O
eight	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Polack	I-pers
,	O
chandler	O
,	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
New-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
;	O
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
154	O
,	O
155	O
,	O
156	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
rupee	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
coin	O
called	O
Fernams	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
October	O
30	O
,	O
1764	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
committed	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1764	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Morgan	O
was	O
a	O
Mahametan	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
continued	O
in	O
gaol	O
for	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
their	O
Lordships	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Alcoran	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Gould	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
unanimous	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Mahometan	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
are	O
people	O
of	O
your	O
profession	O
sworn	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
touch	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
the	O
Alcoran	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
forehead	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
bound	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
sworn	O
upon	O
the	O
Alcoran	O
)	O
.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Bengal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
come	O
here	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
Indiamen	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
this	O
time	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
tyger	O
for	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Pigot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
governor	O
of	O
Madrass	O
,	O
and	O
attend	O
upon	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Soho-square	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
near	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
,	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
later	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brother	O
Mahometan	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
governor	O
's	O
country-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
except	O
my	O
shirt	O
and	O
trowsers	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
husband	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
;	O
(	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
knot	O
in	O
my	O
sash	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
wear	O
about	O
my	O
waist	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
shirt	O
)	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
poker	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
dispute	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
would	O
break	O
my	O
head	O
:	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
Black	O
D	O
-	O
l.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
morning	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
having	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
jacket	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
,	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
and	O
secured	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
stockings	O
and	O
buckles	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
Mahometan	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
in	O
Rag	O
fair	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Lascar	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
without	O
shoes	O
or	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
mentioned	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Cottrell	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
beadle	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nor	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public-houses	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
in	O
Well-street	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Lascar	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
talked	O
Irish	O
together	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cottrell	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
talking	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
:	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
examine	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
this	O
sash	O
(	O
which	O
the	O
Lascar	O
calls	O
his	O
silk	O
purse	O
;	O
it	O
ties	O
round	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
ties	O
up	O
his	O
money	O
)	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
man	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Rupee	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Firnam	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
Thirteen	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Four-pence	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
purse	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
purse	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cottrell	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Murry	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
part	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
I	O
to	O
die	O
this	O
minute	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
confined	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
John	O
and	O
Mary	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Jeremiah	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
February	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
marked	O
by	O
an	O
engraver	O
;	O
every	O
one	O
was	O
marked	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
way	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
this	O
shilling	O
;	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
:	O
a	O
small	O
mark	O
appeared	O
upon	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
candid	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
then	O
did	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
money	O
mentioned	O
,	O
some	O
on	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
another	O
,	O
all	O
different	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
I	O
forgot	O
in	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
false	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Since	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
enquire	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
people	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
she	O
has	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
a	O
man	O
has	O
seduced	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Henry	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pool	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Guess	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
158	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Teares	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
February	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
a	O
grocer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
choping	O
some	O
sugar	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
loaf	O
of	O
sugar	O
moving	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
hogshead	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
out	O
stooping	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
within	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
walk	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
;	O
and	O
turn	O
over	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
our	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
pork	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
lying	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
by	O
our	O
shop-window	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
eye	O
on	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sugar	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
High-holbourn	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
kicked	O
against	O
a	O
lump	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
window	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
loaf	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
rope-maker	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
wooden	O
case	O
for	O
knives	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
fish-skin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
knives	O
,	O
with	O
ivory	O
handles	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
forks	O
,	O
with	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bucannan	I-pers
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
on	O
Botolph-wharf	B-place
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
measuring	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
half	O
off	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
stood	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
rowl	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
by	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
with	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
friend	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
dropped	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
key	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
gang's-men	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
Summer	O
's	O
key	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jebb	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sturney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Bucannan	I-pers
's	O
goods	O
:	O
these	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
)	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Coffe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
stupid	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
:	O
he	O
must	O
certainly	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
heavy	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
161	O
,	O
162	O
,	O
163	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burgin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Spearing	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
aloes	O
,	O
value	O
:	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
:	O
it	O
was	O
also	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
January	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
discharging	O
a	O
lighter	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Barbadoes	O
ship	O
,	O
at	O
Bear-key	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
gourd	O
of	O
aloes	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
on	O
board	O
)	O
:	O
those	O
I	O
missed	O
were	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
copper	O
bottom	O
,	O
nine	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
that	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Spearing	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
calabash	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Bourn	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
followed	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chymist	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
thrown	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
aloes	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
Captain	O
Hall	O
,	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
brought	O
any	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
.	O
Spearing	O
and	O
Bourn	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
after	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
a	O
gourd	O
of	O
aloes	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
my	O
while	O
to	O
buy	O
that	O
alone	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
)	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
aloes	O
at	O
20	O
d.	O
per	O
pound	O
:	O
on	O
paying	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
remaining	O
quantity	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
till	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
Captain	O
Hall	O
,	O
in	O
Burr-street	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
accordingly	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
with	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
aloes	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
their	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
was	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
his	O
measures	O
accordingly	O
:	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jebb	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
information	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
gourd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
.	O
Bourn	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
Spearing	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
gourd	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Burgin	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Spearing	O
is	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
there	O
.	O
Burgin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Spearing	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Take	O
this	O
stuff	O
,	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
doctor	O
stopped	O
two	O
shillings	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
remainder	O
.	O
Spearing	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Bourn	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Burgin	O
was	O
my	O
ship-mate	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
ship-mate	O
?	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
apothecary	O
's	O
shop	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
just	O
by	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
five	O
more	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
164	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
windows	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
reward	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
chased	O
belly	O
'd	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
them	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
milk-pot	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
belly	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
chased	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
Yard	O
,	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Nettle	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
variance	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
murdered	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
marked	O
J.	O
L.	O
N.	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Abbot	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
letters	O
on	O
the	O
tea-tongs	O
?	O
Abbot	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
on	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
566	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
165	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Boyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
past	O
one	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
What	O
does	O
that	O
woman	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
want	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
We	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
walking	O
very	O
fast	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
missing	O
a	O
rump	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
:	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
beef	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
gateway	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
.	O
Ann	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
he	O
gave	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
dog	O
ran	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
saw	O
me	O
pursuing	O
the	O
dog	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
can	O
say	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
satisfied	O
to	O
be	O
condemned	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
from	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
dog	O
near	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
166	O
,	O
167	O
,	O
168	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dix	I-pers
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
coals	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
coals	O
from	O
a	O
barge	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
each	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
coals	O
.	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
barge	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Norton	O
and	O
Hall	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
turn	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
169	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
partner	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
;	O
we	O
sent	O
twelve	O
lumps	O
of	O
sugar	O
down	O
to	O
Harrison	B-place
's	I-place
wharf	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
vessel	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
had	O
word	O
the	O
warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rood-lane	O
,	O
Fenchurch-street	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
the	O
12th	O
and	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
our	O
warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
;	O
these	O
six	O
loaves	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wouldham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
hired	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
three	O
loaves	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
more	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
shutter	O
,	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
loaves	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Wrestlers	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Wouldham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lime-burner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
:	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Casady	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Wrestlers	O
that	O
morning	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
sugar	O
?	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
three	O
more	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
32	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
some	O
rum	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
loaves	O
of	O
sugar	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
not	O
being	O
bound	O
over	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
identical	O
sugar	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
.	O
)	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
170	O
,	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
D'Neal	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Frankland	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
keeps	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
shop	O
together	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
observed	O
to	O
be	O
looking	O
at	O
a	O
cloak	O
under	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
a	O
cardinal	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
172	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
222	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
rope	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
moored	O
my	O
boat	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
Bear	B-place
Key	I-place
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
at	O
New	O
Crane	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
seats	O
and	O
sculls	O
were	O
locked	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eatenton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
New	O
Crane	O
stairs	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
moored	O
my	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
boat	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
shore	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
rope	O
lying	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
scull	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
shore	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
this	O
rope	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bray	O
,	O
above	O
bridge	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
never	O
could	O
bring	O
this	O
boat	O
through	O
bridge	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
scull	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
no	O
waterman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
am	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
somewhere	O
thereabout	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
boats	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
several	O
names	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
mentioned	O
Joyner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
six-pence	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
from	O
below	O
bridge	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
six-pence	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
justices	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
Dangerfield	O
,	O
a	O
fisherman	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
six-pence	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
justices	O
order	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
described	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
prison	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
brig	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
rope	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
failed	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
word	O
before	O
he	O
failed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
oath	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
boat	O
was	O
driving	O
with	O
the	O
tide	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
going	O
to	O
Deptford	O
with	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
this	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
not	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
just	O
below	O
Rotherhithe	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
any	O
nearer	O
than	O
Plymouth	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Rigley	I-pers
Swinney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
handling	O
some	O
stockings	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
folding	O
up	O
the	O
stockings	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
Looking	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
to	O
satisfy	O
my	O
curiosity	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
my	O
boy	O
turning	O
round	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Pilkington	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
stealing	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
another	O
pair	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
boy	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
other	O
stockings	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Pilkington	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
a	O
poor	O
young	O
creature	O
,	O
who	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Pilkington	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fling	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Pilkington	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
own	O
throat	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
cut	O
the	O
skin	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
himself	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
the	O
belly	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
stockings	O
produced	O
,	O
)	O
one	O
pair	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
make	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
have	O
my	O
shop	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
made	O
of	O
worsted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Greenhill	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
steps	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
last	O
step	O
.	O
I	O
tapped	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
cutting	O
his	O
own	O
throat	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
two	O
months	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Chester	O
with	O
letters	O
of	O
recommendation	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
a	O
counting-house	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carwin	O
,	O
in	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Power	O
,	O
a	O
merchant	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
south	O
of	O
France	O
for	O
his	O
health	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
rely	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Carwin	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
succeed	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
wrote	O
down	O
to	O
Chester	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
friends	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
to	O
bear	O
my	O
expences	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
what	O
I	O
owed	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
two	O
necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-park	O
:	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
stockings	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
:	O
the	O
young	O
lad	O
shewed	O
me	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
pair	O
:	O
I	O
fancied	O
one	O
pair	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
recollected	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
folded	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
things	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Carwin	O
?	O
Is	O
he	O
here	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
would	O
write	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
never	O
look	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
174	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Keatley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lockley	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Lockley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lockley	I-pers
:	O
we	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Hall	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
Shepherd	I-place
and	I-place
Flock	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Marybone	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
up	O
so	O
late	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
generally	O
am	O
up	O
last	O
:	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
secured	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
:	O
the	O
wash-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
,	O
was	O
all	O
made	O
fast	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
bolted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
wash-house	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Lockley	O
.	O
It	O
joins	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
wash-house	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
us	O
from	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
linen	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
ladder	O
was	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
tyles	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
tyles	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
from	O
thence	O
down	O
through	O
the	O
cieling	O
,	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
thief	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
chamber	O
over	O
the	O
wash-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
linen	O
and	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
confined	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
the	O
ladder	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Lockley	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
master	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
that	O
generally	O
when	O
out	O
of	O
use	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
in	O
Marybone	O
parish	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
behind	O
a	O
board	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
corner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Portland-street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
foot	O
coming	O
along	O
pretty	O
briskly	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fields	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
opposite	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
pushed	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
halloo	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
something	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
bundle	O
of	O
wet	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
dry	O
and	O
iron	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
does	O
your	O
wife	O
lodge	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hampshire-hog	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
wife	O
a	O
laundress	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
bring	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Flock	O
,	O
at	O
Marybone	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
does	O
your	O
wife	O
iron	O
for	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
wrong	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
;	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
his	O
countrymen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
tossing	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
later	O
than	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
my	O
business	O
:	O
he	O
kept	O
pushing	O
forwards	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
struggled	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
dog	O
came	O
and	O
jumped	O
up	O
towards	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
submitted	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
three	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
hour	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
going	O
to	O
Marybone	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Flock	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
had	O
sent	O
any	O
linnen	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
lost	O
any	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
directly	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
six	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
wrapped	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
table-cloths	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
another	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
handed	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash-house	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
landlady	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
Neal	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
Sir	O
John	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
Neal	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
landlady	O
and	O
his	O
bedfellow	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
proof	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
room	O
enough	O
broke	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
wash-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
wash-house	O
join	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
.	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
place	O
that	O
was	O
broken	O
:	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
wash-house	O
join	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
L.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
wife	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
,	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
;	O
he	O
pays	O
his	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
:	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
slice	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
there	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
after	O
going	O
home	O
every	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
eleven	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
me	O
till	O
twelve	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
man	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
earn	O
six-pence	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
thank	O
him	O
too	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Marybone	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
me	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
this	O
Neal	O
parted	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
that	O
man	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
Marybone	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Hanover-square	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
soon	O
,	O
pitch	O
your	O
load	O
till	O
I	O
come	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
:	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
bringing	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
reward	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
gone	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
small	O
orphans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
helpless	O
father	O
,	O
in	O
Dublin	O
:	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
honourable	O
court	O
will	O
consider	O
my	O
innocence	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
appear	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
175	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Timothy	B-pers
M'Dermot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
coach	O
glasses	O
,	O
with	O
wooden	O
frames	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
:	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
keeps	O
her	O
own	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
serve	O
her	O
with	O
horses	O
;	O
her	O
coach	O
stands	O
in	O
a	O
coach-house	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
glasses	O
lost	O
from	O
that	O
coach	O
,	O
in	O
wooden	O
frames	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
light-coloured	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
27th	O
or	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
:	O
Colonel	O
Dean	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
mentioned	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
gaol	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discharged	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
glasses	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
make	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bland	O
's	O
coach	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
cloth	O
over	O
the	O
frames	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tassels	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
frames	O
are	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
ovaled	O
on	O
the	O
tops	O
than	O
is	O
common	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
confess	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
I	O
behave	O
when	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Cordwell	O
.	O
Very	O
badly	O
,	O
very	O
loose	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
salesman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
:	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
furtout	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
change	O
these	O
two	O
glasses	O
for	O
one	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
40	O
s	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
glasses	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
charge	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
office	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Marlborough-meuse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Leg	O
,	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
glasses	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
two	O
days	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
never	O
came	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
car	O
rying	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
.	O
Shadreck	O
Venden	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-maker	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bland	O
's	O
coach	O
:	O
I	O
very	O
believe	O
these	O
two	O
glasses	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
glasses	O
belonging	O
to	O
her	O
coach	O
;	O
the	O
lineing	O
of	O
the	O
frame	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
frames	O
are	O
made	O
rising	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
coach	O
is	O
rising	O
over	O
the	O
doors	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
canvass	O
shutters	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
answer	O
exactly	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
one	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
hundred	O
will	O
match	O
the	O
place	O
as	O
these	O
do	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cordwell	O
's	O
yard	O
into	O
Marlborough-meuse	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
named	O
Barney	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
shilling	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
to	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Marlborough	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
glasses	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Leg	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
there	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
landlady	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cordwell	O
's	O
yard	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
service	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Monday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Leg	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
not	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
glasses	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
saleshop	O
:	O
whether	O
I	O
offered	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
that	O
was	O
born	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Barney	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
?	O
Coyle	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
176	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shearman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Seven-dials	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
plates	O
mentioned	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
live	O
hogs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Barnsley	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
hogs	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
yard	O
at	O
Drayton	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
horse	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
first	O
at	O
Smallbury-green	O
turnpike	O
;	O
then	O
at	O
Kew-bridge	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mortlake	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
Putney	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
Wandsworth	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Goat's-heads	O
,	O
at	O
Battersea	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
pigs	O
were	O
stopped	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Miller	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
hogs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
for	O
distress	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
He	O
comes	O
out	O
of	O
Northamptonshire	O
:	O
he	O
mowed	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
last	O
harvest	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
lived	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Putney	O
Bowling-green	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
driving	O
the	O
six	O
hogs	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
:	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
just	O
above	O
Putney	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
again	O
beyond	O
the	O
Three	O
Goat's-heads	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Berkshire	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wonder	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Borough	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
25	O
s.	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
15	O
s.	O
apiece	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
chap	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
worth	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
apiece	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Goat's-heads	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
hogs	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
he	O
has	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
as	O
much	O
more	O
as	O
he	O
asks	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
stable	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Goat's-head	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
hogs	O
came	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
William	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Drayton	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hogs	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Nine	O
Elms	O
,	O
in	O
Battersea	O
parish	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
hogs	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
came	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
hogs	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Reading	O
.	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
held	O
his	O
head	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
brewer	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
man	O
:	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
over	O
Hounslow-heath	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
ca	O
me	O
to	O
Cranford-bridge	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
hogs	O
:	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
London	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
drive	O
these	O
hogs	O
to	O
town	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shillings	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
Kew-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Vaux-hall	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
chap	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
money	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
more	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
than	O
the	O
hogs	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
them	O
along	O
;	O
this	O
farmer	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
mile	O
or	O
two	O
:	O
I	O
partly	O
bargained	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
apiece	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
drove	O
them	O
for	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
somewhere	O
near	O
Reading	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
met	O
me	O
near	O
Vauxhall	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
178	O
,	O
179	O
,	O
180	O
,	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Taaf	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
,	O
February	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
ginger-bread-baker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Chesterman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
twenty-five	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
:	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
me	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Chesterman	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Bishop	B-place
's	I-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Old	I-place
Bailey	I-place
:	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
hand	O
about	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
breeches-pocket	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
half	O
crowns	O
last	O
?	O
Chesterman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
miss	O
'd	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Chesterman	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
searched	O
?	O
Chesterman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
left	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
meddle	O
with	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Chesterman	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
near	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
at	O
me	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
my	O
hat	O
into	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
half	O
crowns	O
again	O
?	O
Chesterman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
while	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
had	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
my	O
rounds	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
this	O
charge	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
before	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
Margaret	B-pers
Taaf	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
or	O
goes	O
for	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could-have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
Edwards	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
three	O
buy	O
old	O
cloaths	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
drink	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
cold	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
fellow-prisoners	O
)	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
without	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
some	O
thing	O
else	O
:	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Edwards	O
say	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
man	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
Foliot	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Davis	O
and	O
Taaf	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
181	O
,	O
182	O
,	O
183	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
,	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
some	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
one	O
other	O
customer	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
lady	O
who	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
was	O
serving	O
;	O
my	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Peltroe	O
,	O
of	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
examining	O
my	O
books	O
and	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
apiece	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
they	O
stood	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
stock	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
or	O
500	O
l.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
farther	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
one	O
,	O
prize	O
14	O
d.	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
13	O
d.	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
ten	O
minutes	O
time	O
they	O
returned	O
:	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
swear	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
shall	O
we	O
have	O
this	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
liked	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
said	O
4	O
s.	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
;	O
they	O
stood	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
piles	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
four	O
rows	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
facing	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
gave	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
her	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
loose	O
handkerchiefs	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
board	O
was	O
cleared	O
of	O
one	O
row	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
in	O
length	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
pattern	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
fine	O
blue	O
borders	O
,	O
twenty-one	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
of	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
then	O
three	O
parcels	O
of	O
another	O
pattern	O
of	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
spoiled	O
work	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
cleared	O
at	O
the	O
printers	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
more	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
describe	O
,	O
having	O
such	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
advice	O
:	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
advertise	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
printed	O
some	O
hand-bills	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Field-lane	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
place	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
both	O
my	O
men	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
two	O
parcels	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
(	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
some	O
good	O
and	O
some	O
spoiled	O
work	O
.	O
He	O
takes	O
up	O
two	O
parcels	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
two	O
parcels	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
,	O
by	O
Hicks's-hall	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
quitted	O
their	O
lodging	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
told	O
us	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
more	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
going	O
down	O
Holbourn-hill	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
having	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
pretended	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
and	O
wife	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
twenty	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
spoiled	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
half-piece	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
told	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Magennis	O
,	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
women	O
stood	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
They	O
stood	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Mitre-court	O
,	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
women	O
been	O
in	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
counter	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
counter	O
,	O
but	O
farther	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
abide	O
long	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
the	O
women	O
might	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
possible	O
he	O
could	O
conceal	O
them	O
from	O
your	O
seeing	O
them	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
They	O
will	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
pieces	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
that	O
cost	O
ten	O
guineas	O
a-piece	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
put	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
the	O
women	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
had	O
you	O
missed	O
any	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
covered	O
with	O
light	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
goods	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
went	O
away	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
goods	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Pelteroe	O
went	O
away	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
observe	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
bottom	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
piles	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
that	O
were	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
they	O
could	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
their	O
aprons	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
apron	O
could	O
take	O
away	O
three	O
times	O
as	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
they	O
could	O
take	O
away	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
lay	O
piled	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
hand	O
could	O
sweep	O
them	O
all	O
into	O
an	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
their	O
faces	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
the	O
piles	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
breast-high	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
cheques	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
deal	O
with	O
hawkers	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
13th	O
or	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
they	O
came	O
sometimes	O
with	O
wallets	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
bundles	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
:	O
they	O
brought	O
large	O
quantities	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
they	O
usually	O
brought	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
have	O
linen	O
,	O
till	O
these	O
two	O
parcels	O
I	O
bought	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
as	O
usual	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
very	O
handsome	O
blue-bordered	O
ones	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
produced	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
border	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
like	O
this	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
fine	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Such	O
I	O
missed	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
fancy-grounds	O
,	O
or	O
mosaic	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
money	O
for	O
some	O
damaged	O
ones	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
advance	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
bid	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
for	O
the	O
damaged	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
bought	O
each	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
our	O
people	O
said	O
they	O
behaved	O
very	O
comically	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
afraid	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
amiss	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
read	O
of	O
such	O
goods	O
being	O
stolen	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
(	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
here	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
receipt	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
they	O
served	O
besides	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
named	O
four	O
shops	O
;	O
we	O
enquired	O
at	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
man	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
going	O
up	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
above	O
Turnstile	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
shun	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Can	O
you	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
fetch	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wife	O
that	O
is	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
may	O
stay	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
faster	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
follow	O
them	O
so	O
fast	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
people	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
ruin	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
counters	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenfield	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
persons	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
hawkers	O
:	O
sometimes	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
pack	O
over	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
together	O
when	O
you	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
in	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
licence	O
they	O
had	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
:	O
they	O
always	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
dealt	O
in	O
Spital-fields	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
deal	O
in	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
sometimes	O
good	O
,	O
sometimes	O
bad	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Scotch	O
pedlar	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
country	O
:	O
this	O
woman	O
here	O
by	O
me	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
wife	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
sister-in-law	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
told	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Delvin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
their	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Delvin	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
get	O
their	O
living	O
by	O
dealing	O
in	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
buy	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
going	O
on	O
four	O
years	O
:	O
they	O
have	O
very	O
good	O
characters	O
;	O
they	O
get	O
their	O
living	O
by	O
dealing	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
in	O
buying	O
damaged	O
goods	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
did	O
the	O
man	O
buy	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
bought	O
a	O
blue	O
paste-work	O
one	O
,	O
two	O
different	O
patterns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
one	O
did	O
the	O
woman	O
buy	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
striped	O
silk	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
sort	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
those	O
handkerchiefs	O
worth	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
gave	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Being	O
damaged	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Mary	O
Carroll	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
