TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SirWilliam	O
Stephenson	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1765	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEPHENSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
George	B-pers
Perrot	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
*	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
||	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hanscombe	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phene	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walch	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
for	O
Francis	O
Page	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
ill.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Sharpley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lightwood	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
415	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Howel	B-pers
Pew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
horse-keeper	O
to	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
my	O
horses	O
stand	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
fill	O
the	O
bin	O
with	O
oats	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witnesses	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lennet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
thirteen	O
quarters	O
of	O
oats	O
into	O
the	O
bin	O
over	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
which	O
just	O
filled	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
unlock	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
had	O
been	O
tampered	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
bin	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
sunk	O
,	O
by	O
letting	O
some	O
down	O
a	O
spout	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
bushels	O
or	O
more	O
gone	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
my	O
master	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Peither	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Miles	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
were	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peither	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
were	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Cousin	O
's	O
order	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
came	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
in	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
voice	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
spout	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
slide	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
let	O
down	O
some	O
oats	O
,	O
Thompson	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
sack	O
immediately	O
under	O
the	O
spout	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
key	O
,	O
the	O
proper	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
sack	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
oats	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
then	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
his	O
rabbits	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
Peither	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Peither	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
oats	O
.	O
Peither	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
one	O
hatful	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
rabbies	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
416	O
,	O
417	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Healey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Keeley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
seven	O
silver-handle	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
six	O
silver-handle	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
shagreen	O
case	O
for	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Nangle	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
fork	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Michael	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
case	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
them	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
or	O
15th	O
;	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
produced	O
there	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
table	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
worth	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
prisoners	O
then	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
irons	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Keeley	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Keeley	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
my	O
plate	O
was	O
found	O
:	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deserve	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
plate	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
rob	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
distress	O
'd	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Keeley	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
the	O
reward	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
intitled	O
to	O
that	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
custody	O
but	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Keeley	O
ever	O
since	O
Christmas	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
last	O
sessions	O
ended	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Row	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
door	O
stood	O
a	O
jar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
glass	O
cruets	O
,	O
with	O
silver	O
tops	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
a	O
corner	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
knife	O
case	O
,	O
with	O
twelve	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
six	O
forks	O
and	O
six	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
E.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
a	O
jar	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
silver	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
ofLittle	O
James-street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
chapel	O
,	O
Bedford	O
Row	O
.	O
E.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
;	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
a	O
Jew	O
that	O
lived	O
by	O
Clarkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
share	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
divided	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
had	O
six	O
forks	O
and	O
the	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
.	O
Boyd	O
had	O
six	O
spoons	O
and	O
three	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
:	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
two	O
silver	O
tops	O
of	O
the	O
cruets	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
committed	O
another	O
robbery	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
glass	O
cruets	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
share	O
up	O
,	O
by	O
showing	O
them	O
the	O
place	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
:	O
Boyd	O
went	O
away	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Constables	O
were	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
Keeley	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Morgan	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
evidence	O
against	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Farrell	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
337.	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Farrell	O
:	O
This	O
boy	O
lived	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
every	O
day	O
a	O
robbing	O
.	O
Keeley	O
.	O
this	O
woman	O
is	O
the	O
greatest	O
rogue	O
that	O
ever	O
existed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
that	O
Keeley	O
does	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
body	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
lodging-house	O
;	O
several	O
people	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Keeley	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
I	O
lodge	O
there	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
About	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Keeley	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
at	O
periwing	O
making	O
then	O
.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Keeley	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
two	O
places	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
cleared	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
this	O
robbery	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
Friday	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
place	O
we	O
lodged	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
found	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Morgan	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
spoons	O
,	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Keeley	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Bedford	O
Row	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
crests	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Boyd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
evidence	O
against	O
Keeley	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
likely	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Keeley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Boyd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
after	O
the	O
evidence	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
Boyd	O
;	O
Keeley	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
plate	O
from	O
Keeley	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
Morgan	O
and	O
Boyd	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Morgan	O
;	O
Keeley	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
plate	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
Boyd	O
)	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
Boyd	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
Morgan	O
had	O
been	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
,	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
her	O
share	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Long	O
Fields	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
some	O
earth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
six	O
table-spoons	O
and	O
three	O
knives	O
:	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
(	O
taking	O
up	O
some	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
)	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Keeley	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
bid	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
sell	O
the	O
plate	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
mentioned	O
Boyd	O
too	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barkerthe	I-pers
elder	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Newtener	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
;	O
Boyd	O
came	O
running	O
into	O
our	O
room	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
save	O
me	O
,	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
are	O
thieves	O
and	O
robbers	O
after	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
under	O
my	O
bed	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Haliburton	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Then	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
take	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
bed	O
while	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
found	O
five	O
silver	O
spoons	O
three	O
silver-handled	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
fork	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
boy	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
;	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
rag	O
with	O
a	O
garter	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maroah	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
with	O
the	O
father	O
and	O
son	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haliburton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
'soffice	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
named	O
Farrell	O
,	O
who	O
goes	O
for	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
Morgan	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Boyd	O
's	O
husband	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Wright	O
to	O
their	O
lodgings	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
two	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
another	O
.	O
Before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Montague	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Hyde	O
had	O
got	O
Morgan	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
their	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
glass	O
casters	O
without	O
tops	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
afterwards	O
informed	O
Boyd	O
went	O
down	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
Keeley	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
Boyd	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Barker	O
lodges	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
one	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Keeley	O
and	O
Gahaganwent	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
hardly	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
before	O
they	O
called	O
me	O
.	O
Gahagan	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
six	O
forks	O
and	O
a	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
between	O
Boyd	O
's	O
shoulders	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
run	O
up	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Barker	O
if	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Then	O
take	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
spoons	O
,	O
three	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fork	O
,	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
Barker	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
Gahagan	O
?	O
Haliburton	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
Keeley	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
)	O
when	O
Keeley	O
told	O
Wright	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Keeley	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
Haliburton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Gahagan	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
morning	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
sessions	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Wright	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
something	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
knives	O
,	O
forks	O
,	O
and	O
spoons	O
,	O
that	O
Farrell	O
and	O
Boyd	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
yard	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
some	O
Row	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
Row	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
particular	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
presently	O
came	O
Keeley	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Farrell	O
,	O
and	O
Boyd	O
's	O
husband	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
Hyde	O
in	O
the	O
coal-yard	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
two	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
another	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
meet	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
:	O
the	O
evidence	O
Morgan	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
pond	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
only	O
two	O
glass	O
cruets	O
,	O
which	O
Boyd	O
and	O
Morgan	O
afterwards	O
acknowledged	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
tops	O
belonging	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Keeley	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
do	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
pains	O
that	O
morning	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
thieves	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
all	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
follow	O
his	O
steps	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
have	O
all	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
stolen	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
Gahagan	O
.	O
or	O
the	O
boy	O
Keeley	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Keeley	O
by	O
when	O
Gahagan	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
come	O
.	O
Keeley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
Morgan	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
were	O
eating	O
beef	O
and	O
potatoes	O
at	O
their	O
lodgings	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
Morgan	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
nam	O
'd	O
Farrell	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
ragged	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
?	O
O	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
ragged	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
booty	O
this	O
week	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
forks	O
.	O
Said	O
they	O
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Coffe	I-pers
,	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
things	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
help	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
Coffee	O
tried	O
with	O
Farrell	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
338.	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
)	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
person	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
:	O
they	O
all	O
consented	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
somebody	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
we	O
should	O
get	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
man	O
must	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
buyer	O
of	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
himself	O
a	O
Jew	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Hyde	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Hyde	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Morgan	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
plate	O
?	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
woman	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
Boyd	O
)	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
Morgan	O
cleared	O
her	O
own	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
stole	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
way	O
to	O
come	O
off	O
but	O
by	O
swearing	O
falsely	O
against	O
somebody	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
between	O
thirteen	O
and	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Boyd	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
plate	O
.	O
Gahagan	O
,	O
and	O
Farrell	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
had	O
words	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
knife	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
hide	O
myself	O
from	O
these	O
men	O
:	O
the	O
people	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
constables	O
:	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
hide	O
myself	O
here	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
under	O
his	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
thief	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Gahagan	O
searched	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
Gahagan	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
:	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Morgan	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hide	O
your	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
hid	O
it	O
that	O
very	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Boyd	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
165.	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Healey	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Keeley	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
glass	O
cruets	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
silver	O
tops	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Heron	I-pers
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Jane	B-pers
Melon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Heron	I-pers
(	O
she	O
produced	O
a	O
stand	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
glass	O
casters	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
two	O
)	O
:	O
the	O
two	O
casters	O
wanting	O
here	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
one	O
morning	O
for	O
water	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
silver	O
tops	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
my	O
customers	O
with	O
milk	O
:	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Keeley	O
go	O
twice	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
twice	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Heron	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Milner-street	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
?	O
E.	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Melon	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
that	O
court	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
(	O
two	O
glass	O
casters	O
produced	O
)	O
:	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
stand	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
fitted	O
the	O
frame	O
,	O
and	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
wrought	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
glasses	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
places	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
your	O
master	O
lives	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
called	O
Bragdell	O
Court	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
E.	O
Parker	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
E.	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Melon	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
way	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
water	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
fast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
a	O
jar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
fast	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
meeting	O
this	O
milk-woman	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
the	O
pails	O
of	O
water	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
gentleman	O
by	O
you	O
lost	O
his	O
plate	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
but	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
doors	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Parker	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mayo	O
's	O
plate	O
being	O
lost	O
?	O
E.	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Melon	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
your	O
plate	O
gone	O
?	O
J.	O
Melon	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
plate	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
In	O
over	O
hauling	O
the	O
beds	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mayo	O
's	O
plate	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
cruets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
assisting	O
him	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wright	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
Farrell	O
and	O
these	O
people	O
lodge	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
beds	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Farrell	O
's	O
bed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
'Squire	O
Mayo	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
some	O
people	O
said	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
two	O
robberies	O
about	O
here	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
size	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
cruets	O
?	O
having	O
heard	O
them	O
mentioned	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Mayo	O
that	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haliburton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mayo	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
his	O
plate	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
cruets	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Kelley	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
355.	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
on	O
four	O
indictments	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Brokers-Row	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Vauxhall	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
past	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
named	O
Mackrell	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
prevented	O
him	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
jostled	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
whip	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
put	O
you	O
in	O
fear	O
?	O
Tomlinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
when	O
he	O
jostled	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
almost	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Tomlinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
present	O
any	O
pistol	O
or	O
instrument	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Tomlinson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
Number	O
forgot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Tomlinson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
go	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
Mackrell	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
till	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
low	O
declare	O
by	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Queen	O
,	O
and	O
Parker	O
,	O
in	O
robbing	O
several	O
talk	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
us	O
where	O
his	O
companions	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
some	O
officers	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
persons	O
,	O
Parker	O
,	O
Quin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
holding	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
:	O
he	O
first	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
:	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
twelve	O
months	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
This	O
chap	O
,	O
Mackrell	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
evidence	O
here	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
three	O
different	O
names	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
419	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
wharfingers	O
and	O
partners	O
:	O
we	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
times	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Stubley	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
account	O
John	B-pers
Stubley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
to	O
the	O
steel	O
yard	O
The	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
be	O
sore	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
pile	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
stoop	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
loaded	O
pretty	O
heavily	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
collaring	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robbing	O
they	O
are	O
:	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
one	O
end	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Jones	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
is	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
All	O
iron	O
in	O
our	O
yard	O
we	O
are	O
accountable	O
for	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
bar	O
was	O
lying	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hurt	O
on	O
my	O
scull	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
times	O
an	O
not	O
sensible	O
,	O
especially	O
when	O
I	O
get	O
any	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	O
Floyd	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Fills	I-pers
,	O
Anne	O
Proudfoot	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
get	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Stubley	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fuddled	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Stubley	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
420	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hardware	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
About	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
or	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
charity	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
relief	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
strange	O
voice	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
brought	O
me	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pair	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
asked	O
charity	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
opposite	O
Mercer	O
's	O
chapel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bodker	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
buckles	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
offered	O
some	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
pair	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
buckle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
one	O
buckle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
shops	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
the	O
wrong	O
side	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
about	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church	O
yard	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
other	O
pair	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
senses	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Losbell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
leaning	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pulling	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspicious	O
:	O
I	O
walked	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
cotton	O
near	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
:	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
woman	O
had	O
bought	O
any	O
Irish	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
?	O
(	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
very	O
sharply	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
another	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
:	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
several	O
little	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
down	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
herself	O
turned	O
out	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
Three-pence	O
halfpenny	O
about	O
her	O
:	O
(	O
the	O
cloth	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
very	O
safely	O
make	O
oath	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
I	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
cloth	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
some	O
cloth	O
off	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
put	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
laid	O
on	O
my	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
.	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
422	O
,	O
423	O
,	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Farrall	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
martin	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
fishouse	O
skin	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
Libenrood	I-pers
,	O
August	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
landed	O
some	O
skins	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Libenrood	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
loaded	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
company	O
came	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drove	O
them	O
away	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
the	O
master	O
carman	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
:	O
we	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Martin	O
skins	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
Watkins	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
of	O
Farrall	O
's	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
John	O
Jebb	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
this	O
skin	O
Steward	O
said	O
he	O
dropt	O
under	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
valued	O
at	O
9	O
s.	O
Steward	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
easing	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hauled	O
me	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
.	O
Farrall	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
kicked	O
the	O
skin	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
gate-way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Watkin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
skin	O
lying	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Steward	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Farrall	O
and	O
Watkins	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
425	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
five	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peggy	B-pers
Gordey	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Martha	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Klemast	O
,	O
a	O
furrier	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gray's-inn-lane	B-place
;	O
Peggy	B-pers
Gordey	I-pers
is	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
her	O
things	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Peggy	B-pers
Gordey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
shop-woman	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Klemast	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
426	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Adam	B-pers
Couden	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
August	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Adam	B-pers
Couden	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
instantly	O
by	O
another	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
blow	O
under	O
my	O
left	O
eye	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
cane	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
cane	O
and	O
watch	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
blow	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
my	O
watch	O
is	O
No	O
.	O
168.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
the	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bill	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
that	O
cleaned	O
it	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
,	O
a	O
triangle	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
scollop	O
over	O
the	O
key-hole	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
;	O
he	O
haul	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
fetched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
thirty-five	O
shillings	O
:	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
a	O
lie	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
,	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
stand	O
of	O
coaches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
watch	O
just	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
advertiser	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
advertised	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Ned	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
club	O
:	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
this	O
watch	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
me	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
asleep	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
?	O
they	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
Blinkey	O
Bourn	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
advertised	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
the	O
reward	O
;	O
then	O
Bourn	O
said	O
,	O
Ned	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Ned	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
for	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
shewn	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
offered	O
40	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
sweep-chimney	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Michael	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Forgerson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
M	I-pers
Mar	O
,	O
Bridget	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Leigh	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
427	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Erkenn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
,	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fruiterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
's	O
maid	O
called	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
beauffet	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
over-took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Wakeman	I-pers
was	O
then	O
coming	O
cross	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
within	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
boggy	O
ground	O
between	O
us	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
four	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
brought	O
up	O
four	O
silver	O
spoons	O
:	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
spoons	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
running	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
running	O
for	O
apples	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wakeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
cross	O
the	O
fields	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
James	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
's	O
maid	O
call	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stoop	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
covered	O
;	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
four	O
:	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
;	O
marked	O
P.	O
H.	O
S.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Yarman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fitzpatrick	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
near	O
Statute	O
Hall	O
,	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
Mr.	O
James	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
These	O
spoons	O
are	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
cricket-playing	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
girl	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
apples	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
apples	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Stop	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
must	O
I	O
stop	O
for	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
428	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Devene	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
duffil	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Seyers	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Henry	B-pers
Seyers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Catherine-wheel	B-place
alley	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
only	O
two	O
rooms	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
day	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clarkenwell	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
brandy	O
and	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Surry	O
militia	O
,	O
got	O
intelligence	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
lapell	O
'd	O
blue	O
grey	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
duffil	O
waistcoat	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
at	O
Chatham	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Best	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
without	O
coat	O
or	O
waistcoat	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
torn	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
into	O
one	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
all	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
periwig	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
pieces	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
very	O
proper	O
notice	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
heed	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
before	O
'Squire	O
Best	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
cloaths	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
Horn	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
man	O
for	O
saying	O
so	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Chatham	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
people	O
against	O
me	O
that	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
cloaths	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
owed	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
always	O
love	O
to	O
pay	O
where	O
I	O
owe	O
;	O
presently	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
came	O
and	O
tore	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
rags	O
that	O
were	O
torn	O
to	O
pieces	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
and	O
confined	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
naked	O
through	O
the	O
streets	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
this	O
coat	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
marine	O
society	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
served	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
love	O
to	O
wear	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Horn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
of	O
this	O
story	O
of	O
a	O
madman	O
before	O
?	O
Horn	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
that	O
undress	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Horn	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
cloaths	O
to	O
a	O
cloaths-man	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
pieces	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
coat	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
429	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buckinghorn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
she	O
did	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
her	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
objection	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
broom	O
and	O
swept	O
the	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
for	O
that	O
day	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
fire	O
and	O
got	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
for	O
that	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
constant	O
servant	O
.	O
Thus	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
some	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
expecting	O
she	O
would	O
wash	O
them	O
one	O
day	O
or	O
another	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
shirts	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
nine	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
boiler	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Welch	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
recommended	O
her	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
detain	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Welch	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
your	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
are	O
in	O
pawn	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
shoved	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
There	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
defend	O
yourself	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
conducted	O
out	O
by	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
made	O
and	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
return	O
she	O
stole	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Welch	O
had	O
just	O
brought	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
pawned	O
by	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
a	O
shirt	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
for	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
:	O
in	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
this	O
shirt	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
shirt	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
shirt	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
hands	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
to	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
owned	O
to	O
but	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Platton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Catherine-wheel-alley	B-place
.	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
;	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
young	O
fellows	O
kept	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
:	O
none	O
came	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
not	O
coming	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
morrow-night	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
where	O
bad	O
people	O
resorted	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
accordingly	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
young	O
chaps	O
standing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
stopt	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Catherine-wheel	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
skittle-ground	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
my	O
hat	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
prosecute	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
:	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
forgave	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
se'ennight	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
about	O
twelve	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
hat	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
confession	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
took	O
the	O
hat	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
justice	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
in	O
Abel	O
's	O
Buildings	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
call	O
'd	O
himself	O
Harry	B-pers
Platton	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
this	O
hat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
hat	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
they	O
say	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Bishop	O
,	O
a	O
midwife	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Catherine-wheel-alley	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
bookbinder	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
gunsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
431	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Henry	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
baby	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
servant	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
between	O
16	O
and	O
17	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
Five	O
months	O
,	O
wanting	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
:	O
she	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
till	O
lately	O
:	O
I	O
trusted	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
money	O
while	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
were	O
at	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
just	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
girl	O
for	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
but	O
lately	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
money	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
four	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
two	O
;	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
:	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
herself	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
rich	O
aunt	O
,	O
that	O
sent	O
her	O
things	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
since	O
find	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
mistrust	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
missing	O
money	O
so	O
at	O
times	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
into	O
my	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cowley	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
hid	O
that	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
lock	O
with	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
by	O
the	O
thief-takers	O
;	O
they	O
threatened	O
me	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
prosecute	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
confessed	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
threatning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
of	O
shewing	O
her	O
favour	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
goods	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
10	O
l.	O
13	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
mentioned	O
shoes	O
,	O
gowns	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
hats	O
,	O
cardinal	O
,	O
necklaces	O
,	O
gold	O
bobs	O
,	O
mittens	O
,	O
buckles	O
,	O
stays	O
,	O
petticoat	O
,	O
bonnet	O
,	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
shifts	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
with	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
favour	O
shewed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
young	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
432	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Albin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
husband	O
's	O
word	O
for	O
the	O
bringing	O
the	O
things	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
constantly	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
woman	O
only	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
433	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pembrook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Prince's-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
East	O
Indies	O
:	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
nights	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
dining-room	O
:	O
we	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
:	O
we	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
try	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
scandal	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
character	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
but	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
lodgings	O
in	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
I	O
told	O
his	O
wife	O
my	O
stockings	O
were	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
them	O
against	O
to-morrow	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
my	O
stockings	O
were	O
ready	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
stockings	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
till	O
I	O
get	O
them	O
wash	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
his	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
my	O
legs	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
wife	O
here	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
434	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Levand	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
Aug.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
before	O
she	O
did	O
this	O
fact	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
the	O
lodgings	O
myself	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a-week	O
;	O
the	O
sheet	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
sheet	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
:	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
twenty	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Stockdale	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
liberty	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
?	O
Belcher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stockdale	O
in	O
Great	O
Pultney-Street	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
this	O
sheet	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
justice	O
threatened	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
sheet	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Nash	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
directions	O
about	O
this	O
sheet	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
deny	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
customary	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
people	O
come	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
know	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Whenever	O
a	O
person	O
comes	O
again	O
from	O
a	O
magistrate	O
for	O
things	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
deny	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
richly	O
deserve	O
to	O
stand	O
where	O
that	O
woman	O
does	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
too	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
owned	O
me	O
money	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Rotherhithe	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
and	O
pledge	O
a	O
sheet	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rotherhithe	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
liberty	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
pawning	O
a	O
bl	O
anket	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
know	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
forgave	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
turn	O
my	O
money	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
from	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
letter	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
prison	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
letter	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
letter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
order	O
any	O
letter	O
to	O
be	O
wrote	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
:	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
receive	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
assist	O
you	O
in	O
prison	O
:	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
she	O
now	O
owes	O
me	O
above	O
40	O
shillings	O
,	O
money	O
lent	O
and	O
for	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
agree	O
to	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
send	O
a	O
paper	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
prison	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
line	O
or	O
two	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
fool	O
of	O
me	O
``	O
and	O
yourself	O
too	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
done	O
as	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
``	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
wanted	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
``	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
``	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
fool	O
of	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
``	O
before	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
all	O
shall	O
be	O
made	O
easy	O
.	O
``	O
Pray	O
send	O
me	O
word	O
to-morrow	O
or	O
to-night	O
by	O
``	O
the	O
bearer	O
.	O
''	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Killing	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Scafe	O
's	O
in	O
Baldwin	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
knee	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
throw	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
starved	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
poor	O
mother	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
can	O
do	O
nothing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
436	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Rance	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Rebecca	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler's-shop	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
ready	O
furnished	O
of	O
me	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
cleared	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
all	O
safe	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Rhedoway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Holliday	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
;	O
I	O
detected	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
affair	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
by	O
jumping	O
over	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
had	O
better	O
discover	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
before	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
words	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
James	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
of	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
of	O
Kentish-Town	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Groves	O
of	O
Peckham	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
honest	O
when	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
had	O
known	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
437	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wellius	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
clock	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
inquired	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
clock	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopt	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
such	O
things	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
:	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
pledge	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
438.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
stock	O
,	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
penny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coumbe	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
439.	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
and	O
consent	O
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Her	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
escheated	O
.	O
440	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
live	O
cocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Harmon	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	O
Goodwright	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hanmon	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
at	O
Great	B-place
Ealing	I-place
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
:	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
ten	O
hens	O
,	O
two	O
cocks	O
,	O
six	O
ducks	O
and	O
a	O
drake	O
stolen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fowls	O
shewn	O
him	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
cocks	O
my	O
mistress	O
lost	O
;	O
i	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
his	O
claws	O
;	O
his	O
claws	O
are	O
rotted	O
off	O
,	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
hurt	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
chicken	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
hens	O
and	O
a	O
drake	O
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Marybone	O
parish	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
my	O
rattle	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
home	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
King's-head	O
ale-house	O
bench	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Balsover-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
sack	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
meal-sack	O
hanging	O
wallet-fashion	O
,	O
over	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
some	O
thing	O
about	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
parish	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Parish	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
Marybone	O
parish	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
master	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
are	O
talking	O
of	O
,	O
is	O
Golden-square	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
does	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
there	O
till	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
hard	O
loaded	O
this	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
heavy	O
loaded	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
,	O
having	O
brought	O
it	O
8	O
miles	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
contained	O
fowls	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
stolen	O
goods	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
opposite	O
Argyle	O
Buildings	O
,	O
they	O
crossed	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
back	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
watchman	O
's	O
box	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
watchman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
by	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
down	O
Argyle-street	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Great	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
just	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
set	O
the	O
dog	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
some-resistance	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
quietly	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
set	O
the	O
dog	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
took	O
the	O
fowls	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
hens	O
and	O
a	O
cock	O
,	O
three	O
ducks	O
and	O
a	O
drake	O
;	O
the	O
cock	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
cock	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
from	O
Kensington-Gravel-pits	O
to	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
bargeman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Kensington	O
Gravel-pits	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
our	O
leave	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Soldier	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
?	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
load	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
that	O
is	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
at	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
441	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
Turbot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Rising-sun	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Vine-street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
cup	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
crying	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
cup	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
the	O
cup	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
by	O
the	O
bat	O
:	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
(	O
The	O
cup	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
particular	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
six	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
cup	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
cup	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
liquor	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
my	O
mistress	O
the	O
cup	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
mistress	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
beer	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
four	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
:	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cupboard	O
for	O
the	O
cup	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
beside	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
kitchen	O
in	O
sight	O
of	O
this	O
cupboard	O
?	O
Staples	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
cup	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
bent	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
The	O
cup	O
was	O
bent	O
in	O
very	O
much	O
on	O
the	O
sides	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Staples	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
cup	O
so	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Staples	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Martin	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
cup	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
?	O
(	O
I	O
meant	O
by	O
its	O
being	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
his	O
appearance	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
master	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
cup	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Robert	B-pers
Turbot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
came	O
so	O
far	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
particular	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
valued	O
the	O
cup	O
at	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
5	O
l.	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
but	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
stronger	O
suspicion	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
cup	O
:	O
he	O
affirmed	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
cup	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
vouch	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
send	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
reputable	O
man	O
,	O
would	O
vouch	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
either	O
return	O
him	O
the	O
cup	O
,	O
or	O
purchase	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
somebody	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Daily	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
marked	O
with	O
letters	O
on	O
the	O
handle	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
letters	O
are	O
on	O
the	O
belly	O
of	O
the	O
cup	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
cup	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
submit	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
's	O
mercy	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
accuse	O
me	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
consider	O
my	O
youth	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
three	O
children	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Medley	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
Medley	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
Round-court	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
years	O
1760	O
,	O
1761	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
:	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
and	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
use	O
my	O
house	O
have	O
often	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Salopian	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Medley	O
's	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
in	O
general	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
carries	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
year	O
1763	O
:	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
different	O
places	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
nothing	O
particular	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
sober	O
and	O
just	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearcy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
different	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
:	O
he	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
diligent	O
sober	O
servant	O
,	O
wherever	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
442	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Weeks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
privately	O
,	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Jasper	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
-	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Berkley-square	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
'prentice	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
pursuing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
