TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1765	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEPHENSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
Sidney	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Smythe	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Hon	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
||	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jourdon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ascoe	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Withey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kinnersly	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Champness	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Seber	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
513	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
jobb	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stable	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
French-horn	B-place
,	I-place
High-holbourn	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
too	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
prepare	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
and	O
returning	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
514	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tibbel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
aged	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
(	O
holding	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
)	O
she	O
is	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
my	O
child	O
being	O
very	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
hurt	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Sam	O
had	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
our	O
apprentice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
her	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
little	O
running	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
that	O
soreness	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
having	O
the	O
measles	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
measles	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
very	O
lately	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
child	O
told	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
first	O
complain	O
?	O
G.	O
Duncan	O
.	O
She	O
first	O
complained	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
this	O
came	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
part	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Dermot	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
injury	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
behave	O
so	O
?	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
acted	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
twice	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
?	O
Dermot	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
twice	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
board	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
really	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
twice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
Dermot	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
lying	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
ravishing	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
twice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Dermot	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
confront	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
before	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
very	O
words	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
recollect	O
?	O
Dermot	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
body	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gyle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
really	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
twice	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Duncan	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
part	O
,	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
injury	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
doctor	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
then	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
behave	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
?	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
often	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
since	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duncan	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
boy	O
been	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
apprentice	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
:	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
bear	O
my	O
expences	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
compound	O
a	O
felony	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
child	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
weakness	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
suppression	O
of	O
urine	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
soft	O
medicines	O
to	O
relieve	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
venereal	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
running	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
hurt	O
on	O
the	O
part	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
form	O
any	O
belief	O
whether	O
her	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
enter	O
'd	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Really	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
hurt	O
by	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
entered	O
her	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
complaint	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
any	O
lasceration	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
been	O
called	O
in	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
seen	O
something	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
attempted	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Rosamond	B-pers
Tibbel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
mother	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dermot	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
never	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
poor	O
lad	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dermot	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
true	O
?	O
Dermot	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
this	O
confession	O
was	O
made	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
detained	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
rape	O
.	O
515	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
September	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White	B-place
Lyon	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Hemmings's-row	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
fastened	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
chissel	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Vine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
The	O
robbery	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
at	O
four	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Hemmings's-row	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
candlestick	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
large	O
chissel	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
marble-polisher	O
;	O
the	O
chissel	O
is	O
a	O
tool	O
I	O
use	O
in	O
my	O
business	O
:	O
the	O
cellar-door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
slip	O
'd	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
marble-polisher	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spur	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
sober	O
industrious	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
516	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-two	O
store	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Wallingford	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Oxfordshire	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
twenty-four	O
hogs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
twenty-two	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
Brandford	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
miles	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
hogs	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
bred	O
twenty-three	O
myself	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
chief	O
constable	O
of	O
Brandford	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
had	O
stolen	O
his	O
pigs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
pigs	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pigs	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
yard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Brandford	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
pigs	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
any	O
where	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Luckner	O
,	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
pigs	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
layer	O
for	O
pigs	O
:	O
I	O
expected	O
witness	O
to-day	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
my	O
trial	O
would	O
come	O
on	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
Collings	O
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
pigs	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tufnel	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
brokery	O
way	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
married	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
sister	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
:	O
since	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
into	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
farmer	O
's	O
man	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
We	O
expected	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
tried	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
stain	O
'd	O
before	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Gunston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
though	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
lately	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
before	O
he	O
left	O
Oxfordshire	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
517	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Amey	B-pers
Pinhorn	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Smith	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
October	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Smith	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Tun	O
and	O
Bull	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
shop	O
mate	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
rolls	O
for	O
breakfast	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
my	O
shop-mate	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bread	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
roll	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
complaint	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
some	O
money	O
and	O
a	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
some	O
roast	O
pork	O
:	O
she	O
wanted	O
bread	O
and	O
mustard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
?	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
's	O
widow	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
choice	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
marry	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
all	O
she	O
was	O
worth	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
soldier	O
at	O
the	O
Tun	O
and	O
Bull	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
send	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
victuals	O
for	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
eat	O
any	O
thing	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
her	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Tun	O
and	O
Bull	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
plenty	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
send	O
for	O
something	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
my	O
dear	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
stakes	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
soldier	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
then	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
(	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
five	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
soldier	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tun	O
and	O
Bull	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
followed	O
us	O
.	O
An	O
oyster-woman	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
oysters	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
eat	O
some	O
oysters	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
,	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
eat	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
fine	O
house	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Cousin	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
marry	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
get	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
walked	O
London	O
streets	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
walk	O
home	O
without	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
get	O
a	O
coach	O
you	O
must	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
.	O
The	O
fellow	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
unbuttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
hands	O
upon	O
my	O
private	O
parts	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
:	O
she	O
laughed	O
and	O
sung	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
fine	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
money	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
with	O
myself	O
now	O
she	O
has	O
flung	O
me	O
sure	O
enough	O
:	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
nigh	O
me	O
afterwards	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
matter	O
enough	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
fellow	O
followed	O
her	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
that	O
woman	O
did	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
whore	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
hang	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
best	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
from	O
this	O
bawdy-house	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
talking	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
a	O
rape	O
against	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
I	O
ravished	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
granted	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
offered	O
me	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
buttoned	O
up	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
but	O
ten	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
The	O
warrant	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
offered	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
while	O
the	O
justice	O
was	O
writing	O
her	O
mittimus	O
,	O
she	O
offered	O
a	O
hundred	O
guineas	O
for	O
ball	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
so	O
many	O
different	O
causes	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
ruin	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
together	O
all	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Tun	O
and	O
Bull	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
something	O
would	O
happen	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
infamous	O
woman	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
I	O
the	O
man	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
complained	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
drinking	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
rich	O
brother	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
6	O
d.	O
towards	O
a	O
coach	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
life	O
swore	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
here	O
,	O
would	O
prove	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
375.	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
518	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Caterer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
precinct	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stocking-trimmer	O
and	O
dyer	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
stockings	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
last	O
January	O
:	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
were	O
lost	O
last	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
dye	O
for	O
several	O
hosiers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
short	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
connived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
house	O
last	O
Sunday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
by	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
not	O
what	O
came	O
over	O
number	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
hosiers	O
sent	O
twelve	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
down	O
only	O
eleven	O
,	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
call	O
over	O
number	O
;	O
whereas	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
bills	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
last	O
Sunday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
robbing	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
tops	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
others	O
mark	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
:	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
made	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bignell	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
.	O
Terrence	B-pers
M'Gennis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
the	O
warrant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
tops	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
stockings	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
any	O
over	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vigus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
and	O
draper	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
general	O
good	O
character	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
honestly	O
returned	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
otherwise	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
deal	O
in	O
stockings	O
?	O
Thorp	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
only	O
in	O
cloaths	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
family	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Armisted	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
and	O
draper	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
hard-working	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stocking-trimmer	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty-two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jollard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-Lyon-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
years	O
:	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
:	O
from	O
the	O
knowledge	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
man	O
;	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
family	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
industrious	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
his	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
accused	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
519	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
M'kenzie	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
trivet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blackett	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Blackett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
iron	O
trivet	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
also	O
,	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Ackworthy	I-pers
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ackworthy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
ship-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blackett	O
:	O
the	B-place
snow	I-place
Cumberland	I-place
belongs	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
ship's-bow	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
companion	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
or	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
boys	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
steerage	O
.	O
In	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
trivet	O
was	O
moved	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
proper	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
about	O
five	O
steps	O
up	O
the	O
ladder	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
moved	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
business	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
ship	O
?	O
Ackworthy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
removed	O
the	O
trivet	O
?	O
Ackworthy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
he	O
had	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
ship	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
work	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
boys	O
playing	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
stopt	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
iron	O
trivet	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
520	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Oddy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Rollos	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
||	O
George	B-pers
Rollos	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Warner-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cold-bath-fields	I-place
.	O
I	O
let	O
my	O
parlour	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
:	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
having	O
reasons	O
to	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
married	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
warning	O
;	O
(	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
White	O
)	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
friends	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
received	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
men	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
thieves	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
warning	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
beset	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
fellows	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
for	O
his	O
advice	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
was	O
by	O
taking	O
the	O
door	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
demanded	O
admittance	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
abused	O
me	O
for	O
coming	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
she	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
conducted	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
examined	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
blanket	O
.	O
The	O
under	O
turnkey	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
against	O
her	O
but	O
an	O
assault	O
:	O
thus	O
by	O
deceiving	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
fresh	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
blanket	O
at	O
Mr.	O
William	O
Whitton	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
Hare-street-hill	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
White	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
the	O
lodging	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
?	O
Rollos	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
White	O
,	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
it	O
to	O
?	O
Rollos	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
supposed	O
husband	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
named	O
Oddy	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
indictment	O
mentions	O
it	O
being	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
use	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
521	O
,	O
522	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Walter	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
pint	O
glass	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
cheque	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Club	I-pers
,	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
At	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
up	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
down	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
They	O
ordered	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
warm	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
in	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
women	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
anniseed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
:	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
My	O
maid	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
:	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
Gill	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
chair-woman	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Club	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
robbed	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
:	O
Gill	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
half	O
pint	O
glass	O
mugs	O
put	O
between	O
the	O
water-tub	O
and	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
another	O
glass	O
mug	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
mugs	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
A	O
surgeon	O
,	O
named	O
Maglassey	O
,	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
that	O
in	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
bundle	O
were	O
my	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Club	O
's	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
not	O
mine	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
brought	O
no	O
bundle	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
Gill	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Club	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Club	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
's	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
Gill	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
in	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
gentleman	O
named	O
Hand	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
women	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
peep	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
looked	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
same	O
hole	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
cheque	O
aprons	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
followd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
their	O
coming	O
back	O
:	O
a	O
gentleman	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
it	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
opened	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
my	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
aprons	O
before	O
?	O
Club	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
aprons	O
and	O
sheet	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
our	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Club	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
aprons	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Casterton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
this	O
bundle	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
both	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mills	O
's	O
house	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
Gill	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
Gill	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Pickering	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeymen	O
baker	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
chair-woman	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
aprons	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
make	O
any	O
difficulty	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
?	O
Pickering	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
half	O
pint	O
glass	O
mug	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
Gill	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sitting	O
before	O
.	O
Gill	O
attempted	O
to	O
go	O
backward	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
disowned	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Gill	O
say	O
when	O
the	O
glass	O
mug	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Pickering	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
no	O
bundle	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
For	O
Gill	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
uncle	O
to	O
Gill	O
;	O
his	O
mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
at	O
Kensington	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
wait	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Gill	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
21	O
or	O
22	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
live	O
constantly	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
?	O
Gill	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
backward	O
and	O
forwards	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
a	O
tavern	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Shaw	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grantham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
builder	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
often	O
lodged	O
at	O
Gill	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
lately	O
?	O
Grantham	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
much	O
for	O
this	O
fortnight	O
past	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
523	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lyon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
thirty-five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gittos	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Gittos	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Thomas's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
)	O
:	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
clean	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
my	O
bureau	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
servants	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Gittos	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hendrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
servants	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
accuse	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
two	O
other	O
servants	O
,	O
search	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
boxes	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
agreed	O
upon	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
searched	O
the	O
women	O
and	O
boxes	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
smart	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
in	O
accusing	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
green	O
purse	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gittos	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
his	O
money	O
were	O
some	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
this	O
green	O
purse	O
and	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
hid	O
behind	O
some	O
old	O
boards	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
money	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hendrick	O
.	O
Hendrick	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
1	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
two	O
sixpences	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
half-pence	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
purse	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
purse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
?	O
Hendrick	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
bureau	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
bedchamber	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
524	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maguire	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Strowley	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
privately	O
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
||	O
Dennis	B-pers
Strowley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
talk	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Swan	I-place
with	O
that	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
7	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
it	O
some	O
how	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
pocket	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
side	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
jacket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
together	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
Not	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
you	O
not	O
lose	O
it	O
in	O
pulling	O
your	O
jacket	O
off	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
it	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
some	O
how	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
money	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
yet	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
:	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
sober	O
:	O
)	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
rest	O
:	O
she	O
denied	O
ever	O
seeing	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
that	O
afternoon	O
?	O
Strowley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
525	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Carew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
aunt	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Acorn	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Fore-street	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
yesterday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
by	O
myself	O
:	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
garters	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
somebody	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
she	O
went	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
also	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
shop-lifters	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
looking	O
at	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
went	O
towards	O
Grub-street	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
:	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
five	O
handkerchiefs	O
I	O
had	O
shewed	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Carew	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
:	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
maid	O
had	O
got	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
assist	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
striped	O
bed-gown	O
over	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
up	O
:	O
in	O
bringing	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
strove	O
all	O
she	O
could	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
within	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Carew	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
or	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
and	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Carew	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
letters	O
B	O
G	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
handle	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
526	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ustenson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ustenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
boxmaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Foster-lane	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
coat	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
farthest	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
whip	O
'd	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
the	O
coat	O
into	O
an	O
oil-shop	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Crane-court	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
run	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
there	O
I'took	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ustenson	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
near	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sober	O
?	O
Ustenson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
run	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Ustenson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
box-maker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
smith	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Galley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
which	O
surprized	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sumerfield	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
shop-mate	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
Crutched-Friars	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
place	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
there	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
married	O
my	O
daughter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
fault	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
against	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Batson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
so	O
does	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
527	O
,	O
528	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
and	O
Joshua	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Mocho	O
stone	O
set	O
round	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
September	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
and	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Mocho	O
stone	O
set	O
round	O
with	O
diamonds	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
one	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
,	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
case	O
that	O
stood	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
in	O
with	O
mine	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
:	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Wallis	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
advertised	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ring	O
again	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
two	O
chimney-sweeper-boys	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
boys	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
cut	O
my	O
glass	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
ring	O
out	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
skewer	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
that	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
two	O
chimney-sweepers	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
one	O
was	O
named	O
Joss	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
A	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
pawn	O
or	O
sell	O
this	O
ring	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
threatned	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
two	O
boys	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
opposite	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
seven	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
stept	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
set	O
off	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
took	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Hatton	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
Whitfield	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
ring	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
at	O
Hicks-hall	O
;	O
Hatton	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
ring	O
?	O
Then	O
they	O
both	O
insisted	O
on	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
chimney-sweeps	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
searched	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
diamond	O
to	O
cut	O
glass	O
being	O
found	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wood	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
diamond	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Hatton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
chimney-sweeps	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
groat	O
;	O
we	O
gave	O
them	O
three	O
pence	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
where	O
:	O
then	O
Whitfield	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
knocked	O
their	O
caps	O
in	O
our	O
faces	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
blinded	O
us	O
with	O
soot	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
is	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
public-houses	O
.	O
Whitfield	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Coming	O
through	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
boy	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Hatton	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
top	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
played	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
chimney	O
sweeps	O
that	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
ring	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
groat	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
flung	O
their	O
caps	O
in	O
our	O
faces	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
some	O
apples	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Cow	O
cross	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
529	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
large	O
stick	O
,	O
or	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Stockhill	I-pers
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
forcible	O
and	O
violent	O
manner	O
did	O
demand	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
William	O
Stockhill	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Richard	O
Campion	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
got	O
beyond	B-place
Pancras	I-place
church	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
oaken	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
:	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
my	O
friend	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mother	O
Red-cap	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Harding	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Nesbit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
quarrel	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Stockhill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Stockhill	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Stockhill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Stockhill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
none	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
should	O
have	O
any	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
persuaded	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
hazardous	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
prison	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
might	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
called	O
Mother	O
Red-cap	O
's	O
.	O
Stockhill	O
and	O
Campion	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Nesbit	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
cart	O
and	O
greens	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
night	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
horse	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
Nesbit	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
this	O
very	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
lay	O
there	O
to	O
rob	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
stick	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mother	O
Red-cap	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
they	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
Campion	O
collar	O
'd	O
the	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
and	O
Stockhill	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tasker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
get	O
his	O
living	O
?	O
Tasker	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
little	O
cart	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
digs	O
gravel	O
for	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
greens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Tasker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
?	O
Tasker	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
;	O
he	O
rents	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
about	O
five	O
guineas	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hickering	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
18	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hickering	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hardey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Highgate	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
sixteen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
green	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
six	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
most	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Stockhill	O
?	O
Moss	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Moss	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
forswearing	O
himself	O
?	O
Moss	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ibetts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
market	O
for	O
greens	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
spare	O
times	O
,	O
digs	O
and	O
carries	O
gravel	O
for	O
people	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
that	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
chimney-sweeper	O
and	O
him	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
horse	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
judgment	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
understands	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
at	O
Holloway	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
sold	O
horses	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
green-grocer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Stockhill	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
?	O
Stockhill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
look	O
after	O
a	O
stonehorse	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
,	O
on	O
Bristol-causeway	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
some	O
horses	O
for	O
'Squire	O
Green	O
,	O
at	O
Dulwich	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
five	O
years	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Appleyard	O
,	O
in	O
Carey-street	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Campion	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Campion	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Chicken-house	O
,	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
meet	O
my	O
master	O
returning	O
from	O
Smithfield-market	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Trevis	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
Stockhill	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
530	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Byfield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
Essex-street	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
a	O
customer	O
behind	O
my	O
counter	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
myself	O
round	O
,	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
and	O
how	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
:	O
I	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
attend	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
Byfield	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Jew	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
towards	O
Temple	O
bar	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
pair	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Jew	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Byfield	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
stockings	O
form	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
Byfield	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
the	O
Jew	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Downs	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
we	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Byfield	O
gave	O
me	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
delivered	O
myself	O
up	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
passed	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Byfield	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Territchino	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
are	O
sold	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
the	O
nine	O
pair	O
for	O
?	O
Territchino	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Jew	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
any	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
buy	O
such	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
:	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
things	O
he	O
has	O
bought	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
boy	O
in	O
Newgate	O
now	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
bought	O
things	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
diamonds	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
cut	O
glass	O
windows	O
with	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Hatton	O
and	O
Whitfield	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
these	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
or	O
13	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
:	O
this	O
pair	O
is	O
the	O
worst	O
among	O
the	O
parcel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
This	O
Jew	O
used	O
to	O
encourage	O
us	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
diamonds	O
to	O
cut	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bail	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
encouraged	O
several	O
little	O
boys	O
to	O
thieve	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
large	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
that	O
were	O
worth	O
30	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
accomplice	O
and	O
evidence	O
against	O
Barney	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
385	O
,	O
386.	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
531	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
:	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
William	O
Cornwall	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
person	O
properly	O
claiming	O
the	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Neale	O
,	O
Powe	O
and	O
Crowley	O
,	O
for	O
service	O
done	O
on	O
board	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ships	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
husband	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
William	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
18	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
August	O
was	O
three	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
wages	O
due	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
ticket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
certificate	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
altered	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
ran	O
from	O
other	O
ships	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
himself	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
,	O
saying	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
get	O
a	O
new	O
certificate	O
from	O
Captain	O
Obrian	B-pers
,	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
indebted	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
money	O
due	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
filled	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
read	O
writing	O
?	O
E.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
produced	O
.	O
She	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
writing	O
?	O
E.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wicket	O
,	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Ticket	O
office	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
beat	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
first	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
striking	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
for	O
16	O
l.	O
odd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
name	O
was	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
E.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
forgery	O
.	O
After	O
Mr.	O
Wicket	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
was	O
threatned	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
lawfully	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
thus	O
by	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
that	O
are	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Abraham	B-pers
Elby	I-pers
present	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
refused	O
to	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
people	O
's	O
names	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
witnessed	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
?	O
E.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Legrove	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
looks	O
at	O
it	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
signing	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
sign	O
these	O
names	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
real	O
man	O
that	O
signed	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
E.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
persons	O
?	O
E.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
and	O
Crowley	O
,	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
signed	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
Know	O
``	O
all	O
men	O
by	O
these	O
presents	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
,	O
John	O
``	O
Neale	O
,	O
late	O
quarter-master	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
``	O
Dragon	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
,	O
``	O
late	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Adventure	O
,	O
''	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
form	O
,	O
making	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
their	O
true	O
and	O
lawful	O
attorney	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
their	O
wages	O
,	O
prize-money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
``	O
Signed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
``	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowley	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Abraham	B-pers
Elby	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cornwall	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
right	O
man	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
belonged	O
to	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
false	O
power	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
enticed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
cried	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
mark	O
,	O
or	O
sign	O
a	O
name	O
?	O
E.	O
Cornwall	O
.	O
He	O
wrote	O
a	O
name	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Power	I-pers
;	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1763	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
lieutenant	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
recollect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
some	O
ship	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
belonged	O
:	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Temple	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
men	O
on	O
board	O
these	O
ships	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
what	O
name	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hoffman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Navy	O
office	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
book	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
,	O
who	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
49	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
It	O
was	O
paid	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1765	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
sworn	O
this	O
forgery	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
prison	O
for	O
debt	O
;	O
that	O
shews	O
it	O
is	O
spite	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
has	O
clapt	O
this	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
John	O
Powe	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rees	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
bad	O
action	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
:	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
532	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
McCormack	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
.	O
McCormack	O
is	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
come	O
from	O
India	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
friends	O
in	O
Scotland	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bilingfly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Man	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Cable-street	I-place
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
one	O
or	O
both	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
both	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
lie	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
serjeant	O
a	O
good-looking	O
man	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
serjeant	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
serjeant	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
noint	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
oil	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
noint	O
him	O
too	O
much	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
together	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
remembring	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
serjeant	O
with	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
:	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
money	O
rattle	O
:	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
put	O
three	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
heels	O
over	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
back-side	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
push	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
stopt	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
began	O
fighting	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
taking	O
,	O
I	O
sainted	O
away	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
:	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
below	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
above	O
his	O
private	O
parts	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
serjeant	O
's	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
serjeant	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
serjeant	O
owned	O
:	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
books	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
knees	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
:	O
the	O
serjeant	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
bed	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Is	O
my	O
head	O
prosecutor	O
here	O
?	O
Summers	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
do	O
you	O
hold	O
your	O
tongue	O
;	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
being	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stript	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
and	O
one	O
knee	O
buckle	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
buckle	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
trusted	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
two	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Summers	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
pocket	O
books	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
possession	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
spare	O
his	O
life	O
:	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Scotland	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
papers	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
books	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bilingsly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
distiller	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
witness	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
silver	O
buckles	O
under	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
else	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
interrupted	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
slipp	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
slipp	O
to	O
Mr.	O
McCormack	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
or	O
pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
beef-stakes	O
for	O
supper	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
those	O
things	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
capable	O
of	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
ever	O
a	O
back	O
yard	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
:	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
rummage	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
clouted	O
me	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
strange	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
more	O
capable	O
of	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
namesake	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
wanted	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
438.	O
in	O
last	O
Session	O
's	O
Paper	O
.	O
533	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Devene	I-pers
,	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Devene	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
after	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
tobacco	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
undertook	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
changed	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
brought	O
me	O
my	O
change	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
short	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
with	O
that	O
:	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
:	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
house	O
nor	O
them	O
neither	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
called	O
me	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
getting	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
snapt	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
you	O
home	O
:	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Sullivan	O
:	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
:	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
walked	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
alley	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
:	O
there	O
a	O
woman	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
drinking	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bourn	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
presently	O
:	O
in	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
tongue	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
he	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
Sullivan	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
assist	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
best	O
to	O
dodge	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
,	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
just	O
gone	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
women	O
about	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
ever	O
knowing	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
having	O
a	O
penny	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
When	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
took	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Devene	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
above	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
spent	O
some	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Mold	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Aldgate	O
:	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
constable	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
collecting	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
he	O
mentioned	O
the	O
same	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
here	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
taking	O
two	O
watchmen	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
women	O
:	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
obstropulous	O
:	O
but	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
farthing	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
:	O
which	O
we	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
He	O
declared	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
declared	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
Sullivan	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
Sullivan	O
:	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
swear	O
his	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
Sullivan	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
thrown	O
him	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
then	O
drank	O
it	O
in	O
egg-hot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
yesterday	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
other	O
constable	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
us	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
of	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
,	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
women	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
:	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
evening	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hours	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Sullivan	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
:	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Sullivan	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
so	O
they	O
drank	O
it	O
in	O
egg	O
hot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
disorderly	O
house	O
,	O
yesterday	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
,	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
bed	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
sidler	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
drank	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
half-in-half	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
warrant	O
out	O
against	O
a	O
man	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
change	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
tobacco	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
could	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
six-pence	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
walking	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
down	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
:	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
again	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Buckle-Street	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
Sullivan	O
and	O
two	O
disorderly	O
women	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
drawed	O
it	O
me	O
:	O
these	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
you	O
since	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Knowlton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
shipmate	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
tobacco	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
could	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
change	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
change	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
the	O
Maypole	O
,	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
go-out	O
together	O
to	O
buy	O
old	O
cloaths	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
after	O
a	O
bargain	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
well	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nine	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
