TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1765	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
W.	O
NICOLL	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEPHENSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Sidney	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Smythe	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
,	O
Clayton	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Luckyn	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Ayleward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Annaud	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Major	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Treslove	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dowe	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
*	O
N.	O
B.	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Leonard	O
Bowles	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Fellows	O
.	O
Ellis	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dimes	I-pers
.	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goater	I-pers
,	O
November	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
,	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
at	O
morning	O
prayer	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
the	O
seat	O
in	O
the	O
pew	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
John	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
parish	O
clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Peter	O
's	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
pew	O
behind	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
people	O
went	O
on	O
their	O
knees	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
him	O
take	O
hats	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
twenty	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
many	O
a	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
could	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
215.	O
H	B-pers
-	I-pers
J	I-pers
-	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
dram	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Eters	I-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
216.	O
Richard	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
was	O
set	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
indictment	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
in	O
May	O
Sessions	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
therein	O
mentioned	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
remanded	O
back	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
abroad	O
till	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
term	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
283.	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
Note	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Coventry	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
returning	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
some-mistake	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
or	O
record	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Patrick	I-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
three	O
harateen	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cheque	O
curtain	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
tin	O
boiler	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purney	I-pers
,	O
October	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Purney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purney	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
skinner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
High	B-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
or	O
more	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
their	O
room	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
:	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
gone	O
?	O
E.	O
Purney	O
.	O
He	O
must	O
have	O
known	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
going	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
some	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
since	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
out	O
by	O
his	O
consent	O
?	O
E.	O
Purney	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
they	O
must	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
assistance	O
as	O
to	O
a	O
livelihood	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
husband	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
bibb	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
flowered	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clough	I-pers
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mount-street	B-place
,	I-place
Grosvenor	I-place
Square	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
from	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
in	O
looking	O
up	O
her	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
missed	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
her	O
pocket	O
appeared	O
pretty	O
bulky	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
insisted	O
on	O
seeing	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
examined	O
without	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
about	O
sending	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
carrying	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
whom	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Ann	O
his	O
wife	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
gave	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
as	O
I	O
intended	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
M'Gee	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
treble	O
lac	O
'd	O
russles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
metal	O
buttons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Arundel-street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
from	O
a	O
bureau	O
book-case	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
suit	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
45	O
l.	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
got	O
them	O
advertised	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
reward	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
tucker	O
,	O
by	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
four	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
that	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Mary	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
these	O
things	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
daughter-in-law	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
chairing	O
at	O
a	O
,	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
behind	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
hearing	O
he	O
had	O
advertised	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Mary	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
her	O
daughter	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
's	O
for	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
:	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
keys	O
which	O
opened	O
my	O
bureau	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
drawers	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
220	O
,	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Grudgeworthy	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hemlock	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
King's-gate-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
hung	O
a	O
shirt	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
eldest	O
child	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
back-door	O
,	O
saw	O
Grudgeworthy	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
waited	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
:	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
soon	O
missing	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
:	O
they	O
denied	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Henlon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Good	O
Friday	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
White	O
in	O
a	O
passage	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
Grudgeworthy	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
,	O
hanging	O
to	O
dry	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
Norman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
shirt	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Bream	O
's	O
Buildings	O
:	O
we	O
saw	O
Grudgeworthy	O
going	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
shirt	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
Norman	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
that	O
shirt	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Harper	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
shirt	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Grudgeworthy	O
's	O
room	O
to	O
dry	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
.	O
Norman	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Grudgeworthy	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
222	O
,	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
;	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Jane	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
James	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
boy	O
Robinson	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
meat	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
watches	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
on	O
a	O
hook	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
Christopher	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
brought	O
one	O
watch	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
gypsey	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Lovell	O
had	O
the	O
shoes	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
Lovell	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
for	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Lovell	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
Justice	O
Dawson	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
gypsey	O
threatened	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
had	O
bundled	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
apron	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
Lovell	B-pers
the	O
gypsey	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
pick-pockets	O
;	O
and	O
Lovell	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Lovell	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
silversmith	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bargess	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
and	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
the	O
gypsey	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
:	O
he	O
offered	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
two	O
watches	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
venture	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
Lovell	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
boys	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
aside	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
till	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
:	O
presently	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
wanted	O
change	O
,	O
I	O
changed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
boys	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
behind	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
reckoning	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
boys	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
Lovell	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
it	O
changed	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
that	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
watch	O
you	O
had	O
this	O
morning	O
?	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
gypsey	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
quite	O
a	O
different	O
number	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
gentleman	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
man	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dawson	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
gypsey	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
boy	O
soon	O
confessed	O
the	O
gypsey	O
encouraged	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
master	O
of	O
another	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
:	O
the	O
gypsey	O
pretended	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
silver	O
gilt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Worstenhall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
the	O
words	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
mentioned	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
gypsey	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
Lovell	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
home	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
Lovell	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
this	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
things	O
cut	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
pawned	O
;	O
this	O
boy	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
breast	O
of	O
mutton	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
3	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
me	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Lovell	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
224	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Drummer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mun	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mun	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Pulteney-court	B-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
things	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
one	O
night	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
apprehended	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
aprons	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
this	O
she	O
also	O
said	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wright	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
apron	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wright	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
is	O
my	O
husband	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
cheque	O
aprons	O
upon	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
missing	O
:	O
I	O
Mistrusted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
enquiring	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
:	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
the	O
apron	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Matthew	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
apron	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
Frith	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
feast	O
to-day	O
.	O
Johanna	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
apron	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
's	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
.	O
Frith	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
yard	O
is	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
the	O
apron	O
that	O
I	O
pawned	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smallbrook	I-pers
.	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
trunks	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
one	O
trunk	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
seal-skin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
trunks	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
trunk-maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
Fishmonger's-hall	O
,	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
trunk	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
;	O
nothing	O
appeared	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ealing	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
(	O
describing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
trunk	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mulligan	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
hair	O
trunks	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
all	O
by	O
the	O
sizes	O
,	O
the	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ealing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
broker's-shop	O
,	O
the	O
Salamander	O
,	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
an	O
elderly	O
woman	O
brought	O
three	O
trunks	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
trunk-maker	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
woman	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Rawlinson	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
called	O
her	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Mulligan	I-pers
.	O
A	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
daughter	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
trunk	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
her	O
8	O
s.	O
new	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
daughter	O
's	O
fellow-servant	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
trunk	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
one	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Gale	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
also	O
.	O
Gale	O
.	O
That	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
speaks	O
of	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Penton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mulligan	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
trunks	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
a	O
trunk	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
customers	O
;	O
that	O
woman	O
has	O
passed	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
227	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
John	O
Strickland	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
coat	O
jirk	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
yesterday	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
then	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
then	O
Field-lane	O
again	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
:	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
this	O
pattern	O
in	O
their	O
lives	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
another	O
person	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
letter	O
S.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
walked	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
clapped	O
it	O
behind	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sibons	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
Marshal-court	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
child	O
from	O
a	O
baby	O
:	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Twells	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Twells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
meat	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
safe	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
My	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
meat	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
meat	O
back	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
meat	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
sent	O
any	O
meat	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
answered	O
no	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
street	O
going	O
into	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
mutton	O
and	O
a	O
rump	O
of	O
beef	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
three	O
weeks	O
come	O
from	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
victuals	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
nine	O
days	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
live	O
on	O
Saltpeter-bank	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Bridget	B-pers
Matocks	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
229	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
at	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
's	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
the	O
cardinal	O
was	O
pledg	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
produced	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
wear	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
for	O
mine	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d.	O
The	O
cardinal	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
:	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
refused	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
name	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
one	O
Jemmey	O
gave	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
chamber-door	O
locked	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
upon	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Strong	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
coat	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
this	O
gown	O
in	O
Scotland	O
:	O
the	O
landlord	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
washed	O
for	O
and	O
boarded	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
died	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
and	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
and	O
pawn	O
or	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Delforce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Weaver's-arms	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
woman	O
say	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
nor	O
thought	O
of	O
so	O
doing	O
;	O
this	O
evidence	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
herself	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
at	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Scotland	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
words	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
law	O
would	O
hang	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Fetch	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
any	O
more	O
trouble	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
:	O
her	O
room	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leather	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
bridles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
:	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
bridles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	B-place
and	I-place
Gate-yard	I-place
:	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
ostlers	O
and	O
coachmen	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
peeping	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
stable	O
;	O
the	O
under-ostler	O
and	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
stable	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
bridles	O
hid	O
under	O
some	O
hay	O
under	O
the	O
manger	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
saddle-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Gray's-lnn-lane	O
:	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
brought	O
an	O
old	O
saddle	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
231.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
232.	O
Philip	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
plates	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
four	O
pollishing	O
blocks	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Padell	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Magin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weetch	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Weetch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
:	O
about	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
told	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
pawned	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Adams	O
's	O
in	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Adams	O
delivered	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
window	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gofton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
:	O
this	O
lad	O
was	O
first	O
apprehended	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
what	O
house	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
stockings	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
of	O
taking	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Cock	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Adams	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
delivered	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawning	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
here	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
lad	O
brought	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
234	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
yellow	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
out-side	O
case	O
shagreen	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
Wapping	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gofton	I-pers
.	O
These	O
lads	O
had	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Talbot	O
on	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
in	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Talbot	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
very	O
infamous	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
worst	O
in	O
our	O
parish	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
Johnson	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
the	O
lads	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
lads	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
Talbot	O
had	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
beadle	O
;	O
the	O
beadle	O
said	O
Talbot	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
Talbot	O
there	O
produced	O
it	O
:	O
Magin	O
said	O
Talbot	O
had	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
(	O
his	O
forehead	O
was	O
swelled	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
Talbot	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
needle	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Talbot	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
beadle	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
said	O
before	O
Talbot	O
's	O
face	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Talbot	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
ashamed	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
people	O
enough	O
hanged	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
already	O
;	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
know	O
better	O
.	O
The	O
lads	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
robberies	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
another	O
lad	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
entered	O
into	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
facing	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
Stairs	O
,	O
betwixt	O
2	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
description	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
Magin	O
said	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
one-armed	O
man	O
named	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Talbot	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pension	O
ticket	O
of	O
Johnson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Talbot	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
30	O
s.	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Talbot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
the	O
boy	O
down	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Magin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Two	O
lads	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
us	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Talbot	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
Rice	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Rice	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
Godfrey	B-pers
William	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Talbot	O
was	O
called	O
on	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
:	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
235	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trappel	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Trappel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hide-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
victuals	O
and	O
lodging	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
third	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
nine	O
that	O
evening	O
I	O
hung	O
my	O
watch	O
up	O
over	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
wife	O
her	O
stuff	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
;	O
my	O
buckles	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
under	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
something	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
left	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
speaking	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
miles	O
from	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
:	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
bold	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
all	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
stay	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
round-house	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
Leicester-street	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
sent	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
money	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
236	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
237	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Homell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
700	O
printed	O
sheets	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Jane	O
Shore	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
600	O
sheets	O
of	O
printed	O
paper	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Royal	O
Preacher	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
twenty-five	O
quire	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
100	O
sheets	O
of	O
printed	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
250	O
sheets	O
of	O
stamp	O
'd	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
hawker	O
of	O
news	O
papers	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
about	O
250	O
sheets	O
of	O
stamp	O
'd	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
print	O
for	O
news	O
papers	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
about	O
700	O
sheets	O
of	O
the	O
Tragedy	O
of	O
Jane	O
Shore	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
title	O
sheets	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
my	O
people	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
about	O
my	O
stairs	O
after	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
dispatched	O
with	O
her	O
papers	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
place	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
give	O
the	O
court	O
an	O
account	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
girl	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hawkers	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
following	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
again	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
hawker	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
papers	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
towards	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
printing-house	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
master	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
imagined	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
:	O
in	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
was	O
bringing	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
on	O
Good	O
Friday	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
placed	O
behind	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
coming	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
her	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
somebody	O
coming	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Emerson	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
nothing	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
still	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
cellar	O
under	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
who	O
sold	O
rice-milk	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
the	O
man	O
laid	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
,	O
was	O
some	O
cuts	O
for	O
a	O
Natural	O
History	O
(	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
:	O
immediately	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
books	O
(	O
we	O
call	O
them	O
books	O
,	O
though	O
in	O
sheets	O
)	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
taking	O
the	O
sheets	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Shore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
sheets	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	O
Preacher	O
;	O
and	O
mentioned	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
waste	O
paper	O
;	O
the	O
also	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
stamped	O
paper	O
:	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
we	O
found	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
grocer	O
;	O
and	O
forty-six	O
sheets	O
of	O
stamp	O
'd	O
paper	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Phasey	O
's	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
paper	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
;	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stebbing	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
At	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stebbing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stebbing	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
tripe	O
shop	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
exact	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
over	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
clean	O
pocket	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
very	O
officiously	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
soul	O
one	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
clean	O
one	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
halfpence	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
to	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
turn	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
but	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
called	O
quarter-guineas	O
,	O
among	O
my	O
halfpence	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
gold	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
My	O
husband	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
that	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
servants	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
husband	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
made	O
much	O
to	O
do	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
strange	O
the	O
money	O
should	O
be	O
gone	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
,	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
lie	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
for	O
robbing	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
till	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
spoke	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stebbing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tripe-man	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
a	O
secret	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
for	O
above	O
forty	O
guineas	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
till	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
say	O
threescore	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
coming	O
,	O
always	O
went	O
prodigiously	O
ragged	O
,	O
with	O
great	O
holes	O
in	O
her	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
shoes	O
down	O
at	O
heels	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
dressed	O
out	O
with	O
fine	O
fly	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
good	O
things	O
as	O
any	O
lady	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
:	O
we	O
have	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
16	O
l.	O
she	O
bought	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
keep	O
very	O
bad	O
hours	O
;	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
away	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
for	O
her	O
things	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
bought	O
these	O
fine	O
things	O
with	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
borrowed	O
five	O
guineas	O
of	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
four	O
guineas	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
cost	O
much	O
more	O
than	O
nine	O
guineas	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
another	O
examination	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
borrow	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
all	O
by	O
whoreing	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
at	O
six-pence	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
morning	O
my	O
mistress	O
lost	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
pocket	O
upon	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
dropped	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
taken	O
four	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
rogue	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
Jemmy	O
or	O
Sam	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Luff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
girl	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
2	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
of	O
me	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
her	O
honesty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
her	O
sister	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
behave	O
becoming	O
her	O
station	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Campaign	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
sixteen	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
last	O
place	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
person	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prince	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
January	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
pocket	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
she	O
shook	O
out	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
five-and-threepenny	O
pieces	O
;	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
pork	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
money	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
never	O
mind	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
she	O
has	O
,	O
and	O
may	O
be	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stebbing	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
send	O
that	O
servant	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stebbing	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
tell	O
the	O
prisoner	O
you	O
believed	O
your	O
husband	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stebbing	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
tell	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
Jemmy	O
or	O
Sam	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stebbing	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
ask	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
body	O
pick	O
up	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stebbing	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
fast	O
tied	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Carroll	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
how	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
appear	O
?	O
Carroll	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dress	O
'd	O
better	O
than	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
That	O
was	O
like	O
the	O
common	O
dress	O
of	O
a	O
poor	O
servant	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
239	O
,	O
240	O
,	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Muckleroy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
twelve	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
poker	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
beds	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pewter	O
wine	O
measure	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
lid	O
of	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
pannakins	O
,	O
three	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
wooden	O
frame	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
warming	O
pan	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
warming-pan	O
,	O
three	O
copper	O
tea-kettles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
beds	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
pot	O
,	O
three	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
two	O
pannakins	O
,	O
two	O
warming-pans	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
copper	O
tea-kettles	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hog-lane	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Gyles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
household-goods	O
:	O
on	O
Sunday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
warehouse-door	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
lighted	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
twisted	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hasp	O
broke	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
advertised	O
in	O
Monday	O
's	O
paper	O
following	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
for	O
any	O
person	O
that	O
should	O
stop	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
George	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
things	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
searchwarrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Black-horse-yard	O
,	O
by	O
Nightingale-lane	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
a	O
shovel	O
,	O
tongs	O
,	O
poker	O
,	O
a	O
quart	O
wine	O
measure	O
,	O
twelve	O
new	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
cover	O
,	O
a	O
saucepan	O
)	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
:	O
I	O
lodged	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
to	O
Kelley	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
thieves	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
then	O
Kelley	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
warrant	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
men	O
by	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
Muckleroy	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
Tom	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
:	O
Tom	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
confess	O
'd	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Muckleroy	O
said	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bring	O
back	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
Murphy	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Lee	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Innis	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
lodging	O
house	O
at	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
two	O
beds	O
,	O
two	O
coppers	O
,	O
two	O
warming-pans	O
,	O
three	O
tea-kettles	O
,	O
three	O
sauce-pans	O
,	O
two	O
child	O
's	O
pannakins	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
threw	O
away	O
a	O
brass	O
funnel	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dressing-glass	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
:	O
they	O
being	O
alarmed	O
at	O
these	O
men	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Muckleroy	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Muckleroy	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
know	O
anything	O
amiss	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Mullins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
about	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
hanged	O
twenty	O
years	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
hardly	O
ever	O
worked	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
always	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Langree	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
Muckleroy	O
,	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Muckleroy	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Langree	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Question	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
one	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
Wapping	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mullins	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
said	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
warrant	O
express	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
person	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
:	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
the	O
man	O
a	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
slop	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
ale-house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
first	O
brought	O
the	O
warrant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Kelley	O
;	O
he	O
halloo	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
here	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Tom	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
confession	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Murphy	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
Kelley	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
tied	O
Lee	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
walked	O
before	O
us	O
.	O
Murphy	O
stood	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
arches	O
,	O
Lee	O
went	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
signal	O
to	O
us	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
and	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
Lee	O
said	O
Muckleroy	O
lived	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
with	O
Lee	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Muckleroy	O
;	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
Muckleroy	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blackhorse-yard	O
,	O
Nightingale-lane	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
my	O
pension	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Lee	O
,	O
Murphy	O
and	O
Muckleroy	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
Murphy	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
:	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
Murphy	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
anywhere	O
hereabouts	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
few	O
houshold-goods	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
poor	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
copper	O
pots	O
and	O
some	O
plates	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
within	O
my	O
reach	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
:	O
Murphy	O
had	O
the	O
great	O
copper	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
Lee	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
fire-shovel	O
,	O
tongs	O
,	O
poker	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
cover	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
saucepan	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
six-pence	O
,	O
therefore	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Murphy	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
daunted	O
at	O
these	O
words	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
set	O
a	O
price	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
news-papers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
:	O
they	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Langree	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Peterson	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
Tom	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
came	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Peterson	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Murphey	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
Lee	O
and	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
Muckleroy	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Courtney	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Innis	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
Lee	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
Courtney	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
where	O
the	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
tell	O
and	O
be	O
hanged	O
?	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
nothing	O
.	O
Thoms	O
Lee	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
or	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
early	O
,	O
Muckleroy	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
poker	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Mullings	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
having	O
agreed	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
:	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
hasp	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
poker	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
hasp	O
and	O
padlock	O
off	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
beds	O
.	O
two	O
warming	O
pans	O
,	O
the	O
copper	O
full	O
of	O
tea-kettles	O
and	O
saucepans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
that	O
we	O
broke	O
afterwards	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
saucepans	O
,	O
three	O
teakettles	O
,	O
two	O
pannakins	O
,	O
a	O
fire-shovel	O
,	O
poker	O
and	O
tongs	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
sender	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
lid	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
:	O
these	O
we	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
at	O
twice	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
Fox-and-Knot-court	O
,	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
meet	O
Murphy	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
lodging	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
informed	O
him	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
things	O
:	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
Saltpeter-bank	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
could	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
each	O
an	O
equal	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
we	O
took	O
two	O
beds	O
and	O
three	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Innis	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
Patrick	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
took	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
Murphy	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
Fox	O
and	O
Knot	O
court	O
,	O
to	O
black	O
the	O
pots	O
and	O
saucepans	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
hamper	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Innis	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Courtney	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
about	O
to	O
some	O
brokers	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
sell	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Courtney	O
brought	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
Courtney	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
two	O
beds	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
after	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
9	O
s.	O
Courtney	O
carried	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
beds	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
broker	O
's	O
;	O
Muckleroy	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Wheelwright	O
's	O
arms	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
12	O
s.	O
Murphy	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Courtney	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
pots	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
so	O
we	O
divided	O
16	O
s.	O
we	O
had	O
liquor	O
and	O
victuals	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
all	O
paid	O
part	O
towards	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Innis	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
Courtney	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
should	O
be	O
touched	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
right	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
Muckleroy	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Murphy	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
:	O
that	O
same	O
evening	O
.	O
Muckleroy	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
goods	O
to	O
Kelley	O
's	O
:	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
lent	O
us	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
money	O
was	O
short	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Muckleroy	O
,	O
Murphy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
us	O
off	O
till	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
Murphy	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
Muckleroy	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
be	O
paid	O
:	O
Murphy	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
London-bridge	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
wait	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Murphy	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
Mrs.	O
Innis	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
care	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
we	O
left	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
warehouse	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
joins	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
a	O
door	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Muckleroy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
landlord	O
here	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
done	O
to	O
swear	O
away	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
For	O
Muckleroy	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Macartney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Short's-gardens	O
.	O
Muckleroy	O
has	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Lee	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Muckleroy	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
this	O
fact	O
is	O
sworn	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
night	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
rightly	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
very	O
sure	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
bed	O
till	O
11	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Lee	O
lodge	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
in	O
one	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Muckleroy	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
weeks	O
ago	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Muckleroy	O
lay	O
at	O
home	O
every	O
night	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
home	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
taylor	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
every	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Lee	O
often	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
Muckleroy	O
and	O
Lee	O
much	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Macartney	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Muckleroy	O
but	O
goodness	O
and	O
honesty	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
days	O
of	O
my	O
breath	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Conder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
bread	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Kelly	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
Lee	O
's	O
request	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
aunt	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
lately	O
discharged	O
from	O
the	O
army	O
.	O
Courtney	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Murphy	O
and	O
Lee	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
father-in-law	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
Lee	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
pawn	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
aunt	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Muckleroy	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Murphy	O
and	O
Courtney	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
242	O
,	O
243	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
William	I-pers
Tanner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
one	O
china	O
punch-bowl	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
brass	O
sconces	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
earthen	O
cows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
china	O
swans	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
ten	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
twelve	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
china	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
branch	O
of	O
shell-flowers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
glass	O
decanter	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
ostrich	O
's	O
egg	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
leather	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
gunpowder	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
shot	O
,	O
three	O
stone	O
bottles	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
quarts	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Canner	I-pers
,	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Fishmonger's-hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Hagerstone	B-place
:	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
that	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
buffet	O
stripped	O
of	O
punch-bowls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
servants	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Farr	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
window	O
up	O
stairs	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
screw	O
'd	O
down	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
bottom	O
and	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
shutters	O
open	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiring	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
garden	O
,	O
with	O
flower-roots	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Hager-stone	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
at	O
play	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
me	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
boy	O
seeing	O
that	O
,	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
:	O
he	O
sadly	O
wanted	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
father	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
ostrich	O
's	O
egg	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
china	O
tea	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
punch	O
bowl	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
sconces	O
which	O
were	O
put	O
up	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
leather	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
owned	O
the	O
boy	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
all	O
there	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
road	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
mother	O
,	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
mistake	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
auction	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
will	O
they	O
give	O
you	O
brandy	O
and	O
rum	O
,	O
powder	O
and	O
shot	O
at	O
an	O
auction	O
?	O
In	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
a	O
stone	O
bottle	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
bottle	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
daddy	O
's	O
,	O
touch	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
dare	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
Bradley	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
assisted	O
at	O
an	O
auction	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
his	O
trouble	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
they	O
?	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
accuse	O
an	O
innocent	O
person	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
alehouse	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
:	O
he	O
there	O
impeached	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bonam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
being	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Bonam	O
cut	O
his	O
hands	O
with	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
Bonam	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
We	O
examined	O
his	O
hand	O
where	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
cut	O
in	O
his	O
finger	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
proof	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
house	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
would	O
be	O
bound	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
gentleman	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
bound	O
for	O
a	O
farthing	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
and	O
slipt	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
accused	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Brodrick	I-pers
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
accuse	O
him	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
:	O
now	O
the	O
boy	O
says	O
that	O
Brodrick	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
the	O
justices	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
the	O
father	O
:	O
on	O
coming	O
home	O
one	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
tavern	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
is	O
about	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
lie	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
forge	O
:	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
some	O
old	O
iron	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Banbridge	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
shop	O
at	O
Hagerstone	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Lilley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Jack	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
many	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Father	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
various	O
excuses	O
,	O
uncommon	O
for	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
its	O
mother	O
's	O
belly	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
The	O
Father	O
guilty	O
,	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
244	O
,	O
245	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Story	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Christopher	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Story	I-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lawrence-lane	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
10th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
we	O
sent	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
in	O
Broker's-Row	B-place
,	I-place
Moorefields	I-place
,	O
thirty-five	O
chaldron	O
of	O
coals	O
:	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
there	O
for	O
pressing	O
.	O
We	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
employed	O
to	O
shoot	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
door	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Ingram	O
what	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
coals	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
declared	O
he	O
was	O
absent	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
requested	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
us	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
sent	O
James	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
to	O
to	O
measure	O
the	O
coals	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thistle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
Ingram	O
's	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Stringer	O
take	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sacks	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
Booth	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
large	O
Scotch	O
coals	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
Stringer	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
Ingram	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
at	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
measured	O
the	O
coals	O
at	O
Ingram	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
bushels	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
Stringer	O
called	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smout	I-pers
,	O
and	O
True	O
Jegborn	O
.	O
Booth	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
246	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wacket	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Felix	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Felix	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
in	O
our	O
brew-house	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
leave	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
dung	O
away	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
Whitehart	O
,	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
stoakers	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
reasonable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
frock	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
he	O
sold	O
sixteen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
miles	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
porter	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
frock	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
and	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
his	O
pardon	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frighted	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
247	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
my	O
apprentice	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
behind	O
my	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
button	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
chucked	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
behind	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
three	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
:	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
man	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
unbutton	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
buckle	O
appear	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Blount	I-pers
,	O
the	O
apprentice	O
,	O
confirmed	O
this	O
testimony	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
just	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
248	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oilman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little-Britain	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
had	O
300	O
weight	O
of	O
soap	O
piled	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
morning	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
single	O
cake	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
cakes	O
more	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
one	O
he	O
had	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
cakes	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
soap	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
apprentice	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
soap	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
soap	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
:	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
tea	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
weighed	O
it	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
halpennyworth	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
cake	O
missing	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
five	O
minutes	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
tea	O
:	O
I	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
some	O
soap	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
cloak	O
aside	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
cake	O
of	O
soap	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
sample	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
249	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Murdock	I-pers
was	O
