TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1765	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
EARDLEY	I-pers
WILMOT	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Worthy	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Cantwell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Smith	B-pers
N.	I-pers
Bragrave	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fairsid	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Coster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peirpoint	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
Euclid	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noy	I-pers
,	O
||	O
||	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noy	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Corkhill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Rich	B-pers
Longbottom	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Delaforce	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Delaforce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
over	O
against	O
Spital	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
past	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
a	O
cloak	O
that	O
hung	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
unpinn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
two	O
customers	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pop	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
in	O
Primrose-street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
cloak	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fountain	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
was	O
near	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Fountain	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
60	O
yards	O
distance	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cloak	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
cloak	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
cloak	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
quart	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Middlemarsh	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
glass-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
old	O
barge-house	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Middlemarsh	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
,	O
are	O
partners	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
four	O
porters	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
quart	O
bottles	O
to	O
different	O
customers	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
landed	O
at	O
Black-lion-stairs	B-place
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
basket	O
with	O
six	O
dozen	O
.	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witnesses	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
in	O
Hungerford	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
bottles	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
prittle	O
baskets	O
,	O
the	O
farthest	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
quite	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hounsworth	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
led	O
me	O
through	O
Church	O
court	O
and	O
Round	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
pitching-place	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
White	O
Horse	O
lane	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
three-pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hounsworth	O
informed	O
the	O
porter	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hoy	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
basket	O
and	O
bottles	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hounsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
,	O
a	O
wine	O
merchant	O
,	O
who	O
trades	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
dusk	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Black-lion-stairs	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
prittle	O
basket	O
of	O
bottles	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
some	O
bottles	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Vere-street	O
,	O
Clare	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
broken	O
glass	O
bottles	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
16	O
bottles	O
;	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
new	O
ones	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
broken	O
glass	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
(	O
a	O
basket	O
and	O
bottles	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
name	O
Grant	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
's	O
porters	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
prittle	O
basket	O
with	O
six	O
dozen	O
bottles	O
of	O
our	O
master	O
's	O
lost	O
from	O
Black-lion	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
to	O
Albemarle-street	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Grant	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hounsworth	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
porter	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
Hungerford	O
market	O
,	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prittle	O
and	O
these	O
bottles	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hoy	O
's	O
(	O
here	O
produced	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
basket	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
our	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bottles	O
also	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
none	O
like	O
them	O
made	O
nay	O
where	O
else	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
these	O
men	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
July	O
22	O
,	O
for	O
obtaining	O
20	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Wenman	O
and	O
Co.	O
but	O
the	O
indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
wrong	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
ell	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
ell	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Russia	O
linen	O
cloath	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
wrapping	O
callicoe	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Gerard-street	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
have	O
left	O
off	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holland-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
things	O
till	O
I	O
can	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
your	O
Servant	O
?	O
G.	O
Sheldon	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
just	O
a	O
fortnight	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
our	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
lodge	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
that	O
room	O
at	O
times	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
I	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
dead	O
drunk	O
and	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Deblee	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
we	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
pickle	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
that	O
morning	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
out	O
an	O
apron	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
morning	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
both	O
a	O
thief	O
and	O
a	O
drunkard	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
muslin	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
awaked	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
'	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
unlock	O
her	O
box	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
wrapping	O
callicoe	O
,	O
then	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
shop	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
unlock	O
her	O
trunk	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
with	O
our	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
inquiry	O
,	O
got	O
another	O
piece	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
with	O
Anne	B-pers
Cifford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
off	O
business	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Deblee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
live	O
together	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lodges	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sheldon	O
desired	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
one	O
day	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
pickle	O
her	O
maid	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
drunk	O
and	O
asleep	O
;	O
we	O
awaked	O
her	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
Mrs.	O
Sheldon	O
has	O
mentioned	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
trunk	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Deblee	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
out	O
an	O
apron	O
of	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
(	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
asleep	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
awaked	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
evidences	O
had	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Suffolk-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
Russia	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
two	O
shifts	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
an	O
uncle	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
lawn	O
and	O
muslin	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
callicoe	O
lying	O
among	O
some	O
rubbish	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
very	O
little	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ogle	I-pers
,	O
November	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Ogle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
servants	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
silver	O
spoons	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
servants	O
.	O
She	O
happened	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
her	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
servants	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
strict	O
examination	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
spoons	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
pledged	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
girl	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
she	O
is	O
got	O
among	O
bad	O
people	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
since	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
these	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
she	O
brought	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
8	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
she	O
brought	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Dennis	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
paste	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
five	O
paste	O
breast	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
paste	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
October	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
parlour	O
behind	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
between	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
shop	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
were	O
not	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
break	O
,	O
the	O
coaches	O
making	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
outside	O
sash	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
shop	O
window-shutters	O
were	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
porter	O
that	O
shuts	O
up	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
windows	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
observed	O
the	O
broken	O
glass	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
missed	O
three	O
paste	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
and	O
eleven	O
breast	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
glass	O
was	O
whole	O
that	O
afternoon	O
?	O
Symonds	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
whole	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
A	O
lad	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
broke	O
my	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
persons	O
:	O
so	O
that	O
lad	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Dennis	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
by	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
wire	O
from	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
hook	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
proper	O
instrument	O
to	O
hook	O
things	O
to	O
them	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shire-lane	O
,	O
Temple	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Wynn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Shields	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
at	O
this	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
nibbling	O
at	O
the	O
glass	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
:	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
half	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
Hearing	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Shields	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
errand	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
upon	O
?	O
Wynn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
cobler	O
for	O
some	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
this	O
shop	O
?	O
Wynn	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
between	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
and	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
between	O
14	O
and	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Dennis	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
at	O
the	O
play-houses	O
lighting	O
of	O
links	O
,	O
and	O
Rich	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
every	O
night	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Shields	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
another	O
lad	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
again	O
:	O
there	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
broke	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
met	O
Rich	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
Shields	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
intent	O
upon	O
that	O
particular	O
window	O
before	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Shields	O
told	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
get	O
some	O
silver	O
breast-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
told	O
Rich	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
.	O
Shields	O
broke	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
pushed	O
the	O
glass	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
wire	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
hooked	O
out	O
five	O
breast-buckles	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
Rich	O
one	O
:	O
then	O
Shields	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
six	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
Rich	O
went	O
.	O
Shields	O
gave	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
a	O
girl	O
to	O
put	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
broke	O
the	O
stones	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
odd	O
shoe-buckle	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
that	O
had	O
iron	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
for	O
old	O
silver	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
near	O
Leicester-fields	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
that	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
bulk	O
by	O
Whitehall	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
appointed	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Coal-yard	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
buckles	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
them	O
in	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
met	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
woman	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
We	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
towards	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Eagle-court	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe-buckles	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
we	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
Shields	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
that	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
stolen	O
:	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
so	O
she	O
gave	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
Shields	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
away	O
with	O
your	O
clumsy	O
hands	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
nothing	O
.	O
Shields	O
desired	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
some	O
breast-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pawned	O
three	O
breast-buckles	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
bought	O
some	O
ham	O
and	O
bread	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
shilling	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
silver-smith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
till	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
One	O
Wilkins	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
90	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Shields	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
night	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
and	O
discharged	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
some	O
silver	O
spoons	O
~	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
tried	O
.	O
~	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
ing	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
glass	O
shoved	O
in	O
as	O
the	O
lad	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Shields	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
call	O
Sweepey	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
wire	O
twisted	O
up	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
bag	O
,	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
This	O
bag	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Shields	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
wire	O
is	O
what	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
hook	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
windows	O
with	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
Fleming	O
up	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
One	O
Wilkins	O
took	O
up	O
Brown	O
,	O
Rich	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
confined	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
pledged	O
these	O
buckles	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
shoe-buckles	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
9	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
Eagle-court	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
years	O
or	O
better	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
think	O
such	O
buckles	O
as	O
these	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
hardly	O
one	O
in	O
twenty	O
of	O
those	O
sort	O
of	O
girls	O
but	O
what	O
have	O
such	O
buckles	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
buckles	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
20	O
s.	O
Shields	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Rich	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
nor	O
offered	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
that	O
Shields	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Fleming	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Catherine-street	O
.	O
The	O
boys	O
met	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
them	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
nor	O
after	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Shields	O
.	O
I	O
wanting	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
I	O
once	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
a	O
stationer	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Shields	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Rich	O
and	O
Fleming	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Wooley	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
8	O
guineas	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
my	O
mare	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Fig-lane	B-place
and	O
Tottenham-court	B-place
turnpike	I-place
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
mare	O
some	O
water	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
rode	O
gently	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
when	O
Wilkins	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
left-hand	O
side	O
with	O
a	O
cutlass	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
mare	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
foot	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
his	O
cutlass	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
oaths	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Stop	O
,	O
stop	O
;	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
knees	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
cutlasses	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
horse	O
pistol	O
:	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Scott	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
any	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
loose	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
near	O
ten	O
guineas	O
.	O
Scott	O
weighed	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
almost	O
pulled	O
my	O
shirt	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
destroy	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
watch	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
my	O
glove	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
silver	O
;	O
then	O
Wilkins	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Scott	O
had	O
got	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
spurs	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
only	O
plated	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
knee-buckles	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Scott	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
ever	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
Wilkins	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
pretty	O
low	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
both	O
hands	O
from	O
my	O
breast-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
all	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
pulled	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
mare	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
another	O
8	O
guineas	O
,	O
another	O
6	O
l.	O
made	O
payable	O
to	O
me	O
or	O
order	O
.	O
Neither	O
pocketbook	O
nor	O
notes	O
have	O
been	O
seen	O
since	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
whip	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
towards	O
Fig-lane	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
cart	O
coming	O
caused	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
soon	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
since	O
at	O
New-Prison	O
and	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
both	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
their	O
persons	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Wilkins	O
about	O
Covent-Garden	O
with	O
the	O
chairmen	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
rode	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Wilkins	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
without	O
using	O
me	O
so	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Scott	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
they	O
knew	O
me	O
directly	O
.	O
When	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
Wilkins	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Scott	O
would	O
say	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
without	O
Sir	O
John	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
oath	O
.	O
Wilkins	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
cropt	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
bragging	O
what	O
money	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
they	O
spent	O
it	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
among	O
the	O
boys	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
called	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
cutlass	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
mentioned	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
besides	O
8	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
serve	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
serve	O
you	O
:	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
you	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
your	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
safe	O
enough	O
:	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Monk	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
ring	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
did	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
whip	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
flung	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
,	O
near	O
Marybone	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
examined	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
tell	O
no	O
tales	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
it	O
and	O
notes	O
and	O
all	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
book	O
to	O
Scott	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
notes	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
Wilkins	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
ring	O
off	O
(	O
the	O
ring	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Timperall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
of	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Timperall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-court	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
a	O
five	O
and-threepenny-piece	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
ounce	O
(	O
the	O
buckles	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Rich	O
.	O
Church	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
or	O
26th	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
come	O
through	O
Catherine-court	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Wilkins	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
jacket	O
and	O
trousers	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
:	O
he	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
flourished	O
it	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
times	O
.	O
He	O
talked	O
to	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
After	O
seeing	O
some	O
advertisements	O
about	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
people	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
we	O
apprehended	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
that	O
turns	O
out	O
of	O
Cross-lane	O
up	O
into	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
at	O
first	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
tears	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
own	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
this	O
court	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
plead	O
guilty	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
apprehended	O
some	O
suspicious	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
Scott	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
we	O
took	O
Wilkins	O
)	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Catherine-court	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
he	O
informed	O
us	O
where	O
Wilkins	O
lodged	O
:	O
Scott	O
mentioned	O
him	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Wooley	I-pers
a	O
painter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bryan	O
an	O
anchor-smith	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
partly	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
apprehended	O
Wilkins	O
first	O
:	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
others	O
got	O
scent	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Scott	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
and	O
seal	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
||	O
Scott	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
about	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Wilkins	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
chain	O
and	O
seal	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lines	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haliburton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Scott	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Wilkins	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
shot	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
gang	O
in	O
the	O
knee	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
lame	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Scott	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
powder	O
and	O
slugs	O
in	O
Wilkins	O
's	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
pistols	O
were	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Wooley	I-pers
had	O
them	O
;	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
several	O
times	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hoped	O
Sir	O
John	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
book	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
from	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
for	O
a	O
book	O
.	O
Wilkins	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
last	O
evidences	O
are	O
bad	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
goes	O
to	O
bawdy	O
houses	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
girls	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
thief-takers	O
,	O
that	O
does	O
this	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
seas	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
did	O
my	O
duty	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
and	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
at	O
Belleisle	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
I	O
inlisted	O
as	O
an	O
East-India	O
soldier	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
inlist	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Catherine-street	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
plenty	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
leave	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
;	O
Wooley	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
will	O
cross	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
dirty	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
clapt	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
our	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
rode	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
trembling	O
.	O
Wooley	O
met	O
another	O
gentleman	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
immediately	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
stood	O
shaking	O
,	O
fearing	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
those	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
back	O
I	O
will	O
treat	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
Wooley	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Scott	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Wooley	O
got	O
me	O
in	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
shot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
knee	O
with	O
a	O
horse-pistol	O
;	O
Wilkins	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
shot	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
Scott	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
his	O
father	O
24	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
at	O
sea	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
before	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
youth	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
unlucky	O
boy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
theft	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Treeketchin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
family	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
fallen	O
into	O
very	O
bad	O
company	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nickolls	I-pers
.	O
Scott	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
faithful	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
?	O
Nickolls	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
misdemeanor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
wild	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anderton	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Anderton	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
on	O
oil	O
and	O
colour	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Mark-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Tower-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
grind	O
colours	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
times	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
had	O
stole	O
some	O
soap	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
saw-dust	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
fetch	O
some	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
a	O
little	O
bulky	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
something	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
looked	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
bulge	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
soap	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
rest	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
soap	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
stole	O
any	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
piece	O
to	O
wash	O
his	O
hands	O
with	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
.	O
Roberts	O
the	O
servant	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
soap	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
but	O
one	O
piece	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
hands	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
widow	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jane	I-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
,	O
October	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Abraham	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
in	I-place
Little	I-place
Britain	I-place
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
aniseed	O
,	O
or	O
gin	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
this	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
aside	O
her	O
cloake	O
,	O
and	O
sawit	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ballow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
grate	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
brass	O
stove	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
washing	O
our	O
engine	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
grate	O
from	O
the	O
ruins	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
at	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Cobley	I-pers
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
St.	O
Hellen	O
's	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
we	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
proper	O
owner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
about	O
the	O
Four	O
Swans	O
,	O
or	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
engine	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
grate	O
was	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Margeram	O
,	O
a	O
tin-man	O
.	O
My	O
Lord-Mayor	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
grate	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cobley	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
that	O
Parker	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fountain	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
a	O
grate	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
)	O
lying	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Margeram	O
's	O
ruins	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
upon	O
the	O
ruins	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stove	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
ruins	O
.	O
They	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
escape	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
ruins	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
13	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Nathaniel	I-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Catherine	I-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Catherine	O
Bolton	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
;	O
100	O
yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
gauze	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
200	O
yards	O
of	O
striped	O
gauze	O
,	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
plain	O
gauze	O
,	O
48	O
gauze	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
lawn	O
,	O
50	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
30	O
gauze	O
caps	O
,	O
50	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
one	O
duffil	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
36	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
serge	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
October	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
but	O
keep	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	B-place
.	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
shop	O
safe	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
goods	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
all	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
Mr.	O
Bruin	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
sware	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
recollecting	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
of	O
that	O
gauze	O
,	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
gauze	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
gauze	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
housewife	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
also	O
several	O
lappets	O
made	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
remnants	O
of	O
lace	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
box	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
cap	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
another	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
.	O
Under	O
the	O
dresser	O
one	O
plain	O
gauze	O
flowered	O
bordered	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
gauze	O
laced	O
mob	O
,	O
one	O
queen	O
's	O
mob	O
,	O
one	O
queen	O
's	O
round	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
blue	O
ribbon	O
,	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
edging	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
trimmings	O
of	O
my	O
red	O
cardinal	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Kennet	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
coat	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
sometimes	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sometime	O
swent	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
foot	O
on	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
board	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
with	O
a	O
dirty	O
print	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
foot	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Inspected	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Kennet	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bruin	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
gauze	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
gauze	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
cockloft	O
,	O
a	O
hole	O
was	O
broke	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
communication	O
with	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
woman	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
floor	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
she	O
handed	O
through	O
were	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
blue	O
serge	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
other	O
gauze	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
with	O
caps	O
and	O
ribbons	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
appeared	O
in	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Wilks	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
is	O
turned	O
quack-doctor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
open	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bruin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
sent	O
a	O
warning	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
a	O
shop	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
lawns	O
and	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
that	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
about	O
enough	O
for	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
for	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
to	O
sell	O
gauze	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
some	O
linen	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Beal	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
gauze	O
would	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fetch	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
she	O
walked	O
out	O
very	O
orderly	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Beal	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
got	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
lived	O
long	O
with	O
that	O
man	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hunsdon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
make	O
gauze	O
caps	O
for	O
the	O
shops	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
eight	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Beal	O
of	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
produced	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
matched	O
for	O
quality	O
and	O
colour	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Beal	O
.	O
The	O
lace	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
housewife	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
housewife	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
housewife	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
chid	O
him	O
for	O
staying	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
sister	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
brought	O
something	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
reconciled	O
:	O
he	O
produced	O
several	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
of	O
his	O
sister	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
with	O
this	O
housewife	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
carried	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Jane	B-pers
Dimson	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Kingcart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Tharrol	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
14.	O
Anne	B-pers
Tovey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Vigers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
November	O
13	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Hannah	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
shop	O
in	O
Chandler-street	B-place
,	I-place
Grosvenor	I-place
square	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
before	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
who	O
is	O
aged	O
about	O
18	O
,	O
was	O
up	O
alone	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
is	O
lame	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
well	O
come	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
below	O
in	O
our	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
fustian	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
October	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
in	O
town	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
An	O
account	O
was	O
brought	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
20th	O
from	O
Richmond	B-place
,	O
that	O
our	O
stable	O
there	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
my	O
cloaths	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
room	O
above	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
night	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
secured	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
hand	O
bills	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
brought	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
my	O
thickset	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
in	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
's	O
gardens	O
these	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
father-in-law	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
,	O
is	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
's	O
head	O
gardener	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
gardens	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Richmond	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
:	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
the	O
gardener	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
friends	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
hot-house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
hot-house	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
looked	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Young	O
man	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
your	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
lately	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
pray	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
such	O
a	O
day	O
?	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
thickset	O
frock	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
them	O
withoutside	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
on	O
some	O
dung	O
against	O
a	O
tree	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jowlan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
White-lion-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
those	O
cloaths	O
mentioned	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
frock	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
for	O
24	O
s.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
bill	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
pledged	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
This	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
of	O
Richmond	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
cloaths	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
that	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
gardens	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
for	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
,	O
owed	O
him	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
those	O
cloaths	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
pay	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
I	O
hurt	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
following	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
frock	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
places	O
at	O
Fulham	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
24	O
s.	O
He	O
called	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goad	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Caroline-court	B-place
,	I-place
Saffron-hill	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
ready	O
furnished	O
of	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
bolt	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
staple	O
,	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
missing	O
:	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
one	O
blanket	O
;	O
the	O
wife	O
owned	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
gave	O
them	O
three	O
days	O
to	O
produce	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
sheets	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
somebody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Justice	O
gave	O
you	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
receive	O
them	O
?	O
Carlton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
,	O
fearing	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
do	O
right	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
the	O
things	O
forthcoming	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
word	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
just	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
nor	O
when	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Macky	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
feloniously	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Macky	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Hog-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
awake	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
rumbling	O
noise	O
:	O
I	O
lay	O
still	O
a	O
while	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
gently	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
through	O
the	O
crevices	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
window	O
close	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
light	O
was	O
then	O
put	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
somebody	O
striving	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
watchmen	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
wrenching	O
tool	O
;	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
candles	O
and	O
tallow	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
besides	O
;	O
the	O
hatch	O
was	O
removed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
window	O
fastened	O
?	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bolt	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
slipper	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
nails	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
bolt	O
from	O
going	O
back	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
bent	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
wrenching	O
tool	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
Larimer	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
open	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
great-coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
wrench	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
he	O
hummed	O
and	O
hawed	O
:	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Larimer	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
testimony	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
fall	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
watchmen	O
were	O
asked	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
s	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Suffolk	O
to	O
enter	O
upon	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
porter	O
to	O
Lord	O
Orweil	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
pretty	O
freely	O
with	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
:	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
invitation	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
in	O
Montague-street	B-place
:	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
candle	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
it	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
:	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
challenged	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
:	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
being	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
Murphy	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
shut	O
out	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
Eyles	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
?	O
Jefferys	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
about	O
her	O
having	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
Eyles	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
gave	O
.	O
)	O
Murphy	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
rum	O
:	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
somebody	O
that	O
should	O
make	O
me	O
.	O
Eyles	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
dram	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Murphy	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Eyles	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Whittall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Gertrude	B-pers
Lady	I-pers
Kerry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pigg	I-pers
,	O
September	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Pigg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Lady	O
Kerry	O
:	O
about	O
nine	O
weeks	O
ago	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
silver	O
spoon	O
missing	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
sometimes	O
:	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
another	O
,	O
both	O
with	O
a	O
crest	O
on	O
them	O
:	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
grey	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
one	O
night	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Richmond	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
box	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
lodged	O
near	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Meuse	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
pray	O
Mr.	O
Whittall	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
home	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
all	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Lady	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
expected	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
supported	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
scandal	O
to	O
the	O
breeches	O
to	O
be	O
supported	O
by	O
a	O
wife	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
together	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
an	O
hundred	O
hand-bills	O
printed	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
spoons	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crane-court	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
:	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Fleming	O
,	O
junior	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pigg	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
hand-bill	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
tablespoons	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Clean	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
with	O
silver	O
buttons	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Crosland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edmund	O
,	O
November	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Edmund	B-pers
Crosland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Silver-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
hackney	O
coaches	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
plate	O
buttons	O
on	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
another	O
affair	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round-house	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
buttons	O
off	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
coat	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
buttons	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
saddle	O
to	O
a	O
stage-coachman	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Holborn	O
(	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
buttons	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
dead	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
named	O
Coley	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
took	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
buttons	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
another	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
White-horse-yard	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
my	O
bedchamber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
advertistised	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
,	O
the	O
chief	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
mentioned	O
,	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
26	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
taylor	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
delivered	O
the	O
cloaths	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
alter	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
denied	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Timothy	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Anne	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	O
:	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
and	I-place
Two	I-place
Necks	I-place
in	I-place
Tothill-street	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
a	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Newington	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
benighted	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
decayed	O
gentleman	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
to	O
transact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Drake	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Drew	O
:	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
my	O
maid	O
missed	O
a	O
copper	O
coffee-pot	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
,	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
coffee-pot	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-way	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brazier	O
and	O
broker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coffee-pot	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
showed	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
insanity	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
November	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
coal-merchant	O
at	O
Stamford-hill	B-place
:	O
the	O
boots	O
and	O
shoes	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
hole	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
mitts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Moses	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-road	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
'Squire	O
Allen	O
in	O
Wigmore-street	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
keeper	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
stockings	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
directly	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
maid	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
in	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
with	O
two	O
constables	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
constables	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
mitts	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
stole	O
myself	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
desire	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
been	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
having	O
committed	O
all	O
himself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Christian	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
mitts	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
and	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
;	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
thickset	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
jacket	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
November	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
of	O
Richmond	B-place
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
our	O
stable	O
there	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
:	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
old	O
cloths-man	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
stopt	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
coats	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
.	O
A	O
person	O
offered	O
me	O
those	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
them	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pockets	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
:	O
he	O
looks	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
that	O
way	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Elizabeth	O
Francis	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
and	O
stuff	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
M'Neal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Fleece	B-place
at	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
goods	O
to	O
Hertford	O
fair	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
:	O
they	O
supped	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
:	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
ironing	O
:	O
she	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
linen	O
into	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
they	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
above	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
water	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
maid	O
:	O
they	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
room	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room-door	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
:	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
going	O
in	O
:	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
search	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
:	O
from	O
underneath	O
him	O
we	O
pulled	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
,	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
feather-bed	O
and	O
the	O
bedstead	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
sent	O
the	O
ostler	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rud	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
:	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rud	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
her	O
carrying	O
the	O
linen	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
below	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
leaving	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
mistrusted	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
finding	O
some	O
water	O
spilt	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
maid	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
aprons	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
and	O
done	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
huffed	O
her	O
for	O
finding	O
fault	O
with	O
his	O
goods	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	O
November	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
and	O
carpenter	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
from	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
direction	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
he	O
ordered	O
two	O
journey	O
men	O
bakers	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
pumps	O
from	O
pawn	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
one	O
pair	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Lightfoot	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
send	O
an	O
order	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
send	O
them	O
.	O
An	O
order	O
was	O
sent	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pawn-brokers	O
came	O
with	O
one	O
pair	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
S	O
S	O
,	O
my	O
mark	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
answer	O
they	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
pawn-broker	O
was	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
shoes	O
pawned	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
name	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
then	O
they	O
produced	O
them	O
,	O
marked	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
pledged	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
pawn-brokers	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
pumps	O
in	O
of	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
pledge	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hilman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
cheque	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
November	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
to	O
nurse	O
her	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
coloured	O
aprons	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
bewitched	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
hear	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
as	O
many	O
things	O
out	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
7	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
absconded	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
prayer	O
book	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
recommended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
together	O
:	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawn	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
insisted	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
justice	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
my	O
prayer	O
book	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
coloured	O
aprons	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wright	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hance	O
,	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
by	O
Soho-square	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
are	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
At	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
St.	O
Anne	O
's	O
court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
several	O
things	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
leave	O
your	O
wife	O
so	O
destitute	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
pawn	O
her	O
things	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Only	O
once	O
:	O
she	O
sent	O
out	O
a	O
gown	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
never	O
mentioned	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
china	O
cup	O
,	O
a	O
china	O
saucer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Marten	I-pers
,	O
November	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Lazarus	B-pers
Mordecai	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
oranges	O
and	O
lemons	O
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mount-street	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
marked	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Moses	B-pers
Manuell	I-pers
by	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
somebody	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
bent	O
them	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
sent	O
Moses	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
spoons	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
mistress	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
Kitty	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Manuell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
old	O
cloathsman	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
