TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Arnold	B-pers
Finchett	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
Thornthwaite	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jackes	I-pers
,	O
Zechariah	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Holehouse	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Sidebottom	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Minnet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Arrow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Toone	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Briscall	I-pers
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Sulch	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Frankland	I-pers
.	O
110	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
Penson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
ham	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sumerville	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Sumerville	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Grafton-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
served	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
cry	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
catched	O
a	O
thief	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
neighbour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bramwell	O
,	O
holding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
ham	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
betwixt	O
their	O
legs	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
three	O
hams	O
lying	O
,	O
the	O
uppermost	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
uppermost	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
smoak-dried	O
one	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Grafton-street	O
.	O
Betwixt	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
imagined	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
almost	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
walked	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suspected	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
ham	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sumerville	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
the	O
ham	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
111	O
,	O
112	O
,	O
113	O
,	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
10	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
1	O
linen	O
shaving	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
14	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Merest	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
2	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
boat	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
;	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Foy	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
3	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
2	O
napkins	O
,	O
7	O
towells	O
,	O
2	O
shifts	O
,	O
1	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
apron	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
December	O
17	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Merest	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
Cloysters	O
Westminster	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Watkins	O
at	O
Laleham	O
:	O
she	O
washes	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
unlock	O
and	O
lock	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
pack	O
them	O
up	O
?	O
E.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
last	O
December	O
,	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
West	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
from	O
Chertsey	O
and	O
the	O
west	O
country	O
,	O
to	O
Queenhithe	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
received	O
the	O
box	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Watkins	O
at	O
Laleham	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
near	O
Stanes	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
and	O
tied	O
round	O
with	O
a	O
cord	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Watkins	O
delivered	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
safe	O
,	O
locked	O
and	O
corded	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
boat	O
at	O
Chertsey	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
Scotland-yard	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
many	O
brooms	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
we	O
laid	O
them	O
out	O
upon	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
wharf	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
put	O
the	O
box	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
brooms	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
tired	O
and	O
hungry	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
our	O
boat	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
tide	O
having	O
in	O
part	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
and	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
brooms	O
thrown	O
about	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
betwixt	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
box	O
directed	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
Esq	O
;	O
Merest	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Cloysters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
leave	O
a	O
person	O
on	O
board	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
all	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
morning	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Merest	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
advice	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
hand	O
bills	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
served	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Walker	O
before	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
Black-friars	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Swan	O
;	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
empty	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Lambeth	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
several	O
things	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
boat	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
box	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
tried	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Walker	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
Lambeth	O
said	O
they	O
stole	O
a	O
boat	O
and	O
rowed	O
up	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
gentleman	O
call	O
for	O
oars	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Whitehall	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
west-country	O
barge	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
nothing	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
vessel	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
broom-boat	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
her	O
stern	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
at	O
the	O
cabbin	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
prize	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
let	O
's	O
heave	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
sell	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sit	O
ourselves	O
out	O
for	O
sea	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hole	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
rope	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
upon	O
the	O
bulk	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
put	O
a	O
rope	O
through	O
the	O
iron	O
handles	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
lowering	O
it	O
down	O
into	O
their	O
boat	O
it	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
over-board	O
,	O
near	O
Scotland-yard	O
;	O
they	O
rowed	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
close	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Lambeth	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
.	O
Diana	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
box	O
of	O
linen	O
from	O
the	O
waterman	O
:	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
mentions	O
the	O
things	O
by	O
name	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Laleham	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
washed	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
with	O
this	O
key	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
corded	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
twopenny	O
cord	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
direction	O
on	O
it	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Merest	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Little	O
Cloysters	O
Westminster	O
abbey	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
waterman	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
asked	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
Lambeth	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
rowed	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
Walker	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
as	O
Lambeth	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
sir	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
said	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
box	O
open	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
bought	O
this	O
linen	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Whitmore	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
shoes	O
near	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
came	O
to	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
(	O
producing	O
three	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
six	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shaving-cloth	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bennet	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
E.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
linen	O
was	O
all	O
marked	O
I.	O
M.	O
and	O
numbered	O
.	O
Whitmore	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
brought	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Welch	O
directly	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
buying	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
some	O
sheets	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
asked	O
Welch	O
about	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
take	O
this	O
key	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
open	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
there	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
some	O
sheets	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
hinge	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
broke	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
Foy	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
some	O
linen	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
(	O
producing	O
more	O
linen	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
D.	O
Watkins	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
sent	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
)	O
.	O
Israel	O
Saunders	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Lambeth	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
jacket	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
bought	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
of	O
you	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
sold	O
you	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
bargain	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
and	O
table-cloths	O
that	O
would	O
cover	O
a	O
whole	O
room	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
frigate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
that	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
was	O
killed	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Walker	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
brother	O
by	O
the	O
father	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
b-to	O
-	O
s	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
mother	O
of	O
many	O
things	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
things	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
for	O
14	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
what	O
was	O
worth	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
guineas	O
,	O
to	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
names	O
Welch	O
and	O
Foy	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
bills	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
being	O
stolen	O
into	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
double	O
ell	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
handcuffs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
boys	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
shirts	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
we	O
bought	O
them	O
two	O
cheque	O
ones	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
others	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Welch	O
and	O
Foy	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
dealers	O
;	O
they	O
buy	O
kitchen	O
stuff	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
what	O
they	O
buy	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
they	O
are	O
come	O
by	O
(	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
shirts	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
E.	O
Bennet	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
)	O
.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
These	O
sheets	O
are	O
worth	O
two	O
guineas	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
Walker	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
sea	O
in	O
an	O
east	O
country	O
ship	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
relation	O
in	O
Lambeth	O
parish	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Westminster	O
bridge	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Swan	O
:	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
boat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
carry	O
us	O
under	O
six-pence	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
napkin	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
shirt	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
we	O
bought	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
without	O
we	O
bought	O
the	O
whole	O
lump	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
bought	O
the	O
whole	O
tote	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
saw	O
these	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
do	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
these	O
women	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
that	O
man	O
stopped	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
prison	O
the	O
ship	O
sailed	O
.	O
She	O
lay	O
at	O
Rotherhithe	O
,	O
and	O
belongs	O
to	O
Gottenburg	O
.	O
Lambeth	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
Welch	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
young	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
they	O
shewed	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
for	O
them	O
for	O
23	O
shillings	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
mother	O
was	O
killed	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
9	O
years	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
buried	O
her	O
directly	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Foy	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Welch	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
.	O
Walker	O
and	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
Welch	O
and	O
Foy	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Coventry-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
brother	O
to	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
weeks	O
ago	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
sent	O
a	O
constable	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
silver	O
spoon	O
was	O
shewed	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
brother	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
his	O
brother	O
from	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
blacks	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
,	O
name	O
Flyn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Flyn	O
.	O
There	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Swinton	O
's	O
drawers	O
,	O
while	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
pantry	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
some	O
victuals	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
stove	O
grate	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
January	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
3	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
grate	O
from	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
grate	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
shillings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plasterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sheet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
My	O
baker	O
being	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
cheese	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
was	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
sheet	O
:	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
name	O
Young	O
,	O
near	O
Shoreditch	O
church	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stodard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d	O
,	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
bed	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
,	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
lett	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
wrong	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
December	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bellamy	O
's	O
in	O
James-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
necessary	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
after	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
that	O
pocket	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Shele	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark-court	O
,	O
by	O
Exeter	O
'Change	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
there	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
:	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
three	O
times	O
over	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
to	O
what	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
heard	O
Benson	O
cry	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
hold	O
on	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
duty	O
upon	O
Whitehall	O
guard	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
my	O
pay	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
refresh	O
myself	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
he	O
forced	O
himself	O
into	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
or	O
a	O
pot	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
twopenny	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
boy	O
lighted	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
lighted	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
going	O
to	O
it	O
before	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
struggled	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
eggs	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
120.	O
Owen	B-pers
Cheslyn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bargrove	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
December	O
14	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
without	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
,	O
being	O
but	O
10	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
121	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Solomon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
glass	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
was	O
cracked	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
generally	O
made	O
in	O
dozens	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
this	O
glass	O
was	O
cracked	O
;	O
we	O
pushed	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Abrahams	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
things	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
twelve	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
one	O
piece	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
together	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
detained	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
been	O
tried	O
and	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
122	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Blizard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jellers	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
123	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bramstead	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Bramstead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
sugar-house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Spital-fields	O
from	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
in	O
Buckle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman	I-place
's	I-place
fields	I-place
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
up	O
two	O
air	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
run	O
out	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
way	O
out	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
after	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
candle	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
She	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
struggle	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
murder	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
apron	O
into	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
knife	O
over	O
my	O
throat	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
arm	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
slid	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
doing	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
about	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
minutes	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
came	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Rimington	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
away	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
)	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
using	O
a	O
man	O
ill	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
tell	O
the	O
man	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
owner	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Rimington	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Bramstead	O
.	O
Sebrough	O
Carney	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
does	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
any	O
,	O
she	O
snatched	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
gentleman	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
do	O
not	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
yard	O
,	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rimington	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
other	O
lodgers	O
,	O
men	O
and	O
women	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
man	O
cry	O
murder	O
,	O
murder	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
quitted	O
her	O
lodgings	O
two	O
days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
the	O
old	O
scoundrel	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
watch	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
cutting	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
petticoats	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
thief-taker	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
that	O
woman	O
is	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
124	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
draft	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
102	O
l	O
8	O
s.	O
11	O
d.	O
signed	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huckle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
himself	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
dated	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1764.	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
,	O
January	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Pell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
betwixt	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
to	O
Furnival	O
's	O
Inn	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
several	O
memorandums	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Colebrook	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
102	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
11	O
d.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
book	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Colebrook	I-pers
's	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
should	O
come	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
payment	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
Richards	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Simpson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
a	O
witness	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bullock	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
legacy	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Shirley	O
,	O
who	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
notorious	O
pick-pocket	O
.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
this	O
draft	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Colebrook	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
&	O
c	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mathematical	O
instrument	O
maker	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
changed	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
busy	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Richards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
About	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
gentleman	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Richards	O
?	O
Simpson	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
is	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
proctor	O
in	O
the	O
Commons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
mistaken	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
Shirley	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Shirley	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
left	O
as	O
a	O
legacy	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
declaration	O
you	O
made	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
this	O
draft	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
He	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Richards	O
by	O
then	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Plough	O
,	O
in	O
Black	O
Horse-alley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Shirley	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
met	O
Simpson	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
,	O
Shirley	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Simpson	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Richards	O
:	O
there	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
together	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Simpson	O
.	O
Was	O
Shirley	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Shirley	O
say	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Shirley	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
since	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
125	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
frail	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
50	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Goodson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
frail	O
of	O
raisins	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
frail	O
of	O
raisins	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
frail	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
came	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
raisins	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
gave	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
frail	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
126	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
frail	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
50	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
Goodson	O
,	O
with	O
each	O
a	O
frail	O
on	O
their	O
heads	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
they	O
flung	O
down	O
their	O
frails	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
secured	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
drawer	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
till	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
till	O
strike	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
nobody	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
till	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
call	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Addle-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Philip-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
running	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
or	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
very	O
earnestly	O
at	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
:	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
till	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
one	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Frying-pan	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Staining-lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
with	O
his	O
hair	O
tied	O
behind	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hosley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
men	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
go	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
were	O
running	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
nine	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Philip-lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	O
Hall	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
silver	O
buckles	O
for	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mighell	I-pers
,	O
February	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Mighell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
upon	O
Fish-street	B-place
Hill	I-place
:	O
last	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
boys	O
about	O
my	O
glasses	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
a	O
small	O
hole	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
up	O
Fish-street	O
Hill	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
persons	O
running	O
from	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
robbing	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
past	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Roberts	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
enquired	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
drop	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
hit	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
something	O
like	O
buckles	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
plain	O
silver	O
buckle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
might	O
drop	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kippin	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
other	O
arm	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pocket	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
we	O
found	O
2	O
pair	O
and	O
3	O
odd	O
ones	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
farther	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
long	O
new	O
scarlet	O
cloaks	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
cloaks	O
and	O
buckles	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
passage	O
on	O
Fish	O
street	O
hill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
had	O
two	O
buckles	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
buckles	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Kippin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Champion	O
,	O
in	O
Morgan's-lane	O
,	O
Tooley-street	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
into	O
Lombard-street	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
thought	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
buckles	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Going	O
across	O
Monument-yard	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
surtout	O
coat	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
cloaks	O
and	O
buckles	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
cloaks	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
will	O
and	O
power	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
will	O
and	O
testament	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
,	O
a	O
mariner	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Boscawen	O
Indiaman	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
united	B-pers
company	I-pers
of	I-pers
merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
:	O
laid	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Ynyr	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
8	O
,	O
1765	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Peisley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Faulkner	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
office	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
1765	O
:	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
probate	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
William	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
executor	O
,	O
named	O
in	O
the	O
will	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
a	O
will	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
probate	O
granted	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
not	O
having	O
paid	O
my	O
master	O
:	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
due	O
was	O
50	O
l.	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
30	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
Bank	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burgess	O
the	O
pay-master	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
probate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
demand	O
the	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
?	O
Peisley	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
under	O
that	O
probate	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
and	O
shewed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Mr.	O
Burgess	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
he	O
signed	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
paper	O
.	O
Peisley	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
receipt	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
W.	O
Lane	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
handwriting	O
,	O
one	O
Richardson	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
tavern	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
about	O
the	O
probate	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
knowing	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Captain	O
Arthur	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
captain	O
of	O
the	O
Boscawen	O
Indiaman	O
the	O
last	O
voyage	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
,	O
a	O
mariner	O
on	O
board	O
my	O
ship	O
,	O
died	O
at	O
Calcutta	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
was	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1763	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
My	O
journal	O
will	O
tell	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
looks	O
on	O
it	O
)	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
on	O
our	O
voyage	O
from	O
Bombay	O
to	O
Bengal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
that	O
Duff	O
write	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
(	O
Takes	O
the	O
will	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
witness	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
on	O
board	O
my	O
ship	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
August	O
1763	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
a	O
witness	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
your	O
vessel	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
said	O
from	O
England	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
In	O
May	O
1761	O
,	O
and	O
Duff	O
continued	O
with	O
us	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Bengal	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
purser	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
sailed	O
this	O
voyage	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Duff	O
write	O
,	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
will	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
like	O
his	O
writing	O
;	O
he	O
died	O
at	O
Calcutta	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
this	O
name	O
Brand	O
is	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
often	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
on	O
board	O
our	O
ship	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
your	O
ship	O
at	O
Bengal	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
13	O
months	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
that	O
year	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
sea	O
on	O
her	O
course	O
thithers	O
and	O
she	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1764.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bourk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
13	O
years	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
In	O
last	O
July	O
he	O
was	O
confined	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
distemper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Bourk	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
wife	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
much	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
oftentimes	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
10	O
years	O
and	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
family	O
lived	O
somewhere	O
near	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
through	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
write	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
read	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
will	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
(	O
Takes	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
names	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
.	O
The	O
name	O
Thomas	O
Brand	O
is	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
could	O
write	O
many	O
sorts	O
of	O
hands	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moxey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
1755	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
called	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Monarque	O
,	O
the	O
Magnanime	O
,	O
and	O
Royal	O
William	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
turned	O
over	O
from	O
ship	O
to	O
ship	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
than	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Yuyr	O
Burgess	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
probate	O
of	O
a	O
will	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
William	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
:	O
that	O
person	O
signed	O
a	O
receipt	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
himself	O
the	O
executor	O
named	O
in	O
that	O
will	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
such	O
numbers	O
of	O
people	O
that	O
we	O
pay	O
money	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
sum	O
was	O
exactly	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
paid	O
in	O
a	O
30	O
and	O
20	O
l.	O
Bank	O
note	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Pay-office	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
33	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
always	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
witness	O
receipts	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
to	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
ask	O
executors	O
or	O
administrators	O
where	O
they	O
live	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
any	O
future	O
demand	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
for	O
wages	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
executor	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
direction	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Feathers	O
,	O
on	O
Portsmouth	O
common	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Burgess	O
.	O
If	O
money	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
by	O
you	O
to	O
a	O
false	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
does	O
the	O
loss	O
fall	O
upon	O
?	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
pay	O
any	O
money	O
upon	O
a	O
false	O
demand	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
company	O
issue	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
owners	O
of	O
ships	O
deliver	O
that	O
money	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
commit	O
an	O
error	O
,	O
the	O
company	O
are	O
responsible	O
to	O
the	O
owners	O
of	O
the	O
ships	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
accountable	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
receive	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
would	O
indemnify	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
under	O
a	O
legal	O
authority	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
probate	O
from	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
account	O
with	O
the	O
ships	O
husbands	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
upon	O
myself	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
.	O
The	O
will	O
in	O
question	O
read	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
common	O
form	O
.	O
William	O
Lane	O
,	O
of	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
in	O
Hampshire	O
,	O
executor	O
.	O
Signed	O
Jan.	O
10	O
,	O
1763	O
.	O
Signed	O
,	O
sealed	O
,	O
published	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
receipt	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
received	O
read	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
64	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Signed	O
W.	O
Lane	O
.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
The	O
balance	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
was	O
just	O
sixty	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
by	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
wages	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
commence	O
a	O
prosecution	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
this	O
offence	O
?	O
Burgess	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
,	O
desiring	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Morris	O
of	O
the	O
Boscawen	O
.	O
Richardson	O
was	O
then	O
under	O
sentence	O
of	O
death	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
forging	O
this	O
will	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
proposed	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
pardon	O
.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
promise	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
about	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
several	O
connections	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
will	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
indebted	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
prison	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
you	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
mine	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Duffin	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
likelihood	O
of	O
his	O
dying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
sailors	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Westchester	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
since	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
made	O
his	O
will	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	O
Lane	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
seaman	O
's	O
will	O
.	O
No	O
148.	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
E.	O
Bourk	O
a	O
witness	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Goswell	O
,	O
No	O
41.	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Beckford	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
Bourk	O
against	O
Richardson	O
,	O
No	O
506.	O
in	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
Elizabeth	O
Wood	O
an	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Elizabeth	O
Cox	O
,	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
seaman	O
's	O
will	O
,	O
No	O
436	O
,	O
437.	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Beckford	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Norfolk-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
gun-maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henshaw	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
hooks	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hatton-garden	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
pistols	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
30	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
unfinished	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
15	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
and	O
consequence	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
another	O
pair	O
,	O
silver	O
mounted	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
six	O
guineas	O
for	O
these	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
till	O
somebody	O
came	O
by	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
suspected	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
catched	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
:	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
pistols	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
into	O
the	O
high	O
way	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
here	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
assistance	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
bishop	O
of	O
Ely	O
's	O
gate	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cadwell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Rock	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
running	O
about	O
12	O
yards	O
farther	O
,	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
pistols	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Lambeth	O
Case	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
pistols	O
away	O
so	O
artfully	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
pistols	O
till	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
demanded	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
:	O
coming	O
home	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
church-yard	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
near	O
me	O
stumbled	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
.	O
He	O
claimed	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
show	O
him	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
drink	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
pint	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
half	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
a	O
pair	O
first	O
that	O
were	O
unfinished	O
;	O
a	O
workman	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
4	O
guineas	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
cost	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
more	O
to	O
finish	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
bought	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
pair	O
at	O
home	O
of	O
consequence	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
bring	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
stumbled	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sell	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
pistols	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Elmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
night-man	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
rod	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
church-yard	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
houses	O
:	O
there	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stooped	O
and	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
kept	O
going	O
on	O
towards	O
Catherine-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hanover-street	O
,	O
Long	O
acre	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
look	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
tied	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
We	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hanover	O
street	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
four	O
pistols	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
only	O
once	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
you	O
lived	O
?	O
Elmore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Elmore	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
day	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
subpoena	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
lawyer	O
in	O
Clifford's-inn	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
two	O
letters	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
from	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
Newgate	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
accordingly	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
the	O
letter	O
being	O
signed	O
David	O
Miller	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
person	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
your	O
letters	O
directed	O
to	O
?	O
Elmore	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
.	O
I	O
use	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
leave	O
my	O
rod	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
letters	O
there	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
,	O
night-man	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
,	O
Castle-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
know	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Elmore	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
close	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
mention	O
any	O
mob	O
or	O
fighting	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Janeway	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
letter	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
SIR	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
``	O
see	O
you	O
to-morro	O
w	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
letter	O
``	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
as	O
``	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
``	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
David	O
``	O
Miller	O
.	O
``	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Dated	O
Feb	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
''	O
Acquitted	O
;	O
131	O
,	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
a-la-mode	O
silk	O
,	O
containing	O
70	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
January	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Hermitage	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
silk	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
article	O
I	O
use	O
in	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
to	O
line	O
womens	O
hats	O
and	O
cardinals	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
mentioned	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
an	O
officer	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
Anthony	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
silk	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Fox	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
,	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mary	O
Brown	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
to	O
her	O
apartment	O
,	O
by	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
part	O
in	O
a	O
band	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
:	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
run	O
into	O
two	O
petticoats	O
(	O
some	O
silk	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
lost	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
two	O
different	O
pieces	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
papers	O
,	O
30	O
of	O
half	O
ell	O
,	O
and	O
42	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
3	O
quarters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
measured	O
this	O
you	O
produce	O
here	O
?	O
Horner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
measure	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Horner	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
26	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
24	O
of	O
half	O
ell	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
slighter	O
kind	O
on	O
purpose	O
for	O
our	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
The	O
general	O
run	O
are	O
a	O
stouter	O
kind	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
claim	O
the	O
silk	O
?	O
Horner	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
claimed	O
or	O
disclaimed	O
it	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Close	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
barber	O
's	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
:	O
he	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
several	O
robberies	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
houses	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
:	O
the	O
people	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
mentioned	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
silk	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
silk	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
3	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Burnham	O
was	O
taken	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
Fox	O
the	O
evidence	O
and	O
two	O
boys	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
three	O
girls	O
,	O
like	O
piggs	O
in	O
a	O
barn	O
;	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
boys	O
promised	O
to	O
go	O
all	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
come	O
Michaelmas	O
next	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Burnham	O
about	O
3	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
enticed	O
me	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
into	O
this	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
we	O
crossed	O
to	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
;	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
Burnham	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
's	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
next	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
out	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
below	O
:	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
Burnham	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
that	O
lad	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
licked	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
.	O
For	O
Burnham	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Beehive	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Burnham	O
's	O
mother	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
son	O
away	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
officers	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
of	O
;	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Brown	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
silk	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
14	O
d.	O
per	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
one	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
26	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Wapping	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
borrowed	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
the	O
money	O
up	O
,	O
without	O
borrowing	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Donivah	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Hugo	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Holywell-street	O
,	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
all	O
dealers	O
in	O
cloaths	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Burnham	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Statfield	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
January	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
woollen	O
jackets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
drawers	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
January	O
21	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
woollen	O
jackets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Grieves	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
January	O
17	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
cheeses	O
weighing	O
18	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
tub	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
20	O
pickled	O
herrings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sturgeon	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutors	O
in	O
these	O
indictments	O
could	O
only	O
say	O
they	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
the	O
boy	O
Fox	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
without	O
calling	O
him	O
.	O
133	O
,	O
134	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
M'kenzie	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
outside	O
case	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bready	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Tricket	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
February	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Bready	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
rather	O
too	O
hard	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
waiting	O
for	O
the	O
stage-coach	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
coach	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot-inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
the	O
stage	O
coach	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
jolting	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
liquor	O
together	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
senses	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
missing	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
that	O
had	O
cleaned	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
Goldsmiths	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
out	O
hand-bills	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
horizontal	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
15	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
movement	O
finished	O
up	O
:	O
the	O
gold	O
cases	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Berridge	O
;	O
the	O
chain	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
chain	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
play-house	O
;	O
by	O
mentioning	O
the	O
word	O
play-house	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
from	O
somebody	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
play-house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
:	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
recollected	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warning	O
from	O
Goldsmiths	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
hall	O
for	O
information	O
,	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
,	O
fearing	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
Tricket	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Harriet	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
M'Kenzie	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
M'Kenzie	O
to	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Tricket	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
Tricket	O
took	O
and	O
turned	O
it	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
wound	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
smiled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
offer	O
it	O
soon	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
fetch	O
but	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Tricket	O
?	O
H.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Tricket	O
and	O
M'Kenzie	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Tricket	O
.	O
That	O
evidence	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
slump	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
inn	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
9th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Tricket	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
chain	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
play	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
Suky	O
;	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
seal	O
with	O
a	O
coat	O
of	O
arms	O
engraved	O
on	O
a	O
cornelian	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
seal	O
to	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Olive	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
stone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
gold	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Ealing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
1	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
50	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
watches	O
?	O
Ealing	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
agreement	O
you	O
made	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Ealing	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
in	O
three	O
months	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Julian	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
upon	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
about	O
18	O
guineas	O
.	O
M'Kenzie	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
woman	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
punch	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
inn	O
,	O
pretty	O
merrily	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
buy	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
a	O
gown	O
.	O
Tricket	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
girls	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
said	O
Taylor	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
and	O
fell	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
useless	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
five	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
Tricket	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Tricket	I-pers
his	O
mother	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
care	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
instructions	O
.	O
M'Kenzie	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Tricket	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
spurs	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
February	O
4	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
Leicester-fields	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
weekly	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
136	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Baillie	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
7	O
shirts	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
Duncan	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
footman	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
also	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
might	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
intimately	O
acquainted	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
137	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
at	O
Harefield	B-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
to	O
serve	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
clock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
persued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
138	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
Waley	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Anne	O
Waley	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Jeenes	I-pers
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
Charles	B-pers
Jeenes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
pork-shop	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
since	O
declared	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
married	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
many	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
we	O
found	O
and	O
brought	O
here	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Getens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
as	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
quit	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
139	O
,	O
140	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Vincent	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
February	O
5	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
of	O
four	O
bushels	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
barge	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
o'clock	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
owned	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
barge	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
lifted	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
barges	O
robbed	O
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
oats	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
room	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
Taylor	O
's	O
name	O
at	O
length	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Taylor	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
141	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christian	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
one	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dass	I-pers
,	O
January	O
27	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Dass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Star	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
three	O
nights	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
backwards	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
at	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gowns	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
pawned	O
by	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
devil	O
tempted	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dass	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
gave	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kilderman	O
the	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ashbridge	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Forshell	O
's	O
,	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Dass	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
142	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weed	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
January	O
31	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
some	B-place
inclosed	I-place
grounds	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Barnwell	I-place
in	I-place
Northamptonshire	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
at	O
Potton	O
fair	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
There	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
between	O
Biggleswade	O
and	O
Eaton	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
of	O
whom	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
my	O
neighbour	O
Luke	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
's	O
mare	O
also	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
ground	O
next	O
to	O
mine	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
hedge	O
parted	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
both	O
between	O
Biggleswade	O
and	O
Eaton	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
Potton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
horse	O
worth	O
?	O
Weed	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
worth	O
9	O
l.	O
Luke	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
mare	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Weed	O
did	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
search	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
both	O
between	O
Biggleswade	O
and	O
Potton	O
,	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
horses	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
London	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
fell	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
left	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
Storton	O
,	O
near	O
Kimbolton	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Storton	O
from	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
miles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Potton	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
about	O
30	O
miles	O
,	O
and	O
Smithfield	O
is	O
about	O
80	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Potton	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
?	O
Weed	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
7	O
miles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
both	O
going	O
to	O
Potton	O
fair	O
,	O
between	O
Biggleswade	O
and	O
Eaton	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
town	O
called	O
Wymouth	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Huntingdonshire	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
dealt	O
in	O
horses	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
came	O
from	O
Finden	O
,	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
receipt	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
signed	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Weed	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
receipt	O
before	O
?	O
Weed	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
wrote	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
?	O
Weed	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
one	O
night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
did	O
deal	O
in	O
horses	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
these	O
12	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
extravagant	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
blue-maker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
bought	O
blue	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
horses	O
:	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
fancy	O
for	O
horses	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
horses	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
and	O
chop	O
them	O
.	O
His	O
stables	O
were	O
in	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
near	O
5	O
months	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
stables	O
towards	O
Cold-bath-fields	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
regular	O
man	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
12	O
months	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Cloth-fair	O
about	O
3	O
