TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	B-pers
STAFFORD	I-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Priddle	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Plumley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kidman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hammon	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
,	O
Nathan	B-pers
Torrington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakrell	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Munt	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Tinsdel	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinnard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Deffield	I-pers
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Whittingham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Serjeson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
*	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Hawkins	O
being	O
hard	O
of	O
hearing	O
,	O
David	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
trial	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
LEVI	B-pers
Asher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
hinges	O
for	O
window-shutters	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Woodbridge	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
in	O
the	O
buildings	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Bevis	B-place
Marks	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
hinges	O
for	O
window-shutters	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
houses	O
sitting	O
up	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
going	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
hinges	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
other	O
buildings	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
examined	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Woodbridge	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
drawed	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
a	O
padlock	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
hinges	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
little	O
brother	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
baker	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
baker	O
's	O
brother	O
produced	O
to	O
us	O
three	O
pair	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
buildings	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
no	O
particular	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
from	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
them	O
we	O
missed	O
;	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
hinges	O
you	O
missed	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
?	O
Woodbridge	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
hinges	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
that	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
first	O
pair	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
slip	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bentham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
Mr.	O
Gibbs	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
hinges	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Woodbridge	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
working	O
boy	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
3	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
;	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
ditto	O
,	O
a	O
breast	O
buckle	O
,	O
a	O
hand-whip	O
,	O
4	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
;	O
one	O
leather	O
portmanteau	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Dartmouth	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Earl	O
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
footman	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Dartmouth	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
also	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
footmen	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
and	O
prisoner	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
horses	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
.	O
My	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
servants-hall	O
,	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
people	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Harwich	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
and	O
examined	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
produced	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
portmanteau	O
;	O
pistols	O
,	O
shirts	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
This	O
portmanteau	O
and	O
pistols	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Dartmouth	O
.	O
He	O
takes	O
up	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
mentioned	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
under	O
butler	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Dartmouth	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
11	O
guineas	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
breast	O
buckle	O
,	O
a	O
hand-whip	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
servants-hall	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Creswell	O
's	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
the	O
hand-whip	O
produced	O
there	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sprigins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Artichoke	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
horse	O
from	O
beyond	O
Rumford	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
mile	O
stones	O
betwixt	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bargaining	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
cart	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
he	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Harwich	O
fly	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
there	O
to	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
uncle	O
's	O
horse	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
,	O
Vine	O
inn	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
the	O
fly	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
horse	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
White-hart	O
at	O
Rumford	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
the	O
fly	O
went	O
by	O
at	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
machine	O
;	O
it	O
wanted	O
then	O
5	O
minutes	O
of	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
carriage	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
ride	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Brentwood	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
his	O
uncle	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
White-hart	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
port	O
and	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
barber	O
to	O
dress	O
his	O
hair	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
chaise	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Four	O
pieces	O
produced	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Webb	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
drove	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
Vine	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Harwich	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Dartmouth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Earl	O
's	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
information	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
Harwich	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
an	O
express	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
got	O
there	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
his	O
fellow	O
servants	O
things	O
were	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Creswell	O
and	O
Webb	O
swore	O
to	O
their	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
204.	O
Frances	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
205	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Irvior	I-pers
,	O
February	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Irvior	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Adam	B-pers
Fulner	I-pers
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Chequers	B-place
at	I-place
Charing-cross	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
our	O
fun	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
put	O
my	O
watch	O
into	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
hurry	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Fulner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Irvior	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
organ-builder	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
Wyld	O
street	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Fulner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
organ-builder	O
:	O
)	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pushed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
Irvior	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Scotland-yard	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-house	O
:	O
she	O
swore	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
she	O
went	O
along	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
.	O
When	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
by	O
fifty	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
gave	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Saltmarsh	I-pers
,	O
another	O
soldier	O
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
bound	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
their	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Haggist	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
six	O
knives	O
and	O
six	O
forks	O
,	O
with	O
handles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
twenty-three	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
dollars	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Weskett	I-pers
.	O
February	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Peter	B-pers
Weskett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
'squire	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
:	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Crown	I-place
in	I-place
Eagle-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
there	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
punch-ladle	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jervis	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
dollars	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Monk	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
buttons	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jervis	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Monk	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Weskett	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
for	O
his	O
trouble	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cotterill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
hoop	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
constantly	O
losing	O
iron	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
an	O
iron	O
hoop	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
doubled	O
up	O
,	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
doubled	O
up	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bottom	O
bars	O
to	O
a	O
grate	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Fenley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Drury-lane-playhouse	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
pushed	O
me	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
croud	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
pulling	O
at	O
my	O
sword	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
save	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gilder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Middle-row	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
play	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stop	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
case	O
was	O
separated	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
up	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
my	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
into	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
frequently	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
assaulting	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
case	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
admit	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
case	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Gilder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
at	O
the	O
play	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stoppage	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
case	O
lying	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
one	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
dragged	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
case	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gilder	I-pers
.	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Judith	B-pers
Gilder	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
claim	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Gilder	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gilder	O
,	O
sen.	O
My	O
son	O
and	O
daughter	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
case	O
:	O
my	O
daughter	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
We	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Charles	O
Fenley	O
.	O
He	O
soon	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
the	O
neighbour	O
called	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
stept	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
at	O
Drury-lane	O
playhouse	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
watch-case	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
?	O
God	O
forbid	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
son	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
right	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
case	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
picking	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
advertised	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
son	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
case	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
:	O
Fenley	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
an	O
attorney	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
playhouse	O
:	O
I	O
kicked	O
something	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
stooped	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
not	O
your	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
shake	O
the	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
forced	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ten	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
a	O
turner	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
inn-lane	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
left	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
ago	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
left	O
off	O
business	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
C.	O
Fendall	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
349.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Charles	O
Asgill	O
's	O
Mayorality	O
.	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Staffle	I-pers
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Letherland	I-pers
++	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Letherland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sawyer	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
from	O
Mr	B-place
Territ	I-place
's	I-place
yard	I-place
in	I-place
Black-friars	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
four	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
missing	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
below	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seized	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
coat	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
210	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Righton	I-pers
,	O
February	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Righton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Newgate-street	B-place
,	O
between	O
St.	O
Martin's-le-grand	O
and	O
Butcher-hall	O
lane	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Newgate	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
touched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
three	O
parts	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
two	O
pickpockets	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Peter	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Deane	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Barbary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Barbary	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
bed-gowns	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
warehouse-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
East	O
India-house	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
in	O
Rose-court	B-place
,	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
shirts	O
for	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
daughter	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
and	O
his	O
children	O
's	O
property	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Role	I-pers
(	O
produced	O
the	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
bed	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
aprons	O
;	O
)	O
these	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
advertised	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
wheaten	O
flour	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
loaders	O
at	O
Queenhithe	B-place
;	O
we	O
take	O
in	O
and	O
deliver	O
out	O
goods	O
;	O
we	O
watch	O
every	O
other	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
open	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
flour	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
26	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
flour	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Boys	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
are	O
answerable	O
if	O
any	O
is	O
lost	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
now	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
dumplin	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
for	O
that	O
use	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
victuals	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Magennis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
King	O
's	O
weigher	O
,	O
and	O
attend	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
yesterday	O
at	O
Battle-wharf	B-place
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
tobacco	O
from	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cart	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
23	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jebb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
the	O
scale	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
tobacco	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Darkhouse	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fellowship	O
porter	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Burridge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
four	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
Constantine	B-pers
Varoca	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
walking	O
cane	O
with	O
a	O
metal	O
head	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Constantine	B-pers
Varoca	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
along	O
Chick-lane	B-place
;	O
five	O
people	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
without	O
speaking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
cane	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
say	O
,	O
Kill	O
him	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Slayter	I-pers
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
lodging-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
cane	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Spitalfields	O
to	O
Soho	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
cane	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
examined	O
every	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
beds	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
person	O
suspected	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lodgers	O
a	O
cane	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
cane	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
cane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Still	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
men	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Slayter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
acted	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
you	O
bitch	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
knock	O
my	O
wife	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
near	O
Hatton-garden	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
no	O
cane	O
,	O
so	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
being	O
undressed	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
Edwards	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
cane	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Raven	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Raven	O
to	O
enquire	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Edwards	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
the	O
cane	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Charter-house-square	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
fellow	O
using	O
this	O
gentleman	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
again	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
Richard	O
Wade	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
stranger	O
with	O
this	O
cane	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
lodging	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
eleven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Peter	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Buckle-street	B-place
,	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
supper	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
some	O
gin	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Hamburgh	O
Arms	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
counted	O
it	O
over	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prison	O
's	O
house	O
again	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
my	O
wig	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
stooped	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
me	O
backwards	O
against	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
candle	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
rose	O
up	O
and	O
dropped	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
farthing	O
candle	O
.	O
I	O
stooped	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
slew	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hammond	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
licensed	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Pedler	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
supper	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
eat	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
Poll	O
Barry	O
and	O
him	O
together	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Poll	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sell	O
to	O
play	O
;	O
she	O
beat	O
his	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
candle	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
216	O
,	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Boot	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Haycock	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
gown	O
was	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Haycock	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Benjamin	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
that	O
Boot	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Boot	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitehorse	B-place
alley	I-place
,	I-place
Cow-cross	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wallace	I-pers
's	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wallace	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pledged	O
.	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
a	O
boy	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
218	O
,	O
219	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Woodin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bedhead	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
bedhead	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
summer-house	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Millington	O
's	O
summer-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bedhead	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
rents	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
necessity	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Reader	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Osmond	I-pers
,	O
two	O
watchmen	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
what	O
Wells	O
had	O
given	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
220	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Broad	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
waste	O
paper	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
stockings	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
paper	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
stockings	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
a	O
mistake	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Terence	B-pers
Welder	I-pers
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Macaulay	I-pers
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Orchard-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
lodging	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
bed-curtains	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
curtains	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
.	O
John	B-pers
C	I-pers
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
in	O
Germyn-street	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
two	O
bed-curtains	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
222	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
crape	O
night-gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff-shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chinner	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chinner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Peter	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
own	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
e	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
look	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
my	O
servant	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
assist	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Chinner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
pillowbears	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joiner	O
at	O
Ratcliffe	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
nurse	O
my	O
wife	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
wife	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Seymour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
seen	O
them	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
224	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Trig-lane	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
sack	O
from	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
red	O
mark	O
,	O
E.	O
Rawlins	O
,	O
Dartford	O
,	O
1765	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
the	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mud	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
his	O
stockings	O
very	O
dry	O
,	O
the	O
coals	O
very	O
clean	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
,	O
who	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
the	O
sack	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
sack	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
coals	O
along	O
the	O
shore	O
in	O
different	O
places	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
calicoe	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
calicoe	O
shirts	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drying	O
,	O
at	O
Ironmongers-alms-houses	B-place
.	O
James	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
shirts	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
London	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
he	O
kept	O
running	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
alms-houses	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
these	O
shirts	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
people	O
follow	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
called	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicoll	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
forcible	O
and	O
violent	O
manner	O
did	O
demand	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicoll	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
from	O
Barnet	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
horse	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
grand-daughter	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
Finchley-common	B-place
about	O
20	O
rods	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
on	O
a	O
grey	O
horse	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
my	O
chaise	O
;	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
rode	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
whipped	O
my	O
horse	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pursue	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
horse	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
in	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
days	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
boy	O
likewise	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
boy	O
went	O
and	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
consequence	O
that	O
would	O
attend	O
false	O
swearing	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
in	O
the	O
Birmingham	O
fly	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
fly	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
five	O
mile	O
stone	O
betwixt	O
Highgate	B-place
and	O
Finchley-common	B-place
,	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
both	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
rapped	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
money	O
!	O
money	O
!	O
money	O
!	O
The	O
windows	O
were	O
let	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
27	O
s.	O
piece	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
staid	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
switch	O
tail	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
white	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
day-light	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
surprized	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
quite	O
composed	O
afterwards	O
-	O
he	O
took	O
such	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
again	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Birmingham	O
coach	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
money	O
first	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
coachman	O
drive	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
directly	O
for	O
Highgate	O
.	O
Vincent	B-pers
Willoie	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
George's-court	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
days	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
load	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
betwixt	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
he	O
of	O
?	O
Willoie	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
work	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
keep	O
a	O
horse	O
?	O
Willoie	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
is	O
named	O
Moss	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
we	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
on	O
Finchley-common	O
by	O
a	O
single	O
highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
door	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
furtout	O
coat	O
on	O
and	O
boots	O
very	O
dirty	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
our	O
suspicious	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dobins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
inn	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
switch	O
tail	O
to	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
he	O
mounted	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
was	O
sent	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hertford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
Birmingham	O
coach	O
being	O
robbed	O
?	O
Moss	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
account	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
horse	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
morning	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
horse	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Hertford	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
Islington	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Nosh	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
6th	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
detained	O
me	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
three	O
thief-catchers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
was	O
he	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
place	O
described	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
miles	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
horse	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
227	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
February	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Thistle	I-place
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
by	O
my	O
fellow	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
money	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulling	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
the	O
gates	O
were	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
get	O
into	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
Hargrave	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Wales	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
business	O
and	O
could	O
get	O
none	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
lodging	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
without	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dame	O
Lady	O
Anne	B-pers
Furnesse	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
stable	O
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Bushell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Lady	O
Anne	B-pers
Furnesse	I-pers
in	O
Dover-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
Lady	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
go	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
to	O
buy	O
old	O
cloaths	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Herbert	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
coachman	O
.	O
A	O
witness	O
.	O
This	O
coat	O
Levi	O
offered	O
me	O
to	O
sale	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
intelligence	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
.	O
A	O
man	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
knows	O
me	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Bushell	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
never	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
229	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Minns	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
Hyde-park	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Hyde-park	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
forcibly	O
took	O
two	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
crown	O
pieces	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
frightened	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
soul	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
arms	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
)	O
Webb	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Medley	O
,	O
a	O
builder	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
doing	O
things	O
that	O
he	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
just	O
before	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
picked	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
been	O
lying	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
demand	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
you	O
because	O
you	O
had	O
had	O
familiarity	O
with	O
that	O
woman	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
mention	O
some	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Hickey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
O'Neal	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
O'Neal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair-merchant	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
cupboard	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
carried	O
some	O
loads	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
him	O
till	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Bell	O
ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
coat	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Leyborn	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Dog	O
,	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
O'Neal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
take	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
customer	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
my	O
cupboard	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
talk	O
to	O
my	O
bird	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
there	O
but	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
cupboard	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
me	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
he	O
confest	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
O'Neal	O
,	O
and	O
Parker	B-pers
the	O
constable	O
,	O
answer	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
231	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Upgood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
February	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
clock	O
and	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
robbed	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
caused	O
a	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
seen	O
going	O
into	O
Brentford	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
1	O
o'clock	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Harrow	O
alehouse	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Brentford	O
:	O
there	O
a	O
person	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
all	O
afterwards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Slatter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
at	O
Brentford	O
;	O
)	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
.	O
He	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
denied	O
knowing	O
where	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
a	O
mob	O
be	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
's	O
man	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
garden	O
near	O
Brentford	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
pales	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
them	O
(	O
three	O
pair	O
produced	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
as	O
they	O
I	O
lost	O
:	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
buckles	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
tesitmony	O
given	O
by	O
Slatter	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
232	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lack	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Lack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Shepherd's-bush	B-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
directions	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Shirley	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
Shepherd's-bush	O
.	O
After	O
it	O
was	O
known	O
that	O
Lack	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Harry	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
things	O
,	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
things	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
some	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
sacking	O
apron	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
confession	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
hedge	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
wheel	O
,	O
weight	O
15	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
uncle	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
A	O
brass	O
wheel	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
block	O
at	O
the	O
works	O
belonging	O
to	O
Blackfriars-bridge	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
is	O
master	O
stone-mason	O
at	O
that	O
bridge	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
wheel	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wills	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
wheel	O
we	O
missed	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Necholas	O
Love	O
.	O
This	O
wheel	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Blackfriars-yard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Hearing	O
a	O
wheel	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
block	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
wheel	O
belonged	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
sware	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
's	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
watching	O
a	O
west	O
country	O
barge	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
2	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
2	O
brass	O
wheels	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
now	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
wheels	O
from	O
.	O
First	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Wapping	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
3	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
this	O
brass	O
wheel	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
iron	O
ones	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
stopt	O
me	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
wheel	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
234	O
,	O
235	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
with	O
robbing	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
of	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Mason	O
was	O
attempting	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
strangled	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
charged	O
them	O
could	O
give	O
but	O
little	O
account	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
appearing	O
against	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
for	O
my	O
security	O
.	O
She	O
dropt	O
down	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
jury	O
to	O
fit	O
upon	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
natural	O
death	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
assist	O
the	O
poor	O
woman	O
who	O
is	O
calling	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
assist	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
up	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
3	O
women	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
is	O
dead	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
ill	O
used	O
:	O
she	O
could	O
hardly	O
speak	O
.	O
She	O
described	O
her	O
cloak	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
pin	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
cape	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
string	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
upon	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Jacobs	O
said	O
Mason	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
off	O
the	O
poor	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Jacob	O
's	O
shoulders	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
Mason	O
,	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stripping	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
Jacobs	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
you	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Mason	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
come	O
voluntarily	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Peal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
236	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Solomon	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lutwyche	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Vere	I-pers
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lutwyche	I-pers
.	O
My	O
partner	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Vere	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
goldsmiths	O
and	O
jewellers	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
our	O
shew-glasses	O
,	O
about	O
dusk	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
weighing	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
unperceived	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
price	O
he	O
bid	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
buy	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
large	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
weighed	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
back	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
began	O
to	O
struggle	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
our	O
pair	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
other	O
pairs	O
not	O
ours	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
4	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
concealed	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
has	O
claimed	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
buckles	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
cheaper	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
buckles	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
mixed	O
his	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
that	O
into	O
another	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
2	O
pair	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
3	O
pair	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
produced	O
any	O
buckles	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
237	O
,	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langfor	I-pers
;	O
and	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mittins	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langfor	I-pers
.	O
My	O
son	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Blue-coat	O
boys	O
walk	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
under	O
the	O
gate-way	B-place
out	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
'Change	I-place
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
asked	O
my	O
son	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
Roberts	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
them	O
both	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
He	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
dropt	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
son	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
mob	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
for	O
ducking	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
children	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
walk	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Everett	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
by	O
their	O
collars	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
from	O
under	O
Everett	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
towards	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
pickpockets	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
knowing	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Langfor	O
's	O
son	O
swore	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
swore	O
he	O
saw	O
White	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
Everett	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Everett	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
thigh	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bunch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mittins	O
close	O
to	O
his	O
thigh	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langfor	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Everett	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
recover	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
away	O
like	O
a	O
dog	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
.	O
White	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-chain-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Everett	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rowland	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
3	O
plaisterers	O
;	O
and	O
White	O
called	O
Esther	B-pers
White	I-pers
his	O
mistress	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
239	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
1	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
5	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
1	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
chip	O
hat	O
covered	O
with	O
sattin	O
,	O
3	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
,	O
February	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Hannah	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Deale	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fore-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
missed	O
was	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
lain-in	O
just	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
(	O
mentioning	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
nurse	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
3	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
gown	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
by	O
London-wall	O
,	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Flude	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bushby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
Old	O
Bethlem	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
accused	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
show	O
us	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
all	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
Bushby	O
.	O
Only	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
pawnbrokers	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Clements	O
Hart	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
apron	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
These	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Deale	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
240	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
Bedgood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bedgood	I-pers
,	O
being	O
living	O
,	O
September	O
1	O
,	O
1764	O
.	O
*	O
Rev	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
married	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
to	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bedgood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
in	O
Bristol	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1756	O
:	O
the	O
bans	O
were	O
first	O
published	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
reads	O
the	O
account	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
;	O
witness	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Trinman	I-pers
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
one	O
circumstance	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Flower-de-luce-court	O
,	O
Tooley-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Nicholas	O
Bedgood	O
lived	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
confirmed	O
to	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
at	O
Bristol	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
they	O
live	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
4	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
cyder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
living	O
or	O
dead	O
.	O
Walker	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
alive	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
3	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
works	O
somewhere	O
about	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Tooley-street	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Flower	O
de-luce-court	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
Bed-good	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
call	O
him	O
husband	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
Bedgood	O
these	O
3	O
years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
husband	O
Bedgood	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
Haydon-yard	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
him	O
blackguard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
and	O
she	O
both	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
own	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
oath	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Justices	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
living	O
with	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bedgood	I-pers
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cyder	O
trade	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
Bristol	O
2	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
is	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
first	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dorrington	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
by	O
seeing	O
a	O
ring	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
widow	O
2	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bedgood	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Wicks	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
about	O
20	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
children	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
girl	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
250	O
l.	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
300	O
l.	O
she	O
believed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
about	O
12	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
without	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
produced	O
from	O
Bristol	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
she	O
produced	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
post	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
married	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
doing	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
as	O
all	O
other	O
people	O
would	O
.	O
This	O
letter	O
was	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
.	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
mentioned	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Nicholas	O
Bedgood	O
this	O
morning	O
alive	O
and	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
bottom	I-place
of	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	O
by	O
bans	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1764	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
marriage	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wicks	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
married	O
in	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Jewry	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
justly	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
is	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
September	O
12	O
months	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
Jewry	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
Wicks	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
married	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1764	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bedgood	I-pers
had	O
another	O
wife	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
married	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
girl	O
at	O
Bristol	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
by	O
report	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
Bedgood	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
and	O
claimed	O
him	O
as	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
her	O
certificate	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
lawful	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
saw	O
that	O
woman	O
.	O
Brent	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
8	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bedgood	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
that	O
woman	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Flindell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
41	O
guineas	O
,	O
1	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
18	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Narroway	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
.	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Narroway	I-pers
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
in	O
Blackfriars	B-place
;	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
upon	O
business	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
after	O
putting	O
her	O
door	O
too	O
,	O
which	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
spring-lock	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
just	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
discharged	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
both	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
242	O
,	O
243	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Borne	I-pers
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
55	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
27	O
pounds	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
William	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
Virginia	O
in	O
America	O
.	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
and	O
sell	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
several	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
55	O
pounds	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
one	O
parcel	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
Borne	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
one	O
Banks	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
Brown	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
Banks	O
.	O
Banks	O
returned	O
me	O
26	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
Banks	O
clapped	O
the	O
door	O
too	O
against	O
the	O
headborough	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Borne	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Brown	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
came	O
to	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
tobacco	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
confessed	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
Banks	O
reproved	O
him	O
for	O
shewing	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
indictment	O
found	O
against	O
Banks	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Borne	O
go	O
into	O
Bank	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
that	O
any	O
tobacco	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Borne	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
king	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
Brown	O
;	O
Borne	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Banks	O
bid	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
take	O
her	O
tobacco	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Conner	O
was	O
were	O
present	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Wapping	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
Borne	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Banks	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
rapped	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
one	O
among	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
tobacco	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
deliver	O
him	O
into	O
your	O
hands	O
.	O
Borne	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
tobacco	O
;	O
some	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
and	O
some	O
loose	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
parcel	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
companions	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
door	O
watching	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Brown	O
.	O
Brown	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
Borne	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
in	O
part	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Brown	O
.	O
Borne	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
