TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
.	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
SIR	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EARDLY	I-pers
WILMOT	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YATES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Breed	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sabin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kippax	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jewell	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
Christ	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
being	O
taken	O
ill.	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Durno	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Weatherhill	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Pyle	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cookney	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ratcliffe	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Ratcliff	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
corn	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
barges	O
lying	O
at	O
Paul	B-place
's	I-place
wharf	I-place
,	O
with	O
corn	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witnesses	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sears	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
through	O
bridge	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
lighter	O
to	O
Paul's-wharf	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
moored	O
her	O
,	O
coming	O
on	O
shore	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Cousins	O
's	O
craft	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
move	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
answered	O
;	O
coming	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
along-side	O
the	O
craft	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
oats	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
gunnel	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
sack	O
of	O
corn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
boat	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
his	O
feet	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
backside	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
corn	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
Samuel	O
Robinson	O
,	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
Horsleydown	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stair-head	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulling	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
fall	O
into	O
his	O
boat	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
jumped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Robinson	O
to	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Cousins	O
's	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
hand	O
to	O
chuck	O
the	O
sack	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
harm	O
done	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
the	O
sack	O
is	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Robinson	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cousins	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sack	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
names	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
putney	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
fare	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
sack	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
from	O
the	O
Two	B-place
Blue	I-place
Poits	I-place
,	I-place
Dean-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tap-house	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Packwood	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
absconded	O
;	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
flung	O
into	O
the	O
tap	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Packwood	I-pers
was	O
called	O
upon	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Packwood	O
's	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
canvas	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
,	O
Nov	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
miller	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Rotherhithe	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Mill	O
;	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
from	O
Ratcliff	O
highroad	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Ratcliff-highway	B-place
;	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
row	O
me	O
over	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
dram	O
each	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
had	O
me	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
nearest	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
girl	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
legs	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Gray	O
,	O
pulled	O
my	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right-hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Carney	O
took	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Badcock	O
.	O
They	O
dragged	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
liquor	O
there	O
?	O
Badcock	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
purse	O
?	O
Badcock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
11	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Badcock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
afternoon	O
?	O
Badcock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
pints	O
betwixt	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Gray	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
7	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
farthings	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
farthings	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
plain	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
remarkable	O
one	O
;	O
them	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
were	O
such	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
eating	O
some	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
stuck	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shillings	O
found	O
upon	O
Carney	O
,	O
had	O
cheese	O
stuck	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
;	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
miller	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
(	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
house	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
voice	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
miller	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
Gray	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Carney	O
I	O
found	O
7	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
farthings	O
;	O
I	O
persuaded	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
lower	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
miller	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
money	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Badcock	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
?	O
Badcock	O
.	O
They	O
dragged	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
Carney	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
shewed	O
them	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
gin	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
robbing	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dun	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
miller	O
sober	O
or	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Dun	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
children	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Gray	O
was	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
E.	O
Wall	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
clerk	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
see	O
No	O
l484	O
in	O
Sir	O
W.	O
Stephenson	O
's	O
Mayorality	O
;	O
and	O
No	O
65	O
in	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Nelson	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
evidence	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Jane	O
Collins	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
10	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
She	O
stood	O
charged	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
's	O
inquest	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Cobb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Old	B-place
George-street	I-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
looms	O
in	O
the	O
weaving	O
way	O
for	O
the	O
master	O
weavers	O
,	O
and	O
employs	O
poor	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair-merchant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Cobb	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
off	O
a	O
journey	O
;	O
my	O
warehouse	O
lies	O
backwards	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
busy	O
,	O
my	O
window	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
garden	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
melancholy	O
cry	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
fellow	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
coat	O
upon	O
a	O
large	O
mulberry-tree	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
girl	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
standing	O
upon	O
two	O
arms	O
that	O
branch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tree	O
,	O
crying	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
in	O
size	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
age	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
fastening	O
a	O
cord	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
fellow	O
above	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
good	O
God	O
!	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tree	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
tree	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
,	O
what	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
God	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
;	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
child	O
has	O
done	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
naughty	O
wicked	O
hussey	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
has	O
she	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
twopence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
girl	O
and	O
things	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
other	O
ways	O
of	O
punishing	O
a	O
child	O
than	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cobb	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
was	O
opening	O
the	O
shop-window	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
Cobb	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
wound	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
her	O
temple	O
,	O
the	O
skin	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
hurt	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
above	O
.	O
Several	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
seeing	O
many	O
people	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
the	O
church-wardens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
?	O
Cobb	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
did	O
this	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
affright	O
the	O
child	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
Cobb	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Phebe	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
silk	O
weaver	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
small	O
of	O
her	O
age	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
P.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
last	O
summer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
heard	O
cruel	O
blows	O
struck	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
sticks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
whom	O
?	O
P.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
judge	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
wash-house	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
thin	O
partition	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
look	O
through	O
a	O
wicket	O
into	O
her	O
wash-house	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
pump	O
,	O
over	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
pump	O
serves	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
between	O
us	O
)	O
she	O
struck	O
the	O
child	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
with	O
either	O
a	O
mop	O
stick	O
or	O
a	O
broom-stick	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
blows	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
seeming	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
her	O
shoulders	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
,	O
only	O
hear	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
blows	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
drummed	O
against	O
the	O
partition	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
some	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
leave	O
off	O
beating	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
late	O
,	O
correct	O
her	O
to-morrow	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
kill	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
beating	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
I	O
design	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
but	O
once	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
husband	O
call	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
P.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
abused	O
:	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
never	O
free	O
from	O
bruises	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
she	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
P.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Her	O
eyes	O
were	O
black	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
P.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
daughter-in-law	O
;	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
wash-house	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
mornning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wash-house	O
,	O
squeezing	O
a	O
mop	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tub	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
a	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
blowing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
light	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
mop	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
it	O
two	O
blows	O
cross	O
its	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
mop-handle	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
cry	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
blowing	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
lighted	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
E.	O
Hall	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
blowing	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
about	O
this	O
day	O
three	O
weeks	O
the	O
child	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
some	O
bread	O
on	O
my	O
table	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
mistress	O
is	O
better	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
bread	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
famished	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
fortnight	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
came	O
home	O
seemingly	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
hussey	O
,	O
hussey	O
,	O
light	O
your	O
mistress	O
,	O
you	O
brazen	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
light	O
your	O
mistress	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
brave	O
girl	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
mistress	O
;	O
let	O
your	O
mistress	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
your	O
neighbours	O
see	O
you	O
are	O
alive	O
:	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
out	O
my	O
goods	O
(	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
crying	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
voice	O
,	O
hearing	O
her	O
often	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
blows	O
then	O
?	O
Abbot	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
child	O
with	O
black	O
eyes	O
?	O
Abbot	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Cornhill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
beat	O
her	O
very	O
cruelly	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
girl	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
dear	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
do	O
not	O
beat	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
heard	O
frequently	O
;	O
yesterday	O
fortnight	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
Moll	O
,	O
Moll	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
light	O
me	O
,	O
let	O
my	O
neighbours	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
murdered	O
you	O
yet	O
.	O
A	O
fortnight	O
to-morrow	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
beating	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
dear	O
mistress	O
,	O
pray	O
mistress	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
beat	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
fortnight	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
bought	O
some	O
fish	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
dish	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
M.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wingfield-street	O
;	O
last	O
Saturday	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
after	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
cry	O
,	O
dear	O
mistress	O
,	O
pray	O
mistress	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
beat	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
you	O
'll	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
poak	O
'd	O
my	O
head	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
mistress	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
child	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
use	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
towards	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
beating	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
the	O
stick	O
about	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
from	O
my	O
fingers	O
ends	O
to	O
my	O
elbow	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
strike	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
blows	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
it	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
abouts	O
did	O
she	O
strike	O
her	O
?	O
M.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
her	O
shoulders	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
child	O
came	O
and	O
pushed	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pushed	O
it	O
open	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
came	O
herself	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
barbarous	O
woman	O
,	O
you	O
deserve	O
hanging	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
make	O
any	O
answer	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dowley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Collin	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
my	O
business	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
cry	O
out	O
every	O
night	O
almost	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
child	O
a	O
mess	O
of	O
peas	O
pottage	O
,	O
3	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Sunday	O
;	O
the	O
mistress	O
went	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
mobbed	O
me	O
for	O
giving	O
her	O
the	O
pottage	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
you	O
thanks	O
for	O
giving	O
my	O
apprentice	O
peas	O
pottage	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
poor	O
child	O
eat	O
cabbage	O
leaves	O
and	O
candles	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
searchers	O
belonging	O
to	O
Christ	O
Church	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
word	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
search	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
corpse	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
child	O
lay	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
walk	O
this	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
push	O
the	O
shutter	O
open	O
;	O
her	O
son	O
opened	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
coffin	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
face	O
cloth	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
more	O
light	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
shutter	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stripped	O
the	O
shroud	O
off	O
to	O
the	O
hip	O
bone	O
;	O
it	O
looked	O
very	O
mottled	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
convulsions	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
two	O
legs	O
were	O
scratches	O
,	O
three	O
upon	O
each	O
leg	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
supposed	O
she	O
had	O
scratched	O
her	O
legs	O
on	O
her	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
more	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
lie	O
of	O
the	O
coffin	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
,	O
her	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
ground	O
10	O
s.	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
buried	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
Thursday	O
night	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
murdered	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coffin	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
bed	O
quite	O
naked	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Cobb	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
cheek	O
and	O
eye-brow	O
were	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
right	O
arm	O
was	O
all	O
raw	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
blister	O
I	O
'll	O
been	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
elbow	O
to	O
the	O
wrist	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
;	O
the	O
carcase	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
poor	O
condition	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
all	O
ever	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
observed	O
any	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
?	O
E.	O
Cotton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
the	O
shoulder	O
were	O
two	O
strokes	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
struck	O
with	O
something	O
;	O
it	O
seemed	O
red	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
shoulder	O
like	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
horns	O
;	O
the	O
bowels	O
over	O
the	O
belly	O
was	O
very	O
green	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
common	O
with	O
convulsions	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
seemed	O
mottled	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
blood	O
had	O
settled	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
like	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
she	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
any	O
particular	O
haste	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
body	O
buried	O
?	O
E.	O
Cotton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
it	O
common	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
check	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
in	O
convulsions	O
.	O
E.	O
Cotton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
body	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
each	O
arm	O
a	O
little	O
erasement	O
on	O
the	O
skin	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagine	O
of	O
no	O
consequence	O
;	O
the	O
right	O
arm	O
from	O
the	O
elbow	O
to	O
the	O
fingers	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
mortification	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
upon	O
the	O
elbow	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
bruises	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagine	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
mortification	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
bruises	O
?	O
Edington	O
.	O
Only	O
one	O
bruise	O
;	O
the	O
skin	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
swelling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
part	O
?	O
Edington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
mortified	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
no	O
discovery	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
opinion	O
that	O
bruise	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
mortification	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
before	O
it	O
produced	O
a	O
mortification	O
?	O
Edington	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
shortest	O
time	O
is	O
in	O
48	O
hours	O
;	O
that	O
depends	O
upon	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
the	O
mortification	O
be	O
longer	O
in	O
coming	O
on	O
a	O
strong	O
healthy	O
person	O
,	O
than	O
a	O
poor	O
weak	O
person	O
?	O
Edington	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
would	O
;	O
the	O
skin	O
was	O
off	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
nose	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
the	O
blackness	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
eye	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
scratch	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
spots	O
on	O
the	O
legs	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
appearance	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
blows	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
internal	O
parts	O
in	O
a	O
fair	O
natural	O
state	O
;	O
the	O
stomach	O
and	O
bowels	O
seemed	O
particularly	O
empty	O
,	O
more	O
so	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
any	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
mortification	O
was	O
the	O
immediate	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
;	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
recovered	O
of	O
the	O
injuries	O
she	O
received	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
mortification	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
perceive	O
no	O
bruises	O
to	O
occasion	O
a	O
mortification	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
on	O
her	O
elbow	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
or	O
a	O
blow	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
opinion	O
it	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
some	O
injury	O
it	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
for	O
where	O
they	O
come	O
by	O
blows	O
or	O
falls	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
inflammation	O
attends	O
it	O
.	O
Mortifications	O
generally	O
come	O
on	O
by	O
blisters	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
appearance	O
as	O
a	O
blister	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q.	O
Supposing	O
from	O
a	O
bad	O
habit	O
of	O
body	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
sore	O
,	O
their	O
handling	O
it	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
the	O
repetition	O
create	O
an	O
inflammation	O
?	O
Edington	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
bring	O
on	O
a	O
slight	O
inflammation	O
.	O
Alice	O
Stemson	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Collin	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
the	O
child	O
died	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
altered	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
washing	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
heavy	O
hand	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
fouled	O
itself	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
right	O
senses	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
it	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
right-hand	O
had	O
a	O
swelling	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
it	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
said	O
she	O
fell	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
beds	O
over	O
the	O
hair-broom	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
:	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
came	O
up	O
betwixt	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
syrup	O
of	O
saffron	O
;	O
I	O
added	O
,	O
and	O
treacle-water	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
syrup	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
child	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
breathing	O
sweat	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
disturbed	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
at	O
Rag	O
fair	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
ask	O
how	O
the	O
child	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
A.	O
Stinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
a	O
weak	O
sickly	O
child	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
owned	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
ribbon	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
cane	O
only	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
use	O
the	O
child	O
with	O
any	O
violence	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
words	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
beds	O
,	O
she	O
meant	O
the	O
two	O
bedsteads	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Seething-lane	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
coffin	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
over	O
a	O
broom	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
bedsteads	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
at	O
noon	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Creswell	O
's	O
,	O
an	O
undertaker	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
bespoke	O
a	O
coffin	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
accordingly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
mother	O
use	O
the	O
child	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
within	O
a	O
fortnight	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
death	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
witness	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
belly	O
full	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
supper	O
provided	O
against	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
used	O
to	O
eat	O
her	O
supper	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
pilfering	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
searcher	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
desire	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
conceal	O
the	O
child	O
from	O
inspection	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
bury	O
it	O
privately	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
four	O
weeks	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
and	O
tea	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
eat	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
knife	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
looked	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
still	O
the	O
mistress	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
carried	O
her	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
mistress	O
still	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
mulberry-tree	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
hurt	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
only	O
fright	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Cobb	O
called	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
murder	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
set	O
up	O
between	O
the	O
branches	O
of	O
the	O
tree	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
girl	O
used	O
to	O
wind	O
quills	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
use	O
the	O
child	O
ill	O
,	O
only	O
by	O
beating	O
her	O
when	O
in	O
a	O
fault	O
with	O
a	O
rattan	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
mob	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
being	O
ill	O
?	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Collins	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
oil	O
of	O
Gilead	O
to	O
bathe	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
swelled	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
swelled	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
turn	O
the	O
wheel	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
tumbled	O
over	O
the	O
broom	O
between	O
the	O
beds	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
girl	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
oil	O
in	O
a	O
tea-cup	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
girl	O
last	O
?	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
at	O
her	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
mob	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
outcry	O
by	O
the	O
child	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
?	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Addis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
cast	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
her	O
garret	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
the	O
deceased	O
whether	O
she	O
ever	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
following	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
mean	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
struck	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
when	O
?	O
Addis	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
child	O
crying	O
?	O
Addis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
swelling	O
on	O
its	O
face	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
tumbled	O
over	O
a	O
broom	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
bedsteads	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
always	O
had	O
her	O
belly	O
full	O
of	O
victuals	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
use	O
any	O
cruelty	O
towards	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Edington	O
.	O
From	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
concerning	O
the	O
child	O
tumbling	O
over	O
the	O
broom	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
might	O
occasion	O
that	O
hurt	O
on	O
the	O
elbow	O
to	O
cause	O
the	O
mortification	O
?	O
Edington	O
.	O
That	O
might	O
occasion	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
several	O
children	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
used	O
this	O
child	O
worse	O
than	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Greenaway	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ricks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Creswell	O
deposed	O
the	O
son	O
came	O
publicly	O
and	O
bespoke	O
the	O
coffin	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
name	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Timothy	B-pers
M'Namara	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wolf	O
's	O
skin	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gangsman	O
on	O
Bear-key	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
skins	O
at	O
that	O
key	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
opened	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
stopt	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
wolf	O
's	O
skin	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
dropped	O
it	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
skins	O
as	O
these	O
opened	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
picked	O
the	O
skin	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
took	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cluney	I-pers
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
J.	O
Wylde	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alex	B-pers
Cluney	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
Smart's-key	O
and	O
Dice-key	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lighter	O
of	O
sugar	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Smart's-key	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
tarpaulin	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
bags	O
filled	O
with	O
sugar	O
under	O
the	O
tarpaulin	O
also	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hogsheads	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Wylde	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
brother	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Barking	O
fisherman	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
under	O
the	O
tarpaulin	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Segerly	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Segerly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
minutes	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	B-place
;	O
they	O
asked	O
my	O
father	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
he	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
my	O
father	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
tell	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
dark	O
passage	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
nine	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Segerly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Segerly	I-pers
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
related	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Upton	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
fact	O
,	O
No	O
497	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
11.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Case	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
haunches	O
of	O
venison	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
sides	O
of	O
venison	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
October	O
5	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cadbury	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
chaldron	O
of	O
sea	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
;	O
and	O
12	O
bushels	O
of	O
sea	O
coals	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
;	O
the	O
coals	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
Wapping	B-place
dock	I-place
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
coals	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
at	O
Bell-wharf	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
at	O
Ratcliff-cross	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
and	O
took	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Wapping-dock	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
barge	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
drive	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
Limehouse-reach	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
tier	O
of	O
ships	O
at	O
King	O
Edward	O
's	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
detected	O
with	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
with	O
coals	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
the	O
barge	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gowdey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
barge	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boat	O
and	O
rowed	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
barge	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
chaldron	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
coals	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
they	O
threw	O
coals	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
drove	O
with	O
them	O
from	O
New	O
Crane	O
to	O
Ratcliff-cross	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
men	O
coming	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
they	O
assisted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
confessed	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
barge	O
,	O
there	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
the	O
coals	O
belong	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Walton	O
and	O
Slade	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
rest	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
George	I-pers
indicted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
ill	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
tried	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Hindes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Farrell	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Eleanor	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
iron	O
rails	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Oct.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
bars	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
premises	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
before	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
fixed	O
into	O
store	O
work	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
feet	O
high	O
;	O
the	O
top	O
rail	O
is	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Church	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
these	O
four	O
prisoners	O
betwixt	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
head	O
knocked	O
about	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
cried	O
the	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
walk	O
he	O
turned	O
again	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yard	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
,	O
Hindes	O
had	O
got	O
three	O
bars	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
has	O
got	O
them	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
knock	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
walked	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Blakeney's-head	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
sat	O
;	O
Farrell	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
ears	O
pulled	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
Dyer	O
followed	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
yet	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
stirred	O
I	O
'd	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
shew	O
you	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
more	O
bars	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
cart	O
or	O
a	O
waggon	O
by	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
directions	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
3	O
bars	O
.	O
Dyer	O
said	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
some	O
shall	O
answer	O
for	O
this	O
if	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
liberty	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
to	O
Dyer	O
,	O
swear	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
assisted	O
me	O
was	O
a	O
confederate	O
with	O
us	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
bars	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
every	O
bar	O
fitted	O
the	O
place	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
bars	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
three	O
rails	O
under	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Fly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
helped	O
Church	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
four	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
bars	O
.	O
Hindes	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
some	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Henry	B-pers
Handy	I-pers
,	O
Norris	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
,	O
two	O
copper-plate	O
printer	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Dyer	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Cleaver	I-pers
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Farrell	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Islington	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
Dyer	O
and	O
Hindes	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Highbury-barn	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
near	O
Islington	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
return	O
home	O
Dyer	O
overtook	O
him	O
with	O
three	O
bars	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Hindes	O
,	O
Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
Farrell	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Eleanor	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
woollen	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
on	O
nights	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
awaked	O
betwixt	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
dressed	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
box	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
under	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
removed	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
still	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
curtain	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
box	O
last	O
?	O
Fleming	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
duty	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chest	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
wide	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
deep	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
stockings	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
Brown's-garden	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Black	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
chest	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
shirt	O
near	O
Golden-square	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
broke	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
shirt	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
deposed	O
to	O
his	O
buying	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
about	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
shirt	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Black	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Christopher	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
sells	O
milk	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
in	O
Hare-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
27th	O
and	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Blaney	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
and	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Barney	B-pers
M'Kernon	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Margaret	B-pers
M'Kernon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Barney	B-pers
M'Kernon	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
eight	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
apartment	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Fleet-market	I-place
:	O
I	O
trusted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
by	O
crying	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
Church-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Church-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joshua	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Blomart	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
reason	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
21	O
,	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Webley	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Mendin	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
walnut-tree	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Strouther	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Andrew	B-pers
Strouther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kensington-gore	B-place
,	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
six	O
spoons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Dun	O
Cow	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Spike	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Dun	O
Cow	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
tea-chest	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
persons	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
towards	O
Brumpton	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
had	O
gone	O
by	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Westminster-bridge	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
waterman	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
secured	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
chest	O
and	O
spoons	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
eat	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
chest	O
and	O
spoons	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
Webley	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Kensington	O
turnpike	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
several	O
people	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
ask	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
in	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
openly	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
by	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
called	O
and	O
stopped	O
us	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
honestly	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Hartley	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
Mendin	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
occasions	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
chest	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trout	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
2	O
moidores	O
,	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
8	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
2	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
all	O
my	O
lifetime	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
named	O
James	B-pers
Gawler	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
Newbury	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
Spinham-land	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
from	O
one	O
house	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
not	O
liking	O
this	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
house	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
house	O
but	O
one	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
Trout	O
and	O
Manwaring	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
and	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Brooks-market	O
;	O
in	O
discourse	O
Manwaring	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
countrymen	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
produce	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
40	O
l.	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
purse	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
150	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
receive	O
300	O
more	O
;	O
a	O
wager	O
was	O
soon	O
laid	O
,	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
that	O
amongst	O
us	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
raise	O
any	O
,	O
Gawler	O
can	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
mine	O
from	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
Gawler	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
produced	O
31	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
2	O
moidores	O
,	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
8	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
2	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
told	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
enough	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
yield	O
the	O
wager	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
Gawler	O
produce	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
while	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
abroad	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
out	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
us	O
four	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
stall	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
landlady	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
liquor	O
was	O
paid	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
shun	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
from	O
Cheapside	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
le	O
grand	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
linen	O
drapers	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
bent	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
the	O
edge	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
27	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
I	O
described	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
money	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
crown	O
piece	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
mentioned	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
fainted	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
back	O
into	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
play	O
at	O
a	O
game	O
called	O
hussel-cap	O
,	O
and	O
lose	O
17	O
s.	O
Reed	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
play	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Lion	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
houses	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
signs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
to	O
a	O
gate-way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
cobler	O
's	O
stall	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
landlady	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
alehouse	O
again	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
reckoning	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
above	O
30	O
l.	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
minute	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
her	O
different	O
stories	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
said	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
about	O
or	O
above	O
30	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Reed	O
.	O
Gawler	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
soon	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Casson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
money	O
into	O
my	O
charge	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
31	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
described	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
by	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bent	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
;	O
such	O
was	O
the	O
crown	O
piece	O
the	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
with	O
the	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
moidore	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
before	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
always	O
mention	O
one	O
sum	O
?	O
Casson	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
varied	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
money	O
too	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
council	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Your	O
council	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
do	O
that	O
yourself	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
and	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
alehouse	O
,	O
in	O
Brooks-market	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
October	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
then	O
35	O
l.	O
then	O
25	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
E.	O
Turner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
?	O
E.	O
Turner	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
by	O
themselves	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
lost	O
there	O
?	O
E.	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
upwards	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Turner	O
.	O
What	O
liquor	O
had	O
they	O
had	O
?	O
E.	O
Turner	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
me	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
Beckley	O
.	O
One	O
day	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
stall	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
way	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
directed	O
him	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
say	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
had	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
stall	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
slept	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
40	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
30	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
25.	O
John	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
gateway	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
three	O
and	O
forty	O
guineas	O
,	O
then	O
three	O
and	O
thirty	O
,	O
and	O
thirty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
one	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
five	O
and	O
thirty	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
time	O
five	O
and	O
twenty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
horse	O
dealer	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
:	O
he	O
bears	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Quarry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
trust	O
him	O
any	O
time	O
with	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Geo	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
lodging	O
from	O
whence	O
you	O
fetched	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
near	O
Oxford	O
Chapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
different	O
accounts	O
of	O
the	O
sum	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
varied	O
in	O
my	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
above	O
ten	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Mainwaring	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Gawler	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
stole	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
eight	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
counters	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
like	O
guineas	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
which	O
purse	O
he	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
purse	O
his	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
he	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
through	O
malicious	O
people	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
nobody	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
people	O
pointed	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
opened	O
my	O
surtout	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
four	O
men	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
appeared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Brewster	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
muscovado	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
at	O
Bell	B-place
wharf	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Ratcliff-cross	I-place
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
sugar	O
,	O
rum	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
a	O
Jamaica	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
neither	O
could	O
I	O
tell	O
there	O
was	O
sugar	O
missing	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
freight	O
collected	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
sugar	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Dix	O
,	O
my	O
first	O
mate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Dix	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
charge	O
Dix	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
word	O
and	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
second	O
mate	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
ship	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
dock	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
all	O
unloaded	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
some	O
sugar	O
in	O
bags	O
:	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
's	O
company	O
and	O
Custom-house	O
officers	O
helped	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
boat	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
it	O
sweepings	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
clean	O
and	O
some	O
dirty	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
the	O
captain	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
nine	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Dix	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
tell	O
him	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dear	O
bargain	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
six-pence	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Crisly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
mariner	O
on	O
board	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pay	O
Dix	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sweepings	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
chief	O
mate	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
surveyors	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
ship	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
cleared	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
dirty	O
sweepings	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
gave	O
ourselves	O
any	O
concern	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
to	O
about	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
250	O
pounds	O
weight	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
the	O
custom	O
of	O
the	O
chief	O
mate	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
thinks	O
them	O
worth	O
his	O
acceptance	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
boys	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
dirty	O
sugar	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
vessel	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Crow	O
there	O
after	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Customs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
some	O
wood	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
cleared	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
day	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
chief	O
mate	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
sweepings	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
the	O
mate	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
hold	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
cleared	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
cleared	O
;	O
the	O
sweepings	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
two	O
Irish	O
beef	O
barrels	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
casks	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
second	O
,	O
and	O
third	O
tier	O
had	O
been	O
stoved	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
sugar	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
good	O
was	O
carefully	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
vessels	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
as	O
neat	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dirty	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
these	O
barrels	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dirty	O
stuff	O
that	O
was	O
scraped	O
from	O
the	O
ceilings	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Tilly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Custom-house	O
officer	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Prior	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
nor	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
received	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
waterman	O
employed	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
sweepings	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
in	O
four	O
bags	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
kit	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
chips	O
and	O
dirt	O
among	O
it	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Tombes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
chips	O
and	O
gravel	O
amongst	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
good	O
sugar	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
beef	O
barrels	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
sugar	O
baker	O
,	O
named	O
Toulson	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Toulson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sugar-refiner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Cole-stairs	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
about	O
200	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
weight	O
of	O
sweepings	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
either	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
moidore	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
money	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
fit	O
for	O
melasses	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
10	O
years	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Carsent	I-pers
7	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
10	O
or	O
11	O
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
More	I-pers
about	O
10	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
14	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
25	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Eastock	I-pers
7	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hosley	I-pers
2	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hegan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
muscovado	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
This	O
appeared	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
sweepings	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
mate	O
,	O
Dix	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
At	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
came	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Holbourn-hill	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
immediately	O
;	O
seeing	O
my	O
hat	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
channel	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
hold	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
quietly	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
ran	O
through	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
some	O
high	O
steps	O
;	O
they	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
hat	O
since	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
neither	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
demand	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
put	O
you	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
or	O
drunk	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
troubled	O
about	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
confined	O
all	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
happened	O
that	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
assault	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
down	O
Fleet	O
market	O
from	O
Holbourn-hill	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
running	O
down	O
Holbourn-hill	O
after	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
chimney-sweepers	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
;	O
he	O
overtook	O
him	O
just	O
opposite	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
knocked	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
that	O
man	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
hat	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
watchman	O
who	O
turned	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
had	O
recovered	O
himself	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
wanted	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Brown	O
knocked	O
down	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hat	O
thrown	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
taking	O
him	O
along	O
by	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
accomplices	O
I	O
believe	O
joined	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Turnagain-lane	O
;	O
coming	O
upon	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
five	O
feet	O
ten	O
inches	O
high	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
learned	O
by	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
peeped	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
that	O
night	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
a	O
night	O
cart	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
running	O
after	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
football	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
challenging	O
one	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
having	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
striking	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
that	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
towards	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
antagonist	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
down	O
Fleet-market	O
and	O
up	O
Turnagain-lane	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
they	O
mean	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
my	O
antagonist	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Crosby	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Frazer	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
of	O
wheaten	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Frazer	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
near	B-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
two	O
loaves	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
upon	O
some	O
other	O
loaves	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
maid	O
servant	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
empty	O
a	O
dust-tub	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
some	O
ashes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
loaf	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
with	O
Thompson	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
dust-tub	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
received	O
any	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
loaf	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
pointed	O
to	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Thompson	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
in	O
a	O
stall	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
loaf	O
under	O
a	O
board	O
in	O
his	O
stall	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
and	O
Frazer	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Thompson	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
these	O
loaves	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
7	O
d.	O
they	O
were	O
7	O
d.	O
1/4	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
Thompson	O
said	O
7	O
d.	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
apprentice	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
Thompson	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
two	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
before	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
groat	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
damaged	O
loaves	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
loaf	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
basket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
ash-tub	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tub	O
and	O
loaf	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
Frazer	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
a	O
loaf	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
thinking	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
be	O
angry	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
loaf	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
he	O
called	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
loaf	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
groat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
brought	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
price	O
for	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
his	O
master	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
handle	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
loaf	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
Thompson	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Emerton	O
I	O
know	O
Thompson	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
by	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
stall	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
loaves	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
picked	O
;	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
them	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
saleable	O
;	O
they	O
must	O
certainly	O
be	O
second-hand	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
a	O
good	O
customer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
four	O
children	O
and	O
a	O
sick	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
botch	O
ng	O
taylor	O
,	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
for	O
two	O
loaves	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
picked	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
people	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
picked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Perkins	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
Thompson	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brady	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
employ	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Thompson	O
;	O
one	O
time	O
in	O
particular	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
hurry	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
breeches	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
and	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Thompson	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
fellow	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
credit	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
draper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
credit	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
creature	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Fossey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kentley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
years	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
behave	O
better	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
family	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
boy	O
out	O
with	O
loaves	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
for	O
bread	O
that	O
you	O
sent	O
out	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thirkell	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
