TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
,	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	O
GOULD	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YATES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Rewley	B-pers
W.	I-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Criek	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Connington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beetson	I-pers
,	O
Frederick	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stansbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Liddiard	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Jonath	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Peavey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Worthington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tinley	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
.	O
72	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Stephen	I-pers
Woolf	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Susannah	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
nine	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
parish-house	O
:	O
my	O
sister	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
frequented	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
shirt	O
and	O
the	O
body	O
and	O
sides	O
of	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stepion	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
:	O
I	O
informed	O
her	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
coming	O
home	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
body	O
and	O
sleeves	O
for	O
another	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
Esq	O
;	O
Henley	O
's	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
that	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
others	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
stopped	O
a	O
woman	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Rodbird	O
's	O
,	O
Black-friars	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
shirt	O
body	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
and	O
the	O
pattern	O
shirt	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
others	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
She	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Finley	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
:	O
she	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
She	O
since	O
owns	O
she	O
was	O
deceived	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
with	O
other	O
pieces	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
Woolf	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
pieces	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
debt	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
73	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Brian	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
knee-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Pinchbeck	O
seal	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Timothy	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
,	O
Wapping	O
:	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
water	O
work	O
and	O
engine	O
work	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
at	O
Execution-dock	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Ratcliff-cross	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
More	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cohan	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
tools	O
at	O
Timothy	B-pers
M'Donnel	I-pers
's	I-pers
house	O
,	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
nothing	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
chissel	O
which	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
use	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
my	O
lodgings	O
near	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
throw	O
from	O
my	O
lodging	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
sat	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
treated	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
there	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
because	O
a	O
man	O
is	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
if	O
out	O
late	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
place	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
people	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
the	O
sooner	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
aware	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
blow	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
eat	O
a	O
bit	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
blow	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
fell	O
:	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
stunned	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
recovered	O
my	O
senses	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
tug	O
at	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
chain	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
mettle	O
seal	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
knee-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
strap	O
of	O
my	O
breaches	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
you	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
several	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
men	O
and	O
some	O
women	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
the	O
chissel	O
at	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
intended	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
throat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
cut	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
cheek	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
spirting	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
back	O
to	O
M'Donnel	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
borrowed	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
officers	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
day	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Swinney	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
opposite	O
M'Donnel	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
M'Donnel	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
four	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Christmas-eve	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
near	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
wound	O
then	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sear	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
raw	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
my	O
escape	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
posts	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
scar	O
now	O
on	O
his	O
cheek	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
the	O
widow	O
Doudle	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
delivered	O
me	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
and	O
trousers	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
times	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
warrant	O
for	O
one	O
Swinney	O
,	O
whose	O
christian	O
name	O
was	O
unknown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
after	O
supper	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sitting	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
seat	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
seat	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
sit	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
seat	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
angry	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
you	O
are	O
speaking	O
to	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
poker	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
strike	O
me	O
I	O
'll	O
strike	O
you	O
.	O
Come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
:	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
four	O
times	O
with	O
the	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
stunned	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
a	O
chissel	O
into	O
my	O
cheek	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
mine	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
named	O
Mahony	O
saw	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
quarrel	O
there	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
strike	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
was	O
you	O
knocked	O
down	O
with	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
iron	O
poker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
)	O
Cha	O
.	O
Mahony	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Doudle	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
almost	O
every	O
night	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lodged	O
there	O
?	O
Mahony	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
draw	O
beer	O
there	O
.	O
Dunn	O
used	O
to	O
breakfast	O
and	O
dine	O
there	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Mahony	O
.	O
He	O
works	O
with	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
mention	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
this	O
dispute	O
was	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
an	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Dunn	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
drawed	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
;	O
before	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Mahony	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
Dunn	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
facing	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
company	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Mahony	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
else	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
together	O
?	O
Mahony	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
drinking	O
together	O
.	O
Dunn	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
woman	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Said	O
Dunn	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
woman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
and	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Said	O
Dunn	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
you	O
are	O
talking	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
pot	O
;	O
the	O
sailor	O
and	O
I	O
helped	O
him	O
drink	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lick	O
Swinney	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
desired	O
Swinney	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
Swinney	O
took	O
the	O
poker	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Dunn	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
Swinney	O
throwed	O
him	O
down	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
Dunn	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
both	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
Dunn	O
made	O
a	O
step	O
forward	O
and	O
struck	O
Swinney	O
with	O
the	O
chissel	O
;	O
Swinney	O
never	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
God	O
Almighty	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
bled	O
very	O
fast	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
with	O
the	O
chissel	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
bled	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
Dunn	O
's	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
Swinney	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Dunn	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stay	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Mahony	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
seeing	O
this	O
witness	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
thus	O
used	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Mahony	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lighted	O
candle	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
attacked	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Seven	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
rather	O
under	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Doudle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Swan	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
both	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Dunn	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
M.	O
Doudle	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
opposite	O
to	O
Dunn	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
but	O
Mahony	O
and	O
one	O
M'Carty	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
lodge	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
seafaring	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Doudle	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Dunn	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Dunn	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Dunn	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
woman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
lawful	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
so	O
words	O
arose	O
.	O
Dunn	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
puppy	O
,	O
who	O
do	O
you	O
talk	O
to	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
speak	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
lick	O
you	O
well	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
chissel	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
his	O
holiday	O
dress	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
seeing	O
that	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
too	O
.	O
Dunn	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
engagement	O
without	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
M.	O
Doudle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
chissel	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
a	O
mischief	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
engagement	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
dress	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
?	O
Doudle	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
M'Carty	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Doudle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
below	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Dunn	O
come	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Swinney	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Dunn	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
Swinney	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
and	O
drove	O
it	O
at	O
Swinney	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
Dunn	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
dropt	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
fray	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
three	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
held	O
the	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
Mahony	O
held	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
declared	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
74	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lubenham	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Market	I-place
Harborough	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
year	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
him	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
white	O
hairs	O
on	O
his	O
forehead	O
,	O
by	O
trying	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
star	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
a	O
livery	O
stable	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
this	O
day	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Leicester	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
bay	O
gelding	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
gelding	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
;	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bay	O
gelding	O
in	O
of	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
a	O
fortnight	O
yesterday	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
has	O
evidence	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
that	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
talked	O
about	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
rode	O
him	O
90	O
miles	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
Market-Harborough	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chauler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
fed	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
market	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
his	O
mind	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
market	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
7	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
standing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ostler	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
described	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
proper	O
description	O
of	O
that	O
horse	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
secured	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
persisted	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
Oakham	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	O
by	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
overtook	O
me	O
on	O
this	O
horse	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
miles	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Oakham	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
8	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
six	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
6	O
guineas	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Hope	O
and	O
Co.	O
brewers	O
,	O
in	O
Spital-fields	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
us	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
spareman	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
another	O
brewing	O
season	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
opinion	O
of	O
his	O
honesty	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
for	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
months	O
;	O
had	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
several	O
years	O
clerk	O
at	O
Mess	O
.	O
Hope	O
and	O
Stubbs	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
year	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
many	O
cellars	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
value	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
well	O
respected	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
now	O
in	O
business	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
Job	O
Forrest	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
tap-house	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
He	O
comes	O
from	O
Leicestershire	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
winters	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
horse-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
his	O
way	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Walthamstow	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
both	O
born	O
at	O
Lubenham	O
,	O
in	O
Leicestershire	O
.	O
He	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
farmer	O
's	O
service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
that	O
country	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
thence	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
business	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
6	O
weeks	O
last	O
summer	O
.	O
His	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
stage	O
at	O
Walthamstow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
His	O
friends	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
75	O
,	O
76	O
,	O
77	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Martha	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Buterfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Furnican	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
sack	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
three	O
gauze	O
handkerchiefs	O
laced	O
,	O
one	O
gauze	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
bead	O
necklace	O
,	O
a	O
stone	O
necklace	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Furnican	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Sugarloaf-court	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-yard	I-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
laundress	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
mother	O
,	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
daughter	O
;	O
she	O
follows	O
the	O
same	O
business	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
I	O
could	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
8	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
home	O
upon	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Furnican	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
you	O
fastened	O
your	O
window	O
?	O
Furnican	O
.	O
I	O
fasten	O
that	O
with	O
a	O
shutter	O
with	O
a	O
bolt	O
;	O
sometimes	O
I	O
pin	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
window	O
shutter	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
;	O
one	O
pane	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
locks	O
broke	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
muslin	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gauze	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
My	O
neighbour	O
that	O
lives	O
between	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Blaze	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
headborough	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
,	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
headborough	O
's	O
wife	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
for	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
warrant	O
without	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
against	O
some	O
body	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Anne	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
:	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Coves	O
the	O
headborough	O
wanted	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
her	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
lay	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Martha	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
caused	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
down	O
into	O
my	O
cellar	O
?	O
Furnican	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
ill	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Blaze	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
6	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sharp	O
frosty	O
weather	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
filling	O
my	O
two	O
water	O
tubs	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
the	O
water	O
running	O
flush	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
girl	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Buterfield	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
pail	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
borrowed	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
walked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
before	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
water	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
Shap	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
halloo	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
cock	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
window	O
?	O
Blaze	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
30	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
heard	O
that	O
noise	O
?	O
Blaze	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
my	O
pail	O
:	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
yards	O
distant	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Coves	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
about	O
business	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
has	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
who	O
do	O
you	O
suspect	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
some	O
neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
advice	O
how	O
to	O
proceed	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-Office	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
complaint	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
apprehended	O
they	O
would	O
grant	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Buterfield	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
me	O
tell	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
her	O
business	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Coves	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
of	O
a	O
neighbour	O
that	O
was	O
deceased	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
business	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
immediately	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Anne	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Furnican	O
's	O
things	O
below	O
in	O
their	O
cellar	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
(	O
producing	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
lay	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
sieve	O
,	O
squeezed	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
muslin	O
gown	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
care	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
mother	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
answered	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
entirely	O
ignorant	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
notice	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
window	O
that	O
looked	O
into	O
their	O
yard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
flat	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
no	O
shutter	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Whoever	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
must	O
come	O
into	O
their	O
yard	O
and	O
poke	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
before	O
?	O
Coves	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Coves	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
8	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
sincere	O
had	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
lad	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
harmless	O
lad	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
character	O
asked	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Coves	O
.	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
William	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Martha	O
's	O
defence	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
78	O
,	O
79	O
,	O
80	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
M'Cullock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
frail	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
January	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Prestage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
constables	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
kays	B-place
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Fowler	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
frail	O
of	O
raisins	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
persons	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
prisoners	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
frail	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
they	O
stole	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
chemist	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
these	O
fruit	O
upon	O
the	O
wharf	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
frail	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
frail	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Fowler	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
means	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
emptied	O
it	O
into	O
their	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
chemist	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
their	O
faces	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
pilfering	O
upon	O
the	O
kays	O
daily	O
.	O
M'Cullock	O
and	O
James	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Fowler	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
frail	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
No	O
farther	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
81	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
alley	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
January	O
8	O
,	O
1764	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1764	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopenny	O
by	O
myself	O
.	O
Two	O
women	O
were	O
fetched	O
in	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
their	O
companions	O
,	O
we	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
this	O
gentleman	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
dressed	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
dram	O
of	O
gin	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
drank	O
gin	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
rum	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
rattan	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
laying	O
upon	O
Baker	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
usage	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
son-in-law	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
,	O
come	O
into	O
this	O
room	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
fell	O
a	O
laying	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
that	O
intent	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
past	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
running	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
us	O
righted	O
:	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
bring	O
some	O
men	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
righted	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
has	O
used	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
our	O
parts	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
they	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Doleman	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
see	O
him	O
righted	O
.	O
Said	O
Wright	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
go	O
,	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
us	O
in	O
spirits	O
before	O
we	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
then	O
up	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
one	O
's	O
name	O
and	O
another	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
signify	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
matter	O
of	O
damage	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
.	O
Said	O
they	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
quartern	O
would	O
be	O
too	O
little	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
rum	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
women	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
righted	O
;	O
we	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
see	O
us	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
pretty	O
well	O
dressed	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
will	O
meddle	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
Whitecross-street	O
was	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Lingard	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
:	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Doleman	O
borrowed	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Africa	O
,	O
Captain	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
foremast	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
all	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
by	O
Turnagain-lane	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
house	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
up	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
here	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
all	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
treated	O
them	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
There	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
one	O
among	O
another	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
in	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
watchmen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Doleman	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
Turnagain-lane	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Whitecross-street	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
were	O
disputing	O
,	O
came	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
all	O
three	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
named	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
knowing	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
what	O
women	O
are	O
these	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
knows	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
's	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
fine	O
cordial	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
gone	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
then	O
into	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
then	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
dirty	O
place	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
since	O
to	O
be	O
Blackboy-alley	B-place
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
yards	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Whitecross-street	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
more	O
than	O
us	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
woman	O
is	O
not	O
afraid	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
.	O
They	O
turned	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
whistle	O
immediately	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
immediately	O
surrounded	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
truncheon	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
blackguard	O
,	O
have	O
we	O
got	O
you	O
here	O
at	O
last	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Barnsley	O
opened	O
her	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
(	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
cloaths	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
have	O
mercy	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
freely	O
forgive	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
They	O
laid	O
on	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
stick	O
.	O
The	O
blood	O
ran	O
down	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
condition	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
by	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
they	O
pinched	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
catched	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
hawled	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
drawed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
dunghill	O
:	O
there	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
very	O
safely	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
neither	O
Doleman	O
nor	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
,	O
Doleman	O
came	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
pocket	O
out	O
;	O
saying	O
you	O
old	O
dog	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
totes	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
rattle	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
all	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
12	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
quitted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
at	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hawled	O
him	O
out	O
into	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
the	O
watchman	O
would	O
assist	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
durst	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
murdered	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
rescued	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
is	O
executed	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
175	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Bridgen	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
)	O
Anne	O
Hill	O
is	O
since	O
transported	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
545	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	O
Stevenson	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
)	O
Doleman	O
is	O
since	O
transported	O
by	O
another	O
name	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Kingsland-green	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
sessions	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
going	O
along	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
in	O
robbing	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
,	O
in	O
Blackboy-alley	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
?	O
Hailey	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
stealing	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
dollars	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
ingot	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
evidence	O
against	O
?	O
Hailey	O
.	O
Against	O
one	O
Eggleston	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
:	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
whole	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
dollars	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
Eagle-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
has	O
made	O
his	O
brags	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
for	O
casting	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
evidences	O
here	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
that	O
Jack	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Hailey	O
:	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
this	O
Jack	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Page	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
brick-maker	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
brick-fields	O
,	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
months	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
pointed	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taller	O
than	O
Jack	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
;	O
then	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
touch	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
touched	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hailey	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
plush	O
coat	O
.	O
Hailey	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
plush	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
that	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
the	O
question	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
at	O
brick-making	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
near	O
Battle-bridge	O
Wells	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
,	O
in	O
Red-cross-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
Inn	O
back	O
gate	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
almost	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
lost	O
1	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
chuse	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
less	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
82	O
,	O
83	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
140	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
dollars	O
,	O
and	O
parts	O
of	O
dollars	O
,	O
each	O
ounce	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
value	O
37	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
108	O
ounces	O
,	O
11	O
penny-weights	O
of	O
other	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
13	O
ounces	O
and	O
2	O
penny-weights	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
grains	O
of	O
antient	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
51	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
one	O
foreign	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
15.	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
one	O
other	O
foreign	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
metal	O
tankard	O
silvered	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
metal	O
pint	O
mugs	O
silvered	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
each	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiggan	I-pers
:	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
40	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
silver	O
dollars	O
,	O
some	O
foreign	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
metal	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
December	O
4	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiggan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
packed	O
them	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Bristol	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
Robert	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
Barbican	O
,	O
London	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
received	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
by	O
?	O
Wiggan	O
.	O
By	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
that	O
box	O
that	O
my	O
master	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
carrier	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
deal	O
box	O
.	O
Wiggan	O
.	O
The	O
carrier	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Walter	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Bath	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	O
,	O
the	O
carrier	O
puts	O
up	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
box	O
out	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
Barbican	O
,	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
round	O
to	O
divers	O
places	O
with	O
goods	O
;	O
going	O
round	O
by	O
Moorfields	B-place
I	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
case	O
of	O
books	O
to	O
deliver	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Foundery	B-place
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
carman	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
books	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
words	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
carman	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
books	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Barbican	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
carman	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
little	O
box	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
only	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Foundery	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
whip	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
turn	O
about	O
and	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
since	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
to	O
the	O
Swan-inn	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
with	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
Vine	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
square	O
box	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Moorfields	O
the	O
porter	O
left	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
large	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Foundery	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
up	O
my	O
tail	O
rope	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
wanted	O
my	O
whip	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
little	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
only	O
two	O
women	O
near	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
past	O
by	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
bothered	O
about	O
my	O
whip	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
from	O
the	O
cart	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
antient	O
coin	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
near	O
a	O
patten-maker	O
's	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warning	O
from	O
Goldsmiths-hall	O
of	O
such	O
things	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
insist	O
upon	O
her	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
they	O
were	O
consigned	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
and	O
Carter	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Le-Grand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
had	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
stopped	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
some	O
broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Jane	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
wrong	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
that	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
an	O
exact	O
account	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
constables	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
French	O
plate	O
.	O
and	O
this	O
bag	O
of	O
dollars	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
sacking	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
there	O
are	O
47	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
Wrights	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
expecting	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
lodged	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
John	O
and	O
James	B-pers
both	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
:	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
John	O
's	O
pocket	O
we	O
found	O
13	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
dollar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
nothing	O
concerning	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Allcock	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
ticket	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
prize	O
money	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
tied	O
them	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
with	O
a	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
having	O
a	O
hearing	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
Red	O
Bull	O
yard	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dollars	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sacking	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
constable	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
issued	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Red	O
Bull-alley	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
lived	O
at	O
Islington	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
answered	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
's	O
light	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
stepped	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
:	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
pockets	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
dollar	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
13	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Allcock	O
,	O
in	O
Cow	O
cross	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
ticket	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
prize	O
money	O
.	O
Before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
again	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
keeper	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
all	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
ingot	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
Spaw-fields	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
James	O
had	O
hid	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
13	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
information	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
two	O
other	O
dollars	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
My	O
uncle	O
is	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
business	O
is	O
all	O
conducted	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
of	O
a	O
capital	O
nature	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
flush	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
perhaps	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
may	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
to	O
the	O
uttermost	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
get	O
you	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
discover	O
all	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
encouragement	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
provided	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
he	O
mentioned	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Eggleston	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
took	O
Eggleston	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
one	O
Eadey	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
,	O
whose	O
son	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
near	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
had	O
12	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
wanted	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
us	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
what	O
step	O
we	O
must	O
take	O
next	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
ingot	O
of	O
silver	O
buried	O
,	O
just	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
dunghill	O
;	O
by	O
this	O
direction	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
Spaw	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
silversmiths	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
parted	O
with	O
some	O
dollars	O
and	O
silver	O
coin	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
by	O
eleven	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
:	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
with	O
us	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Bottle	O
in	O
Crooked-lane	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
coin	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
dollars	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
louisd'or	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
buying	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
presence	O
.	O
then	O
Wright	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
silversmiths	O
shops	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
confirmed	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
had	O
melted	O
them	O
down	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
tavern	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret's-hill	O
to	O
dine	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
10	O
yards	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
both	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
and	O
he	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
had	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
clear	O
off	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
went	O
over	O
Westminster-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
over	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
before	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Le-Grand	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
consigned	O
to	O
us	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
warnings	O
printed	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
intelligence	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
stopped	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
being	O
apprised	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
compting-house	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Cox	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Aylesbury-street	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
knowing	O
her	O
,	O
confronted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
lodged	O
at	O
one	O
Wayling	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
chairman	O
in	O
Red	O
Bull-yard	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
dollars	O
,	O
47	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
John	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
waited	O
till	O
betwixt	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wayling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Allcock	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
sent	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
Sharp's-alley	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
8	O
l.	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
foreign	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
debt	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
by	O
his	O
persuasion	O
I	O
bought	O
7	O
l	O
dollars	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
gold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
betwixt	O
22	O
and	O
23	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
sell	O
them	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
J.	O
Allcock	O
.	O
You	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
some	O
rent	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
John	O
Wright	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
box	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
lying	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
seeing	O
before	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
gold	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
goldsmith	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
their	O
characters	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
hogs	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cow-cross	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
3	O
or	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
brick	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
of	O
Marybone	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wayling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
Evans	O
,	O
only	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
their	O
way	O
.	O
John	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
James	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Evans	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
James	O
was	O
detained	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
next	O
sessions	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
shrub	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eggleston	I-pers
.	O
84	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Plint	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Jan.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
engraver	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
married	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
account	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Plint	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
lodgings	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
She	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
porter	O
every	O
day	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
porter	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
and	O
she	O
another	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
apartment	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
man	O
produced	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
all	O
again	O
but	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
all	O
her	O
defence	O
was	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
in	O
another	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Anne	O
or	O
Sarah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
The	O
next	O
time	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
pledge	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
lodging	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
turn	O
you	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
When	O
first	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
clerk	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
12	O
weeks	O
ago	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
clerk	O
had	O
married	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
servant	O
maids	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allison	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Ryder's-court	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
tea-kettle	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
that	O
are	O
found	O
pledged	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Price	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mother	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
lodging	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
two	O
young	O
women	O
that	O
were	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
places	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
twice	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
Carolina	I-pers
Errington	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
40.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fludyer	I-pers
's	I-pers
mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Lane	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
otherwise	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Errington	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
wife	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
53.	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
she	O
was	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Anne	O
Powell	O
,	O
otherwise	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
for	O
marrying	O
Adam	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
being	O
living	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
and	O
was	O
branded	O
.	O
85	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
bombazeen	O
,	O
containing	O
110	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Barbutt	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Hilyer	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Barbutt	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Philip	B-pers
Hilyer	I-pers
is	O
my	O
partner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
we	O
lost	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
bombazeen	O
:	O
we	O
immediately	O
dispersed	O
handbills	O
about	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
each	O
piece	O
.	O
That	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
in	O
the	O
Daily	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
offering	O
the	O
same	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
we	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
inform	O
me	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
weaver	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
mentioned	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
our	O
number	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
one	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
certainly	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
riot	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
lying	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
for	O
security	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
buckle	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
slight	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
one	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
by	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
would	O
make	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
I	O
understood	O
they	O
were	O
bombazeens	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
do	O
his	O
sister	O
any	O
good	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Fagan	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
understood	O
Fagan	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
when	O
sold	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Eagle	O
and	O
Child	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
then	O
say	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
J.	O
Davis	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
spoke	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
Core	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barbutt	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
escaped	O
from	O
the	O
constable	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
retaken	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
kept	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Buridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
going	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
warehouse	O
where	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
once	O
before	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
made	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
nobody	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
King	O
John's-court	O
,	O
where	O
Fagan	O
lives	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bombazeen	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
King	O
John's-court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
Fagan	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
place	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
they	O
shall	O
not	O
stay	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
pieces	O
here	O
produced	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
send	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Stot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gullen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Gullen	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Purpool-lane	B-place
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
lodging	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
herself	O
.	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
appeared	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Gullen	O
.	O
87	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
nightcaps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Dec	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Catherine	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
laundery-maid	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
.	O
Another	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
stays	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
We	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
laundery-door	O
open	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
got	O
hand-bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
a	O
discovery	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
pawnbrokers	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
needless	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
88	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Owen	B-pers
Casaley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
woollen	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
called	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arey	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Arey	I-pers
is	O
now	O
at	O
sea	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fisherman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
my	O
vessel	O
at	O
Gravesend	B-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
London	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
except	O
the	O
pumps	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
89	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Minty	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rowsam	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Rowsam	I-pers
.	O
On	O
New	O
Year's-day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
,	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
treat	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
good	O
lodgings	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Church-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
merry	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
another	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
my	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
wrapped	O
up	O
my	O
gold	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
breeches	O
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pockets	O
had	O
been	O
rifled	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
silver	O
and	O
halfpence	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
bustle	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
mince-pies	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
girl	O
whom	O
they	O
call	O
Fat	O
Moll	O
had	O
distributed	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
King's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
three	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Terence	B-pers
M'Ginnis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Atwood	O
's	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
Atwood	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
girl	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
bustled	O
about	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
new	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
examined	O
and	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
9	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
particular	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
particular	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
toe	O
of	O
her	O
shoe	O
hit	O
against	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
by	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
12	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
purl	O
,	O
their	O
fire	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
drink	O
but	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
lodge	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
people	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
will	O
give	O
3	O
d.	O
may	O
go	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
beds	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
90	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plymmer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
11	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
manslaughter	O
.	O
+	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Vicer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
near	O
the	O
turnpike	O
at	O
Black	B-place
Mary's-hole	I-place
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
driving	O
some	O
cattle	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
turnpike	O
.	O
As	O
his	O
cattle	O
turned	O
short	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Black	O
Mary's-hole	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
field	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
gate	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
through	O
that	O
field	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
that	O
bullock	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
that	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
leaning	O
with	O
his	O
body	O
on	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
post	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
bullocks	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
bullock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
smith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
deceased	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drive	O
the	O
cattle	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
cattle	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
through	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Vicar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Vicar	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
blow	O
was	O
just	O
above	O
his	O
nose	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
directly	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
that	O
blow	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
rails	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
murdered	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
seeing	O
him	O
black	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
collar	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
turned	O
the	O
cattle	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
murdered	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
!	O
The	O
man	O
expired	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
blow	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
Sir	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
murdered	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
lancet	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
opened	O
a	O
vein	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
surgeon	O
)	O
the	O
deceased	O
bled	O
but	O
a	O
trifle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
concern	O
in	O
that	O
field	O
?	O
Vicar	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
authority	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
his	O
cattle	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
authority	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
drovers	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
practice	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
those	O
fields	O
to	O
baulk	O
the	O
turnpike	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hearn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
mother	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
On	O
examining	O
the	O
part	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
nose	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
ear	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
confusion	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
extravasated	O
blood	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
skull	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
amiss	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
blood	O
vessel	O
broke	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
form	O
some	O
judgment	O
what	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
?	O
Hearn	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
that	O
small	O
vein	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
coagulated	O
blood	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
between	O
16	O
and	O
17	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
cattle	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
bullocks	O
strayed	O
through	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
field	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
cattle	O
were	O
;	O
people	O
sometimes	O
drive	O
their	O
cattle	O
across	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
turnpike	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
above	O
his	O
usual	O
wages	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
prevent	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
91	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boram	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jabez	B-pers
David	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
copper	O
stewpans	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jabez	O
.	O
||	O
Jabez	B-pers
David	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Ibbot	O
the	O
evidence	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
both	O
lodge	O
together	O
?	O
David	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
:	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
evidence	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Globe	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
get	O
him	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
one	O
pawned	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
another	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
another	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ibbot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
Christmas-eve	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
back	O
alley	O
where	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
open	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
shutter	O
while	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
and	O
moved	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
bar	O
up	O
and	O
shoved	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
shutter	O
tumbled	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
helped	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
by	O
lifting	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
those	O
stewpans	O
and	O
saucepans	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Heritage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
12	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
waggons	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Heritage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
an	O
inn	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Nov.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
,	O
and	O
work	O
sometimes	O
on	O
the	O
dust-hill	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
go	O
a	O
nursing	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
sheets	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
this	O
linen	O
wet	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
people	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	O
,	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	O
Cotton	O
to	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
shift	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
lodger	O
at	O
Riley	O
's	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
her	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bring	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
truth	O
in	O
all	O
they	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
lawful	O
goods	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Innis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bacon	O
ham	O
,	O
containing	O
19	O
pounds	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Heming	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Heming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
