TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
;	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Rennoldson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Delver	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lingard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Button	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Holliday	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Mynett	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Musson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
.	O
392	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
was	O
indict-	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
,	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Nicholas-lane	B-place
,	I-place
going	I-place
into	I-place
Cannon-street	I-place
,	O
Mr.	O
Wall	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
take	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Bond	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Devereux	O
Wall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
seeing	O
I	O
observed	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
boy	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
lives	O
in	O
Bridgewater-Gardens	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
dropt	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
393	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wenwright	I-pers
.	O
T	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
394	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
;	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Blue	B-place
Boar-inn	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
stables	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
at	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
shirt	O
,	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
exposing	O
the	O
breeches	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Jaques	O
.	O
The	O
breeches	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
drove	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
395	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
left	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
Christian	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Jones	O
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
by	O
Isabella	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Jones	O
.	O
++	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
each	O
trial	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
each	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
facts	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
396	O
,	O
397	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sell	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol-stone	O
studs	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Flint	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Prince's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Christy	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
Child	O
came	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
bundle	O
out	O
of	O
Christy	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
up	O
a	O
street	O
where	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
a	O
watchman	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
believed	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Child	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
Sell	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
Christy	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
honour	O
robbed	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
secure	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Flint	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
Sell	O
would	O
take	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
Child	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chrisly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Flint	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
Child	O
came	O
and	O
snatched	O
away	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
searching	O
where	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Sell	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
has	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
,	O
has	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
spring	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
hold	O
me	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
first	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Child	O
go	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
Sell	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
leave	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Child	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Child	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
Sell	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Sell	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
wished	O
each	O
other	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
soldiers	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
presently	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
that	O
gentleman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
as	O
soldiers	O
are	O
often	O
used	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fighting	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
Child	O
's	O
part	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Akeman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
serjeant	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Child	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
footman	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Sell	O
is	O
given	O
to	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Child	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Sell	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
398	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Beatrice	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
check	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Beatrice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Burleigh-street	B-place
by	I-place
Exeter	I-place
Exchange	I-place
;	O
I	O
lett	O
a	O
lodging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
in	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
husband	O
?	O
Fowler	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lett	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
now	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
calls	O
himself	O
Starkey	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
being	O
not	O
laid	O
right	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
399	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
12	O
knives	O
with	O
silver	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
forks	O
with	O
silver	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
doctor	O
in	O
physic	O
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
behaviour	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
in	O
confinement	O
,	O
as	O
appeared	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Akerman	O
's	O
servants	O
,	O
discovered	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
insane	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
No	O
305	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
400	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
dozen	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
New-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bedfordbury	I-place
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
to	O
let	O
light	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
smashed	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
breeches	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
for	O
body	O
linings	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
shutter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
big	O
was	O
that	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
shutter	O
?	O
Shakespear	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
arm	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
breeches	O
pieces	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
three	O
bundles	O
,	O
with	O
boards	O
on	O
the	O
outsides	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
packthreads	O
were	O
cut	O
and	O
the	O
boards	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
upon	O
Levi	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
a	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
was	O
this	O
hole	O
in	O
your	O
shutter	O
?	O
Shakespear	O
.	O
The	O
hole	O
is	O
near	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
must	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
ledge	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
watchmen	O
were	O
talking	O
to	O
my	O
landlady	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
colour-maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
scourer	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
eight	O
worsted	O
pieces	O
for	O
breeches	O
to	O
sell	O
by	O
commission	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Hyam	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Shakespear	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
have	O
my	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
are	O
two	O
threads	O
and	O
three	O
threads	O
,	O
such	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
marked	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
pieces	O
upon	O
Hyam	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
of	O
a	O
stocking-shop	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
the	O
street	O
calling	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
Peter-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
others	O
concerned	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
something	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
;	O
but	O
Sir	O
John	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Crips	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
August	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Crips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
scourer	O
and	O
dyer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
cloaths	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
holes	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
light	O
in	O
,	O
are	O
cut	O
like	O
a	O
club	O
,	O
called	O
club-holes	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
drawn	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
to	O
scower	O
;	O
all	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
several	O
people	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
scower	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hutchinson	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
one	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
advertised	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
coat	O
?	O
Crips	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
slit	O
under	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
owner	O
's	O
stock-buckle	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bellamy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
cleaned	O
it	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
well	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
now	O
appears	O
in	O
a	O
rumpled	O
condition	O
,	O
by	O
drawing	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
Turnstile	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
of	O
Levi	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
coat	O
to	O
sell	O
by	O
commission	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
and	O
paid	O
honestly	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
breeches	O
pieces	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
witnesses	O
enough	O
here	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Myer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisone	O
r	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
bad	O
things	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
a	O
good	O
or	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
?	O
Myer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
no	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Frederick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
cousin	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
goods	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
401	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
wooden	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
tin	O
canisters	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Wardour-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
backward	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
both	O
my	O
parlour	O
doors	O
stood	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
tea-chest	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
two	O
gowns	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
canisters	O
,	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
strainer	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
every	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
lay	O
her	O
hands	O
on	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
had	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
sucking	O
at	O
her	O
breast	O
;	O
she	O
throwed	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
lap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
M'Grew	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
M'Grew	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
vile	O
woman	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
licked	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
402	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Dunning	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
rags	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Hanover-street	B-place
:	O
I	O
first	O
missed	O
an	O
apron	O
in	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
stockings	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rawlins	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
in	O
Belton-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
Sometime	O
about	O
the	O
eighth	O
or	O
ninth	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
stay	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
till	O
then	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
then	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
me	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
reason	O
for	O
letting	O
her	O
abide	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
who	O
you	O
said	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
403	O
,	O
404	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Hunphrey	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
Catherine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
up	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
in	O
Bedford-street	O
,	O
by	O
Bedfordbury	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
treated	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
made	O
her	O
drunk	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
liquor	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
houses	O
there	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Holbourn	B-place
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
strive	O
to	O
hinder	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
playing	O
with	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
another	O
girl	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
only	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
joke	O
,	O
to	O
warn	O
me	O
never	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
opportunity	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
opportunity	O
enough	O
had	O
I	O
known	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
her	O
up	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
after	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
her	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
405	O
,	O
406	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Byfield	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
horn-box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
harbouring	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
Byfield	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Beet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White's-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Chancery-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
horn-box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
place	O
was	O
this	O
little	O
box	O
put	O
?	O
Beet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
Byfield	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
for	O
my	O
linen	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
keys	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
missing	O
that	O
,	O
knew	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
suspected	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
room-door	O
locked	O
or	O
unlocked	O
?	O
Beet	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
Byfield	O
?	O
Beet	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Her	O
confession	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
against	O
herself	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
tender	O
years	O
.	O
Beet	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Evans	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
we	O
found	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
lived	O
opposite	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
key	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
among	O
some	O
shells	O
of	O
pease	O
in	O
Evan	O
's	O
cellar	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Byfield	O
but	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
tender	O
years	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
407	O
,	O
408	O
,	O
409	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cockelwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
being	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
pump	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
August	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Broken-wharf	B-place
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Aston	O
and	O
Cockelwell	O
,	O
were	O
stopped	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
by	O
comparing	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
pump	O
on	O
my	O
premisses	O
;	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
were	O
labourers	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Cockelwell	O
and	O
Aston	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
something	O
on	O
their	O
shoulders	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Lombard-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
lead	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
you	O
carry	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
my	O
short	O
staff	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wicks	O
's	O
at	O
Broken-wharf	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
seemed	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
willing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
carry	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wicks	O
's	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
acquaint	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
it	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
sent	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
his	O
clerk	O
)	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
pump	O
on	O
his	O
premisses	O
;	O
upon	O
our	O
examining	O
it	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
there	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
confessed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Church	O
's	O
coat	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
cover	O
it	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
bring	O
Church	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
facing	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Sir	O
William	O
would	O
have	O
admitted	O
one	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Church	O
say	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
cutting	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
disown	O
his	O
knowing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
Aston	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
above	O
40	O
men	O
working	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Phesant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
Aston	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wicks	O
pays	O
his	O
men	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
no	O
ill	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Cockelwell	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pigeon	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
in	O
some	O
rubbish	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Aston	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
pigeon	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
nick-name	O
they	O
give	O
to	O
things	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dolings	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hucks	O
the	O
brewer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Cockelwell	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
once	O
kept	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
by	O
Red-lion-square	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
,	O
what	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
is	O
he	O
in	O
?	O
Dolings	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
for	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
past	O
what	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hind	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Thrist-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
once	O
failed	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
up	O
his	O
affairs	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
very	O
justly	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
his	O
creditors	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Church	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
off	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gamage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Church	O
these	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
410	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
since	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1764	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
water-cock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
++	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Watkins	O
when	O
he	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
For	O
want	O
of	O
room	O
here	O
,	O
we	O
refer	O
the	O
reader	O
to	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Watkins	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
cast	O
and	O
executed	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
79.	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
411	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Newbery	I-pers
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Francis	B-pers
Newbery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
bookseller	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	B-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
passage	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
counter	O
and	O
till	O
,	O
beyond	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
till	O
divers	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
led	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
frequent	O
errands	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
a	O
bookseller	O
in	O
Ave-Maria-lane	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
three	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
till	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
this	O
lad	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
evening	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
into	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
particular	O
marks	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
27	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
5	O
guineas	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
planted	O
George	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
peep	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
crevice	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
the	O
command	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
passage	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
numbers	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
alone	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
customer	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
soon	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
serve	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
my	O
lad	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
he	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
flung	O
down	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
done	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
three	O
guineas	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
he	O
took	O
last	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
sware	O
to	O
each	O
separate	O
piece	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newbery	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
planted	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
till	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fore-shop	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
marked	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
had	O
a	O
scratch	O
on	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
nose	O
to	O
the	O
letter	O
G	O
,	O
the	O
date	O
1747	O
;	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
were	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
N	O
under	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
inspected	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
marked	O
as	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
412	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Mackintosh	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
housing	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
full	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
sugar	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
hogsheads	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
.	O
Ruben	B-pers
Rutlidge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
constables	O
of	O
Tower-ward	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
detected	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
some	O
sugar	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
sugar	O
were	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
sweepings	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
nine	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
some	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
that	O
lay	O
near	O
London-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
haled	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
the	O
mate	O
came	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
any	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
good	O
Barbadoes	O
sugar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
to	O
see	O
two	O
shipmates	O
;	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
.	O
Who	O
will	O
work	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
kay	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knees	O
and	O
beg	O
pardon	O
,	O
or	O
go	O
to	O
goal	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Austin	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
.	O
Austin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
ask	O
pardon	O
.	O
Austin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
413	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Aaron	B-pers
Hyams	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
William	I-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Cross-keys	I-place
in	I-place
Old	I-place
Belton-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
where	O
the	O
company	O
that	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
had	O
set	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kates	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
this	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
it	O
had	O
R	O
M	O
in	O
a	O
cypher	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
giving	O
me	O
satisfactory	O
answers	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
cypher	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
legacy	O
by	O
a	O
lady	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
give	O
some	O
better	O
account	O
I	O
shall	O
keep	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
somebody	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
414	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Winks	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Israel	B-pers
Woolf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
one	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
by	O
the	O
ditch-side	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pencil	O
maker	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hairy	O
knapsack	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
?	O
Woolf	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Hamburgh	O
arms	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
either	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
ask	O
so	O
much	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
:	O
worth	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
please	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
wait	O
for	O
you	O
here	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
bring	O
the	O
proper	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
pit	O
of	O
my	O
stomach	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
bowl	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
handle	O
to	O
twist	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
spoon	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
Stratford	O
and	O
Ilford	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
road	O
which	O
I	O
often	O
travel	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
way	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
marked	O
their	O
spoons	O
with	O
M.	O
W.	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Rising	O
Sun	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
three	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Winks	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
loss	O
lately	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
letters	O
were	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
M.	O
W.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Butcher-row	O
,	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
there	O
you	O
will	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
spoon	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wilford	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilford	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
spoon	O
of	O
Israel	O
Woolf	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
spoon	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Winks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Rising	O
Sun	O
between	O
Stratford	O
and	O
Ilford	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
spoon	O
.	O
M.	O
Winks	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
like	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilford	O
.	O
This	O
gentlewoman	O
has	O
acknowledged	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
before	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
different	O
people	O
.	O
M.	O
Winks	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
415	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
August	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Margaret	O
Burch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
almost	O
12	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
and	O
she	O
sell	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
several	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
?	O
M.	O
Burch	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
some	O
muslin	O
,	O
laced	O
caps	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
than	O
I	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
box	O
that	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
chairman	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
M.	O
Burch	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
?	O
M.	O
Burch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
gown	O
at	O
one	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silk	O
,	O
not	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
chairman	O
's	O
wife	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Burch	O
.	O
The	O
chairman	O
's	O
wife	O
used	O
often	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
drawed	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
marble	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Marsden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Titchfield-street	O
,	O
Mary-le-bon	O
parish	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
gentleman	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
,	O
a	O
statuary	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
marble	O
missing	O
about	O
the	O
12th	O
or	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
yard	O
in	O
Charles-street	B-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
foot	O
eight	O
by	O
one	O
foot	O
three	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
thick	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
about	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Lovell	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
very	O
valuable	O
,	O
called	O
Sienna	O
marble	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
marble	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
with	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
inferior	O
marble	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
marble	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
advise	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
rightly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
,	O
but	O
Gray	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
:	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
people	O
have	O
been	O
after	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
400	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Flowers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
216	O
yards	O
of	O
chair	O
girth	O
web	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
two	O
sons	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
journeywork	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
my	O
son	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
found	O
some	O
web	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
gross	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
unpacked	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
rum	O
puncheon	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
compare	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
web	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
John	O
Brown	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
package	O
that	O
we	O
missed	O
,	O
to	O
compare	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
web	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
convinced	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
property	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
peculiar	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
O	O
O	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
mark	O
for	O
that	O
kind	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
other	O
people	O
mark	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
they	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
patterns	O
correspond	O
;	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
rum	O
puncheon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
gross	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
only	O
half	O
a	O
gross	O
:	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
being	O
accused	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
web	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
two	O
shops	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
shop	O
where	O
we	O
missed	O
it	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
reasons	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
use	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Cokayne	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
bailed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
comes	O
upon	O
a	O
surrender	O
:	O
(	O
the	O
web	O
produced	O
,	O
about	O
72	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
About	O
13	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
besides	O
this	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
web	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
web	O
;	O
that	O
room	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cord	O
to	O
put	O
round	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Stationer's-alley	O
,	O
Ludgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
breakfast	O
and	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
to	O
his	O
work	O
very	O
orderly	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
liquor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Duck-lane	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
his	O
friends	O
live	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
very	O
responsible	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
orderly	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
quantity	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
web	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
confused	O
,	O
and	O
hesitated	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
use	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
412	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Martin	B-pers
Vasthold	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
ounces	O
of	O
sterling	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Panton-street	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Aug	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
weighed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
cuttings	O
of	O
silver	O
for	O
the	O
caster	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
melt	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
caster	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
till	O
after	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
weighed	O
sixty	O
ounces	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
weights	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
weighed	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
about	O
12	O
ounces	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
but	O
sixty-six	O
ounces	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
cover	O
of	O
a	O
coffee-pot	O
to	O
solder	O
a	O
button	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
not	O
finding	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
board	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
silver	O
cuttings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
as	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
scale	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
again	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
about	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
at	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Curry	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
board	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
grown	O
dark	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
ours	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
cuttings	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
necessary	O
to	O
search	O
all	O
the	O
workmen	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
imagine	O
he	O
slipped	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
into	O
the	O
sink	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
shuffling	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
grinding-stone	O
trough	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
in	O
searching	O
his	O
lodgings	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
nine	O
ounces	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
silver	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
it	O
into	O
medals	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
weigh	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
trough	O
of	O
the	O
grinding-stone	O
?	O
Ansell	O
.	O
They	O
weighed	O
about	O
nine	O
ounces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Ansell	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
mould	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
a	O
large	O
medal	O
of	O
King	O
Charles	B-pers
the	O
Second	O
:	O
(	O
a	O
medal	O
produced	O
cast	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
silver	O
in	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
since	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
himself	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Ansell	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
to	O
mend	O
a	O
spoon	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
silver	O
under	O
the	O
board	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
mending	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
silver	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
left	O
off	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Ansell	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
we	O
all	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sink	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
slipped	O
the	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
into	O
the	O
grinding-stone	O
trough	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
done	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Curry	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
strict	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Blowet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-lion-street	O
,	O
Seven-dials	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
served	O
him	O
with	O
bread	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
betwixt	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
472	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
show	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
none	O
would	O
do	O
;	O
she	O
ordered	O
a	O
pair	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
bed-gown	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
another	O
shop	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
leather	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
sieve	O
of	O
fruit	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
head	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
service	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
four	O
pair	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
wide	O
enough	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
remarkable	O
wide	O
foot	O
.	O
Our	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
wants	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
She	O
ordered	O
a	O
pair	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bulk	O
by	O
her	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
stooped	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
head	O
to	O
the	O
half	O
sieve	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
arose	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shoes	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
another	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
baskets	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pair	O
;	O
none	O
fitted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
against	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
contented	O
.	O
A	O
fellow	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
fruit	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
420	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
nine	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
seven	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
eight	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
three	O
china	O
bowls	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
china	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hayes	B-place
,	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
upon	O
trial	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
four	O
weeks	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
The	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
servant	O
maid	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
through	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
his	O
bed	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
that	O
morning	O
an	O
hour	O
sooner	O
than	O
usual	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wegg	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
she	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
apprehended	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
At	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
things	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
clerk	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
advertise	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
from	O
such	O
circumstances	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
clear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
headborough	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
mercy	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
alarm	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
naming	O
them	O
)	O
some	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
scullery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
pantry	O
door	O
locked	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
searching	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
then	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
gave	O
you	O
a	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
passage	O
that	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
pantry	O
.	O
The	O
casement	O
was	O
not	O
opened	O
;	O
the	O
leaden	O
bands	O
that	O
go	O
round	O
the	O
bars	O
were	O
untwisted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bar	O
cut	O
in	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
light	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
twisted	O
the	O
bands	O
to	O
try	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
untwist	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
impossible	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
cracked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
bands	O
twisted	O
close	O
before	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
and	O
all	O
whole	O
;	O
this	O
confirmed	O
my	O
supposition	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
walnuts	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
while	O
we	O
searched	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
china	O
in	O
the	O
manger	O
,	O
under	O
some	O
hay	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
to	O
assist	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
their	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
show	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
concealed	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
ceiling	O
in	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
nine	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
three	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
the	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
china	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
rather	O
than	O
lose	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
he	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
this	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
Before	O
me	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
light	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
whole	O
fact	O
.	O
There	O
grows	O
some	O
flowers	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
edging	O
of	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
broke	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
thought	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
goal	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
for	O
that	O
had	O
no	O
foundation	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
but	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
but	O
what	O
are	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
hole	O
through	O
the	O
candlestick	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
we	O
all	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Douse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
whole	O
fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
J.	O
Douse	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
looked	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
show	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
sent	O
for	O
assistance	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
than	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
by	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
order	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
keep	O
a	O
secret	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
desired	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
very	O
cross	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
once	O
before	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
now	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
break	O
the	O
bureau	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
what	O
money	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
to	O
g	O
o	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
cut	O
the	O
bar	O
herself	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
plate	O
again	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
me	O
as	O
sure	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
poisoned	O
my	O
master	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
poison	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
beat	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
poison	O
the	O
rats	O
;	O
I	O
beat	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
boiled	O
milk	O
,	O
and	O
crumbs	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
rats	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
good	O
for	O
the	O
rats	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
freely	O
give	O
it	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
ho	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
from	O
Buckingham	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
body	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
time	O
fixed	O
for	O
the	O
doing	O
this	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
agreed	O
upon	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
saying	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
All	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
saying	O
is	O
false	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
despiseable	O
a	O
fellow	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Young	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
or	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
find	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Wegg	O
,	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
were	O
for	O
laying	O
the	O
indictment	O
only	O
to	O
transport	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Wegg	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
as	O
he	O
understood	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
;	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
in	O
their	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
cart	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
White-horse	O
at	O
Shepherd's-bush	O
,	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
backwards	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
street-door	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
question	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
could	O
resolve	O
but	O
he	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
see	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
forth-coming	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
tied	O
?	O
Young	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
suffered	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
headborough	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
behave	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
hanged	O
upon	O
any	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
action	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
angry	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
to	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
wholly	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
eaten	O
our	O
dinners	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
horse	O
we	O
returned	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
,	O
at	O
Aylesbury	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Wegg	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
then	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
order	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
some	O
slight	O
hints	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
this	O
till	O
then	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Coombs	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
charge	O
this	O
on	O
his	O
mistress	O
?	O
Coombs	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
that	O
his	O
mistress	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wegg	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
these	O
were	O
not	O
half	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
?	O
Coombs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
running	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
pursue	O
?	O
Coombs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
thick	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Douse	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
J.	O
Douse	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
mistress	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
his	O
wages	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Miss	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
borrow	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
mistress	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
ruffled	O
shirt	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
that	O
was	O
slit	O
down	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
basket	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
8	O
s.	O
that	O
being	O
my	O
own	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
being	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
bits	O
of	O
silk	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
describe	O
the	O
shirt	O
rightly	O
?	O
J.	O
Douse	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
know	O
of	O
that	O
by	O
rummaging	O
about	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
mistress	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
pray	O
for	O
her	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
directly	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
necessary	O
you	O
should	O
explain	O
what	O
has	O
come	O
out	O
from	O
those	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wegg	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
it	O
frightened	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
that	O
excuse	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
receive	O
the	O
8	O
s.	O
nor	O
shirt	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
surely	O
be	O
hanged	O
;	O
now	O
make	O
your	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
Almighty	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
Madam	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
pray	O
for	O
you	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
shirt	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
retaken	O
,	O
we	O
examined	O
the	O
bundle	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
shirt	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
your	O
compassion	O
has	O
thrown	O
a	O
great	O
cloud	O
over	O
this	O
affair	O
:	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
ask	O
you	O
a	O
few	O
questions	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
directly	O
or	O
indirectly	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
order	O
or	O
encouragement	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
Not	O
the	O
least	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
your	O
Lordship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cut	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
walnuts	O
,	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
threaten	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
him	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
thought	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
walnu	O
's	O
.	O
Coombs	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wonder	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
comeback	O
;	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
Who	O
would	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
should	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
there	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
telling	O
my	O
wife	O
of	O
that	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
made	O
my	O
wife	O
suspect	O
the	O
things	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
,	O
thoroughly	O
satisfied	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
truth	O
in	O
all	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
her	O
design	O
in	O
letting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
real	O
mercy	O
and	O
compassion	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
any	O
word	O
in	O
quarrelling	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
lived	O
on	O
good	O
terms	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
angry	O
at	O
her	O
letting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
saved	O
a	O
thief	O
from	O
the	O
gallows	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
cut	O
your	O
throat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold-headed	O
cane	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
September	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
Vere-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clare-market	I-place
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
cane	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
by	O
who	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
was	O
fetched	O
to	O
Weatherby	O
's	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Holebrook	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
spending	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
at	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
cane	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
cane	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
ago	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
utter	O
strangers	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
:	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
ramble	O
into	O
Weatherby	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
recollected	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
(	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
that	O
sat	O
contiguous	O
to	O
where	O
Sir	O
James	O
sat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
keep	O
an	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
acquaint	O
Sir	O
James	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
came	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
cane	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
wheel	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Belbin	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
James	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
cane	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directly	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
gentleman	O
a	O
bribe	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Kynaston	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
oath	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
spring	O
away	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
coming	O
up	O
towards	O
Covent	O
garden	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
for	O
yourself	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
confirmation	O
of	O
your	O
guilt	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
liberty	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Belbin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
liquor	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
lost	O
his	O
cane	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
after	O
Sir	O
James	O
lost	O
his	O
cane	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Weatherby	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Sir	O
James	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
both	O
sticks	O
or	O
canes	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
his	O
cane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
that	O
cane	O
:	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
resistance	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Sir	O
James	O
's	O
cane	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
his	O
crest	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
release	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
liquor	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
chose	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
trifling	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
twenty	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
work	O
is	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
home	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
clean	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
nephew	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Mogul's-head	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
come	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
pretty	O
merry	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
home	O
brew	O
'd	O
beer	O
in	O
Vere	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
:	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
cane	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Mogul	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
till	O
about	O
twelve	O
;	O
coming	O
away	O
very	O
much	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
cane	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Blue	O
Posts	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
more	O
liquor	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Weatherby	O
's	O
there	O
came	O
Sir	O
James	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
cane	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
their	O
cane	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Ferdinand	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
accident	O
happened	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
supped	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Mogul's-head	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
a-la-mode	O
beef	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
punch	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
fine	O
ale	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
Sir	O
James	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
only	O
two	O
jugs	O
of	O
ale	O
there	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
cane	O
at	O
the	O
Mogul's-head	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
drunk	O
when	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
drunk	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
kept	O
better	O
hours	O
than	O
he	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
disturbance	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
noted	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
sticks	O
close	O
to	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
gets	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
week	O
regular	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
at	O
Plaistow	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holbrook	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
courtyard	O
here	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Alice	I-pers
Smithers	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cotton	O
robe	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
five	O
diaper	O
clouts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Huitson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Huitson	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
motion-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
an	O
alley	B-place
near	I-place
Golden-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
robe	O
,	O
five	O
clouts	O
,	O
a	O
candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
stays	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
at	O
Mr.	O
West	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
423	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hariott	B-pers
M'Cartney	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
M'Cartney	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
footman	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
two	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
two	O
spoons	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
signed	O
a	O
ticket	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
Bray	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
lady	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
pledged	O
them	O
for	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
name	O
Bradshaw	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
accidentally	O
.	O
met	O
with	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
424	O
,	O
425	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
worsted	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
gauze	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
