TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
MANSFIELD	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
SIDNEY	B-pers
STAFFORD	I-pers
SMYTHE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
HENRY	B-pers
BATHURST	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Commen	O
Pleas	O
||	O
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maile	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Morrel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Meares	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickford	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fillingham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gary	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Longland	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Langser	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
.	O
472	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
chrystal	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailcloth-maker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Old-street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
it	O
being	O
Bartholomew-fair-time	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
hospital-gate	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
men	O
,	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
put	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
shoulder	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cried	O
,	O
Drive	O
through	O
,	O
drive	O
through	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stop	O
.	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
got	O
myself	O
back	O
again	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
gate	O
till	O
the	O
mob	O
was	O
dispersed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
reading	O
a	O
play	O
bill	O
that	O
was	O
stuck	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
will	O
all	O
be	O
acted	O
tonight	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
plays	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
pretty	O
clear	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
hospital-gate	O
,	O
again	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
situation	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
shoulders	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
before	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
cry	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
Drivethro	O
'	O
,	O
drive	O
thro	O
'	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
they	O
drove	O
me	O
almost	O
down	O
by	O
showing	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
hand	O
away	O
the	O
prisoner	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
more	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
insulted	O
me	O
while	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
;	O
a	O
boy	O
who	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
me	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
pointing	O
towards	O
Pye-corner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
trust	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
another	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
down	O
towards	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
the	O
the	O
first	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
goes	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Windmill-court	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
seeing	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
a	O
spur-stone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
my	O
watch	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
stoop	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
near	O
us	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
constable	O
yourself	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
here	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
was	O
sitting	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
inward	O
room	O
before	O
an	O
Alderman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
first	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
story	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Whitechapel	O
officer	O
,	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
citizen	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Whitechapel	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
his	O
name	O
on	O
a	O
sign	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
in	O
George-yard	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
the	O
watch	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
his	O
companions	O
have	O
prevented	O
me	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
boy	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
hospital-gate	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
driving	O
by	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
crowd	O
with	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
towards	O
Windmill-court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
advertised	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
hundred	O
watches	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
escape	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
trod	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hot-presser	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Chiswell	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
Bartholomew-fair	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Howard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Cloyster-gate	O
and	O
the	O
Red-cow	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
way	O
between	O
the	O
rails	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
many	O
people	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
very	O
few	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stooping	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
lie	O
before	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
directly	O
into	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
as	O
he	O
rose	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
or	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
towards	O
the	O
Red-cow	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
finding	O
it	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
stranger	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
pocket	O
in	O
Bartholomew-fair	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
there	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
out	O
of	O
curiosity	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
enquire	O
for	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
enquire	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
the	O
gate	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
So	O
you	O
are	O
got	O
here	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
got	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
you	O
said	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
just	O
looked	O
round	O
on	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
a	O
subpoena	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
prisoner	O
you	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
you	O
lived	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
the	O
subpoena	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
guess	O
how	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
paper	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
your	O
name	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
find	O
you	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
it	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
used	O
the	O
Ship	O
alehouse	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
this	O
month	O
past	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
work	O
are	O
you	O
employed	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hot-presser	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
subpoena	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
you	O
where	O
you	O
lived	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
my	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
if	O
wanted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
George-yard	O
near	O
Whitechapel-church	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
sign	O
as	O
such	O
;	O
all	O
I	O
say	O
is	O
he	O
behaved	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
George-yard	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
but	O
honesty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Malkin	I-pers
,	O
that	O
live	O
in	O
George-yard	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
directly	O
turned	O
his	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
company	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Alderman	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
man	O
here	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
whose	O
evidence	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Ship	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
George	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
by	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
(	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
Howard	O
.	O
)	O
Cousins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hot-presser	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
with	O
one	O
that	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
particular	O
circumstance	O
relative	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
whose	O
pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
Howard	O
upon	O
that	O
subject	O
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
changed	O
any	O
words	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
serving	O
him	O
with	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
or	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
give	O
evidence	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Cousins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
telling	O
us	O
that	O
a	O
stranger	O
was	O
telling	O
him	O
one	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
wanted	O
.	O
Cousins	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
never	O
no	O
such	O
words	O
pass	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Howard	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
month	O
last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
certain	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
473	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Pattey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Betty	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Betty	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
.	O
On	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
named	O
French	O
,	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
my	O
ring	O
from	O
my	O
finger	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
awaked	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
awaked	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
ring	O
;	O
the	O
lodging	O
is	O
in	O
New-court	B-place
,	I-place
Duck-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
court	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
ring	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
finger	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
my	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Hetty	O
French	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
French	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
it	O
?	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
center	O
betwixt	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
ring	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Betty	B-pers
Bath	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
French	O
,	O
never	O
came	O
for	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
lad	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
her	O
went	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
with	O
French	O
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
;	O
French	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
474	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
and	O
seven	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rolfe	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Tho	B-pers
Rolfe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
and	O
corn-chandler	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
of	O
corn	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
waters	O
the	O
roads	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
sack	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
oats	O
in	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
bushels	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
his	O
binn	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
compared	O
with	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agreed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
prisoner	O
keep	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
or	O
deal	O
in	O
corn	O
?	O
Rolfe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
works	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
to	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
other	O
sacks	O
of	O
mine	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Edw	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
oats	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Rolfe	O
saw	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
mother-in-la	O
w	O
used	O
to	O
rake	O
corn	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
thrashed	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
sacks	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
475	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckle	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederic	B-pers
Laber	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
I	O
live	O
facing	O
Catharine-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
missing	O
three	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
knee	O
buckle	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Frederic	O
Laber	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
chamber-door	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
lighted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
a-jar	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
calling	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
to	O
consider	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
knock	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
sword	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
knocking	O
hard	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
some	O
body	O
was	O
walking	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
nobody	O
answer	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
shove	O
the	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
an	O
opposition	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
rattle	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
again	O
,	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
post	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
sword	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
at	O
arms	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
till	O
a	O
watchman	O
came	O
I	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
lunge	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
observe	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
my	O
sword	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
shirt	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
off	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
near	O
Exeter-exchange	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
hit	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
reel	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
attempt	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
certainly	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
brought	O
Capt	O
.	O
Laber	O
's	O
hat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
your	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
not	O
belonging	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
upon	O
returning	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
drop	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Crispin	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
except	O
a	O
silver	O
knee-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
myself	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
your	O
sword	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Crispin	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
lunge	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
calling	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-court	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
White-hart-yard	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
's	O
light	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
stop	O
thief	O
again	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
is	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
running	O
towards	O
me	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
my	O
stick	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
staggering	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
turn	O
about	O
and	O
tussel	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
my	O
stick	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
collared	O
him	O
with	O
both	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
my	O
knee	O
on	O
his	O
guts	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
assistance	O
came	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
captain	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
something	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
throw	O
'd	O
something	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
captain	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
knee-buckle	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
gentleman	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Gibson	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tablespoon	O
in	O
Burleigh-street	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Beasley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
hat	O
facing	O
Exeter-exchange	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
and	O
Burleigh-street	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Leaber	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
bit	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
stand	O
is	O
facing	O
Exeter-exchange	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
street-door	O
over	O
night	O
myself	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
and	O
bolted	O
and	O
chained	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
more	O
particular	O
in	O
securing	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
than	O
usual	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
stop	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
it	O
awaked	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
two	O
friends	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
up	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
dropt	O
our	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
church-yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
a	O
companion	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
;	O
going	O
by	O
Catharine-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
girl	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
ill	O
language	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
rushed	O
by	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
picked	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
sword	O
;	O
they	O
secured	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
imagine	O
the	O
watchman	O
that	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
wanting	O
a	O
candle	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Dean	B-pers
Evitt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-fleece	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
about	O
dinner-time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
journeyman	O
's	O
house	O
by	O
Hungerford	O
market	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Longden	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bred	O
and	O
born	O
in	O
Shropthire	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-head	O
tavern	O
,	O
Great	O
Queen's-street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-inn-fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
he	O
put	O
himself	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
476	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
September	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
shift	O
on	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
rather	O
have	O
robbed	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
England	O
or	O
Ireland	O
than	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
freely	O
forgive	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
shift	O
?	O
East	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
East	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
shoved	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lock	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
shift	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
without	O
shoe	O
or	O
stocking	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Consider	O
,	O
Mr.	O
East	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
native	O
country	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Irishwoman	O
)	O
they	O
have	O
transported	O
my	O
husband	O
already	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
husband	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
474	O
.	O
477	O
,	O
478	O
,	O
479	O
,	O
480	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Donnoly	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
and	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
worsted	O
piece	O
for	O
breeches	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chandler-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
neighbour	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
on	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
shut	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
absent	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
your	O
shop	O
broke	O
?	O
Day	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
broke	O
a	O
square	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
looks	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
candle	O
burning	O
just	O
opposite	O
the	O
glass	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
fine	O
cotton	O
and	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
five	O
yard	O
worsted	O
piece	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
pane	O
that	O
was	O
broken	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
my	O
neighbour	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
five	O
hundred	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
bills	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
pledged	O
in	O
Catharine-street	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Styles	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
pledged	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Donnoly	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
seen	O
two	O
pair	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cawdey	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
stopped	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
there	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
Donnoly	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
all	O
my	O
stockings	O
again	O
within	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cawdey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Berwick	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
Saturday	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
own	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Black-horse	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
sold	O
oysters	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
gave	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
then	O
Webb	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
husband	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
7	O
s.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
fetch	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
9	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
fetch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
came	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
and	O
Webb	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
stockings	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stocking	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
circumstances	O
in	O
the	O
workmanship	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Styles	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
in	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Donnoly	I-pers
was	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
last	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
betwixt	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
;	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Wyld	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Donnoly	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
halting	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Donnoly	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
nobody	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
were	O
standing	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Dragan	O
alehouse	O
and	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dv	O
's	O
shop	O
is	O
directly	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
they	O
seemed	O
very	O
busy	O
;	O
this	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
some	O
thing	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
to	O
make	O
observations	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
50	O
or	O
60	O
yards	O
higher	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bagnio	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
no	O
good	O
began	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
and	O
turned	O
their	O
backs	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
walked	O
away	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
withdrew	O
;	O
then	O
Donnoly	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
neighbour	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
round	O
and	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
shall	O
come	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
of	O
Wyld-street	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
Donnoly	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
slapped	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
Webb	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
remained	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
his	O
rent	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
but	O
very	O
indifferent	O
hours	O
:	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
,	O
two	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
later	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
warning	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
a	O
quarter	O
's	O
rent	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
defiance	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
pleased	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
girls	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
are	O
like	O
servants	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
lame	O
boy	O
that	O
goes	O
a	O
begging	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
daddy	O
's	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
girls	O
to	O
be	O
hard	O
working	O
poor	O
girls	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
stockings	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Hoop	O
and	O
Magpie	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sing	O
ballads	O
.	O
Donnoly	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
singing	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
Cranbourn-alley	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
Kitty	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Kitty	O
?	O
M	O
Stevens	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
sing	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Styles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
duplicate	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
M	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
harm	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
by	O
his	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Kitty	O
.	O
Donnoly	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
stockings	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
coming	O
through	O
Cranbourn-alley	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
that	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
borrowed	O
a	O
shilling	O
of	O
a	O
soldier	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
gin	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
was	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Wadsley	I-pers
lent	O
me	O
the	O
shilling	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
Donnoly	O
.	O
The	O
witness	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
fish	O
and	O
oysters	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
night	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taking	O
stockings	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
was	O
this	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
which	O
side	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
near	O
the	O
playhouse	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
Within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
play-house	O
gate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Donnoly	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Hospital	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
sore	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
today	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
buy	O
the	O
stockings	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
asked	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
to	O
Russel-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
borrowed	O
the	O
shilling	O
of	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
The	O
soldier	O
left	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
stockings	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
lightish	O
coloured	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
so	O
particular	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
Because	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
there	O
with	O
my	O
oysters	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wadsley	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Donnoly/	O
15	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
on	O
Friday	O
or	O
Saturday	O
night	O
to	O
bay	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
James-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
the	O
play	O
house	O
is	O
on	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
bagnio	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
person	O
did	O
he	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
He	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
by	O
chance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
stockings	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shilling	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
over	O
or	O
under	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
whitish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Wadsley/	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
alone	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
15	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
new	O
buildings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
employed	O
lately	O
?	O
Wadsley	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
jury	O
a	O
reason	O
why	O
you	O
pawned	O
them	O
so	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
cheap	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Webb	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
stockings	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
fourteen	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
2	O
s.	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
owed	O
my	O
landlady	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
raise	O
my	O
rent	O
.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Webb	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
his	O
landlady	O
's	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
stockings	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
Webb	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
pedlar	O
;	O
Powell	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
where	O
we	O
sell	O
oyners	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
bring	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
Powell	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Webb	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
purl	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
both	O
come	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
his	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
stockings	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
his	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
stopped	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
one	O
pair	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bland	O
's	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Webb	O
pawned	O
two	O
pair	O
at	O
one	O
place	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
body	O
pawned	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pair	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
14	O
pair	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
of	O
a	O
pedlar	O
.	O
For	O
Webb	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Webb	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
affair	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
and	O
Donnoly	O
are	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Donnoly	O
asked	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
oath	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
Sir	O
John	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
no	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Hutchens	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
Webb	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
he	O
gave	O
these	O
women	O
these	O
stockings	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Donnoly	O
and	O
Webb	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Powell	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Donnoly	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
,	O
No	O
183	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
most	O
gracious	O
pardon	O
.	O
481.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
482	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Eady	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Poultry	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
comb	O
maker	O
and	O
hardware-man	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Crooked-lane	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
frighted	O
by	O
some	O
men	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
glasses	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
without	O
bidding	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
about	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
glasses	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
my	O
glass	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
thumb	O
and	O
finger	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
wriggling	O
and	O
shaking	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
removed	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
place	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
them	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
in	O
pairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
removed	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
deep	O
did	O
it	O
lie	O
beneath	O
the	O
glass	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
It	O
lay	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
from	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
crack	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
a	O
fresh	O
place	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Deptford	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
his	O
glass	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
pump-maker	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Tanton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-court	O
,	O
Cow-lane	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest-hard	O
working	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
483	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
printed	O
book	O
,	O
intitled	O
,	O
Memoirs	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Lady	O
of	O
Family	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Susanna	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
bookseller	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
King's-head-court	B-place
,	O
which	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
Shoe-lane	O
into	O
Gough	O
square	O
;	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
Anne	B-pers
Showell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
to	O
sit	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
soon	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
books	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
catched	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
the	O
book	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
courtand	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
and	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
girl	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
shelf	O
withinside	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
book	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
outward	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
book	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
away	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
let	O
people	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
nothing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Showell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Edmunds	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
first	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
pamphlet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
directly	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
bound	O
book	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Shoe-lane	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
book	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
book	O
up	O
(	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
young	O
fellows	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
myself	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
and	O
hawled	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carver	O
and	O
gilder	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
of	O
a	O
frolick	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
that	O
seems	O
plain	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
confinement	O
before	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
proved	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King's-road	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
going	O
by	O
another	O
name	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
readily	O
refer	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
484	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
64	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
At	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	B-pers
More	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Oxley	I-pers
called	O
out	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
butter	O
?	O
Strange	O
.	O
The	O
gross	O
weight	O
was	O
eighty-seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
butter	O
was	O
sixty	O
four	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Strange	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Oxley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
Mess	O
More	O
and	O
Strange	O
;	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
our	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
hear	O
me	O
say	O
a	O
man	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Oxley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Butter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
More	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Oxley	O
,	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Townshend	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
for	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
weaver	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Beef	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
weaver	O
by	O
trade	O
in	O
the	O
silk	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
485	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
a	O
fish-skin	O
case	O
,	O
two	O
metal	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
necklaces	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
September	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hand-alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
?	O
Horton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
tongs	O
,	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
earrings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Horton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
M.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
M.	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
22	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wardenbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
my	O
entry	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
one	O
Dixon	B-pers
a	O
barber	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
she	O
clapped	O
her	O
hands	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
barber	O
she	O
was	O
ruined	O
for	O
ever	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
been	O
up	O
to	O
miss	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
These	O
spoons	O
were	O
made	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
486	O
,	O
487	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrill	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Siseland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
five	O
petticoats	O
,	O
three	O
gauze	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
quarter	O
of	O
burdett	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
September	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wills	O
's	O
in	O
Friday-street	O
,	O
No	O
44	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
lost	O
I	O
left	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
sugar-baker	O
at	O
Puddledock	B-place
in	I-place
Thames	I-place
street	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
and	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
key	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
I	O
should	O
want	O
any	O
cloaths	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
trouble	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
box	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Sep	O
tember	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
his	O
man	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
wig	O
and	O
a	O
whitish	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
box	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
alley	O
by	O
Sand-wharf	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
box	O
full	O
of	O
brickbars	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l	O
is	O
it	O
that	O
makes	O
it	O
so	O
heavy	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
carrying	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
fellow	O
servants	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
full	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
carried	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
coach	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
fellow	O
servants	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
turn	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
drove	O
me	O
to	O
Pye	O
corner	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
shortest	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
coach-box	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
madam	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
this	O
Phoenix-court	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
in	O
Phoenix-court	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
madam	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
this	O
hat-box	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
bring	O
your	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Mr.	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
my	O
hat-box	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
,	O
take	O
my	O
hat-box	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
neither	O
coach	O
nor	O
coachman	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
the	O
rattling	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Saffron-hill	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
coach	O
,	O
stop	O
coach	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
make	O
yourself	O
quite	O
easy	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
expect	O
you	O
will	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Carnaby-street	O
,	O
Golden-square	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Siseland	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
aprons	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
petticoats	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
wife	O
to	O
Siseland	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
Siseland	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
they	O
lay	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
guessed	O
within	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
right	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
for	O
17	O
s.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Sitting	O
Alderman	O
,	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Gynn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
a	O
messenger	O
came	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
two	O
coachmen	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
girl	O
of	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
there	O
Siseland	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
free	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
at	O
this	O
last	O
witness	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
Wardour	O
street	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
Knave's-acre	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
pawned	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
said	O
Barrill	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lodge	O
at	O
New	O
Prison	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
himself	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
Siseland	O
and	O
he	O
handcuffed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
very	O
readily	O
:	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Hanse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
name	O
was	O
it	O
pledged	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Barrill	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
6	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
at	O
a	O
workhouse	O
by	O
Berkeley-square	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Siseland	O
's	O
direction	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
gown	O
at	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
at	O
Knave's-acre	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
Siseland	O
,	O
(	O
all	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gown	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
described	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
heard	O
Barrill	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
flung	O
away	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Barrill	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
Great	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
coach	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
Sifeland	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
his	O
wife	O
carry	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
accordingly	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Siseland	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
box	O
and	O
desired	O
leave	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
liberty	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
.	O
To	O
Barrill	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Furnis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Barrill	O
two	O
years	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
James-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
he	O
drives	O
for	O
a	O
master-coachman	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
tall	O
chandler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
by	O
Chapel	O
street	O
,	O
Soho	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Barrill	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
Grosier	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dean	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
St.	O
Anne's-court	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Barrill	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
-	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
universal	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
drove	O
my	O
Lady	O
Firebrace	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Meeten	I-pers
.	O
Barrill	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
going	O
on	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
E.	O
Meeten	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
;	O
I	O
lett	O
out	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
lodgers	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Barrill	O
six	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
488	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
thickset	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
thickset	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thickset	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
;	O
one	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
;	O
one	O
thickset	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
thickset	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Kenelm	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
separate	O
traders	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
thickset	O
coats	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
thickset	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thickset	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
at	O
separate	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
?	O
J.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
thickset	O
coat	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
or	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
(	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
in	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
thickset	O
coat	O
,	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
these	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
Soho	O
,	O
at	O
Mr	O
Cordey	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
several	O
names	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
leather	O
breeches	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
near	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
1	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
who	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cardey	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
here	O
produced	O
were	O
pawned	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
genteely	O
dressed	O
,	O
every	O
time	O
in	O
different	O
sorts	O
of	O
cloaths	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
together	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
(	O
produced	O
a	O
thickset	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
)	O
These	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Miller	O
.	O
J.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
question	O
to	O
ask	O
but	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
indict	O
me	O
.	O
J.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
promise	O
him	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
indict	O
him	O
capitally	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
of	O
his	O
pawning	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
The	O
Jury	O
were	O
satisfied	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
489	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Strut	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Britain	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
prisoner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
||	O
Francis	B-pers
Britain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
August	O
she	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nobody	O
belonging	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
her	O
key	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
that	O
woman	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
second	O
examination	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
sheet	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
sheet	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Britain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
are	O
our	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
aunt-in-law	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
often	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
A.	O
Nesbit	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
above	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
behaved	O
well	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
while	O
in	O
service	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
under	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
?	O
A.	O
Nesbit	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
lately	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
in	O
Last	O
Sessions-paper	O
,	O
No	O
468	O
.	O
490	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift-sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
wig	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Spong	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Hannah	B-pers
Spong	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Owen	B-pers
Spong	I-pers
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
coming	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
H.	O
Spong	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
also	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
gate-way	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
pursued	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
coarse	O
apron	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
about	O
the	O
bundle	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Spong	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
seeing	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
coarse	O
apron	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
Mrs.	O
Spong	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Five	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
I	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
beans	O
of	O
Shock-a-Tory	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
who	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
makes	O
short	O
measure	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
black	O
eye	O
,	O
the	O
swelling	O
fell	O
down	O
just	O
like	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
blood	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
then	O
brought	O
down	O
here	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
my	O
bare	O
bedstead	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
penny-post	O
letter	O
for	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
shift	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
all	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
my	O
poor	O
bedstead	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
gown	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
pawned	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
hopping	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
and	O
Shock-a-Tory	O
dragged	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
naked	O
sword	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
was	O
no	O
thorough-fare	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
coming	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
mouths	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
enemies	O
when	O
they	O
seized	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
an	O
inch	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
491	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Loxham	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jane	I-pers
Gadson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brandel	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Brandel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Brandel	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Piccadilly	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
difficulty	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sheet	O
from	O
her	O
bed	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Brandel	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
one	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
?	O
M.	O
Brandel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
bed-curtains	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
trunk	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
at	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
them	O
also	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
granted	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
without	O
any	O
expence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
confession	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
sold	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Joland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
two	O
bed	O
curtains	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
Joland	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
White-lion-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
two	O
separate	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
utter	O
stranger	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
necessaries	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
curtains	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
492	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
More	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Silver-court	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bartholomew-fair	O
along	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6th	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
cloak	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Hosier-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
cry	O
out	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
had	O
put	O
my	O
cloak	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
cloak	O
was	O
never	O
found	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Iverson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bartholomew-fair	O
along	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
her	O
cloak	O
was	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
right-hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
Hosier-lane	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
little	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Hosier-lane	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
among	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
chaps	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Nevil	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drawing	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
and	O
Nevil	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
cardinal	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Hosier-lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Nevil	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
pocket	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
cloak	O
into	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Mich	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Nevil	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
city	O
marshal	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
came	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
called	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
for	O
the	O
cardinal	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
the	O
city	O
marshal	O
said	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
scandal	O
of	O
a	O
prosecution	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
part	O
were	O
for	O
going	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
having	O
the	O
cardinal	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
two	O
boys	O
had	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
mob	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
on	O
my	O
legs	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
493	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nineteen	O
live	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hounslow	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
nineteen	O
live	O
geese	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pen	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
betwixt	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
geese	O
also	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
dead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Whitney	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beds	I-pers
worth	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Turk's-head	O
at	O
Stainers	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
horse	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
ass	O
,	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
some	O
dead	O
geese	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
a-piece	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
Hounds	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
afterwards	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sack	O
and	O
bag	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
spoil	O
by	O
lying	O
together	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
nineteen	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
their	O
throats	O
were	O
all	O
cut	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
some	O
faggots	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
to	O
Justice	O
Bulstrode	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Bedsworth	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
geese	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
foot	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
the	O
mark	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
near	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
his	O
ass	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
geese	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
sold	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
Staines	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
headborough	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Turk's-head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
clear	O
myself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Turk's-head	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Conner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull's-head	O
in	O
Kent	O
street	O
;	O
coming	O
to	O
Brentford	O
I	O
met	O
some	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Staines	O
;	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Hounslow	O
some	O
boys	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
rogue	O
with	O
my	O
ass	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
crupper	O
,	O
saddle	O
and	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Staines	O
,	O
by	O
people	O
that	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
part	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
heath	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
awaked	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
cock	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
some	O
geese	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
they	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
them	O
here	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
drove	O
them	O
from	O
Wiltshire	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
grew	O
so	O
tired	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
kill	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
an	O
ass	O
you	O
are	O
capable	O
of	O
carrying	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
all	O
lay	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
lose	O
no	O
great	O
matter	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
19	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
nineteen	O
geese	O
:	O
I	O
cry	O
about	O
hair	O
skins	O
,	O
rabbit	O
skins	O
,	O
old	O
rags	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
flint	O
glass	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
494	O
,	O
495.	O
John	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
resisting	O
the	O
officers	O
of	O
the	O
customs	O
in	O
their	O
duty	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
496	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Judith	B-pers
Flood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Stephen	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
eating-house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fox's-court	O
,	O
Gray's-inn	O
lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
this	O
silver	O
spoon	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
on	O
referring	O
to	O
the	O
papers	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
advertised	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
peace	O
officer	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
the	O
party	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
or	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
charged	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
appeared	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
lad	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
497	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Segerly	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Segerly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Prince's-street	B-place
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pushed	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Halloo	O
,	O
then	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
others	O
full	O
drive	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Segerly	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
were	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
snatched	O
