TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
SIR	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HEWITT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
+	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Markbee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chamin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crockett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shackle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Lark	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
Benj	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
Rich	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Wm	B-pers
Sheeringham	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
129	O
,	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Pouting	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
linen	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
dusk	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
glass	O
crack	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
Hewit	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
broken	O
glass	O
,	O
almost	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
elbow	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
hole	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
drawn	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
through	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
brother	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Hewit	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
boy	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
)	O
took	O
and	O
pushed	O
my	O
arm	O
in	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
uncle	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
workhouse	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Pouting	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
chair-maker	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Hewit	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Pouting	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
131	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
girdle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
crape	O
hatband	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	B-place
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
maid	O
at	O
home	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
home	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
chests	O
and	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
girdle	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
quantity	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
begging	O
in	O
the	O
hard	O
weather	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
clothe	O
him	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
good	O
boy	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
evidences	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
things	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
friend	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Lion	O
at	O
West-end	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
heard	O
people	O
talking	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
described	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Grove	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
boy	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
bye	O
lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
barn	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
about	O
,	O
trod	O
upon	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
feet	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
covered	O
in	O
the	O
hay	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
his	O
cloaths	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
crape	O
hat-band	O
,	O
and	O
silk	O
girdle	O
;	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
)	O
we	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
tiles	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
January	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Doget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Cook	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Lion	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
suspected	O
described	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
where	O
we	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
barn	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
hay	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Grove	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saville	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hand-raw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Constance	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Constance	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
Crompton-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Salisbury	B-place
street	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
work	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
using	O
not	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Barley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
saw	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
job	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
job	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
a	O
job	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
saw	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
133.	O
Miles	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
jointer	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pannel-saw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Lambert-court	B-place
,	I-place
Long-acre	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
work-shop	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
apprentice	O
to	O
enquire	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Clegg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
these	O
things	O
here	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
above	O
8	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lent	O
me	O
tools	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
apprentice	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
lend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tools	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
pawn	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
tools	O
which	O
you	O
lent	O
him	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
lend	O
him	O
any	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
raise	O
money	O
on	O
them	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
work	O
unfinished	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
through	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
that	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
tools	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pillow-bears	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
stuff	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
prisoner	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	B-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
;	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
quarrelled	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
set	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
advance	O
money	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Hutchinson	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Jackson	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
concerned	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
carrying	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
callicoe	O
bed-quilt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
with	O
a	O
pass	O
to	O
our	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
this	O
quilt	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
evening	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
hostler	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
quilt	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
quilt	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
let	O
my	O
master	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Moore	B-pers
the	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
quilt	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
into	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
quilt	O
and	O
torn	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
other	O
part	O
behind	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gates	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
direction	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
quilt	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
confederates	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
bringing	O
you	O
off	O
easier	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
confess	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
we	O
found	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
heel	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
shoe	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
's	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shoe	O
and	O
buckle	O
by	O
her	O
bed-side	O
without	O
a	O
heel	O
;	O
we	O
fitted	O
the	O
heel	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
compared	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
fellow	O
buckle	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
shoe	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
buckle	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
shoe	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
136	O
,	O
137	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Sullinge	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Row	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
33	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Balch	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Balch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-end	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
33	O
geese	O
in	O
a	O
shed	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
One	O
Abraham	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
inform	O
me	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
bought	O
these	O
geese	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
picked	O
out	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
's	O
house	O
;	O
Wilkinson	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
geese	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
great	O
dogs	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
dog	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
worked	O
there	O
.	O
Balch	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
up	O
,	O
Wilkinson	O
owned	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
geese	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
Sullinge	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
Sullinge	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
away	O
18	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
,	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Row	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
Wilkinson	O
opened	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
a	O
great	O
dog	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
out	O
his	O
stick	O
;	O
the	O
dog	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
33	O
geese	O
and	O
a	O
turkey	O
.	O
Sullinge	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wash	I-pers
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
led	O
me	O
into	O
this	O
bad	O
way	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
Sullinge	O
.	O
138	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Sullinge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
fish	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
brass	O
fish-pans	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
jelly-glasses	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Hugh	O
Lake	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
Levi	B-pers
the	O
Jew	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
mentioned	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wash	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
John	O
Row	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
brass	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
dog	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
drove	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Wash	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
this	O
wall	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
139	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
shagreen	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
metal	O
watch-chain	O
and	O
trinkets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
garnet	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
red	O
coloured	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
go	O
ld	O
,	O
one	O
chrystal	O
stone	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
breast-buckle	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
hose	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Denter	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Denter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Cable-street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
betwixt	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
lame	O
some	O
time	O
about	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
trust	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
key	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
drawers	O
for	O
money	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
or	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
look	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
my	O
affairs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
three	O
stone	O
rings	O
,	O
breast	O
buckle	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
known	O
my	O
loss	O
,	O
and	O
people	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
apprehend	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
pulling	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
;	O
then	O
upon	O
examining	O
further	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
keys	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
soon	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
my	O
keys	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
rather	O
sullen	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
three	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
breast-buckle	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stays	O
,	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
cotton	O
hose	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
send	O
her	O
with	O
any	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
those	O
places	O
?	O
M.	O
Denter	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
her	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
these	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
18	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
things	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Denter	O
use	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
M.	O
Denter	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
sent	O
ready	O
money	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
bought	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
girl	O
went	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
any	O
particular	O
place	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Penning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Denter	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
leading	O
her	O
home	O
drunk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
there	O
;	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
reading	O
the	O
prisoner	O
me	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
drawers	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Justice	O
Hodgson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
Morton	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
hang	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
only	O
transport	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
care	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Evan	I-pers
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
d.	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
insist	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
sending	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
two	O
disorderly	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
three	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
rings	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
lend	O
but	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
hat	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
7	O
d.	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
fell	O
a	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
character	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
disorderly	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
friends	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
140	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Solomon	B-pers
Benandine	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Aderley	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
paviour	O
's	O
labourer	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Aderley	I-pers
;	O
the	O
shovel	O
of	O
his	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
using	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
work	O
last	O
Friday	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
near	O
Shoemaker-row	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
some	O
pipes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
shovel	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Sculley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Moor-lane	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
;	O
last	O
Friday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
building	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
shovel	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
we	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
only	O
the	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
stopped	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
above	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
mark	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
owns	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
last	O
Friday	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
:	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
offered	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
shovel	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
.	O
Griffith	B-pers
Benbow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
with	O
Sculley	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
this	O
shovel	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
filled	O
up	O
with	O
mud	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
shovel	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
shovel	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
owner	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
quiet	O
as	O
a	O
lamb	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
141	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Loft	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Loft	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Mitre	I-place
,	I-place
Thames	I-place
street	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
three	O
weeks	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
my	O
boy	O
drawed	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
and	O
drank	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
mug	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Loft	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
his	O
uncle	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
and	O
write	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
his	O
uncle	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Loft	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l	O
was	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
necessitated	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rotchford	O
for	O
2	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
he	O
wrote	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Frank	B-pers
Rotchford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridges	O
street	O
,	O
Covent	O
garden	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
silver	O
mug	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
it	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
annuity	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lowing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Loft	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
uncle	O
brought	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
mug	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
down	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
Steel-yard	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
down	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
named	O
Cox	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
together	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
it	O
grew	O
late	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
a	O
favour	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cream	O
jug	O
and	O
some	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
pledge	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rotchford	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
uncle	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Loft	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
all	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
I	O
pawned	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
142	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Winefred	B-pers
Vanderplank	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Vanderplank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bartholomew-close	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cloth-worker	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
mentioned	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Justice	O
say	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
it	O
?	O
Vanderplank	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Vanderplank	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vigers	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
and	O
draper	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
dishonestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
during	O
the	O
discourse	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
prevaricated	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Justice	O
might	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
his	O
prevaricating	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
me	O
too	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
goods	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Justice	O
thought	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
at	O
farther	O
light	O
;	O
perhaps	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
other	O
people	O
concerned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
arguments	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Vigers	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
discover	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
?	O
Vigers	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
manufacturer	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
asking	O
a	O
price	O
considerably	O
under	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
he	O
allowed	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
more	O
;	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
my	O
judgement	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
discovered	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
manufacture	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
discourse	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
also	O
increased	O
my	O
suspicion	O
;	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Vanderplank	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
cloth	O
.	O
Vanderplank	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
waited	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
cloth	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
143	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
ax	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Jacob	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barrel	O
;	O
the	O
ax	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
working-shop	O
near	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Dough-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
after	O
it	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
borrowed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
laugh	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
losing	O
the	O
ax	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
me	O
cry	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
an	O
ax	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
Gifford	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
down	O
into	O
an	O
area	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
frame	O
that	O
Saturday	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
frosty	O
weather	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
frame	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
mother	O
lives	O
at	O
Wapping	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
his	O
tools	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
we	O
put	O
our	O
tools	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
at	O
the	O
Northumberland	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
going	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
worked	O
,	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
ax	O
lie	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
twice	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
heard	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
ax	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
thought	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
144	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
||	O
David	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
small	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Kingsland	B-place
road	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
circumstances	O
decline	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Saturday	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
baker	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
concluded	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
bread	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
baker	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
proper	O
place	O
to	O
lock	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
Saturday	O
night	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
baker	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
what	O
money	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
sunk	O
in	O
our	O
substance	O
daily	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
taking	O
and	O
being	O
accountable	O
for	O
the	O
bread	O
money	O
on	O
every	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
baker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
she	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
nail	O
and	O
pushed	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
my	O
husband	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
E.	O
Riddle	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
only	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
shift	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
shift	O
lay	O
there	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
apron	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Collins	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
sent	O
Collins	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Cox	O
's	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
also	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
here	O
?	O
E.	O
Riddle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
145	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gray	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Chitch	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Chitch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
with	O
two	O
horse	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
gray	O
gelding	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
brewhouse	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
servant	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Chitch	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
new	O
servant	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
horses	O
to	O
myself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
horse	O
and	O
cart	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
gray	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
without	O
the	O
gray	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Terry	O
's	O
at	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
gelding	O
13	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Chitch	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
this	O
;	O
gray	O
gelding	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
wants	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
good	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
does	O
he	O
stand	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cap	O
on	O
like	O
a	O
light	O
horseman	O
's	O
cap	O
with	O
the	O
word	O
Glory	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
serjeant	O
belonging	O
to	O
Elliot	O
's	O
fight	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
lame	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
rode	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
without	O
a	O
shoe	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
golding	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
earned	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
horse	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Tyburn-road	O
.	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
serjeant	O
lived	O
.	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
pay	O
the	O
serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
proper	O
receipt	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
stop	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
cried	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
him	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
found	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Shooter	O
's	O
hill	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brick-maker	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
horse	O
by	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
between	O
Tooley	O
street	O
and	O
the	O
gully-hole	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
harness	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
comes	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
charged	O
me	O
16	O
d.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
horse	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
Tyburn-road	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pirks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
E.	O
Pirks	O
.	O
He	O
drives	O
a	O
carman	O
's	O
cart	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spittle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
going	O
on	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
146	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Edmund	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Goswell-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
adjoining	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
window	O
break	O
very	O
loud	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
breeches	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
irons	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
did	O
not	O
order	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
them	O
on	O
him	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
flap	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dickerson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
17	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
William	O
Skeele	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
breeches	O
;	O
Skeele	O
pushed	O
out	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Martin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Dickerson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
waiting	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
not	O
above	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
then	O
as	O
Martin	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
wear	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
5	O
d	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Dickerson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Dickerson	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
breeches	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
Dickerson	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Dickerson	O
?	O
M.	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
till	O
within	O
this	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
in	O
Hartshorn	O
court	O
,	O
Golden	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
M.	O
Cox	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
18	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
pump-maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Dickerson	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allohy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
sober	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
147	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stock	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
woollen	O
cover-lid	O
,	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
one	O
feather	O
pillow	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
jacket	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
and	O
callimanco	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
plaid	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
baize	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Michel	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seaman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ship-keeper	O
to	O
the	B-place
ship	I-place
Neptune	I-place
,	I-place
lying	I-place
at	I-place
Mr.	I-place
Smith	I-place
's	I-place
wharf	I-place
below	I-place
the	I-place
Hermitage	I-place
;	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
board	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
shore	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
supper	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
shut	O
my	O
hatches	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
cabbin	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Dorrits	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Ratcliffe-highway	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
rug	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
Russia	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Stewart	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
who	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
Dorrit	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
the	O
goods	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
there	O
by	O
two	O
boys	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chesham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
jackets	O
or	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
148	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Berridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
;	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
that	O
evening	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Stanton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
away	O
after	O
she	O
told	O
you	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
stopped	O
?	O
M.	O
Stanton	O
.	O
She	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bruin	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
this	O
table-spoon	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
you	O
;	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
owner	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
spoon	O
was	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mussle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bruin	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
account	O
for	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
means	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stanton	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
prosecuting	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
helped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
discharged	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Stanton	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
liable	O
to	O
a	O
prosecution	O
for	O
a	O
false	O
imprisonment	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
brother-in-law	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
return	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
passed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
149	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bottom	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
evidence	O
Carney	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
pick	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
frail	O
of	O
raisins	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
directed	O
us	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
on	O
Salt-petrebank	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
either	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
gaming	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
Carney	O
also	O
described	O
a	O
bag	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
raisins	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
marked	O
as	O
he	O
described	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
hole	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jebb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
Carney	O
mentioned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Nash	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
also	O
found	O
this	O
bag	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
bed	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
,	O
with	O
small	O
holes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
evidence	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
these	O
holes	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Jebb	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
raisins	O
over	O
found	O
again	O
?	O
Jebb	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
next	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Salt-petre-bank	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
lodging-house	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
mother	O
alive	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Buckle-street	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
boys	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
thieving	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
o'clock	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
raisins	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
watchman	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
under	O
a	O
ladder	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
raisins	O
from	O
a	O
parcel	O
under	O
a	O
shed	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
archway	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
along	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
the	O
city	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
round	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
meet	O
the	O
watchmen	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
above	O
three	O
farthings	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
five	O
farthings	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
13	O
d.	O
Barney	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
boy	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Carney	O
)	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
one	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
they	O
awaked	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
plums	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
his	O
shoes	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
till	O
towards	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
handful	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
boy	O
(	O
meaning	O
Carney	O
)	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
almost	O
every	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
talk	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
most	O
handkerchiefs	O
by	O
picking	O
of	O
pockets	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
150	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hasker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
;	O
we	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Bull	I-place
and	I-place
Butcher	I-place
in	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
third	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
a	O
wet	O
shirt	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
maid	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
supper	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
man	O
are	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hosier-lane	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shirt	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
shirt	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
necessity	O
,	O
almost	O
starving	O
and	O
perishing	O
on	O
the	O
earth	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
within	O
six	O
weeks	O
of	O
66	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
opposite	O
the	O
church	O
at	O
Islington	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
151	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fearn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
shift-sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
dimity	O
stomachers	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Radgate	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Radgate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
in	O
Mark-lane	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
my	O
mistress	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
hearing	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
counting-house	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
wine	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
opened	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
table-cloths	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Stephen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
lay	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
that	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
search	O
I	O
still	O
search	O
things	O
mentioned	O
)	O
the	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
her	O
that	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
brought	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
shoes	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
walked	O
without	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
on	O
her	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
clean	O
;	O
had	O
she	O
came	O
without	O
shoes	O
,	O
her	O
feet	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
wet	O
and	O
dirty	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Alsop	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Radgate	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
shoes	O
found	O
?	O
M.	O
Radgate	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
children	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
fell	O
from	O
a	O
scaffold	O
in	O
Marybone	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
that	O
day	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
mistress	O
coming	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
crammed	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
.	O
Goodson	O
.	O
Her	O
excuse	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
boys	O
had	O
pinned	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
tied	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
string	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
letter	O
?	O
Goodson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
memorandum-book	O
,	O
with	O
nothing	O
wrote	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
both	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Radgate	I-pers
.	O
M.	O
Radgate	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
letter	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
sent	O
me	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Wellington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
trunk	O
locked	O
?	O
M.	O
Radgate	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
nurse-keeping	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
spin	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
152	O
,	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
widows	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
sattin	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stansbury	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
that	O
shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stansbury	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	B-place
Long	I-place
wall	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
cloisters	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
West	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
they	O
are	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
do	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
young	O
child	O
in	O
their	O
arm	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
now	O
;	O
)	O
they	O
both	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
a	O
little	O
larger	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
cloak	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
shewed	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
trimming	O
and	O
pattern	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
flowered	O
sattin	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
no	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
bid	O
me	O
money	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
asked	O
27	O
s.	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
agreeing	O
for	O
price	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
would	O
abate	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
would	O
leave	O
6	O
d	O
earnest	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
come	O
out	O
by	O
mistake	O
without	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
desired	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
partly	O
pulled	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
answered	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
on	O
their	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
one	O
cloak	O
fell	O
from	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
fall	O
which	O
fell	O
from	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Matthews	O
was	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
knees	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
ordered	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
cloaks	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
tickets	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
imagine	O
the	O
other	O
cloak	O
was	O
taken	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Stansbury	O
and	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
while	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
cloaks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
with	O
a	O
lady	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
a	O
cloak	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
say	O
something	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
their	O
knees	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
shake	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
cloak	O
drop	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
their	O
knees	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
squalling	O
out	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
hackney	O
coach	O
was	O
getting	O
ready	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
White	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
scarlet	O
cardinal	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
covered	O
her	O
child	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
cloaks	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
figured	O
cloak	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
servant	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
when	O
Matthews	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
White	O
had	O
left	O
6	O
d.	O
earnest	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
both	O
on	O
their	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
their	O
children	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Mercy	O
,	O
mercy	O
,	O
mercy	O
,	O
which	O
raised	O
the	O
whole	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
cloaks	O
lay	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
thing	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
before	O
there	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
shewed	O
the	O
cloaks	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
cloaks	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
mercy	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
children	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
2	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
154	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Bow-church	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
twitch	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
withdraw	O
his	O
hand	O
carelessly	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
fall	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
compleatly	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
155	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Rowls	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
brass	O
cranks	O
for	O
hanging	O
of	O
bells	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
,	O
brazier	O
,	O
and	O
smith	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
working	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
night	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
work	O
finished	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
when	O
wanted	O
)	O
cranks	O
for	O
hanging	O
of	O
bells	O
,	O
which	O
work	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
them	O
in	O
pieces	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
old	O
brass	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
hang	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
chose	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
impertinent	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
being	O
transported	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
cross	O
the	O
water	O
before	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
foreman	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
last	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
a	O
lock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Paterson	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
bell-hanger	O
,	O
lock-smith	O
,	O
and	O
jobbing-smith	O
;	O
seeing	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
drunk	O
,	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
down	O
,	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
new	O
brass	O
cranks	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
more	O
cut	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
new	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
third	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
gallows	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
choaked	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
surely	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
Harry	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mind	O
that	O
.	O
James	O
Grove	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
brass	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
of	O
cutting	O
these	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
defraud	O
your	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
frivolous	O
affair	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
perquisite	O
?	O
Grove	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
such	O
word	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
troubled	O
in	O
mind	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
156	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
jam	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Caruthers	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Caruthers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
;	O
yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
linen	O
and	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
at	O
the	B-place
Apple	I-place
Tree	I-place
in	I-place
Cursitor-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
dropped	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
bundle	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
wash	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
at	O
the	O
Romish	O
chapel	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
one	O
shirt	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cowley	O
's	O
,	O
facing	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
shirt	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
admitted	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
shirt	O
that	O
he	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
E.	O
Caruthers	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
shirts	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
a	O
plain	O
one	O
and	O
a	O
ruffled	O
one	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
ruffled	O
one	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
washed	O
it	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
John	I-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Knowland	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Margaret	O
Knowland	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
china	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
china	O
tea-pot	O
stand	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
china	O
coffee-cup	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
china	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
swanskin	O
flannel	O
for	O
a	O
cover	O
to	O
a	O
side-faddle	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
Anne	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Winefred-street	B-place
,	I-place
Marybone	I-place
parish	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
many	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
work	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
stocks	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
cloth	O
to	O
cover	O
a	O
saddle	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cogan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
milk-woman	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
china	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
china	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
rather	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
mistake	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
the	O
china	O
before	O
the	O
milk-woman	O
brought	O
the	O
pot	O
and	O
stand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cogan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
china	O
tea	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
china	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
M.	O
Cogan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
's	O
kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
her	O
fellow-servants	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
family	O
with	O
milk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
pot	O
?	O
M.	O
Cogan	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
Mrs.	O
Cogan	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
from	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
;	O
her	O
sister	O
wanted	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dorkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
my	O
mistress	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
very	O
ill	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
sister	O
wanted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Martin	O
's	O
that	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Cogan	O
,	O
we	O
call	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
christian	O
name	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
sister	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
by	O
the	O
cat	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
out	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
talked	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Dorkin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
158	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
under	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
Bolt	O
and	O
Tun	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
One	O
Sunday	O
night	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mutton-lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Saffron-hill	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chick-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
belly	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
ran	O
away	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
in	O
Chick	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
shoved	O
her	O
belly	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
pass	O
between	O
you	O
besides	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
talked	O
to	O
any	O
woman	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
gardens	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
named	O
Frances	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
watch	O
that	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
leg	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
25	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Louisa	B-pers
Ormond	I-pers
had	O
been	O
together	O
this	O
night	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
he	O
walked	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
distance	O
might	O
they	O
go	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Page	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
above	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
Dick	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
into	O
Black-boy-alley	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
mother-in-law	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
7	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Sunday	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicate	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
Page	O
at	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
her	O
mother	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
took	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
bushels	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
malster	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Walham-green	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Bear-key	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
malt	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
sacks	O
with	O
some	O
malt	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Major	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
sack	O
over	O
in	O
his	O
barge	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
right	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
malt	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Major	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
sell	O
corn	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
malt	O
that	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
malt	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
bargain	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
to	O
surprize	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
malt	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
neighbours	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
of	O
them	O
privately	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
some	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
while	O
I	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
malt	O
;	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
J.	O
Higley	O
at	O
length	O
on	O
the	O
sack	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Higley	O
's	O
sack	O
,	O
of	O
Walham-green	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Higley	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
malt	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Higley	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Covent-garden	O
Round-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Higley	O
's	O
sack	O
and	O
malt	O
;	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
sweepings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
servant	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sack	O
over	O
tale	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
understood	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
thus	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
servant	O
lost	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
make	O
it	O
good	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
sack	O
over	O
and	O
above	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
their	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sweepings	O
that	O
I	O
swept	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
barge	O
,	O
time	O
after	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saved	O
it	O
till	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
almost	O
a	O
sack	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
save	O
it	O
than	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
frighted	O
when	O
they	O
talked	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
160	O
,	O
161	O
,	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sideaway	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
diaper	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
one	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
girl	O
's	O
pumps	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
with	O
a	O
whalebone	O
handle	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Sideaway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Barking	I-place
Dogs	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
fortnight	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
near	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
Joseph	B-pers
Trussel	I-pers
came	O
early	O
to	O
brew	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
one	O
story	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
shutters	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
rush-light	O
that	O
was	O
burning	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
several	O
things	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
till	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
with	O
about	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
farthings	O
and	O
two	O
pocket-books	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
diaper	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
girl	O
's	O
new	O
pumps	O
,	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
a	O
cannister	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
case	O
of	O
lump	O
sugar	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
with	O
a	O
whalebone	O
handle	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
groove	O
of	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
you	O
left	O
your	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to-bed	O
?	O
Sideaway	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
maid	O
up	O
alone	O
;	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
was	O
then	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
they	O
fasten	O
?	O
Sideaway	O
.	O
They	O
slide	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
within	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
maid	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
very	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
she	O
goes	O
by	O
my	O
chamber-door	O
to	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
evidence	O
Norbury	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
that	O
accompanied	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
)	O
and	O
locked	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
