TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
23rd	O
,	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
SIR	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
MANSFIELD	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	O
STAFFORD	O
SMYTHE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lambell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
Jabez	B-pers
Bloxham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bumfryes	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Norrill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Standert	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Job	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Green	O
,	O
Rich	B-pers
Longbottom	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Blackgr	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lungley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bane	I-pers
.	O
517	O
,	O
518	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Nowls	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Still	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
fathom	O
of	O
hempen	O
rope	O
,	O
called	O
cable	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Eade	I-pers
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
and	O
lighterman	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
powder	O
vessel	O
;	O
yesterday	O
three	O
weeks	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
vessel	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
fast	O
at	O
Wapping-dock	B-place
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
the	O
rope	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
fathom	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
King	O
James's-stairs	O
with	O
some	O
rope	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
several	O
other	O
ropes	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
vessel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mess	O
.	O
Wilton	O
and	O
Eade	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
;	O
betwixt	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
nightly	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
come	O
rowing	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
several	O
ropes	O
;	O
Nowls	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
tools	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
oar-maker	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
both	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
saw	O
the	O
rope	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
rope	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Johnson	O
;	O
)	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
knife	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
hawser	O
from	O
the	O
vessel	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
Bean	O
.	O
Nowls	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
stole	O
any	O
rope	O
.	O
Still	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
river-side	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ropes	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
519	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Stephen	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gangsman	O
on	O
Ralph's-key	O
;	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
two	O
pockets	O
full	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
weighted	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hogshead	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
head	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prestage	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
sugar	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
weighed	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cooper	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
being	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
some	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hogshead	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
520	O
,	O
521	O
,	O
522	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Laroach	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
sheet	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Laroach	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chambers	B-place
's	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
;	O
I	O
lett	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
;	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
lodging	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
blankets	O
and	O
two	O
sheets	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
Bracket	O
,	O
and	O
Manning	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
sold	O
a	O
sheet	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Scott	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
then	O
Bracket	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Manning	O
the	O
younger	O
had	O
assisted	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
she	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
lodger	O
;	O
Bracket	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
wound	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
sheets	O
round	O
Manning	O
's	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
dark	O
passage	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
Bracket	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
two	O
blankets	O
in	O
Bracket	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
(	O
one	O
sheet	O
and	O
two	O
blankets	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
Manning	O
the	O
mother	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
Manning	O
the	O
younger	O
pledged	O
the	O
two	O
blankets	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
Bracket	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
intoxicated	O
me	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Manning	O
the	O
mother	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Bracket	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
daughter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
against	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
sheet	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Miller	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
18	O
d.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
daughter	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Bracket	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Bracket	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Manning	O
the	O
mother	O
Acq	O
.	O
Manning	O
the	O
daughter	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
523	O
,	O
524	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Bitters	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
five	O
silk	O
hats	O
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
chip	O
hat	O
,	O
two	O
sattin	O
bonnets	O
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
twenty-three	O
pieces	O
of	O
blond-lace	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
ribband	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
three	O
ruffles	O
,	O
four	O
blond-lace	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
twenty-six	O
china	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
two	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
two	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
china	O
punch	O
bowl	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
blond-lace	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
sarcenet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
36	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
At	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
millener	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Mile	O
end	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
house	O
fast	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
immediately	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
had	O
a	O
pane	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
back-door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
attend	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
Harvey	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
mentioning	O
stealing	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
J.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rightly	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
four	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Bitters	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
was	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
who	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
J.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
one	O
Friday	O
night	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mile-end	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
twelve	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Bitters	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
Harvey	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
Bitters	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
wash-house	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
;	O
how	O
they	O
opened	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
brought	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
they	O
brought	O
out	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
hats	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
laces	O
,	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
cloak	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
china	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
and	O
a	O
punch	O
bowl	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
four	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Abraham	B-pers
Teracona	I-pers
;	O
I	O
carried	O
all	O
the	O
china	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
there	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
Teracona	O
took	O
the	O
china	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
left	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
S.	O
Carr	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
;	O
Bitters	O
asked	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
Harvey	O
said	O
take	O
them	O
at	O
two	O
;	O
then	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
for	O
Harvey	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Bitters	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
a	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
S.	O
Carr	O
.	O
Harvey	O
is	O
a	O
painter	O
,	O
and	O
Bitters	O
is	O
a	O
glazier	O
and	O
painter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
them	O
?	O
S.	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
S.	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
wind	O
silk	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
lives	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Teracona	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Abraham	O
*	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Northumberland-alley	O
,	O
Crutched-friars	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
hat-box	O
,	O
containing	O
six	O
hats	O
,	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
two	O
bonnets	O
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
several	O
white	O
aprons	O
,	O
four	O
gauze	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
ruffles	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
ruffles	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
them	O
came	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
china	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
china	O
bowl	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
bought	O
things	O
of	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
lion	O
's	O
mouth	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
more	O
harm	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
Bitters	O
asked	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
Harvey	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Bitters	I-pers
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
Carr	O
a	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
more	O
things	O
last	O
Saturday	O
five	O
weeks	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
they	O
broke	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
stir	O
and	O
disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
conscience	O
began	O
to	O
prick	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Bitters	O
secured	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
up	O
as	O
many	O
goods	O
as	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
eleven	O
robberies	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Tinsey	O
,	O
Gibson	O
,	O
and	O
Mackaway	O
,	O
No	O
407	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
they	O
got	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
M.	O
Teracona	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brebrook	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
sessions	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Hickes's-hall	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
;	O
there	O
this	O
last	O
evidence	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
locked	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
seven	O
robberies	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Bitters	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Northumberland	O
alley	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
produced	O
divers	O
goods	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
caps	O
,	O
ruffles	O
,	O
blond-lace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
parcel	O
of	O
millenery	O
goods	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
china	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
here	O
in	O
writing	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
hammer	O
,	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
a	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
)	O
these	O
Sarah	B-pers
Teracona	I-pers
told	O
me	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
tools	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
worked	O
with	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Teracona	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
these	O
tools	O
?	O
S.	O
Teracona	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Bitters	O
say	O
he	O
used	O
these	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
houses	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
once	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Harvey	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
now	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
leave	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
they	O
committed	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
things	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Dominick	B-pers
Rewer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
parish	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
watch	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
information	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
th	O
at	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
taking	O
Harvey	O
and	O
Bitters	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
watchmen	O
and	O
searched	O
many	O
bad	O
houses	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
watchmen	O
brought	O
Harvey	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
secured	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
committed	O
Harvey	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
Sir	O
John	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
Carr	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
farther	O
discovery	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
her	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
a	O
tub	O
,	O
a	O
pail	O
,	O
a	O
pan	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
tubs	O
were	O
seventeen	O
clouts	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
carpet	O
;	O
Carr	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
many	O
robberies	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
owned	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
back	O
to	O
their	O
owners	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
for	O
burglaries	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
525	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Tape	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rumbolt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Grange-inn	O
,	O
Carey-street	O
;	O
he	O
pledg	O
'd	O
this	O
coat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
526	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
mortar	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
purl	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
brass	O
mortar	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
setting	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
brass	O
mortar	O
from	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
brass	O
or	O
iron	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
527	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Leith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
also	O
missing	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
our	O
ship	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
knocked	O
to	O
pieces	O
and	O
melted	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
brass	O
chapes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Stranger	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
bad	O
woman	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
from	O
on	O
,	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
magistrates	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
No	O
2.	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
duplicate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
;	O
the	O
silversmith	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
melted	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
was	O
called	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
528	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
live	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willan	I-pers
.	O
*	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
live	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
practice	O
to	O
get	O
farmers	O
hogs	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
grounds	O
,	O
and	O
pound	O
them	O
;	O
Dawson	B-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
16	O
s.	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
two	O
again	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
a	O
trespass	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
529	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bowl	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Lambert	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
boys	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
some	O
neighbours	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
Bagnell	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bagnell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
fifteen	O
years	O
old	O
last	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
White	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
and	O
Tomlin	O
was	O
standing	O
three	O
doors	O
off	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
of	O
White	O
and	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
?	O
Bagnell	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
Bagnell	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
530	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Huntley	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Huntley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Black	I-place
Dog	I-place
,	I-place
Gray's-inn-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
things	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
saucepan	O
to	O
dress	O
some	O
muscles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
dress	O
them	O
yourself	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
shall	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
dressed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
then	O
moved	O
from	O
that	O
box	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
then	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
under	O
her	O
capuchin	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
saucepan	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
left	O
side	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
pint	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pots	O
of	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Brooksby	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
their	O
seeing	O
the	O
saucepan	O
and	O
pot	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
struggling	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
stealing	O
pots	O
.	O
531	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Amcote	I-pers
,	O
September	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Amcote	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
from	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
Somerset-house	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
guard	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
guard-house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
serjeant	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
he	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
coat	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
532	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Tabble	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
58	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
butter	O
firkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
is	O
a	O
book-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lad	O
carry	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
butter	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
certainly	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
worked	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
rescued	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
loose	O
man	O
,	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
had	O
detained	O
the	O
butter	O
while	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
round	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
tub	O
and	O
see	O
who	O
will	O
hinder	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
push	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
empty	O
tub	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
;	O
this	O
tub	O
with	O
butter	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
his	O
care	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
answerable	O
if	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
mark	O
well	O
,	O
W.	O
M.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
tub	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
put	O
my	O
butter	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
says	O
he	O
works	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
stop	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
butter	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
's	O
labourer	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
533	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stobey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pounds	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
cut	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Liske	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Laiden	I-pers
,	O
September	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Liske	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Laiden	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
on	O
Snow-hill	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
us	O
in	O
stripping	O
tobacco	O
;	O
our	O
general	O
rule	O
is	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
them	O
in	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
tobacco	O
found	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
dropt	O
off	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pocket	O
in	O
it	O
full	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
petticoat	O
and	O
tobacco	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
pocket	O
made	O
near	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
tobacco	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
heap	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
doing	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
think	O
of	O
dropping	O
down	O
dead	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
my	O
poverty	O
should	O
be	O
known	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
get	O
pieces	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
that	O
pocket	O
;	O
how	O
the	O
tobacco	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
534	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Corke	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jasper	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
19	O
++	O
Jasper	O
Holmes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Corke	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
loaded	O
our	O
cart	O
with	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
were	O
three	O
tubs	O
of	O
Irish	O
butter	O
as	O
a	O
fence	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
cart	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Ivy-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
lean	O
over	O
the	O
tubs	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
cheese	O
and	O
rest	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
butter	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
and	O
jump	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
time	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
near	O
Gray-friars-gateway	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
carman	O
bid	O
him	O
get	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
or	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
535	O
,	O
536	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
September	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Billingsgate-market	B-place
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pickpockets	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
public-house	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
;	O
upon	O
hearing	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
for	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
mine	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
tied	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
form	O
at	O
Billingsgate-market	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
form	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
stood	O
and	O
jostled	O
Mr.	O
Simonds	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rogue	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
nothing	O
out	O
.	O
Justinian	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
gill	O
of	O
wine	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
together	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
them	O
,	O
Brian	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
about	O
ten	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Brian	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
having	O
no	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
West-India	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
then	O
that	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
gentleman	O
lost	O
nothing	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
rule	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
Sept.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
wipe	O
my	O
hands	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
feel	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
rule	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
secured	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
George-alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
taken	O
from	O
Brian	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
rule	O
also	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Clark	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
rule	O
found	O
on	O
Brian	O
.	O
Brian	O
's	O
defence	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
than	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Brian	B-pers
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Clark	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
537	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Edie	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Edie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Smith	B-place
's	I-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
Bridgewater's-gardens	I-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
ready	O
furnished	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
eight	O
weeks	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
sheets	O
from	O
his	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
get	O
any	O
rent	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
sheets	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Dandy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
sheets	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
15th	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
goods	O
of	O
theirs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
sheets	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
should	O
never	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
his	O
daughter	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
branded	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
No	O
187	O
,	O
188	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Nelson	O
.	O
538	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
damask	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ebenezer-square	B-place
,	I-place
Houndsditch	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Jew	O
schoolmaster	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
maid	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cobb's-yard	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
as	O
she	O
called	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
she	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Alefounder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
sheet	O
and	O
shirt	O
;	O
)	O
one	O
was	O
pawned	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
but	O
who	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
called	O
herself	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
the	O
12th	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
in	O
Hebrew	O
letters	O
upon	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Basden	I-pers
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
promised	O
not	O
to	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
prison	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
her	O
such	O
promise	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Martha	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Lowrey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
539	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Courtney	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Courtney	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Holbourn	B-place
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
down	O
an	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
my	O
stick	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lovelock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
the	O
gentleman	O
swang	O
his	O
stick	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
which	O
drawed	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
brick-fields	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
muffins	O
in	O
the	O
winter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
540	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norwington	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Norwington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
George	O
Tilt-boat	O
of	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lancaster	O
's	O
,	O
the	B-place
Queen	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
Darkhouse	I-place
lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
to	O
come	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
my	O
clothes	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
pillow	O
and	O
bolster	O
,	O
with	O
money	O
in	O
both	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
disturbed	O
by	O
the	O
drawing	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
wakeful	O
enough	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wheeler	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
lay	O
between	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
my	O
bed's-head	O
,	O
quite	O
visible	O
;	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wheeler	O
took	O
the	O
light	O
and	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
watch	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Norwington	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
my	O
hand	O
happened	O
to	O
lie	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
upon	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
hey	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
Norwington	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
more	O
than	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
called	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
jumpt	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
have	O
him	O
here	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stuck	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
here	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Norwington	O
said	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
the	O
man	O
here	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
left-side	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
for	O
himself	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Small	I-pers
.	O
When	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
from	O
shifting	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
thigh	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
apple	O
or	O
turnip	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Wheeler	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shirt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seaman	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
rummaged	O
that	O
room	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
bed	O
never	O
touched	O
nor	O
tumbled	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
candle	O
burning	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
socket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
541	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Elard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
four	O
gold	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
watches	O
with	O
metal	O
and	O
fish	O
skin	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
watches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Territt	I-pers
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
cast	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
+	O
See	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Territt	O
,	O
No	O
498	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
and	O
conviction	O
of	O
Territt	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
;	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
robber	O
was	O
discovered	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
a	O
letter	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
six	O
of	O
these	O
watches	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
Territt	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
redeemed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
raise	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
took	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
man	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
employed	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
advertised	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
apprehending	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
early	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Snow's-fields	O
,	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
him	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
off	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
then	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
watches	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
quietly	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
name	O
Scott	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
watches	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
go	O
away	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
assault.	O
?	O
Scott	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
1767	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
Territt	O
,	O
named	O
Anthony	B-pers
Praty	I-pers
,	O
1602	O
;	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Hallam	I-pers
,	O
No	O
5003	O
;	O
one	O
silver	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Toulmin	I-pers
,	O
London	O
;	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Threlkill	I-pers
,	O
London	O
,	O
No	O
2685	O
:	O
one	O
Lory	O
Paris	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hornaby	I-pers
,	O
all	O
pawned	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Territt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
sessions	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
redeemed	O
the	O
several	O
watches	O
mentioned	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
April	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Territt	I-pers
,	O
as	O
represented	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Scott	O
.	O
Only	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
thirty-one	O
watches	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Territt	O
last	O
sessions	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
names	O
and	O
numbers	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
filed	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
certainty	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Toulmin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Lory	O
Paris	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
them	O
two	O
,	O
as	O
positive	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
can	O
well	O
do	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Scott	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-shop	O
in	O
Red-lion-market	O
,	O
Whitecross-street	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Smith	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
you	O
paid	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
part	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
note	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
26	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
paid	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
saving	O
the	O
6	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
Territt	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
watches	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
writ	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
just	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
19	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
want	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
them	O
out	O
directly	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
was	O
going	O
abroad	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
these	O
six	O
watches	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
Mr.	O
Territt	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
22	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
19	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
trust	O
me	O
the	O
rest	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
watches	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Territt	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
your	O
shop	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watches	O
above	O
a	O
month	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
handbills	O
,	O
describing	O
them	O
almost	O
all	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Smith	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
all	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
these	O
watches	O
tallied	O
with	O
the	O
papers	O
.	O
Scott	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Territt	O
here	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
right	O
names	O
and	O
numbers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
put	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
in	O
Whitecross	O
street	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Stockdon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
in	O
Red-lion-market	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
542	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shatlock	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Shatlock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
vinter	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
vault	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
drummer	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
,	O
quartered	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
things	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
on	O
Friday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Convent-garden	O
Round-house	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
about	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
hear	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
lace	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
and	O
pawning	O
some	O
shirts	O
near	O
Horseshoe-alley	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
in	O
Stretton's-ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
promise	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
?	O
Shatlock	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
easy	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Setker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
last	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
confessed	O
to	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
his	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
543	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
inch-deal	O
board	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
fourteen	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
deal	O
boards	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
bushels	O
of	O
live	O
hair	O
,	O
four	O
hods	O
of	O
lime	O
and	O
mortar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
laths	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
544	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Eyloe	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
weight	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
flour	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
weight	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Eyloe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Orchard-house	B-place
,	I-place
Blackwall	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
East-India	O
company	O
send	O
their	O
people	O
to	O
board	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Lascar	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
three	O
,	O
four	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
pounds	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
two	O
nights	O
following	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
cellar-window	O
broke	O
open	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
veal	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
cellar	O
door	O
made	O
;	O
he	O
ripped	O
the	O
hinges	O
from	O
the	O
posts	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
wine	O
cellar	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
iron	O
bar	O
off	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
hen-roost	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
eight	O
hens	O
and	O
a	O
cock	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
suppose	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
adry	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
beer	O
,	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
brandy	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
house	O
and	O
cellar	O
made	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Eyloe	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
ten	O
bottles	O
of	O
brandy	O
to	O
;	O
that	O
man	O
sent	O
word	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
hearing	O
about	O
the	O
brandy	O
;	O
ordered	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
summer-house	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
countrymen	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
was	O
cut	O
:	O
the	O
countrymen	O
of	O
his	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
prevented	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
my	O
kitchen	O
window	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
hatchet	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Lascar	O
from	O
Bengal	O
,	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
East-India	O
company	O
;	O
they	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
board	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
white	O
men	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
545	O
,	O
546	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lucy	B-pers
May	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
clouts	O
,	O
the	O
propetty	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Parish	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
suspicion	O
of	O
loosing	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
charged	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Lucy	B-pers
May	I-pers
;	O
after	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
things	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Parish	O
pledged	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
linen	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
547	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gillfoot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
and	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
bonnet	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
bonnet	O
about	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
keep	O
your	O
things	O
,	O
here	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
this	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
up	O
within	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
mamma	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
548	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
teaspoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mattam	I-pers
,	O
September	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mattam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mattam	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
named	O
Whiteman	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
many	O
years	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
twenty	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
549	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
forty-two	O
worsted	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
some	O
breeches	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
wrapper	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
on	O
a	O
certain	O
wharf	O
,	O
adjacent	O
to	O
a	O
navigable	O
river	O
,	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
October	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
voice	O
of	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
goods	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
with	O
people	O
round-him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
twopence	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
lay	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
entered	O
in	O
Captain	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
's	O
cargo	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
America	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
no	O
proper	O
place	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ricketts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
busy	O
upon	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
up	O
this	O
truss	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
sharp	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
run	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
softly	O
;	O
I	O
hallooed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
produce	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
bale	O
of	O
goods	O
?	O
Ricketts	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
such	O
words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Ricketts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
bale	O
of	O
hosiery	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
-	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
on	O
that	O
wharf	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
bale	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
hallooed	O
out	O
for	O
one	O
Tom	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Tom	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
two	O
pence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
got	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
stopt	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
goods	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Thomas	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
550	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
of	O
striped	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parminter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parminter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Sleigh	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
551.	O
John	B-pers
Coke	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Papley	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
552	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Fanten	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Troot	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Troot	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
aprons	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nursed	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
that	O
was	O
ill	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Elizabeth	O
Troot	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nursed	O
my	O
wife	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
two	O
children	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
black	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
shifts	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
directed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Debulk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
husband	O
gets	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
lay	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
for	O
her	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
a	O
shillings	O
each	O
;	O
she	O
sold	O
a	O
black	O
one	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
two-pence	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
for	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cardinal	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
cheated	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
farthing	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Troot	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lamb-alley	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
in	O
Lamb-alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
aprons	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	O
Debulk	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
carried	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
broke	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
that	O
good	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Debulk	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
553	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	O
Hudson	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
some	O
thing	O
move	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
turning	O
round	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
boy	O
did	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
standing	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
little	O
rogue	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
dare	O
you	O
pick	O
my	O
picket	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
nothing	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
other	O
pocket	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
daytime	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
concourse	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
554	O
,	O
555	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baldock	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Baldock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Nettleton-court	O
,	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cobler's-stall	O
in	O
Bell	B-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
my	O
stall	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
secure	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
partly	O
stripped	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
thirteen	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
odd	O
ones	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
going	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
I	O
imagined	O
the	O
thief	O
might	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
asking	O
Martin	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
old	O
shoe-shop	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
shoes	O
offered	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
nine	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
people	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
mother	O
and	O
son	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
woman	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
odd	O
ones	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
eighteen-pence	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
seven	O
pair	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
five	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
some	O
stall	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
Ham	O
common	O
from	O
his	O
aunt	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
up	O
left-off	O
shoes	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
leave	O
the	O
shoes	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
shoes	O
your	O
son	O
has	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
up	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
Bridgeman	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
nineteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Baldock	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
mend	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
these	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
they	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
six-pence	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bridgeman	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
his	O
father	O
lives	O
in	O
Monkwell-street	O
.	O
To	O
their	O
characters	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bunney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Nettleton-court	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Elizabeth	O
Brown	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
son	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
wore	O
petticoats	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
heard	O
any	O
complaint	O
of	O
the	O
son	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
556	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Belchier	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
William	O
Belchier	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
to	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Birchin-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
into	O
Three	O
King-court	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
that	O
is	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
shall	O
catch	O
you	O
(	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
,	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
push	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
Lombard	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
lathering	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
take	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
that	O
will	O
acquit	O
you	O
without	O
lathering	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
drop	O
those	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
but	O
this	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
poor	O
mother	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
abroad	O
she	O
will	O
perish	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
children	O
besides	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
fist	O
tobacco	O
at	O
the	O
Highlander	O
,	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
557	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Letter	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Lucy	B-pers
Letter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little-Britain	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
drawers	O
left	O
locked	O
or	O
open	O
?	O
L.	O
Letter	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
door	O
when	O
you	O
returned	O
?	O
L	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
left	O
as	O
usual	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
often	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
L.	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
my	O
gown	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Broker's-row	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
me	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
damage	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
demand	O
?	O
L.	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
valued	O
my	O
gown	O
at	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
?	O
L.	O
Letter	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
L.	O
Letter	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
gown	O
for	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Cain	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
apron	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Angus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
bind	O
shoes	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
at	O
Holbourn-bridge	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
three	O
shirts	O
to	O
repair	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
upper-leathers	O
to	O
bind	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
gown	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lose	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
what	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
delivered	O
the	O
gown	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Angus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Angus	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
worn	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
seen	O
after	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
till	O
Mrs.	O
Cain	O
's	O
daughter	O
came	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cain	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Cain	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
this	O
gown	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
one	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
your	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
,	O
in	O
Salisbury-court	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
morsel	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
to-morrow	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
;	O
my	O
maid	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
colour	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
price	O
was	O
16	O
s.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
dispute	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
bring	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
gown	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
sell	O
your	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Letter	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
quitted	O
my	O
lodging	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
owed	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
558	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Love	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
some	O
for	O
other	O
the	O
day	O
day	O
week	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
between	O
Ramonton	B-place
and	O
Tottenham	B-place
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
for	O
the	O
cysters	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
about	O
my	O
arms	O
and	O
shoulders	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
all	O
about	O
my	O
petticoat	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
even	O
to	O
my	O
private	O
parts	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
clothes	O
were	O
so	O
tumbled	O
about	O
with	O
struggling	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
wound	O
on	O
my	O
eye	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
)	O
this	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
With	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
weapon	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
coming	O
with	O
a	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
many	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
used	O
you	O
thus	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
call	O
you	O
by	O
your	O
name	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
surgeon	O
's	O
and	O
got	O
my	O
wounds	O
dressed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
family	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
five	O
children	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
with	O
my	O
oysters	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
thought	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
that	O
public-house	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
when	O
he	O
attacked	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sober	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
such	O
an	O
attempt	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
He	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
perceived	O
the	O
light	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
might	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
A.	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
twenty	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
;	O
last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
bloody	O
and	O
dirty	O
condition	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
wash	O
her	O
face	O
well	O
with	O
a	O
sponge	O
and	O
warm	O
water	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
discover	O
her	O
wounds	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
wound	O
over	O
her	O
left	O
eye	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sewed	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
dressed	O
her	O
wounds	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
happened	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
attended	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
bruised	O
and	O
hurt	O
so	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
hardly	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
should	O
then	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
the	O
seven	O
years	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
journeyman	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
behaved	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
?	O
Stanley	O
.	O
He	O
may	O
have	O
got	O
fuddled	O
and	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
that	O
afternoon	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
hurt	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stanley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
rob	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
but	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
sober	O
till	O
lately	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
559	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dowe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Martha	B-pers
Scrivener	I-pers
.	O
