TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Turvey	I-pers
,	O
Abrah	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Benj	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Glanville	I-pers
,	O
Randol	B-pers
Somfield	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Segrist	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Dormor	B-pers
Heiford	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Mark	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Temple-bar	O
;	O
when	O
very	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
started	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
behind	O
a	O
carriage	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
crowding	O
it	O
up	O
under	O
the	O
knee	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Temple-lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pursued	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
were	O
soon	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Temple-lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pursued	O
by	O
many	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
he	O
was	O
seized	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
held	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
another	O
boy	O
picked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
more	O
boys	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
lie	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
mine	O
as	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Green	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Muller	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Muller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Rood-lane	B-place
in	I-place
Fenchurch-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
take	O
something	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
keeps	O
a	O
peter-boat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
rope-ground	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
time	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
stoop	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
passing	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
seeing	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bridget	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
eighteen	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Drout	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linger	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Drout	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seaman	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Montreal	O
frigate	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
York	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
India-house	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
girl	O
singing	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Star	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
ship-mates	O
there	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
slip	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
an	O
oyster	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
oysters	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
18	O
d.	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
Nanny	O
King	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
by	O
the	O
bed-side	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
herself	O
a	O
spring	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Drout	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
shutter	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
light	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
a	O
piece	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
eighteen	O
shilling	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
nor	O
money	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Drout	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
house	O
her	O
room	O
is	O
in	O
?	O
Drout	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Linger	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Drout	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
face	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
reckoning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Star	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
sausages	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
that	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
two	O
girls	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
drank	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
six-pence	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
for	O
so	O
little	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
some	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
her	O
husband	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
down	O
without	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
and	O
pinched	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
every	O
body	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
102	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
see	O
her	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Wall	O
,	O
No	O
411	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waddington	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
October	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Waddington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bear-street	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
that	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
in	O
our	O
parish	O
:	O
he	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
his	O
way	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chandois-street	O
,	O
by	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
twelve	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
wound	O
my	O
watch	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
mend	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
late	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
walked	O
about	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
house	O
open	O
in	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Red	I-place
Lion	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
three	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
one	O
side	O
a	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
quite	O
opposite	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
besides	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
with	O
my	O
head	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
slept	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
dial	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
awake	O
about	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
about	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
left	O
word	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
might	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Couch	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
)	O
Couch	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
water-tub	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
where	O
I	O
slept	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Couch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
post-boy	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
according	O
to	O
agreement	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
liked	O
it	O
after	O
a	O
month	O
's	O
trial	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
awaked	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
stir	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
lose	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
was	O
as	O
full	O
as	O
it	O
could	O
hold	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
all	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
me	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
left	O
word	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
water	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tub	O
to	O
wash	O
my	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
hang	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
tub	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
steel	O
hook	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
advertised	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Arnold	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
blocks	O
with	O
brass	O
pulleys	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
and	O
Geo	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
are	O
builders	O
and	O
partners	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
,	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Lord	O
Hertford	O
's	O
in	O
Grosvenor-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
two	O
blocks	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
work	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
use	O
there	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
blocks	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
blocks	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
iron	O
at	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
brass	O
at	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
constable	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
fellow	O
block	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
promise	O
him	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
said	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
Lord	O
Hertford	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
.	O
The	O
blocks	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
to	O
do	O
Lord	O
Hertford	O
's	O
business	O
;	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
hay	O
lost	O
on	O
nights	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
James	B-pers
Hamockson	I-pers
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
four	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lascow	I-pers
one	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Hall	O
two	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bess	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cheeses	O
,	O
the	O
weight	O
84	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Watson	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Leather-lane	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
maid	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
a	O
little	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taking	O
three	O
cheeses	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
calling	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
past	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
,	O
a	O
double	O
Glaucester	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
single	O
Gloucester	O
cheese	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
cheese	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Eastly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
for	O
small	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
these	O
cheeses	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
his	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
called	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
cheeses	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
went	O
off	O
immediately	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Gahagan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
leaden	O
shifters	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
Earl	O
of	O
Hertford	O
,	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
were	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
hay	O
loft	O
at	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Hertford	O
's	O
in	O
Grosvenor-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
hod	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
bricklayers	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
cover	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
three	O
times	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
three	O
leaden	O
shifters	O
,	O
(	O
three	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
these	O
;	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
where	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
bricks	O
and	O
mortar	O
for	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
scaffold	O
for	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
weights	O
among	O
the	O
rubbish	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
lumber	O
was	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Pardue	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Pillson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
left	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
October	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
baize	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
October	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
and	O
hosier	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
street	I-place
;	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Walsum	I-pers
(	O
an	O
accomplice	O
)	O
a	O
lad	O
of	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Turvey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
near	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
turned	O
round	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
something	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
confusion	O
I	O
dropt	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
Darkhouse-lane	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
just	O
now	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
saw	O
four	O
boys	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
towards	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
opposite	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
before	O
ever	O
I	O
accused	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
against	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
up	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
their	O
arms	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
rather	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
three	O
parts	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
not	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Lorimer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Summerfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
officer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lighter	O
of	O
sugar	O
lay	O
at	O
Fresh-wharf	B-place
;	O
a	O
brother	O
officer	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
body	O
had	O
robbed	O
it	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
that	O
lighter	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
went	O
;	O
the	O
lighter	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
lighter	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
three	O
bags	O
of	O
sugar	O
into	O
a	O
boat	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
consulted	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
ship	O
's	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
lighter-man	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
lighter	O
has	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
had	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
consulted	O
whether	O
we	O
should	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
vessel	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
about	O
100	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
three	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
large	O
handkerchiefs	O
full	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
sugar	O
that	O
is	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Towse	I-pers
was	O
with	O
the	O
witness	O
Summerfield	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
more	O
tarpauling	O
to	O
cover	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
captain	O
of	O
the	O
Trent	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
the	O
lighter	O
was	O
loaded	O
from	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
lighter	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
voyages	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
this	O
lighter	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
at	O
Bottle-wharf	O
;	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
we	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
watchman	O
came	O
down	O
afterwards	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
alehouse	O
with	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
better	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
,	O
went	O
all	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
vessel	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
carried	O
up	O
to	O
Fresh-wharf	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Anchor	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
near	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
halfpenny-worth	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
gate-way	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
went	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
left-hand	O
side	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
her	O
arm	O
round	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
saw	O
some	O
sugar	O
spilt	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
under	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
trowsers	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Anchor	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodhouse	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
were	O
with	O
some	O
sugar	O
under	O
a	O
gate	O
way	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Anchor	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hogshead	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
rope	O
ladder	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
Newman	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
five	O
minutes	O
when	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Skelton	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
groat	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Newman	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
sugar	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
clothes	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
;	O
this	O
day	O
week	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
above	O
3	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
her	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
be	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
counter	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Banes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
shop-door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
under	O
her	O
cardinal	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
witness	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
gave	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
20	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lockhead	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Lockhead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
opposite	O
Surry-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
Myers	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
a	O
messenger	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
and	O
Magpie	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
stopped	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pot	O
which	O
had	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
kettle	O
and	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Goodwin	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Lockhead	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Debote	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
and	O
Magpie	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drawed	O
down	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
pots	O
away	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dun	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
also	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
and	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lockhead	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
and	O
Magpie	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
a	O
pint	O
dropped	O
from	O
Goodwin	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
name	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Robert	B-pers
Lockhead	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
something	O
bulge	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
something	O
else	O
here	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
handle	O
.	O
Myers	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
mug	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
rent	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
and	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Myers	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
kettle	O
mended	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Myers	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Danborough	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
soup-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
butter-ladle	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	B-pers
company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Key	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
company	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
there	O
was	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tureen	O
ladle	O
,	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
butter-ladle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
tureen	O
ladle	O
?	O
Key	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
to	O
ladle	O
the	O
soup	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tureen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
that	O
last	O
?	O
Key	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
out	O
somewhere	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
beanset	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
table	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
butter-spoons	O
and	O
table-spoons	O
upon	O
all	O
the	O
four	O
tables	O
;	O
by	O
counting	O
up	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
tureen	O
ladle	O
,	O
one	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
butter-spoon	O
missing	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
there	O
are	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
butter-ladles	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
tureen	O
ladles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
delivers	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Key	O
.	O
They	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
are	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
waiters	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
waiters	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
employed	O
there	O
?	O
Key	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
employed	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cawthorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
being	O
beadle	O
to	O
the	O
worshipful	O
company	O
of	O
Goldsmiths	O
.	O
Last	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
I	O
attended	O
at	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
in	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
hall	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
their	O
business	O
;	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
informed	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
servants	O
waiting	O
for	O
liverymen	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
whose	O
servant	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
whiffler	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
the	O
cook	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
porter	O
Mr.	O
Wren	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
see	O
this	O
whiffler	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Whiffler	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
passing	O
and	O
repaffing	O
several	O
times	O
between	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
employed	O
in	O
?	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
In	O
carrying	O
dishes	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
dishes	O
away	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
dinner	O
?	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
not	O
many	O
whifflers	O
there	O
?	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
There	O
may	O
be	O
many	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
at	O
the	O
hall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
these	O
whifflers	O
employed	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
cook	O
?	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
,	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
to	O
carry	O
dishes	O
to	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
tables	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
lapidary	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
our	O
hall	O
last	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
on	O
our	O
cook	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
showed	O
him	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three-times	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
on	O
our	O
cook	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
tureen	O
things	O
with	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
soup	O
ladles	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hillyard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fair	O
.	O
I	O
dined	O
at	O
Goldsmiths-hall	O
last	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bring	O
dishes	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
waiter	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
dishes	O
from	O
the	O
waiters	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
towards	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
particular	O
what	O
dishes	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dispute	O
with	O
the	O
waiters	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
cook	O
;	O
the	O
beadle	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
tureen	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
baby	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
silver	O
melted	O
in	O
little	O
comical	O
ingots	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
10	O
ounces	O
13	O
penny-weights	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
silver	O
advertised	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
weight	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Goldsmiths	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
hall	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
advice	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
assay	O
made	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
never	O
cou	O
ld	O
be	O
melted	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
they	O
know	O
there	O
how	O
to	O
melt	O
it	O
as	O
we	O
do	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
workmanlike	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
Gutter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Fair	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
Chatham	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fair	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
letter	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
examination	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
kicked	O
against	O
something	O
in	O
Goldsmiths-street	O
,	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
tavern	O
for	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
refused	O
him	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
thousand	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
brought	O
this	O
silver	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
enquiry	O
made	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
in	O
Gutter	O
lane	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
silver	O
from	O
Chatham	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Goldsmiths-street	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
examined	O
?	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
prevaricated	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Fair	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Chatham	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
made	O
out	O
a	O
lame	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
expected	O
any	O
lenity	O
from	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
he	O
sighed	O
and	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
of	O
all	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
poverty	O
and	O
the	O
want	O
of	O
business	O
that	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Key	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
hall	O
?	O
Key	O
We	O
weighed	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
butter	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
tureen	O
ladles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
sort	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
ten	O
ounces	O
thirteen	O
pennyweights	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hardy	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
It	O
weight	O
ten	O
ounces	O
thirteen	O
penny-weights	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
Mention	O
the	O
words	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cawthorn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
expect	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
ample	O
discovery	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
this	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
my	O
Lord	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
that	O
confession	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Goldsmiths-hall	O
on	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
table	O
laid	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Cartwright	O
the	O
head	O
cook	O
seeing	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
doing	O
nothing	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
this	O
key	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
for	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
and	O
me	O
some	O
wine	O
;	O
then	O
things	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
dish	O
and	O
follow	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
carried	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
dishes	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
a	O
tureen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Goldsmiths-street	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
against	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
had	O
kicked	O
against	O
something	O
in	O
Goldsmiths-street	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
this	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
paper	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Swift	O
that	O
has	O
given	O
evidence	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
required	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
candle	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
kicked	O
against	O
something	O
in	O
Goldsmiths-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
after	O
he	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
deserves	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
charge	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
very	O
intimate	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
tavern	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
night	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
kicked	O
against	O
something	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
jingled	O
like	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
moon	O
did	O
not	O
shine	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
King's-head-court	O
,	O
Gutter-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
distant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
is	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
this	O
intimate	O
friend	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
imagined	O
he	O
had	O
kicked	O
against	O
a	O
watch	O
or	O
some	O
silver	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitten	O
.	O
He	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
any	O
way	O
dishonest	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Buttery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
two	O
years	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
his	O
care	O
,	O
diligence	O
,	O
and	O
sobriety	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
eight	O
men	O
under	O
his	O
direction	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
from	O
me	O
near	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Cheshire	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
November	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Francis	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
;	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
cheese	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
over-heard	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
be	O
frightened	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
half	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
cheese	O
produced	O
;	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
young	O
fellows	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
talking	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
,	O
all	O
is	O
clear	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walked	O
in	O
;	O
one	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
this	O
street	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
fellow	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
cheese	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Westridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
once	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
honest	O
and	O
just	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
24	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stone	O
bottle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
lamp	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wandsworth	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Queenhithe	B-place
with	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
mine	O
is	O
a	O
passage-boat	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
was	O
looking	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
people	O
there	O
staying	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
stood	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
boat	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
Hoare	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
Edwards	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
flesh	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
rescued	O
the	O
other	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
punt	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
punt	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
bottle	O
of	O
oil	O
in	O
the	O
punt	O
;	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
five	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
and	O
Hoare	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
punt	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
Edwards	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
oil	O
cost	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
bottle	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
stern	O
of	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
bottle	O
of	O
oil	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
directly	O
in	O
the	O
stern	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
again	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
bottle	O
of	O
oil	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
deposed	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
boat	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
stood	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
lost	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
oil	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
punt	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hoare	O
was	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
for	O
taking	O
Hoare	O
away	O
,	O
Edwards	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
the	O
boy	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
strike	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
.	O
Hoare	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
oil	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
punt	O
.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
disturbance	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
oil	O
found	O
in	O
our	O
punt	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
rude	O
chaps	O
running	O
over	O
the	O
vessels	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Plumeridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Hoare	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ringstead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
plain	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Walter	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
Hoxton	I-place
Market-place	I-place
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny-worth	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
draught	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
bags	O
with	O
blue	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
blue	O
and	O
indico	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
then	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
staggered	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
more	O
liquor	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
landlord	O
,	O
your	O
wife	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
cross	O
,	O
why	O
will	O
you	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
;	O
I	O
drawed	O
a	O
pint	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
noisy	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
rather	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
more	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
beer	O
here	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hearty	O
fellow	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
I	O
come	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
and	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
wife	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
cross	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
shake	O
hands	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
plain	O
gold	O
ring	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
slap	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
hearty	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
shake	O
hands	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
smart	O
slap	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
hearty	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
ring	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
fellow	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
ring	O
from	O
my	O
finger	O
;	O
he	O
stooped	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
bags	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
ring	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
immediately	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
his	O
shaking	O
hands	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
more	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
enough	O
already	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
another	O
pint	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Field	O
and	O
him	O
clap	O
hands	O
together	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
blow	O
that	O
he	O
hit	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
ring	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
's	O
little	O
finger	O
;	O
they	O
shook	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
they	O
parted	O
hands	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
ring	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
ring	O
on	O
his	O
finger	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
people	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
people	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
being	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
myself	O
;	O
we	O
waited	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
came	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
stripped	O
himself	O
to	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
fuddled	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pretty	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
pretty	O
drunk	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
drunk	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
ring	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
come	O
drink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
speak	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
drunk	O
also	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
said	O
,	O
stand	O
away	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
of	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
gang	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
will	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
bags	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
hurt	O
you	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
clapping	O
of	O
hands	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
shake	O
hands	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
without	O
holding	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
plain	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
ring	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
stick	O
close	O
by	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
clapping	O
of	O
hands	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
ring	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
That	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
clapping	O
of	O
hands	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
submitted	O
freely	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
all	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
ring	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
whole	O
transaction	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
after	O
the	O
clapping	O
of	O
hands	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
complaint	O
of	O
losing	O
his	O
ring	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
jury	O
declared	O
they	O
were	O
satisfied	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
called	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
d.	O
a	O
feather	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
another	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
a	O
fore-room	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
at	O
first	O
telling	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
pledge	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Gate	O
street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-inn-fields	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bolster	O
)	O
these	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
finishing	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
finished	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bretton	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
jack	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pannel	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
smoothing	O
plane	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Lapthorne	I-pers
;	O
one	O
agree	O
plane	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
jack	O
plane	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Peter	B-pers
Lapthorne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journyman	O
carpenter	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
tools	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
imagined	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
place	O
at	O
Battle-bridge	O
Wells	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
tool-handles	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
tools	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
tools	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
imagined	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
old	O
barn	O
under	O
some	O
straw	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
an	O
Alderman	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-market	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
well	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
robbed	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
either	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
or	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
tools	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
ours	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Battle	O
bridge	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
he	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
our	O
tools	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
barn	O
Acquitted	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Key	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farest	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
Oct	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
;	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
more	O
sick	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
wife	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
room	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
ship	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
pull	O
my	O
clothes	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
trouble	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
pull	O
my	O
breeches	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
pillow	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
cover	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
left-hand	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
his	O
landlady	O
:	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
ship-mate	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
breeches	O
lying	O
with	O
one	O
part	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
hanging	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
captain	O
had	O
just	O
paid	O
me	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knew	O
that	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
10	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
;	O
a	O
coachman	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
us	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
spent	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
five	O
halfpence	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
show	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
halfpence	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
yourself	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
,	O
pull	O
off	O
your	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
right	O
foot	O
be	O
very	O
willingly	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
dilatory	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
chose	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
about	O
unbuckling	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
one	O
guinea	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
he	O
had	O
stepped	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
no	O
other	O
account	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
captain	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
working	O
his	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
shillings	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
here	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
my	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
pray	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
lie	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
grow	O
mighty	O
pert	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
what	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
search	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
five	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shook	O
cut	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
money	O
than	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
dare	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
what	O
we	O
want	O
;	O
the	O
Frenchman	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
slip	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
shoe	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
very	O
readily	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
right	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
the	O
shoe	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
fob	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
the	O
other	O
shoe	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
abuse	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
shoe	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
shuffled	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
off	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
dropped	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
two	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Computer	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
bring	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
rest	O
back	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Manchester	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
voyages	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
without	O
a	O
character	O
to	O
nurse	O
the	O
wife	O
in	O
a	O
fever	O
;	O
at	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
they	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
fortnight	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
never	O
found	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
31	O
,	O
32	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Mary	O
Pitt	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Anne	O
Taylor	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
rose	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
ring	O
with	O
diamond	O
sparks	O
and	O
green	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pillowbear	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
worked	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
dimitty	O
petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coloured	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
one	O
flowered	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
worked	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
worked	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
russles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
worked	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Moreal	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
double	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Julian	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
a	O
striped	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
new	O
muslin	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannh	B-pers
Warnham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Susannah	B-pers
Warnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Anne	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
I	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Julian	I-pers
at	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
Park-street	B-place
,	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
on	O
that	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
we	O
fastened	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
and	O
chained	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
secured	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
the	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
We	O
lay	O
backwards	O
next	O
the	O
Park	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
:	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
who	O
we	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
nobody	O
but	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
and	O
myself	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
your	O
house	O
has	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
if	O
him	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
sash	O
frame	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
bolt	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
was	O
forced	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
window	O
fronting	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
is	O
rather	O
higher	O
than	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
first	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
chairs	O
thrown	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
kitchen	O
was	O
wet	O
with	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
broke	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
red	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
white	O
;	O
there	O
lay	O
two	O
large	O
tallow	O
candles	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
what	O
were	O
locked	O
in	O
a	O
candle	O
chest	O
,	O
we	O
used	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
wax	O
one	O
to	O
light	O
us	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
new	O
striped	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
new	O
striped	O
muslin	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
locked	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
trunk	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
scattered	O
about	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
baskets	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
missing	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
room	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
napkin	O
,	O
pillowbear	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
small	O
linen	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Julian	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
pump	O
in	O
Park-street	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
pump	O
drains	O
the	O
water	O
from	O
the	O
kitchens	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
houses	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
pump	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
against	O
a	O
wall	O
that	O
divides	O
Queen's-square	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
door	O
when	O
it	O
opens	O
from	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pump	O
as	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
tall	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
turned	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
habit	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
striped	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
draggled	O
up	O
the	O
tail	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
hat	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
under	O
her	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
like	O
a	O
white	O
counterpane	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
the	O
stocking	O
down	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
leg	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
dark	O
brown	O
hair	O
tied	O
behind	O
in	O
a	O
club	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
lay	O
cross	O
his	O
two	O
arms	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
move	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
pumping	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
door	O
a-jar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
evidence	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
clapped	O
her	O
hands	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Richard	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
fasten	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
carpenter	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
drunk	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
so	O
far	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
him	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
discharge	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
very	O
plain	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
suspected	O
from	O
my	O
information	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
lodged	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Peter-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
such	O
people	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
madam	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
pray	O
walk	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
gown	O
on	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
coachman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
knowing	O
the	O
coachman	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Phil	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Miller	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
downright	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
,	O
not	O
finding	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
searched	O
their	O
lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
their	O
landlady	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
oath	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
lodgings	O
the	O
night	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
from	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
nine	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
discharged	O
again	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
about	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
by	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
swore	O
positively	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
well	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
Tothill-fields	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
clear	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
by	O
her	O
height	O
and	O
clothes	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
uncertain	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
and	O
yet	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
?	O
Knot	O
.	O
Because	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
grows	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
in	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
diamond	O
ring	O
(	O
holding	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
18	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Smithfield	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
Red	O
Lion-street	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Anne	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
mistress	O
desired	O
nobody	O
might	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
ring	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
master	O
was	O
come	O
home	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
ring	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
or	O
the	O
tavern	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
mistress	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
ring	O
was	O
advertised	O
;	O
finding	O
none	O
between	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Daily	O
and	O
Public	O
Advertisers	O
,	O
and	O
Gazetteer	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
applied	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
ring	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
ring	O
,	O
her	O
daughter	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
more	O
clear	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
two	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Anne	B-pers
Nevell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Epsom	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
two	O
maids	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
examined	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Park-street	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
takes	O
the	O
ring	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
ring	O
which	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
the	O
very	O
night	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
great	O
disorder	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
maids	O
have	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
had	O
both	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
;	O
this	O
ring	O
(	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
35	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
Martha	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
about	O
nine	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
Martha	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
gave	O
it	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
it	O
particularly	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
flaw	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
stone	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
within	O
Mrs.	O
Nevell	O
's	O
house	O
not	O
near	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
no	O
nearer	O
than	O
Dartmouth-street	O
.	O
Mary	O
Griffiths	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Masters	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
woman	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
ring	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
one	O
child	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
E.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
,	O
unless	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
they	O
both	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
Sunday	O
?	O
E.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
Sunday	O
night	O
?	O
E.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
then	O
?	O
E.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
swear	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
E.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
oath	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
?	O
E.	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
on	O
that	O
morning	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
behaved	O
well	O
while	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
Sunday	O
night	O
?	O
Bartlet	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
nine	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
Sunday	O
night	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
or	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
trouble	O
my	O
head	O
with	O
any	O
lodgers	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Masters	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
she	O
appeared	O
paler	O
than	O
she	O
did	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
expressed	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
order	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
knowing	O
she	O
was	O
absolutely	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
nine	O
ounces	O
of	O
unwrought	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
56	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
,	O
a	O
weaver	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
silk	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
wind	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
her	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
nine	O
ounces	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
since	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
declared	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
his	O
wife	O
?	O
Hurst	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
i	O
n	O
common	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
lived	O
together	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
now	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
35	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-six	O
English	O
porcelain	O
ornamental	O
images	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
proprietor	O
at	O
Bow	O
in	O
the	O
porcelain	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
by	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
Hart	O
Naphtali	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
our	O
numbers	O
are	O
such	O
it	O
is	O
almost	O
impossible	O
to	O
miss	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Hart	B-pers
Naphtali	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
Phillips	O
offered	O
36	O
images	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
in	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
Phillips	O
said	O
his	O
young	O
master	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
Levi	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
or	O
lent	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
five	O
figures	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Naphtali	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
Myer	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
September	O
this	O
evidence	O
brought	O
some	O
figures	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
36	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
five	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
