TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OVER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
SIR	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Lord	O
MANSFIELD	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	B-pers
STAFFORD	I-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
;	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BATHURST	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cheeswright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kersill	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Venham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholl	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hayley	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Angell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Lightwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Sharpley	I-pers
.	O
188	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicated	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
live	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
live	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Randal	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
Randal	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bromley	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
live	O
cock	O
and	O
seven	O
hens	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shed	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bone	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Stepney	O
church-yard	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
good	O
morning	O
to	O
you	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
but	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
fowls	O
heads	O
and	O
legs	O
hang	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
hens	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
comical	O
cloaths	O
to	O
talk	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
fowls	O
and	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
hens	O
and	O
a	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ripping	O
chissel	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
fowls	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
that	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bone	I-pers
.	O
Matthews	O
brought	O
the	O
fowls	O
and	O
two	O
bags	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
fowls	O
alive	O
and	O
two	O
dead	O
.	O
Two	O
days	O
after	O
we	O
found	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blue	O
bays	O
on	O
the	O
leg	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
them	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Ellaker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
tin	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
padlock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Jones	O
;	O
we	O
lived	O
in	O
the	B-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Twickenham	I-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Marathy	O
,	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
boat	O
lying	O
by	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
one	O
Walker	O
that	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
account	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
soon	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
Walker	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
padlock	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
were	O
then	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
up	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
that	O
blow	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
190	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
M'Knaught	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
M'Knaught	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
shirts	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
his	O
lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
191	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pitaway	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Pitaway	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
down	O
below	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Makin	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
saying	O
.	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
hand	O
out	O
two	O
half	O
Cheshire	O
cheeses	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
dress	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cap	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
jockey	O
cap	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
dirty	O
apron	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
his	O
dress	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Makin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Portland	O
street	O
,	O
it	O
wanted	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
has	O
two	O
fronts	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
two	O
half	O
cheeses	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
two	O
different	O
ways	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Argyle-buildings	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
eight	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
192	O
,	O
193	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Churcher	I-pers
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
called	O
Wilton	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Churcher	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Churcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
my	O
partner	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
first	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
observed	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
lying	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
hand-bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
at	O
shops	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
with	O
such	O
cloth	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
offering	O
such	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
could	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
concerned	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Blackmore	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
slipt	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
sell	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Churcher	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
40	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
partner	O
live	O
?	O
Churcher	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
that	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
Leach	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
white	O
cloth	O
,	O
it	O
measured	O
16	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
more	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
another	O
piece	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
cloth	O
down	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Nursey	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
we	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
her	O
at	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
that	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
13	O
d.	O
1/2	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
Leach	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Merrit	O
took	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
1	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Merrit	O
?	O
Blackmore	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
gang	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
tried	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
us	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
Merrit	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
.	O
Blackmore	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
;	O
he	O
once	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
here	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nursey	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Leach	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
offered	O
me	O
this	O
small	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
wet	O
and	O
dirty	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
flannel	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
produced	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
buying	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
this	O
piece	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
cloth	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
that	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
compared	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
agrees	O
with	O
the	O
pattern	O
.	O
Leach	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Merrit	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
cloth	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
accidently	O
dropt	O
in	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Leach	O
calls	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
were	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Merrit	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
Blackmore	O
,	O
was	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
Westminster	O
,	O
about	O
some	O
china	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
and	O
Leach	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Leach	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Merrit	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
194	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Manwarring	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
at	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
men	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
gentlemen	O
doing	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
about	O
any	O
business	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
handed	O
our	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
their	O
porter	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
gentleman	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
out	O
at	O
another	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
,	O
peeping	O
into	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Yeandle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wandsworth	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
have	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
another	O
fellow	O
or	O
two	O
began	O
to	O
hustle	O
the	O
countryman	O
about	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
wanted	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
fellows	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
ale-house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fellows	O
set	O
himself	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
with	O
assistance	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
being	O
engaged	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
appears	O
you	O
are	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
bad	O
gang	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
impeach	O
and	O
save	O
yourself	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Lord	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
countryman	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
doors	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
which	O
door	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
,	O
while	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
defrauded	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
impudent	O
rascal	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
you	O
before	O
;	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
coach	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
three	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
up	O
to	O
Marybone	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
till	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
came	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Crown	O
Court	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
seven	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Trout	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
No	O
23	O
,	O
24	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
195.	O
James	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
cut	O
for	O
soles	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sterry	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
To	O
which	O
be	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
196	O
.	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Chaff	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Martin	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
by	O
the	B-place
Change	I-place
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
4th	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
Claxton	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
apothecary	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
two-more	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
discharged	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
Claxton	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
a	O
brother	O
porter	O
,	O
observed	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
by	O
the	O
'Change	O
,	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
make	O
motions	O
at	O
several	O
gentlemens	O
pockets	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
got	O
nothing	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
his	O
pocket	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
open	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
pastry	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
Chaff	O
take	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Claxton	O
;	O
Palmer	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
an	O
apothecary	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
Claxton	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Chaff	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
lad	O
(	O
meaning	O
Claxton	O
)	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
a	O
basket-maker	O
.	O
Claxton	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
my	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
White	O
Friars	O
glass-house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
other	O
lad	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
198	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dilkill	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dolkill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Governor	O
Peachy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
sister	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
can	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
upon	O
this	O
account	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
My	O
sister	O
was	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
shifts	O
and	O
aprons	O
are	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
my	O
aunt	O
;	O
the	O
shifts	O
,	O
aprons	O
,	O
ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
200	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Donnelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
chrystal	O
sleeve-buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lacuse	I-pers
;	O
and	O
41	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Clement	B-pers
Corderoy	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Lacuse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clement	B-pers
Corderoy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
makes	O
irons	O
for	O
saddle-trees	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Lower	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
the	B-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
,	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
40	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
knee-buckles	O
and	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
chairman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
for	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
one	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
Princes-street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
searching	O
him	O
we	O
found	O
34	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
knee-buckles	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
sleeve-buttons	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
sleeves	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
knee-buckles	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
buttons	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
as	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
trusted	O
with	O
that	O
money	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
very	O
imprudently	O
lay	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
spent	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
received	O
that	O
money	O
for	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
night-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
before	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
pillow	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
served	O
of	O
your	O
time	O
?	O
Lacuse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
served	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Tom	B-pers
the	O
Sailor	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
plyed	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
watched	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
34	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
knee	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
sleeve-buttons	O
in	O
his	O
sleeves	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
thingunder	O
my	O
foot	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
is	O
person	O
T	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Free	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Free	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
street	O
.	O
by	O
Piccadilly	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
thou	O
heard	O
something	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
meet	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
at	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
tylors	O
here	O
.	O
He	O
opened	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
intend	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
satisfied	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
hinder	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
backwards	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
ladle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
missed	O
seven	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
counted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
six	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
counted	O
wanted	O
6	O
d.	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
afterwards	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
papers	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
silver	O
and	O
small	O
gold	O
,	O
ready	O
for	O
change	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Free	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Free	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
ladle	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
ladle	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Freeto	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
delivered	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
picklocks	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
trembling	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
that	O
man	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
keys	O
in	O
the	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
also	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
one	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
Lane	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartlett	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
slippers	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
William	O
Clements	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
backwards	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
somebody	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
Run	O
;	O
then	O
Webb	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
slippers	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
somebody	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
slippers	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
slippers	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
and	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glove-maker	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Rice	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clement's-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
lodging	O
ready	O
furnished	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
her	O
lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
in	O
Clare	O
market	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
College-street	O
,	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
and	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
,	O
out	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
surgeon	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
his	O
brother	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
settle	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
help	O
carry	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
husband	O
till	O
yesterday	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
bed	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
her	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
takes	O
the	O
letter	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
her	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
I	O
find	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
is	O
opened	O
;	O
the	O
``	O
bed	O
is	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
all	O
in	O
``	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
``	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
``	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
real	O
want	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
''	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
bed	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
that	O
woman	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
go	O
abroad	O
than	O
stay	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
204	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
Dec.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Bear	I-place
inn	I-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
hung	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
hand-bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
gold	O
one	O
was	O
not	O
brought	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
another	O
crime	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Ireland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mar	O
y	O
Ireland	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
gold	O
watch	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
with	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
fetch	O
out	O
a	O
gold	O
laced	O
hat	O
that	O
was	O
pledged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
deliver	O
things	O
If	O
the	O
person	O
comes	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
named	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
had	O
pledged	O
a	O
god	O
watch	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
of	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pledged	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
our	O
house	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
wife	O
.	O
)	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
her	O
watch	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Philips	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
describing	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
made	O
a	O
different	O
appearance	O
from	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
does	O
now	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
like	O
him	O
in	O
make	O
an	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Ireland	O
lived	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
,	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
seeing	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pledged	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Shrewsbury	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
.	O
205	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
tortoise-shell	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Grace	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
||	O
Grace	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Darby-court	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
as	O
described	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hand-bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
without	O
giving	O
me	O
any	O
notice	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
he	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
glazier	O
putting	O
in	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
presently	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
your	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
plumber	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
standing	O
with	O
some	O
paviours	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
bill	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
.	O
describing	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
such	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
lives	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
I	O
or	O
my	O
wife	O
could	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
one	O
Allison	O
that	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
working	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
in	O
my	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
for	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
One	O
night	O
before	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
going	O
away	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair-dresser	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Steadman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
town	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Pilewood	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
behaviour	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Elliott	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bramble	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
eight	O
iron	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
cheek	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
iron	O
trevet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
hanging	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Bramble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
and	O
ironmonger	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
after	O
all	O
my	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
all	O
made	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
shutter	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
made	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
watchmen	O
informed	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
Marybone	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Elliott	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
suspected	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
together	O
at	O
times	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
,	O
in	O
Benham	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Elliot	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
I	O
behave	O
when	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Bramble	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
wronging	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
cause	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
neglect	O
their	O
business	O
by	O
drinking	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Benham	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Bramble	O
.	O
Benham	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
lay	O
any	O
theft	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
while	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
betwixt	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
Elliott	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
pot	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
pot	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
off	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collat	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
another	O
watchman	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
pot	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vitu	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
Parker	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
Elliott	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Bramble	O
's	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
Marybone	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
Elliot	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
pot	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
Mr	O
Bramble	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
pot	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
pots	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
taken	O
upon	O
Elliott	O
had	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
Elliott	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
meaning	O
Benham	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
Bristol	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
iron	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
take	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
got	O
;	O
when	O
Parker	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
,	O
I	O
intended	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
adverse	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
Benham	O
's	O
defence	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
pots	O
in	O
Benham	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Benham	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Susanna	I-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
||	O
Caleb	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
time	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
;	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
we	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Thrift	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
Murphey	O
's	O
door	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
you	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
somewhere	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
away	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
me	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
companions	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
watchman	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
glass	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
finding	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
cut	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
bloody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
drop	O
it	O
in	O
running	O
?	O
Pritchard	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
John	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
bloody	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
fellow	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
searched	O
about	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
seal	O
,	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
particular	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Church	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Price	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Constabie	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
chearful	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
varied	O
from	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
first	O
gave	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
has	O
accused	O
me	O
wrongfully	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
210	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Downe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
23	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newlove	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cragg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	B-place
Butcher-row	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Newlove	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
trunk	O
open	O
,	O
two	O
locks	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
brocaded	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
India	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
mistrust	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
somebody	O
else	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
after	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
betwixt	O
sleeping	O
and	O
waking	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
;	O
be	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
chamber-pot	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
(	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
up	O
higher	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
23	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
10	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
shillings	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
to	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Indies	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
another	O
bed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Portal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
a	O
brocaded	O
waistcoat	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
much	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
although	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
people	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
old	O
shirts	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newlove	I-pers
The	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
my	O
uncle	O
to	O
take	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
drawer	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
somebody	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
two	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckels	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
at	O
sea	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
all	O
my	O
wages	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
lodge	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nineteen	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
at	O
Aldgate	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
ribbon	O
;	O
she	O
stole	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
detected	O
her	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
box	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Showers	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
throwster	O
in	O
Leman-street	O
,	O
Goodman's-fields	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
nineteen	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
ditto	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
;	O
she	O
died	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
things	O
missed	O
in	O
your	O
mother	O
's	O
life-time	O
?	O
Caley	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hawkesworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Caley	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
these	O
goods	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
by	O
her	O
fellow-servant	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
Mrs.	O
Caley	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Hawkesworth	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
blond	O
lacc	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
about	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
1	O
s.	O
by	O
noon	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
blond	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
shewed	O
any	O
lace	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
lay	O
wait	O
for	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
white	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
every	O
parcel	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
white	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
next	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
confronted	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
searched	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
her	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
when	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
believe	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
customer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Caley	O
's	O
death	O
?	O
Hawkesworth	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
these	O
goods	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Caley	O
's	O
death	O
?	O
Hawkesworth	O
.	O
They	O
might	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Showers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
us	O
very	O
near	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
accuse	O
her	O
with	O
wronging	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
usual	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
any	O
connexions	O
with	O
bad	O
people	O
?	O
Showers	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
any	O
great	O
connexions	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hawkesworth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
blond	O
lace	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
white	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
lace	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
mens	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brewer's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden	I-place
square	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
hat-maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
hats	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
five	O
old	O
ones	O
and	O
one	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
with	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
same	O
morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
offer	O
several	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
Lower	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
his	O
mother	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
mother	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
dust-hole	O
in	O
Marybone	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
dust-hole	O
there	O
,	O
cross	O
questioned	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
meet	O
them	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cokayne	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
owner	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lived	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
soon	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wingfield	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
mark	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
five	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
nine-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Martha	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Joseph	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
and	O
Magpie	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
,	I-place
partly	I-place
facing	I-place
the	I-place
Compter	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
apprentice	O
that	O
worked	O
for	O
a	O
master	O
carpenter	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
bag	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
count	O
the	O
money	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
fearing	O
a	O
mistake	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
counted	O
one	O
guinea	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
counting	O
a	O
second	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
counting	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
his	O
score	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
nobody	O
shall	O
pay	O
my	O
reckoaing	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
your	O
way	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
plaguing	O
me	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
silver	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
my	O
eye	O
on	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
away	O
your	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
bag	O
of	O
gold	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
people	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
stifly	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
all	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
sink-holes	O
,	O
and	O
raked	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
being	O
sabbath-day	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Morton	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
your	O
loss	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
betwixt	O
Gold-street	O
and	O
here	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
your	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
five	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
nine-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
wrapped	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
twisted	O
round	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
:	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
paper	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bag	O
and	O
paper	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sixteen	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
speaking	O
about	O
his	O
reckoning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
snatch	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
that	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
his	O
score	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
directly	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Butler	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
run	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Martha	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l	O
was	O
in	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
opposite	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
betwixt	O
a	O
stone	O
and	O
a	O
post	O
:	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
and	O
Magote	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hern	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Hern	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
concerning	O
his	O
bringing	O
and	O
delivering	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
this	O
lad	O
Robinson	O
has	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
those	O
affairs	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
there	O
He	O
called	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sergeant	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Butler	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
could	O
only	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
and	O
honest	O
when	O
a	O
youth	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Garbett	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
bottle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pewter	O
syringe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pewter	O
milk-pots	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
pap	O
boats	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sugar-castor	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shoe-lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
shopman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
female	O
thief	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
my	O
chamber-maid	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
all	O
again	O
but	O
a	O
sugar-castor	O
and	O
tea-pot	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
and	O
pewter	O
teapot	O
to	O
a	O
cousin	O
she	O
had	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Sunday	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
soup	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
me	O
again	O
with	O
another	O
parcel	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
more	O
than	O
common	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
were	O
two	O
children	O
's	O
boats	O
,	O
two	O
milk-pots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sugar-castor	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
letters	O
on	O
the	O
pots	O
,	O
R	O
for	O
Henry	O
and	O
H	O
for	O
Joseph	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
read	O
?	O
Faulkner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
such	O
letters	O
?	O
Faulkner	O
.	O
Now	O
you	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
stand	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
mark	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
mark	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
apprentice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
those	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
in	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
till	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
and	O
castor	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
denied	O
ever	O
seeing	O
them	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Lhouse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
pew	O
be	O
:	O
tle	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sa	O
without	O
it	O
:	O
about	O
two	O
after	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
little	O
so	O
little	O
boy	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
that	O
for	O
her	O
brother	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
ask	O
pardon	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
suffer	O
any	O
thing	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Zechariah	I-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Phebe	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
by	B-place
Fleet-ditch	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
chair	O
woman	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
the	O
week	O
after	O
Michael	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
washing	O
or	O
ironing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
sheets	O
found	O
,	O
one	O
under	O
some	O
rags	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
first	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
then	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
then	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bad	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
tallyman	O
at	O
18	O
d.	O
per	O
week	O
;	O
then	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Hen	O
and	O
Chickens	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
eight	O
years	O
ago	O
at	O
the	O
Hen	O
and	O
Chickens	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
216	O
,	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
deal	O
board	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jourdan	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Jourdan	O
's	O
foreman	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
we	O
lost	O
a	O
deal	O
board	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
building	O
in	O
the	B-place
Minories	I-place
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
South	O
's	O
yard	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
board	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
well	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Parry	O
take	O
the	O
board	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
South	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Parry	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
off	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
Maddox	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Jourdan	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
South	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Parry	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
Maddox	O
might	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Parry	O
was	O
building	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
shed	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
stuff	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Castle	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
Maddox	O
to	O
be	O
charged	O
?	O
Castle	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
by	O
Parry	O
.	O
Parry	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Maddox	O
got	O
the	O
board	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Parry	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
Maddox	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
live	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
live	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Waggitt	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.+	O
Christopher	B-pers
Waggitt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hockley	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Hole	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cock	O
and	O
three	O
hens	O
between	O
the	O
18th	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hen-roost	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
beds	O
in	O
our	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
here	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
alive	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
White-cross-street	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
three	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
January	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	O
Wall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Golden-lane	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
lodger	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
one	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
also	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
after	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
cloth	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
Mrs.	O
Wall	O
's	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
367	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Bridgen	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
220	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
prints	O
with	O
wooden	O
frames	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bearby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Bearby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
,	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
blanket	O
and	O
sheet	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
)	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
for	O
the	O
pictures	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
and	O
cloath's-shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
blanket	O
and	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Flight	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
2	O
pictures	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
's	O
clerk	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
to	O
these	O
people	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
since	O
starved	O
to	O
death	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Backhouse	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Roger	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
jeans	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sergeant	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Sergeant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Little	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
slopseller	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
white	O
jeans	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
sustain	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
linings	O
of	O
waistcoats	O
and	O
breeches	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
white	O
jeans	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
flung	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
another	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
be	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
boy	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
past	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
222	O
,	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hencher	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
shop	O
and	O
a	O
lower	O
apartment	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
duty	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
from	O
my	O
watch-box	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
bolted	O
and	O
key	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
fa	O
street	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
13	O
inches	O
square	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
which	O
belong	O
to	O
ker	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
,	O
ght	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoner	O
both	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
found	O
.	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
H	O
broke	O
the	O
place	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
enticed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Harris	O
as	O
he	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
his	O
face	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
his	O
feet	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
pushed	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
downwards	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
bleeding	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
Harris	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
draw	O
them	O
beer	O
.	O
Hencher	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
will	O
bring	O
any	O
bad	O
people	O
here	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
drawed	O
them	O
some	O
beer	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
Harris	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
seemingly	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
distribute	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
not	O
being	O
within	O
.	O
About	O
one	O
o'clock	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
Harris	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
Hencher	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
whispering	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Harris	O
in	O
the	O
plight	O
I	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
there	O
lay	O
his	O
hat	O
under	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Hencher	O
broke	O
the	O
place	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
knew	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
watch-box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
when	O
Hencher	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Elson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
returned	O
from	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
one	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
Harris	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
wide	O
is	O
the	O
window	O
where	O
Harris	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Elson	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
ten	O
inches	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
sash	O
turned	O
sideways	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
upper	O
pane	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
the	O
shoes	O
were	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Harris	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Harris	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
15th	O
year	O
of	O
my	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
Hencher	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Harris	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
he	O
might	O
stay	O
in	O
his	O
watch-house	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
room	O
for	O
us	O
all	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Harris	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
crowded	O
into	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
rainy	O
night	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
Hencher	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
shop	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
Harris	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
Harris	O
shook	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Hencher	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
round	O
his	O
beat	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
boots	O
and	O
shoes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
then	O
Harris	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
cry	O
the	O
beat	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Harris	O
cry	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Harris	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
Hencher	O
staid	O
in	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
Harris	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
bleeding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
,	O
Harris	O
do	O
for	O
a	O
livelihood	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
rides	O
horses	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
got	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
once	O
by	O
knocking	O
the	O
lobb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
about	O
with	O
a	O
jack-ass	O
;	O
and	O
sell	O
potatoes	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Harris	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
Hencher	O
can	O
witness	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Harris	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Hencher	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
224	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Black	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Standen	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
Samuel	B-pers
Standen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheepskin	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
is	O
wrong	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
My	O
apprentice	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
for	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
up	O
his	O
frolick	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
did	O
I	O
did	O
with	O
honesty	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
cannisters	O
,	O
with	O
tea	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
counter	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
green	O
the	O
other	O
bohea	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
below	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Toler	I-pers
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
missed	O
the	O
cannisters	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cannister	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Toler	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
lads	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
cannisters	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
lads	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
of	O
some	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cannister	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
a	O
mark	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
put	O
on	O
it	O
when	O
the	O
exciseman	O
took	O
it	O
last	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
Toler	O
had	O
deposed	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
seeing	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
lads	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
cannister	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Toler	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Toler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
lads	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
boys	O
that	O
are	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
pointing	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
boys	O
.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
After	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
cannister	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
kicked	O
it	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Horton	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
ing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
house	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
he	O
said	O
another	O
gentleman	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
