TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
JULY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
SIR	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chamin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Margarum	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Corrock	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ribright	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Winwood	I-pers
,	O
Amos	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sheredine	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Juby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Treslove	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
335	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Court	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Benge	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Benge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
messenger	O
of	O
the	O
Navy-office	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	B-place
Post-office	I-place
,	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
tug	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
crowd	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
free	O
with	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
me	O
no	O
understand	O
English	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
forward	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
to	O
stoop	O
,	O
much	O
less	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
336	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cosser	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Cosser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Cosser	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Earl-street	I-place
,	I-place
Seven-dials	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lett	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
back	O
garret	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
se'nnight	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
flat	O
iron	O
and	O
sheets	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Seven-dials	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
sheet	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gibson	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
King-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
sheet	O
and	O
flat	O
iron	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
(	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
sheet	O
produced	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
flat	O
iron	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
337	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
,	O
from	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
privately	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Joseph	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
day-labouring	O
man	O
;	O
last	O
Whitsun-Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
at	O
Ashford	B-place
all	O
night	O
,	O
dancing	O
there	O
,	O
fifteen	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pinch	O
of	O
snuff	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
two	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
pieces	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
iron	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
pinch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
some	O
hours	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
a	O
pinch	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
feel	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
pinch	O
of	O
snuff	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
found	O
two	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
pieces	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
pocket-handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
prosecute	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dancing-room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
at	O
two	O
separate	O
times	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
338	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Wykes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
iron	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
paviour	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Pear-tree-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
game	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
behave	O
well	O
so	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
very	O
short	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
followed	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
house	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
and	O
they	O
sell	O
old	O
iron	O
;	O
he	O
soon	O
came	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
his	O
bag	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
chain	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Compton-street	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
is	O
cock	O
pipe	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Cherry-tree-alley	O
,	O
Blue-anchor-alley	O
,	O
and	O
Chequer-alley	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
in	O
the	O
places	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
themselves	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
chain	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
lead	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
concern	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
them	O
places	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
hauled	O
words	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
these	O
men	O
in	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
339	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Calf	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bringhurst	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	B-place
Noah	I-place
's	I-place
Ark	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
about	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
l.	O
but	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
about	O
half	O
that	O
sum	O
;	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
loitering	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
find	O
something	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
she	O
grumbled	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
did	O
nothing	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
help	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
get	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
but	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
bag	O
kept	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
locked	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
below	O
;	O
we	O
in	O
general	O
take	O
the	O
bag	O
up	O
stairs	O
when	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
we	O
left	O
it	O
locked	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
suspicious	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Stationer	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
having	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
rogues	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
silver	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
brass	O
thing	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
pigeon	O
hole	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
upper	O
liberty	O
of	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
to	O
the	O
Stationers	O
Arms	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
this	O
bundle	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
black	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
purple	O
ditto	O
,	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
some	O
silk	O
,	O
some	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
;	O
)	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
master	O
of	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
s.	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
summed	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
said	O
each	O
cost	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
brass	O
nut-crackers	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
six-pences	O
,	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
copper	O
)	O
which	O
all	O
together	O
made	O
up	O
about	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
trifle	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
denied	O
taking	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
promise	O
her	O
favour	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
?	O
Sheldon	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
many	O
times	O
promise	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
particularly	O
say	O
what	O
money	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
silver	O
and	O
gold	O
together	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
fetch	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
husband	O
promise	O
her	O
any	O
favour	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
promised	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
own	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
wrong	O
my	O
conscience	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
by	O
her	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
hired	O
herself	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Calf	I-pers
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Bringhurst	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
your	O
daughter	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
these	O
things	O
here	O
produced	O
?	O
M.	O
Clark	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
340	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Doland	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Wicksteed	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
*	O
Hen	O
Wicksteed	O
I	O
make	O
gold	O
beater	O
's	O
skin	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
journeywoman	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
who	O
to	O
accuse	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
shirts	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
a	O
general	O
search	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
six	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
seventh	O
shirt	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
certainly	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
present	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wicksteed	I-pers
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
seven	O
shirts	O
,	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
stock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
table-spoon	O
and	O
shirts	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
the	O
spoon	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
marked	O
)	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
usual	O
to	O
pawn	O
things	O
and	O
release	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
341	O
,	O
342	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bagnell	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
millener	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Lee-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Red-lion-square	I-place
.	O
Between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
hang	O
out	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
garters	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
garters	O
:	O
Bagnell	O
took	O
up	O
some	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
brush	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
ran	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
Fisher	O
dropped	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
ribbon	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
another	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Fisher	O
give	O
the	O
piece	O
to	O
Bagnell	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
lady	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
go	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
the	O
ribbons	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Fisher	O
take	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
;	O
Bagnell	O
came	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Fisher	O
gave	O
him	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
Bagnell	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Thompson	B-pers
the	O
boys	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Fisher	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
you	O
gave	O
something	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
lady	O
has	O
lost	O
some	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Bagnell	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
Bagel	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
some	O
ribbon	O
lying	O
near	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
.	O
M.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
piece	O
that	O
was	O
dropped	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Bagnell	O
called	O
Anne	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
of	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
of	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Bagnell	O
recommended	O
.	O
Fisher	O
T	O
.	O
Bagnell	O
B	O
.	O
See	O
Fisher	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Harris	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
in	O
May	O
Sessions	O
,	O
No	O
222	O
.	O
343	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dellot	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Herbert	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Herbert	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Gibson	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Church-yard-alley	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
instant	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
within	O
five	O
minutes	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
hat	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
name	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forsell	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
our	O
shop	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
often	O
with	O
things	O
?	O
Beckford	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
come	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
many	O
such	O
customers	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Beckford	O
.	O
We	O
may	O
have	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
hundred	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
come	O
to	O
bring	O
and	O
fetch	O
out	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
threw	O
this	O
hat	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
hat	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
pledge	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
6	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
hat	O
?	O
Beckford	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
had	O
4	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
that	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
this	O
for	O
four-pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
?	O
Beckford	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Blue-anchor-yard	O
,	O
in	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
book	O
every	O
thing	O
?	O
Beckford	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
curiosity	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
,	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
pawned	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
but	O
twice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
344.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
paste	O
shirt	O
breast-buckle	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
stand	O
at	O
the	B-place
Thistle	I-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
in	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
paste	O
breast-buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
glass-case	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
cleaned	O
it	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
George's-court	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
sold	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
fetched	O
him	O
1	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murthwaite	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
George's-court	O
,	O
Princess-street	O
,	O
near	O
Leicester-fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
shirt-buckle	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
that	O
he	O
liked	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Manilla	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
345	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aylesbury	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Twining	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Twining	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ealing	B-place
;	O
my	O
mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
farming	O
business	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
recruit	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
quartered	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
breeches	O
were	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Tyburn	O
turnpike	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
guinea	O
into	O
the	O
quart	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mouth	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
black	O
spot	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
guinea	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
spot	O
on	O
it	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
on	O
which	O
side	O
the	O
spot	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
on	O
which	O
side	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
on	O
the	O
tail	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
side	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
serjeant	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
recruits	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Shea	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
recruit	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
he	O
an	O
apprentice	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
be	O
advised	O
by	O
the	O
landlord	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
tinkle	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
pot	O
that	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
directly	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
a	O
fresh	O
tankard	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
the	O
beer	O
out	O
into	O
another	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
guinea	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
it	O
till	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
gold	O
about	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
among	O
some	O
silver	O
and	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Justice	O
Spinnage	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
spot	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
tail	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
pay	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
thirteen	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
serjeant	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
,	O
the	O
serjeant	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
look	O
,	O
landlord	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
this	O
pot	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
decided	O
,	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Chatham	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
brother	O
recruits	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
that	O
the	O
others	O
should	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
servant	O
for	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
drinking	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Shea	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
the	O
servant	O
for	O
change	O
?	O
Shea	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
three	O
feet	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
346	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
table	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Philip	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
might	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
wine	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
being	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
knocked	O
against	O
the	O
partition	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
girl	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
girl	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
coat	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
silver	O
spoons	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
the	O
stairs	O
below	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
)	O
we	O
sent	O
people	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
sheet	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
,	O
wrapped	O
round	O
his	O
body	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
up	O
the	O
spoons	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
sheet	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
missing	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Cat	O
's	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
spoon	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
sheet	O
and	O
spoons	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
necessary-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
whether	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
their	O
property	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
347	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waine	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
David	B-pers
Riddle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
watchman	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
dropped	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
two	O
more	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
three	O
keys	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bent	O
like	O
a	O
book	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Waine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
beef	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
pay	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
to	O
hang	O
my	O
meat	O
there	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
up	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
shop-door	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
's	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
soon	O
after	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
the	O
beef	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
market	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
immediately	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
farther	O
accusation	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
answer	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
small	O
bag	O
lying	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
dirt	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
flung	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
are	O
any	O
farther	O
charge	O
?	O
(	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
affront	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
an	O
Englishman	O
I	O
would	O
plead	O
my	O
own	O
cause	O
.	O
)	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
morning	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
thinking	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
something	O
ran	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
hook	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Camomile-street	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
watchmen	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
hardly	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
directly	O
;	O
they	O
collared	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
pushed	O
me	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
another	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
pushing	O
me	O
this	O
hook	O
dropped	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
some	O
vulgar	O
words	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
drinking	O
strong	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
discharged	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
watchmen	O
said	O
they	O
saw	O
something	O
drop	O
;	O
then	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
butcher	O
's	O
hook	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
unacquainted	O
in	O
your	O
affairs	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
answer	O
until	O
I	O
come	O
before	O
a	O
superior	O
court	O
;	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
I	O
might	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
a	O
wise	O
magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
speak	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
good	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
which	O
)	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
reverential	O
bow	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
affront	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
only	O
just	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
by	O
your	O
Lordship	O
's	O
good	O
leave	O
-	O
A	O
proper	O
Englishman	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
convicted	O
,	O
unless	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
sufficient	O
witnesses	O
to	O
affect	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
none	O
,	O
you	O
see	O
by	O
your	O
wise	O
enquiry	O
,	O
can	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
I	O
stand	O
accused	O
of	O
at	O
this	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
wish	O
I	O
might	O
fall	O
under	O
a	O
wise	O
and	O
prudent	O
judge	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
,	O
judicious	O
,	O
tender	O
,	O
conscientious	O
and	O
righteous	O
jury	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
never	O
more	O
to	O
offend	O
my	O
King	O
,	O
my	O
God	O
,	O
or	O
my	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk-weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Whitecross-street	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
place	O
as	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
348.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stocking	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
medal	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
,	O
2400	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
200	O
copper	O
farthings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	B-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
sign	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
of	I-place
Prussia	I-place
on	I-place
horseback	I-place
;	O
I	O
bolted	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
taken	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
Five	O
Inkhorn-court	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
,	O
could	O
put	O
an	O
arm	O
in	O
and	O
reach	O
the	O
bolt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
two	O
pins	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
screw	O
of	O
the	O
casement	O
;	O
the	O
shutter	O
did	O
not	O
quite	O
reach	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
shutter	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
shut	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
shutter	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
two	O
doors	O
open	O
,	O
one	O
opens	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
bar	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
upwards	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
with	O
upwards	O
of	O
200	O
farthings	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
from	O
a	O
shelf	O
in	O
the	O
bar-room	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
a	O
penknife	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
handle	O
made	O
of	O
brass	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
watch-house	O
that	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
3	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
a	O
penknife	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
penknife	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
pumps	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
George-yard	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
parish	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Warner	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
there	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
were	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
pumps	O
,	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
pewter	O
medal	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
where	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
call	O
a	O
bad	O
half-crown	O
)	O
and	O
about	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
pumps	O
,	O
cannister	O
,	O
bad	O
half-crown	O
,	O
leather	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
penknife	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
broke	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
somebody	O
to	O
assist	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
bolt	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
July	O
was	O
my	O
watch-night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
catched	O
in	O
a	O
publican	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
servant	O
lay	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
halfpence	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Tomlinson	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
penknife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Tomlinson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
pumps	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
cannister	O
,	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
bad	O
half-crown	O
,	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
penknife	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
set	O
me	O
at	O
liberty	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
Norwich	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
but	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
promise	O
made	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
349	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sleath	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Snow-hill	B-place
;	O
a	O
nephew	O
of	O
mine	O
who	O
was	O
walking	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
past	O
you	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
people	O
passing	O
and	O
repassing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
My	O
uncle	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
,	O
were	O
walking	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
fellow	O
with	O
him	O
behind	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
fall	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
uncle	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
you	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
behind	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
having	O
got	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Jacob's-court	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
350	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spink	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Spink	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Marybone	I-place
parish	I-place
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brass	O
pottage-pot	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
area	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
a	O
woman	O
from	O
my	O
area	O
with	O
a	O
pottage-pot	O
up	O
to	O
Cavendish-square	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
pot	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
pot	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
round	O
silent	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
own	O
pot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
going	O
towards	O
Fleet	O
street	O
?	O
Abel	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
standing	O
stock	O
still	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
before	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
part	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Spink	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
sting	O
and	O
tear	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
tore	O
the	O
clothes	O
off	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
take	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
quit	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
get	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Spink	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Spink	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
pot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
daily	O
labour	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
hired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
that	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
King's-head	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Abel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Abel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
351	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brown	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
metal	O
buttons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
borrow	O
the	O
Gazetteer	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
paper	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
advertised	O
,	O
stopped	O
,	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
hands	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bond	B-pers
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
doe-skin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fingers	O
cut	O
part	O
off	O
on	O
the	O
left-hand	O
glove	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
them	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
;	O
he	O
examined	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wooler	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
detained	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
Danes	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig	O
maker	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
my	O
lodger	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
these	O
clothes	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
clothes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
till	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
pilser	O
something	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
stranger	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
beadle	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
clothes	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
ask	O
for	O
Dr.	O
Carrol	O
?	O
Wooler	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
such	O
Doctor	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Doctor	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
earnestly	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
kinswoman	O
rapped	O
hard	O
under	O
where	O
I	O
sat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
clothes	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
kinsman	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
being	O
much	O
the	O
colour	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
very	O
willingly	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
backwards	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
clothes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
James's-gate	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
detained	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
varied	O
every	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Arundel-street	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
clothes	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
child	O
while	O
she	O
paid	O
some	O
money	O
for	O
some	O
clothes	O
,	O
which	O
woman	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
woman	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
J.	O
Layton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
coming	O
here	O
?	O
J.	O
Layton	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
?	O
J.	O
Layton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
this	O
story	O
there	O
?	O
J.	O
Layton	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
did	O
she	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
mentioned	O
?	O
J.	O
Layton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
J.	O
Layton	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
washing	O
and	O
scouring	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
old	O
clothes	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
farthing	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
her	O
mention	O
such	O
a	O
name	O
as	O
Dr.	O
Carrol	O
?	O
M.	O
Doyle	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
Poppin's-court	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
single	O
or	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
M.	O
Kelly	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
paviour	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
M.	O
Kelly	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
buys	O
rags	O
and	O
old	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
myself	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
352	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Goadson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
containing	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roworth	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Roworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
maid	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
sacking	O
lay	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
concealed	O
in	O
her	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
bundle	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
coal-shed	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
ribbons	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
blond	O
lane	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
some	O
gauze	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
callimanco	O
pumps	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
for	O
children	O
,	O
two	O
red	O
Morocco	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
greatest	O
quantity	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
coal-shed	O
or	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Roworth	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
greatest	O
quantity	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
body	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
live	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Roworth	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Stark	O
,	O
a	O
hair-merchant	O
in	O
Bartholomew-close	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
lodging	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
he	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
shoes	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
shoes	O
have	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
that	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Roworth	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
months	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
marked	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
well	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Roworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
trifling	O
things	O
of	O
mine	O
not	O
worth	O
mentioning	O
;	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
bed	O
I	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
some	O
ribbon	O
,	O
some	O
lace	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
which	O
lay	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Roworth	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
get	O
out	O
backwards	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Kitty	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
sad	O
girl	O
,	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
will	O
transport	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
nor	O
owned	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
warning	O
above	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
left	O
me	O
as	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
but	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
box	O
to	O
lock	O
any	O
thing	O
up	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
warning	O
?	O
M.	O
Roworth	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
young	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
nursing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
353	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pier-glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
nineteen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
garden	O
spades	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pick	O
axes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
hatchet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Joshua	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Peerless-Pool	B-place
;	O
my	O
place	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
By	O
virtue	O
of	O
an	O
advertisement	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
Swindal	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
them	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Swindal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
read	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
;	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
spades	O
and	O
pick-axes	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
gardens	O
at	O
Peerless	O
Pool	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lumber-room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pier-glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cold-bath	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
towels	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Coverly's-fields	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
watchman	O
of	O
our	O
town	O
stopped	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
calls	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
our	O
parish	O
,	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
gutter-lead	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
for	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
all	O
except	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
pieces	O
of	O
,	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
wrote	O
upon	O
the	O
glass	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
,	O
Peerless-Pool	O
,	O
pray	O
stop	O
the	O
bearer	O
(	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
glass	O
produced	O
)	O
we	O
imagine	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
words	O
out	O
.	O
Croker	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Joe	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
showed	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
Swindal	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
directly	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
things	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
landlord	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
seize	O
his	O
things	O
for	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
iron	O
pottage-pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
(	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Bear	I-place
in	I-place
Well-street	I-place
,	I-place
Mile-end	I-place
New-town	I-place
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
iron	O
pots	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
other	O
neighbours	O
had	O
lost	O
goods	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
iron	O
pots	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
closet	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
354	O
,	O
355	O
,	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
garnets	O
and	O
rose	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gad	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Gad	I-pers
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Gad	I-pers
is	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Somerset-house	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
neither	O
I	O
nor	O
my	O
husband	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
playing	O
before	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
our	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
A.	O
Gad	O
.	O
The	O
oldest	O
is	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
they	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
sold	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
Dawson	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
had	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
the	O
tongs	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
the	O
tongs	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
having	O
offered	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
live	O
?	O
A.	O
Gad	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
in	O
Black-boy-alley	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
tongs	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Clark	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
boys	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
boy	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
Cox	O
brought	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Benjamin-street	O
,	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
tea-tongs	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
these	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Dawson	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
tongs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
drawer	O
under	O
her	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
tongs	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
Dawson	O
and	O
Smith	O
were	O
committed	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
we	O
met	O
Cox	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Cox	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
boy	O
a	O
little	O
bigger	O
than	O
Dawson	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
ring	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
said	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
leave	O
the	O
ring	O
till	O
his	O
master	O
comes	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
Cox	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
fearful	O
you	O
are	O
bad	O
boys	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
keep	O
the	O
ring	O
till	O
they	O
bring	O
somebody	O
to	O
testify	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Cox	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
somebody	O
in	O
Bedford-row	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
the	O
ring	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
part	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
you	O
bring	O
your	O
master	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
ring	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Cox	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
little	O
boy	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
play	O
by	O
that	O
old	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
school	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
ring	O
to	O
the	O
goldsmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
a	O
spoon	O
to	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
Smith	O
)	O
we	O
lost	O
that	O
other	O
boy	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
tongs	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
lives	O
in	O
Bedford	O
row	O
.	O
Cox	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Betsworth	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hickley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Dawson	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Another	O
boy	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
trap-ball	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
market	O
;	O
then	O
that	O
boy	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Cox	O
carried	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Jemima	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
J.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
not	O
older	O
?	O
J.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
The	O
truth	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
oranges	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Dawson	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
dunghill	O
by	O
our	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
a	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
dunghill	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea-tongs	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
stocking	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
tongs	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
snatch	O
the	O
tongs	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
dropt	O
six-pence	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sells	O
oranges	O
and	O
lemons	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
pawn	O
her	O
things	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Cox	O
and	O
Dawson	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Smith	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
357	O
,	O
358.	O
Henry	B-pers
Donnelly	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mungo	B-pers
Baikie	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
teaspoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mungo	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
Mungo	O
Baikie	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Orange-street	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
small	O
house	O
and	O
garden	O
behind	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
at	O
Tottenham-court	B-place
turnpike	I-place
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
for	O
this	O
three	O
summers	O
past	O
I	O
have	O
resided	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
some	O
looking-glasses	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
last	O
?	O
Baikie	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
it	O
since	O
last	O
summer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
this	O
card	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
card	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
looking-glass	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
frame	O
,	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
taken	O
off	O
of	O
a	O
pillow	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
china	O
half	O
pint	O
bason	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
?	O
Balkie	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
place	O
broke	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
new	O
paper	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
were	O
looking	O
out	O
for	O
other	O
people	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
information	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
seeing	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
with	O
their	O
pockets	O
encumbered	O
,	O
we	O
stopt	O
them	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
Donnelly	O
two	O
napkins	O
and	O
a	O
china	O
bowl	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sale	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Devil's-gap	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
them	O
;	O
Jones	O
had	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
teaspoon	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
bason	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
bason	O
;	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cupboard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
card	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop-bills	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
haymaking	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
saved	O
up	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
ten	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
One	O
is	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
fortnight	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
light	O
of	O
Jones	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
sleep	O
among	O
the	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
Jones	O
slept	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
into	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
some	O
cucumbers	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
Donnelly	O
went	O
over	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
Jones	O
;	O
finding	O
no	O
cucumbers	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
summer-house	O
;	O
he	O
slept	O
up	O
upon	O
two	O
chairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
corner-cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
pillow	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
five	O
china	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
a	O
half-pint	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
frame	O
.	O
Jones	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
five	O
china	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
summer-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
call	O
that	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
call	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
sleep	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wright	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Crofts	O
when	O
you	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
designed	O
thing	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
our	O
lives	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Crofts	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jones	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
breechees	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
evenings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
Somewhere	O
by	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Donnelly	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
me	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Donnelly	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
persuade	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Donnelly	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
hay-making	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
any	O
longer	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
which	O
way	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
to	O
what	O
part	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
towards	O
Tooley-street	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
us	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Devil's-gap	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
they	O
stopt	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
us	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
thing	O
we	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
an	O
evidence	O
with	O
us	O
handcuffed	O
,	O
watching	O
for	O
other	O
persons	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
looking-glass	O
at	O
Donnelly	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
pockets	O
stuffed	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
stopt	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Jack	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
distressed	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
sessions	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
turned	O
slag	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
young	O
fellows	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
pastrycook	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
suppose	O
is	O
turning	O
slag	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
against	O
who	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
against	O
Harry	B-pers
Donnelly	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Harry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
fell	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
blood	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
'll	O
cloath	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Catherine-street	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Tothill	O
fields	O
Bridewell	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
disorderly	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
for	O
picking	O
of	O
pockets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
Donnelly	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
Donnelly	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
house-keeping	O
soon	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
asked	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
before	O
Crofts	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
Donnelly	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Tooley-street	O
;	O
Crofts	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
Jones	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Newport-market	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
while	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
will	O
you	O
take	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
said	O
Donnelly	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Devil's-gap	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
stopt	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
then	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
Crofts	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
Crofts	O
go	O
;	O
presently	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
handcuffed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
up	O
came	O
he	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wright	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
Crofts	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Donnelly	O
nine	O
months	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
;	O
Donnelly	O
served	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
conclusion	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
soberly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
honestly	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
idle	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
reproved	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
can	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
get	O
at	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
He	O
may	O
get	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
indict	O
them	O
for	O
breaking	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
made	O
out	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
latch	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
gives	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
or	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
observable	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
careful	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
the	O
burglary	O
;	O
Jones	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
To	O
Donnelly	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Donnelly	I-pers
.	O
Donnelly	O
's	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
kinsman	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
least	O
thing	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Donnelly	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
careful	O
lad	O
till	O
this	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shagreen	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
mettle	O
watch	O
hook	O
and	O
chain	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hewerdine	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hewerdine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Gun-dock	B-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
.	O
Yesterday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
and	O
pay	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
near	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
gone	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
watermen	O
's	O
boys	O
and	O
others	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
people	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
dunghill	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
over	O
.	O
-	O
Lavender	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
behind	O
the	O
church	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
brick-wall	O
very	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
one	O
Domony	O
ran	O
a	O
nearer	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
round	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
went	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
a	O
butcher	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Lavender	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
strike	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
the	O
left-side	O
of	O
his	O
cheek	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
quiet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
?	O
Lavender	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Branham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
the	O
butcher	O
had	O
just	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
some	O
mud	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
cast	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friends	O
here	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bamboe	O
joint	O
for	O
a	O
fishing-rod	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
ferril	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
six	O
hazel	O
joints	O
for	O
tops	O
of	O
fishing	O
rods	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
other	O
joints	O
for	O
tops	O
of	O
fishing-rods	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
spelter	O
solder	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Emory	I-pers
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Emory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fishing-rod	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
journeyman	O
,	O
from	O
October	O
to	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
here	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
bamboe	O
butt	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
screw	O
ferril	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
workshop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
concealing	O
some	O
hazel	O
joints	O
for	O
fishing-rods	O
under	O
his	O
work	O
bench	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
six	O
pieces	O
under	O
his	O
bench	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
offering	O
a	O
fishing-rod	O
in	O
Crooked-lane	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Worthington	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
one	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
very	O
bulky	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
