TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
SIR	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Percy	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Wheat	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiston	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Whiston	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Blakesley	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
Silver	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smithers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gowland	I-pers
,	O
Wm	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
.	O
84	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
hat-band	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
January	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Purpool-lane	B-place
,	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
last	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloaths	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Thoy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
old	O
cloaths-man	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
cloaths-man	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
asked	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shewed	O
me	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
14	O
s.	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
message	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
your	O
cloaths	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
an	O
alehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
use	O
that	O
alehouse	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
key	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
used	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
85	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
square	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
,	O
January	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Jacob	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
last	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
peruke-maker	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
my	O
servant	O
hear	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
shed	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
people	O
with	O
my	O
loss	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
Samuel	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pockets	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
my	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
me	O
seven	O
years	O
for	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
cloaths	O
by	O
paying	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
week	O
into	O
a	O
club	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
spoons	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
square	O
was	O
a	O
brass	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Polock	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Polock	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
master	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Knock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
plough	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
long	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pannel	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
stock	O
,	O
two	O
smoothing	O
planes	O
,	O
one	O
pannel	O
saw	O
,	O
one	O
mortise	O
chisel	O
,	O
three	O
bead	O
planes	O
,	O
two	O
oval	O
planes	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
chisel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
December	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joiner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Putney	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
journeyman	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Grantham	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
discharged	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
tools	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Elsby	I-pers
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
tools	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
came	O
at	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
pledged	O
this	O
chisel	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
that	O
and	O
a	O
saw	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knock	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
saw	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
chisel	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Little	O
Pultney-street	O
;	O
this	O
plough	O
,	O
long	O
plane	O
,	O
stock	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
off	O
a	O
scaffold	O
and	O
hurt	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
work	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Richard	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
pannel	O
saw	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
William	O
Knock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
infirmary	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Priestbird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
seven	O
planes	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
tools	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
where	O
these	O
tools	O
were	O
pledged	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
mentioned	O
how	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
they	O
did	O
make	O
him	O
the	O
promise	O
he	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
tools	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
fellow	O
workmen	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
also	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
those	O
promises	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
hoped	O
this	O
will	O
warn	O
prosecutors	O
not	O
to	O
draw	O
out	O
confessions	O
with	O
promises	O
of	O
favour	O
.	O
87	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
October	O
30	O
.	O
1765	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milk-woman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Rider's-court	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1765	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
distant	O
relation	O
:	O
he	O
absconded	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
puppet-show	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
at	O
Chatham	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
E.	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
have	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
E.	O
Yates	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
88.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
89.	O
John	B-pers
William	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
hat-buckle	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
camblet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
90	O
,	O
91	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
tons	O
weight	O
of	O
stones	O
for	O
paving	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Mayor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Commonalty	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
city	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
J.	O
Norton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
loading	O
stones	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Fleet-ditch	B-place
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hedderly	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
load	O
the	O
cart	O
each	O
day	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
stones	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
from	O
Fleet-ditch	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
any	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
under	O
the	O
commissioners	O
for	O
paving	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
one	O
cart	O
load	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
Poor	O
Jury-lane	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
who	O
drove	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
one	O
Gregory	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Kingsland	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
two	O
cart	O
loads	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Gregory	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
load	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
but	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
load	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
said	O
Gregory	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Gregory	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
stones	O
from	O
the	O
heap	O
at	O
Fleet-ditch	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
ready	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Freeman	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Kingsland	O
when	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
gravel	O
to	O
Leadenhall-street	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
,	O
paviour	O
to	O
the	O
commissioners	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
more	O
stones	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
some	O
gravel	O
to	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
stones	O
to	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
deficient	O
in	O
his	O
days	O
works	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
two	O
loads	O
of	O
stones	O
to	O
Gregory	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cokayne	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
Gregory	O
up	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
employed	O
Gregory	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
to	O
pave	O
before	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
five	O
guineas	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
find	O
stones	O
and	O
gravel	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
brought	O
them	O
two	O
loads	O
of	O
stones	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
Gregory	O
and	O
Wright	O
borrowed	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
11	O
s.	O
each	O
day	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
surveyor	O
to	O
the	O
commissioners	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
pebbles	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
were	O
deposited	O
on	O
the	O
w	O
ground	O
on	O
Fleet-ditch	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
were	O
carted	O
occasionally	O
to	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
wanted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Wyat	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Mayor	O
and	O
Commonalty	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
ground	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
Kingsland	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Brick-lane	O
;	O
Gregory	O
and	O
Wright	O
hallooed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
what	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
looked	O
after	O
the	O
stones	O
in	O
Fleet-ditch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
body	O
takes	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
Freeman	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Kingsland	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
stones	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
||	O
Kingsland	O
having	O
received	O
his	O
punishment	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
branded	O
,	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
loaded	O
one	O
load	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Gregory	O
and	O
Wright	O
,	O
in	O
Brown's-lane	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
agreed	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
stones	O
?	O
Kingsland	O
.	O
Wright	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Gregory	O
say	O
?	O
Kingsland	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
agree	O
amongst	O
yourselves	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
his	O
work	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
lent	O
them	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
us	O
.	O
Gregory	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
paid	O
;	O
we	O
received	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
one	O
load	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Gregory	O
pay	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Kingsland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lucy	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
Gregory	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
stones	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
Kingsland	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
load	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wright	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
labourer	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
paviour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
partners	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Gregory	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
frighted	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
stones	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
sent	O
a	O
fishing	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
I	O
understood	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
and	O
Wright	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Kingsland	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Lucy	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
stones	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
desirous	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
stones	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
?	O
Perkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
counted	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Richard	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hard-working	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thwack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
general	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nightingale	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
thirteen	O
and	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hard-working	O
man	O
of	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Case	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
thirteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nolder	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
always	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Curle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
betwixt	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Collinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
certain	O
inland	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
drawn	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
banker	O
,	O
requiring	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
16	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
forged	O
acceptance	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
Sir	O
,	O
``	O
Please	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Collinson	I-pers
,	O
or	O
his	O
``	O
order	O
,	O
16	O
l.	O
fourteen	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
place	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
.	O
``	O
October	O
14	O
,	O
1765	O
.	O
Accepted	O
,	O
Hankey	O
and	O
``	O
Company	O
.	O
''	O
and	O
for	O
uttering	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Abraham	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
;	O
and	O
also	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
,	O
1765	O
.	O
+	O
Abraham	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
lodge	O
and	O
board	O
while	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
somebody	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
an	O
uncle	O
)	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
had	O
died	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
administer	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
administer	O
without	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Reading	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
two	O
guineas	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
sister	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
indorsed	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
returned	O
post-chaise	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
from	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
from	O
Reading	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
it	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
apprehended	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
ten	O
months	O
after	O
,	O
upon	O
another	O
forged	O
note	O
(	O
the	O
note	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
note	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
delivered	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
Sir	O
,	O
``	O
Please	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Collinson	I-pers
,	O
or	O
his	O
``	O
order	O
,	O
16	O
l.	O
fourteen	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
and	O
place	O
``	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
``	O
Your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Howden	O
,	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
,	O
1765	O
.	O
Accepted	O
,	O
Hankey	O
and	O
Co.	O
Indorsed	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Collinson	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
when	O
he	O
indorsed	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
boots	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
jockey	O
hat	O
slapt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
recommended	O
him	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
He	O
mentioned	O
some	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
from	O
that	O
country	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
about	O
eight	O
miles	O
off	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
niece	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twice	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
waited	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
J.	O
Allen	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
round	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
boots	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
?	O
J.	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
ask	O
my	O
uncle	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
upon	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
J.	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
uncle	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
pen	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
with	O
your	O
uncle	O
?	O
J.	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
staid	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
pretty	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
conversation	O
your	O
uncle	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
J.	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
administer	O
to	O
a	O
will	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
till	O
his	O
sister	O
from	O
Reading	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Oromd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
(	O
he	O
takes	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
there	O
are	O
five	O
partners	O
with	O
Sir	O
Joseph	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
Sir	O
Joseph	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
(	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
acceptance	O
)	O
nor	O
none	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
time	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
has	O
it	O
been	O
since	O
?	O
Oromd	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
at	O
our	O
office	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
offered	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
that	O
keeps	O
cash	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Oromd	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
such	O
an	O
acceptance	O
as	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Allen	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
carried	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
's	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
seven	O
years	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
lord	O
Talbot	O
,	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn-fields	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
publishing	O
the	O
acceptance	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forged	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
94	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Orris	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
linen	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Orris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
new	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
at	O
Old	B-place
Brentford	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
opposite	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lodged	O
there	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
From	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
apartment	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Onley	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
the	O
question	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Ball	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
agreeable	O
,	O
they	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
fellow	O
used	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
worse	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
me	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
get	O
your	O
pocket	O
by	O
pulling	O
you	O
about	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
pull	O
particularly	O
at	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
By	O
pulling	O
me	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
moon-lightish	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
fellow	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
stripped	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
this	O
from	O
where	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
stones	O
cast	O
;	O
they	O
dragged	O
me	O
in	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
nastiness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consider	O
this	O
as	O
using	O
you	O
thus	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
take	O
your	O
money	O
from	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
me	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
or	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
cardinal	O
neither	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wegg	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
over	O
night	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
spent	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
7	O
1/2	O
d.	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
thrown	O
that	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
watch	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Orris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
woman	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
you	O
used	O
ill	O
cross	O
the	O
road	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
no	O
body	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
used	O
my	O
wife	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
several	O
bruises	O
about	O
her	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
cardinal	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
calls	O
it	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
This	O
may	O
be	O
near	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
opposite	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
do	O
all	O
his	O
life-time	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
your	O
wife	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
with	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
first	O
complain	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
your	O
wife	O
follow	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
Any	O
thing	O
that	O
she	O
can	O
get	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
sober	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
did	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
wife	O
's	O
stock	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
what	O
I	O
got	O
I	O
always	O
gave	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
labouring	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
14	O
d.	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
your	O
wife	O
do	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
She	O
goes	O
a	O
haymaking	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
ask	O
charity	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
married	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
ask	O
charity	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
given	O
her	O
any	O
money	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
ill	O
?	O
Orris	O
.	O
Fifteen	O
weeks	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
at	O
Richmond	O
,	O
at	O
gentlemens	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Orris	I-pers
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
Richmond	O
for	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
ask	O
charity	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
halfpence	O
of	O
a	O
gardener	O
,	O
one	O
Whitehouse	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
got	O
?	O
M.	O
Orris	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
silver	O
six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
wrapped	O
in	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
rag	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Nevett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
or	O
upwards	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
sober	O
and	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old	O
Brentford	O
,	O
just	O
where	O
this	O
pretended	O
robbery	O
was	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
I	O
know	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
worse	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
Stanhope	O
Hillier	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
earn	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
95	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bourke	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Carre	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
silk	O
waistcoats	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
silver-hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
belt	O
,	O
three	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Haselby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
colonel	O
Carre	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
service	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
upon	O
New-year's-day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
by	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Carnaby-market	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
near	O
Swallow-street	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
colonel	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lydard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
a	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
coming	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
highwayman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Wright	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
examined	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bourke	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
with	O
one	O
'Squire	O
Bourke	O
,	O
an	O
Irishman	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
relation	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
five	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Ireland	O
to	O
Bath	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Ware	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
above	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
booted	O
and	O
spurred	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
boots	O
and	O
spurs	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
rode	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
horse	O
from	O
Ware	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
shilling	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
key	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
clothes	O
chest	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
his	O
apartment	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
loaded	O
pistol	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
friends	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
laced	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
colcxel	O
's	O
property	O
by	O
Haselby	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
laced	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Haselby	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
silver-hilted	O
sword	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
coat	O
I	O
stopped	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Haselby	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
wages	O
raised	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
96	O
,	O
97	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
twelve	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Letterman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
.	O
||	O
Anne	B-pers
Letterman	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
Charles	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	B-place
in	I-place
Red-lion-street	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
sign	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
White-lion	I-place
:	O
last	O
Saturday	O
fortnight	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
talking	O
to	O
them	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
person	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
red	O
barrel	O
box	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Christmas-box	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
going	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
stood	O
talking	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
how	O
near	O
to	O
them	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
Letterman	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
maid	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
;	O
at	O
my	O
coming	O
in	O
White	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
brandy	O
hot	O
,	O
but	O
Merchant	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
liquor	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
9	O
l.	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
money	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
A.	O
Letterman	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
twelve	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
whole	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
box	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
among	O
the	O
silver	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
six-pence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
loss	O
;	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
half	O
six-pence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
rags	O
they	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
)	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
dressed	O
out	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
use	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
A.	O
Letterman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
Merchant	O
proffered	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
pay	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
her	O
new	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
stand	O
the	O
chance	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Letterman	O
;	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
butcher	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
brandy	O
hot	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopenny	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
an	O
egg	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
change	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
once	O
apiece	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
White	O
immediately	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
with	O
about	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
look	O
about	O
;	O
then	O
Merchant	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
walked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
about	O
half	O
the	O
brandy	O
hot	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
we	O
suspected	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
different	O
clothes	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
out	O
from	O
four	O
other	O
young	O
women	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
all	O
strangers	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
Anne	B-pers
White	I-pers
said	O
,	O
Merchant	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
pocket	O
for	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Merchant	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Mills	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
.	O
Merchant	O
said	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
hang	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
our	O
tap-room	O
Merchant	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
mistress	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
her	O
clothes	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
from	O
eight	O
till	O
two	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
going	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
proffered	O
give	O
us	O
the	O
clothes	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
.	O
A.	O
Letterman	O
.	O
White	O
would	O
have	O
delivered	O
her	O
clothes	O
up	O
with	O
all	O
her	O
heart	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
fortnight	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
clothes	O
shop	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Letterman	O
's	O
?	O
E.	O
Haines	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
distant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
sold	O
gowns	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
each	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
an	O
upper	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
aprons	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
ragged	O
clothes	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
looked	O
very	O
smart	O
about	O
their	O
heads	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
got-each	O
a	O
new	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
coloured	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
lay	O
out	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
to	O
about	O
6	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
E.	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
girls	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
such	O
often	O
come	O
to	O
clothe	O
themselves	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
spark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
money	O
did	O
they	O
pay	O
you	O
with	O
?	O
E.	O
Haines	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
separate	O
as	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
two	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Christmas-box	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Letterman	O
has	O
described	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
her	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
housewife	O
;	O
White	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
sixpence	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
dropped	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
just	O
before	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fling	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
go	O
among	O
old	O
silver	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Letterman	O
has	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
let	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
half	O
sixpence	O
.	O
White	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
her	O
fellow	O
prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
brandy	O
hot	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
stocking	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
kicked	O
a	O
box	O
before	O
me	O
with	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
.	O
Merchant	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
two	O
girls	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
White	O
find	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
,	O
halves	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
98	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Cluse	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
guines	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Rolls	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
journeymen	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
play	O
with	O
a	O
female	O
acquaintance	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
punch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
to	O
regale	O
ourselves	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
sisters	O
;	O
they	O
lived	O
separate	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
friends	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
in	O
service	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
we	O
being	O
loth	O
to	O
disturb	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
sister	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
near	O
Bow-church	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
return	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
go	O
very	O
well	O
by	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
either	O
from	O
the	O
Old	O
'Change	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
;	O
her	O
reply	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
r	O
-	O
er	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
an	O
immediate	O
reply	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
still	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
prevail	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
,	O
she	O
dragged	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
passage	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-house	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
followed	O
behind	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
petticoats	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
unbuttoning	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
my	O
hands	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
she	O
had	O
completed	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
only	O
unbottoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
pocket	O
also	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
;	O
she	O
presently	O
pushed	O
me	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
comes	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
run	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
run	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
ran	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
into	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
I	O
stared	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
tucked	O
my	O
watch-chain	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
into	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
by	O
the	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
into	O
Pater-noster-row	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
by	O
accident	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
these	O
women	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
and	O
catched	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
searched	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Flower	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
women	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
run	O
,	O
run	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Flower	O
came	O
up	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
lend	O
me	O
assistance	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
by	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
rather	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
no	O
man	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Flower	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-house	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
money	O
found	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
somebody	O
to	O
search	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
into	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
turning	O
down	O
into	O
Pater-noster-row	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
three	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
that	O
gentleman	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
you	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
me	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
rude	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
any	O
ill	O
,	O
charge	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
searched	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
us	O
searched	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Might	O
you	O
not	O
lose	O
your	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
situation	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Flower	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
watchmen	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
money	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Flower	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
elevated	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
99	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wardle	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wardle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Cheapside	O
towards	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
I	O
felt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
draw	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
)	O
Immediately	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
concourse	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
Wardle	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
hold	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Montague	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
mob	O
gathered	O
about	O
,	O
some	O
wanted	O
to	O
duck	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
porters	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
my	O
pockets	O
inside	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carver	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Molney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
marked	O
No	O
.	O
428.	O
dated	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
19	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Deptford-bridge	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Biles	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
Peter	O
Molney	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
's	O
footman	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
the	O
date	O
,	O
and	O
name	O
to	O
whom	O
payable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
James	O
.	O
who	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
transactions	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
our	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
describing	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Biles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Bryant	O
and	O
Mason	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
bank-note	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
No	O
.	O
428	O
.	O
Nov.	O
12	O
,	O
1766	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rossy	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Co.	O
signed	O
Charles	B-pers
Iveson	I-pers
,	O
entered	O
S.	O
Gore	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
paper	O
and	O
note	O
in	O
it	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
undressing	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
paper	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
signed	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
30	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
that	O
note	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
over	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
passed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
number	O
and	O
other	O
remarks	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
tavern	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
after	O
dinner	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
for	O
66	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
banker	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
for	O
it	O
two	O
80	O
l.	O
notes	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Bryant	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
who	O
described	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
corresponded	O
with	O
that	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
indicted	O
for	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Balchard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
'Squire	O
Bryant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
.	O
One	O
morning	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ws	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
clothes	O
to	O
brush	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brushing	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
some	O
papers	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
tols	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
character	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
his	O
late	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
papers	O
were	O
two	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
certainly	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
filled	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
doubled	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
master	O
's	O
pocket	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
clothes	O
away	O
without	O
master	O
giving	O
him	O
warning	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Down	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rossy	O
;	O
Mr.	O
James	O
brought	O
a	O
draft	O
for	O
66	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
change	O
for	O
it	O
two	O
30	O
l.	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
No	O
.	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
was	O
428	O
,	O
dated	O
Nov.	O
12	O
,	O
1766	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rossy	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Co.	O
(	O
he	O
takes	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
question	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
master	O
from	O
'Change	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
paper	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
little	O
bill	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
kitchen-table	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
book	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
101.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
and	O
worsted	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
window-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
teakettle	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
wrong	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
102	O
,	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Biddy	I-pers
,	I-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
May-pole	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
beer	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
Biddy	O
King	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
;	O
then	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
almost	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
trust	O
you	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
you	O
come	O
this	O
road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
North	O
Briton	O
,	O
a	O
sea-faring	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
their	O
lodging	O
in	O
Black-horse-yard	B-place
;	O
Wall	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
candle	O
burning	O
;	O
King	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
bed	O
we	O
are	O
to	O
lye	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
stripped	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
leaned	O
over	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
bed-cloaths	O
up	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
King	O
got	O
up	O
from	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
buckles	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
put	O
them	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
buckles	O
from	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
silver	O
,	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
30	O
s.	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
then	O
Biddy	O
King	O
wanted	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
Elizabeth	O
Wall	O
desired	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
deliver	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Wall	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
Biddy	O
King	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
keep	O
till	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
true	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
my	O
rounds	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
soon	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
King	O
desired	O
Wall	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
Wall	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
watchman	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
buckles	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Biddy	O
King	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Lucas	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Biddy	O
King	O
and	O
Wall	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
of	O
his	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
soon	O
taken	O
after	O
that	O
:	O
Wall	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
King	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
the	O
man	O
his	O
buckles	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
Wall	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
?	O
Sibley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
King	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
two	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
board	O
such	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
looked	O
like	O
an	O
old	O
shipmate	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Wheelwrights-arms	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Elizabeth	O
Wall	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
us	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve-buttons	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
farthings	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
night	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
pay	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
money	O
's	O
worth	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
his	O
buckles	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
damages	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Wapping	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
morning	O
:	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
Wall	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Wall	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
these	O
buckle	O
,	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
agreeable	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dry	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
one	O
petticoat	O
and	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
pin	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
here	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
taken	O
my	O
buckles	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
Wall	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
his	O
buckles	O
directly	O
.	O
Wall	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
wished	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
round	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
more	O
proper	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
wrapped	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
coming	O
into	O
Biddy	O
King	O
's	O
room	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
night	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
words	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
save	O
myself	O
from	O
blows	O
;	O
Wall	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
and	O
some	O
gin	O
:	O
he	O
after	O
that	O
took	O
his	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Bet	O
Wall	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
King	O
it	O
to	O
put	O
about	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
her	O
warm	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sleeves	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
liquor	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Wall	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
clerk	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
No	O
484	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	O
Stephenson	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Adams	O
,	O
No	O
65	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Nelson	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
To	O
correct	O
a	O
mistake	O
in	O
No	O
1	O
,	O
of	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
page	O
3	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
E.	O
Wall	O
,	O
read	O
,	O
of	O
E.	O
Adams	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
word	O
,	O
read	O
,	O
tried	O
.	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
in	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
four	O
gold	O
rings	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
pepper-boxes	O
,	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
buttons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
10	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
diamond	O
stay-hook	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
medals	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
enameled	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
||	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
divers	O
sorts	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six-and-thirty	O
months	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
:	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
somebody	O
that	O
knew	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
stay-hook	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Humphreys	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
West-street	O
,	O
Seven-dials	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
spectacles	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
fresh-coloured	O
girl	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
get-into	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
must	O
conceal	O
herself	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
fifteen	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
character	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
West-street	O
,	O
Seven-dials	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
stay-hook	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
five	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
observing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
cost	O
her	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
swore	O
a	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
character	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
character	O
he	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
stay-hook	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
shewed	O
her	O
one	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
's	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
H.	O
Ward	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
stay-hook	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
4	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
Berkhamstead	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Bibby	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Bedford-street	O
,	O
Bedford-row	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
silver	O
pepper-castor	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
1	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
in	O
Baldwin's-gardens	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
she	O
made	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
cause	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
notices	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
about	O
them	O
?	O
Arthur	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
H.	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
every	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
produced	O
them	O
.	O
Arthur	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
thirty-two	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	B-pers
that	O
evening	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
concealed	O
herself	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
without	O
her	O
consent	O
did	O
embezzle	O
and	O
convert	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
said	O
mistress	O
,	O
safely	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
her	O
use	O
,	O
December	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
house-keeper	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
maiden	O
lady	O
,	O
in	O
Chandois-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
butler	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
the	O
salver	O
in	O
question	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
lady	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
twenty-one	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
waiter	O
was	O
missed	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
day	O
also	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
concerned	O
in	O
liquor	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
company	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
public-house	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
light	O
them	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
lady	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
company	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
came	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
keys	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
street-door	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
really	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
salver	O
or	O
waiter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
waiter	O
till	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behaved	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
your	O
lady	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
time	O
very	O
regular	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
had	O
one	O
that	O
kept	O
his	O
time	O
so	O
regular	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
servant	O
that	O
behaved	O
better	O
,	O
nor	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
affair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
plate	O
being	O
lost	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
employed	O
that	O
afternoon	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
He	O
waited	O
at	O
tea	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
missing	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
waiting	O
at	O
tea	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
tea	O
last	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
May	O
be	O
it	O
lasted	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
concealed	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
up	O
,	O
paying	O
his	O
reckoning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
inches	O
diameter	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
E	O
Terry	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
lady	O
's	O
waiter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
livery	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
sometimes	O
he	O
wears	O
a	O
frock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
livery	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
change	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
fixed	O
any	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
lady	O
,	O
named	O
Pickering	O
,	O
died	O
in	O
George-street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
by	O
will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
livery	O
or	O
in	O
a	O
frock	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
frock	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
waiter	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
apprentice	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pickering	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
,	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
such	O
things	O
left	O
the	O
servants	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
money	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
keys	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
houses	O
distant	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Pickering	O
?	O
E.	O
Terry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Aspley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
bring	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
plate	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
now	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
universally	O
good	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
mistress	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
salver	O
worth	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Parker	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Carlisle	O
;	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
speak	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
spoke	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
good	O
servant	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
woollen-draper	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Vaughan	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
there	O
;	O
his	O
mistress	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
behaved	O
so	O
well	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
think	O
of	O
getting	O
a	O
better	O
place	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
thinking	O
her	O
place	O
not	O
good	O
enough	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lun	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Welbeck-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
well	O
behaved	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
and	O
better	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Bishop	O
of	O
Carlisle	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
translated	O
to	O
the	O
see	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cholmondeley	O
's	O
butler	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
universal	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Welbeck-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
frequently	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
106.	O
James	B-pers
Reene	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
an	O
inland	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
with	O
a	O
forged	O
acceptance	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Anne	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
This	O
appeared	O
rather	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Without	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Neptune	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Burage	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
Catharine	B-pers
Burage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
Abraham	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
shirt	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burage	I-pers
to	O
wash	O
on	O
Twelfth-day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
since	O
in	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
Frank	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
shirt	O
in	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
named	O
Sarah	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
C.	O
Burage	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
shirt	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burage	I-pers
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Burage	I-pers
delivered	O
me	O
this	O
shirt	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
washed	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
ironed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
E.	O
Burage	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
sister-in-law	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
place	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
;	O
she	O
absconded	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
three	O
nights	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
Catharine-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shift	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rochfort	O
's	O
.	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shift	O
in	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
(	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burage	I-pers
my	O
gown	O
and	O
shift	O
to	O
wash.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
S.	O
Mercer	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
shift	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
108.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
and	O
worsted	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
worsted	O
piece	O
for	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
109	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
brass	O
ferrels	O
for	O
angling-rods	O
,	O
four	O
cocoa-nut	O
heads	O
for	O
canes	O
,	O
four	O
brass	O
screw	O
ferrels	O
,	O
four	O
bamboo	O
canes	O
,	O
one	O
walking-cane	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
metal	O
heads	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Emory	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Emory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fishing-rod	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
two	O
months	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
journeyman	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
sheet-brass	O
to	O
make	O
ferrels	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
brass	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
more	O
ferrels	O
than	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
quantity	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
at	O
least	O
sixteen	O
dozen	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
finished	O
the	O
brass	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
made	O
but	O
eleven	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
fully	O
convinced	O
he	O
had	O
wronged	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
but	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
counted	O
a	O
drawer	O
of	O
nut	O
heads	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
drawer	O
of	O
screw	O
ferrels	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apprentice	O
counted	O
them	O
likewise	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
work-shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
below	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
work-shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
drawers	O
carried	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
deficient	O
four	O
nut	O
heads	O
and	O
eight	O
screw	O
ferrels	O
;	O
I	O
contrived	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
all	O
day	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
must	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
early	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
and	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
ale	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
an	O
officer	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
nut	O
heads	O
and	O
screw	O
ferrels	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
tremble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
you	O
marked	O
them	O
?	O
Emory	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
pencil	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
at	O
separate	O
times	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
heads	O
and	O
four	O
ferrels	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
key	O
of	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
mine	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
landlord	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
four	O
bamboo	O
canes	O
and	O
a	O
walking-cane	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
