TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
of	O
JUNE	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
SIR	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
KNT	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
KITE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YATES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blakesley	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Graffley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ringwood	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Langthorne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bamford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grape	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Portall	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
C	B-pers
Dollinson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Crace	I-pers
,	O
Adam	B-pers
Dunkley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Marriott	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Turing	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dimes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hooke	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
.	O
277	O
,	O
278	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
edging	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Leny	I-pers
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Leny	I-pers
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Leny	I-pers
is	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
lace	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Round-court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
Saunders	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
new	O
customer	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
look	O
sharp	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
valuable	O
lace	O
lying	O
on	O
one	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
another	O
counter	O
where	O
the	O
black	O
lace	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
lace	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
Saunders	O
bought	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
lace	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
Saunders	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
apron	O
off	O
,	O
fearing	O
the	O
lace	O
should	O
stick	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
let	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
counter	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
lace	O
at	O
that	O
counter	O
before	O
.	O
Gibbons	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
several	O
pieces	O
;	O
Saunders	O
called	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
Myner	O
;	O
Saunders	O
turned	O
her	O
head	O
round	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
lace	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
such	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
other	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
looking	O
towards	O
Gibbons	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
in	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
bosom	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doubles	O
hung	O
out	O
under	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
edging	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
behind	O
her	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
swore	O
many	O
oaths	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
insolent	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
trying	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
edging	O
drop	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
Saunders	O
saw	O
me	O
both	O
take	O
the	O
lace	O
from	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
edging	O
up	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
stood	O
up	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
she	O
would	O
ruin	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
depart	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
people	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
continued	O
using	O
me	O
ill	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
girl	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
one	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
Saunders	O
sent	O
Gibbons	O
out	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
ruin	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
neighbour	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
(	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
that	O
which	O
fell	O
behind	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
,	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
in	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Saunders	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
this	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
Gibbons	O
)	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
country	O
,	O
(	O
Ireland	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
for	O
some	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
quarter	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
keep	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
shop	O
;	O
what	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
says	O
is	O
false	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
recommend	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
six	O
weeks	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
I	O
may	O
never	O
be	O
delivered	O
,	O
or	O
see	O
my	O
other	O
children	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
mentioned	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
clean	O
lawn	O
apron	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
buckle	O
had	O
torn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
quarter	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
running	O
worm	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
wait	O
a	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
dispatch	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
taking	O
up	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
put	O
your	O
apron	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
quarter	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
never	O
mentioned	O
the	O
wanting	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
lace	O
till	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
buy	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
cap	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
;	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
above	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
thread	O
her	O
needle	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
sighted	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
lace	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
catched	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
your	O
bosom	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
very	O
high	O
words	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
cursed	O
our	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
country	O
might	O
ever	O
come	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
maid	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wished	O
somebody	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
she	O
insisted	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
begged	O
somebody	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
her	O
child	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
insisted	O
on	O
taking	O
us	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
us	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
brother	O
keeps	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
shop	O
over	O
against	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
object	O
to	O
going	O
there	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Saunders	O
from	O
the	O
year	O
1757	O
,	O
in	O
Galway	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
serjeant	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
have	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
attends	O
an	O
auction	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
child	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Saunders	O
's	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
this	O
shop	O
into	O
Round	O
court	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Polly	O
,	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
for	O
your	O
child	O
to	O
go	O
round	O
her	O
cap	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
cheaper	O
than	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
above	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
that	O
lace	O
;	O
Mrs	O
Saunders	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
people	O
come	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
look	O
at	O
things	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
buy	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
custom	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
both	O
go	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
call	O
somebody	O
in	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
meddle	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
279	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
:	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hempen	O
cable	O
rope	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
hempen	O
sling	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Tatton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
stone	O
merchants	O
on	O
Mill	B-place
bank	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
morning	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
shift	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
within	O
the	O
reach	O
of	O
the	O
crane	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
stones	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
barge	O
's	O
cabin	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
a	O
corn	O
barge	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boat	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
barge	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
it	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
rope	O
lying	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
from	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
ropes	O
than	O
ours	O
of	O
other	O
peoples	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
old	O
rope	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
in	O
a	O
lighter	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
they	O
were	O
wet	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
lately	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
boat	O
and	O
rope	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
through	O
our	O
yard	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
barge	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
cable	O
was	O
loosened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
was	O
fresh	O
cut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
cable	O
?	O
Tatton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
boat	O
that	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
barge	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
many	O
pieces	O
of	O
rope	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sling	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Fletcher	O
and	O
Arnold	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
rope	O
we	O
use	O
to	O
put	O
about	O
a	O
block	O
of	O
stone	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
move	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
crane	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Miller	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
wharf	O
where	O
the	O
sling	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
neither	O
had	O
I	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
wharf	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
boat	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
280	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hans	B-pers
Knutson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
scum	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Spalding	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mark	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
;	O
one	O
thickset	O
frock	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
nankeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
3	O
linen	O
stocks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Ulmore	I-pers
;	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Conrode	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Ecliars	I-pers
;	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freemouse	I-pers
;	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Albatch	I-pers
;	O
a	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sugar-refiner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Mansfield	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
.	O
James	B-pers
Spalding	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
are	O
partners	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Dane	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
our	O
servant	O
from	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
to	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
lost	O
their	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
our	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
over	O
Tower	O
hill	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
men	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
their	O
cloaths	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Ulmore	O
told	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
following	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
going	O
to	O
Norway	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
called	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Bockman	O
or	O
Beckman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
assistance	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
proceed	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
Ulmore	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
ship	O
had	O
failed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
boat	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Hope	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
deck	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
captain	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
the	O
thief	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
if	O
we	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
him	O
on	O
shore	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
heart	O
;	O
the	O
captain	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Ulmore	I-pers
looked	O
at	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
captain	O
ordered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
chest	O
and	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
done	O
up	O
into	O
our	O
scum	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
our	O
boat	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
cry	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
his	O
box	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
particularize	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
this	O
brass	O
tobacco-box	O
there	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
fastened	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
left	O
that	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Gravesend	O
boat	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
understanding	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
or	O
change	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
C	O
C.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Downing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
thing	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
sugar-oue	O
window	O
was	O
sawed	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
opened	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
our	O
bed	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
all	O
lay	O
,	O
seven	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
by	O
getting	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
they	O
oculdtasily	O
come	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
not	O
being	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
(	O
mentioning	O
there	O
by	O
name	O
;	O
)	O
we	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
then	O
all	O
our	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
were	O
gone	O
by	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Downing	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
this	O
watch	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Downing	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
281.	O
Henry	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
armed	O
with	O
offensive	O
weapons	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
assembled	O
together	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
assisting	O
in	O
running	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Jan.	O
9	O
,	O
1762	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
produced	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
282	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Doleman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Evan	O
,	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Evan	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
that	O
lay	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
two	O
doors	O
below	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
window	O
and	O
break	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
slapped	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
hardly	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
passage	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Richardson	B-pers
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
E.	I-pers
I	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
upon	O
he	O
ran	O
in	O
,	O
glaletly	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
this	O
little	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
m	O
that	O
passage	O
,	O
a	O
poit	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
but	O
little	O
resistance	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
pushed	O
against	O
he	O
window	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
his	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
pushed	O
through	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
account	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bric	O
layer	O
's	O
Arms	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
blood	O
on	O
his	O
neckcloth	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
that	O
came	O
;	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
was	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
finger	O
was	O
fresh	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
push	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
scratch	O
of	O
a	O
pin	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
there	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
clerk	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
luck	O
to	O
escape	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
the	O
next	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
cast	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
this	O
;	O
the	O
clerk	O
said	O
,	O
search	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
got	O
a	O
Holland	O
doit	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
finest	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
glass	O
window	O
break	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
run	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
asked	O
if	O
any	O
stockings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
No	O
250	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Nelson	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
and	O
No	O
274	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
hand-whips	O
.	O
283	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
sixteen	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Lowle	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Lowle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
dishes	O
and	O
plates	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
detected	O
her	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Lea	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Caleb	B-pers
Lea	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
My	O
gold	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
it	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
gold	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
Baldwin's-gardens	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
returned	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
satisfy	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
journeyman	O
baker	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
watch	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Baldwin's-gardens	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
she	O
had	O
mentioned	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
journeyman	O
baker	O
was	O
named	O
Delmey	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
lived	O
in	O
Moor-lane	O
;	O
we	O
enquired	O
all	O
over	O
Moor-lane	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
an	O
owner	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Little	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
baker	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
284	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
gridiron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
hanging	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Gerard	B-pers
Vandergucht	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Gerard	B-pers
Vandergucht	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-bone	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
gridiron	O
and	O
hanging	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
immediately	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
having	O
missed	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
a	O
brazier	O
in	O
Mary-le-bone	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
up	O
as	O
old	O
metal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
me	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
twenty-five	O
years	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
but	O
sixteen	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
when	O
taken	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
together	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Spinnage	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
which	O
had	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
gridiron	O
and	O
hanging	O
iron	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
than	O
the	O
honourable	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
Justice	O
Spinnage	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
three	O
articles	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
285	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
pictures	O
on	O
paper	O
,	O
with	O
wooden	O
frames	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
fender	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
poker	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
tongs	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
ivory-handled	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Grindal	I-pers
,	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Grindal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
servants	O
acquainted	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
things	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Small	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Vine-court	O
,	O
Moor-lane	O
,	O
Fore-street	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
lodging	O
we	O
found	O
four	O
of	O
my	O
prints	O
,	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
eight	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
particular	O
frames	O
,	O
and	O
glazed	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
new	O
house	O
in	O
Moor-lane	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
regain	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
only	O
the	O
copper	O
pottage	O
pot	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Cook's-court	O
,	O
Grub-street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
iron	O
sender	O
,	O
poker	O
,	O
tongs	O
,	O
twelve	O
prints	O
,	O
five	O
ivory-handled	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
laid	O
the	O
twentieth	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
found	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
except	O
the	O
copper	O
pottage	O
pot	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
pictures	O
,	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
and	O
sender	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
twelve	O
prints	O
,	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
in	O
Grub-Street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
her	O
master	O
,	O
never	O
kept	O
a	O
proper	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
goods	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Donovan	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Susanna	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
James	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
sweet-heart	O
,	O
Small	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
286	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wallford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Mrs.	O
Bacon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
Holbourn-hill	B-place
,	I-place
opposite	I-place
Hatton-garden	I-place
;	O
we	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
our	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
of	O
having	O
done	O
something	O
wrong	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
observation	O
on	O
what	O
passed	O
;	O
the	O
counting-house	O
is	O
parted	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
always	O
kept	O
;	O
we	O
can	O
see	O
from	O
the	O
counting-house	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
passes	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
view	O
round	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
chair	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
through	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
off	O
from	O
an	O
iron	O
bracket	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
unlocked	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
rattle	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
sum	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
large	O
cannister	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
filled	O
a	O
large	O
paper	O
bag	O
with	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
replaced	O
the	O
cannister	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
placed	O
the	O
chair	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
the	O
key	O
on	O
the	O
bracket	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
tea	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chair	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
entry	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
spring	O
lock	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
there	O
came	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
named	O
Lyes	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
enquired	O
whether	O
Mr.	O
Bacon	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
rather	O
willing	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
pretty	O
near	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
maid-servant	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
home	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
release	O
the	O
porter	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
paper	O
bag	O
of	O
tea	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
paper	O
bag	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
bag	O
he	O
had	O
filled	O
with	O
tea	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
maid	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Bacon	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bacon	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
counting-house	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
we	O
had	O
such	O
positive	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
about	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
an	O
ounce	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
eight	O
pounds	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
tea	O
are	O
here	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Bacon	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
free	O
and	O
open	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Strekon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
acknowledge	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
His	O
master	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
tea	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
tea	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
his	O
master	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
?	O
Strekon	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
promise	O
made	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
to	O
receive	O
favour	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bacon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
own	O
to	O
nothing	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
about	O
six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
bare	O
weight	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
made	O
him	O
?	O
Gurney	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
ingenuous	O
confession	O
,	O
very	O
likely	O
his	O
master	O
might	O
favour	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
only	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
witnesses	O
here	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
my	O
behalf	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
subpoened	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Bacon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
made	O
him	O
?	O
S.	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
promise	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Gurney	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wallford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
287	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Vicars	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bush-lane	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
in	O
my	O
employ	O
till	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
that	O
afternoon	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
produced	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
old	O
cocks	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
mark	O
of	O
the	O
goodness	O
of	O
the	O
solder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
bag	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
evening	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
men	O
their	O
wages	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
before	O
broken	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
compleat	O
piece	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
about	O
forty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
business	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
solder	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
into	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
concealed	O
it	O
among	O
some	O
rubbish	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
.	O
in	O
Bush-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
leave	O
to	O
leave	O
an	O
empty	O
bag	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
solder	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
towards	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
more	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
abide	O
there	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
house	O
is	O
about	O
250	O
or	O
300	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Puley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Paterson	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Paterson	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
his	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
best	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
old	O
brass	O
cocks	O
and	O
some	O
solder	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
till	O
his	O
men	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
paid	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
seen	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
40	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
solder	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
old	O
brass	O
cocks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
solder	O
there	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
joint	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
paid	O
me	O
my	O
wages	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
solder	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Gamson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
288	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
May	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
are	O
partners	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
Manchester	O
warehouse	O
in	O
King	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
night	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
we	O
sold	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
delivered	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
parcel	O
was	O
missed	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
;	O
the	O
piece	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
that	O
very	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
cut	O
off	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
oil	O
and	O
lemons	O
about	O
;	O
Daniel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
last	O
Friday	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
velvet	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
head	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alesounder	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
this	O
velvet	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
agreeable	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
was	O
offered	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
that	O
for	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Alesounder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
velvet	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Moses	O
,	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blaney	O
,	O
a	O
puolican	O
.	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
damaged	O
goods	O
by	O
the	O
colour	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
bill	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
velvet	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
Moses	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
publican	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
woman	O
have	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
information	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
his	O
word	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
appearing	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Alesounder	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
velvet	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
employs	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
any	O
goods	O
are	O
out	O
of	O
date	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
Mr.	O
Blaney	O
was	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alesounder	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
velvet	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Blaney	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blaney	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
buying	O
the	O
velvet	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
account	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
partner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
velvet	O
taken	O
off	O
our	O
counter	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Archey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
velvet	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
velvet	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
trouble	O
my	O
self	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
velvet	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
289	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Hammet	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Francis	B-pers
Hammet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Hammet	O
,	O
a	O
fellow	O
has	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
fellow	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
last	O
I	O
passed	O
Captain	O
Hammet	B-pers
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
lads	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
draw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
convey	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
seing	O
me	O
observe	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
captain	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
the	O
captain	O
owned	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nigh	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
290	O
,	O
291.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
live	O
eels	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
boat	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
kept	O
for	O
preserving	O
of	O
fish	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
fish	O
by	O
commission	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
of	O
Ely	O
;	O
he	O
sends	O
me	O
up	O
eels	O
,	O
pike	O
,	O
and	O
perch	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
by	B-place
London-bridge	I-place
water-works	I-place
;	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
well-boat	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
year	O
round	O
,	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
store-boat	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
wells	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
lies	O
always	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
locked	O
down	O
with	O
great	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
any	O
gentlemen	O
or	O
fishmonger	O
want	O
any	O
fish	O
,	O
we	O
supply	O
them	O
;	O
sometimes	O
we	O
have	O
two	O
thousand	O
weight	O
of	O
eels	O
,	O
sometimes	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
hundred	O
jacks	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
demand	O
in	O
London	O
I	O
send	O
word	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
send	O
up	O
what	O
is	O
wanted	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
great	O
chain	O
she	O
was	O
fastened	O
to	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
Black-friars	O
bridge	O
,	O
with	O
every	O
well	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
what	O
eels	O
were	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
boat	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
four	O
well	O
hinges	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
staples	O
drawn	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
fish	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
every	O
well	O
;	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
130	O
pounds	O
of	O
eels	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
fish	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
from	O
morning	O
till	O
dinner	O
time	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
clerk	O
what	O
method	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
people	O
out	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
named	O
Elliot	O
,	O
in	O
White-street	O
,	O
should	O
say	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
eels	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Harris	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
told	O
their	O
names	O
were	O
Harris	O
and	O
Saunders	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
Harris	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
passed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
White-street	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
Harris	O
on	O
St.	O
Margaret's-hill	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
he	O
openly	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
filed	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
while	O
Saunders	O
towed	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
eels	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
goal	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
Saunders	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
;	O
Saunders	O
confessed	O
he	O
helped	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
wells	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
eels	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
they	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
they	O
gave	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
they	O
eat	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Falcon	O
in	O
White-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
full	O
of	O
eels	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Dutch	O
eels	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
river	O
eels	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
caught	O
them	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
foul	O
on	O
some	O
Dutch	O
boat	O
's	O
stern	O
and	O
cut	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
one	O
for	O
my	O
breakfast	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
eat	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Fenn	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
they	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Falcon	O
in	O
White-street	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
up	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
catch	O
flounders	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
that	O
Saturday	O
night	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
five	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
basket	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
very	O
heavy	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
eels	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fenn	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Harris	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
and	O
Saunders	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
eels	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
well-boat	O
,	O
and	O
towed	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
Black-friars	O
bridge	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
watermen	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
with	O
whom	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
Saunders	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fenn	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
Harris	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fenn	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
between	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
well-boat	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
moorings	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
her	O
wells	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
hinges	O
were	O
ripped	O
from	O
the	O
well	O
heads	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eels	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
by	O
who	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
just	O
above	O
Black-friars	O
bridge	O
,	O
hauled	O
in	O
between	O
two	O
lighters	O
and	O
made	O
fast	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Harris	O
say	O
he	O
filed	O
the	O
lock	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
bulk	O
head	O
,	O
while	O
Saunders	O
towed	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Harris	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
eels	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
salt	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
to	O
buy	O
fish	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Saunders	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Harris	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Nathanael	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Feltham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Heychurch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
292	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phineas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Naphtali	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
Meyers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Naphtali	O
Hart	O
Meyers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
sexton	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
synagogue	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
silver	O
cup	O
and	O
silver	O
castor	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
are	O
the	O
wardens	O
of	O
that	O
synagogue	O
;	O
the	O
cup	O
and	O
castor	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
the	O
synagogue	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
used	O
in	O
certain	O
benedictions	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
wardens	O
being	O
chosen	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
the	O
vestments	O
and	O
things	O
given	O
them	O
from	O
warden	O
to	O
warden	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Franks	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
custody	O
and	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
synagogue	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
sexton	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
private	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
about	O
the	O
districts	O
of	O
Duke's-place	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
all	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
and	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
describe	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
we	O
may	O
sooner	O
come	O
at	O
a	O
discovery	O
;	O
accordingly	O
we	O
let	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
and	O
old	O
cloaths	O
people	O
know	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
informed	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
a	O
broken	O
silver	O
cup	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
on	O
paper	O
a	O
sketch	O
of	O
the	O
foot	O
(	O
the	O
paper	O
and	O
cup	O
produced	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
exchange	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
Jew	O
barber	O
's	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
blinks	O
with	O
his	O
eyes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
sexton	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Jew	O
barber	O
's	O
boy	O
;	O
the	O
sexton	O
soon	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
peace	O
officer	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
lad	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
mercy	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
directly	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
castor	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
;	O
the	O
peace	O
officer	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
castor	O
in	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
cup	O
,	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
call	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
among	O
the	O
Jews	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
synagogue	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
gave	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Mark	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Myers	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
synagogue	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
ruins	O
in	O
Bear	O
Jury-lane	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
building	O
new	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
castor	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
the	O
rubbish	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
delivered	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
run	O
away	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
293	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Martha	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pierce	O
in	O
Duck-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
apron	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
hung	O
behind	O
the	O
entry	O
door	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
betwixt	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
lad	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
that	O
and	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
leaned	O
over	O
the	O
ballusters	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
the	O
apron	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
our	O
entry	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
tea	O
with	O
my	O
spouse	O
;	O
my	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
behind	O
them	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
rapped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
of	O
mine	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hands	O
behind	O
him	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
shifted	O
the	O
apron	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
his	O
left-hand	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shifted	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
left-hand	O
by	O
putting	O
that	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
temple	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
another	O
blow	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
down	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
it	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
immediately	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
strike	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
strike	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
raised	O
a	O
mob	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
stole	O
an	O
apron	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
till	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Anne	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
his	O
own	O
sister	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Preslow	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Maden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
6	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Currey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
M'Grath	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Deborah	O
,	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Jane	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
is	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Hanway-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
just	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
she	O
denied	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
ran	O
away	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
again	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sharpless	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
questioned	O
the	O
prisosoner	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
theft	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
it	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
an	O
untruth	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Mrs.	O
Kelly	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
gateway	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
something	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
between	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
her	O
back	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Sharpless	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
on	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
something	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
striped	O
borders	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
dropped	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
by	O
who	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Sharpless	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sharpless	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Sharpless	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
striped	O
borders	O
kenting	O
,	O
folded	O
up	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
paper	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
met	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
a	O
market	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
hiring	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
Court-road	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
touched	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
dropped	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
woman	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
coming	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
she	O
called	O
Eliz	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
of	O
Paul's-wharf	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
of	O
Long	O
lane	O
16	O
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Sheridan	I-pers
of	O
Poppin's-alley	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gambling	I-pers
three	O
or	O
four	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
worked	O
hard	O
in	O
selling	O
fruit	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
295	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Helingford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
cocks	O
,	O
weight	O
60	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Yandle	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Matthew	B-pers
Yandle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
place	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
,	O
a	O
printing-shop	O
and	O
dye-house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Wandsworth	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
keys	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brickinshire	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
somebody	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
dye-house	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
coppers	O
and	O
cocks	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
coppers	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
as	O
old	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cocks	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brickinshire	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
brickmaker	O
;	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
paying	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
Denham	O
that	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
men	O
cutting	O
the	O
coppers	O
with	O
a	O
hatchet	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
catch	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
are	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
round	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bird's-nesting	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
;	O
there	O
Denham	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
all	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Gregory	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Denham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
dye-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
halloo	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Brickinshire	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
away	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
we	O
knocked	O
the	O
cocks	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dye-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Gregory	O
did	O
it	O
all	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
good	O
load	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
copper	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
knocking	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
save	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
will	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
140	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Yandle	I-pers
,	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
brick	O
building	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Matthew	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
This	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
lead	O
that	O
was	O
placed	O
round	O
the	O
coppers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
296	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Morehane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bouvilla	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Bouvilla	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	B-place
Bond-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
over	O
night	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
safe	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cupboard	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
kitchen-door	O
the	O
hinges	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
this	O
opens	O
to	O
the	O
stair-case	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
nothing	O
broke	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
imagine	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
by	O
opening	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
bolted	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
on	O
the	O
spring-lock	O
,	O
unbolted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
advertised	O
;	O
Martha	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
brought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
there	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
cream	O
pot	O
and	O
some	O
stockings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
cream	O
pot	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
as	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
take	O
this	O
hat	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Bouvilla	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Oliver	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
heat	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Bouvilla	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Pancras	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
cream	O
pot	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
pot	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
bundle	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
lady	O
would	O
be	O
extremely	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
opening	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cream-pot	O
and	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
smallest	O
pair	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
one	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Salt-hill	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
away	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
two	O
pair	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
cream-pot	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
cream-pot	O
advertised	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
as	O
other	O
people	O
do	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
My	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
inn	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
4th	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Halliburton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
this	O
hat	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Richards	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
be	O
merciful	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
six	O
china	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
china	O
bowl	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Hollings	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
lives	O
at	O
Isleworth	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bouvilla	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
service	O
before	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
down	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
window	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
Hollings	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sometime	O
near	O
dinner-time	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
desert	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
china	O
dishes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
china	O
punch-bowl	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
parlour	O
was	O
not	O
used	O
in	O
common	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
storeroom	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steps	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
bolted	O
over-night	O
?	O
Hollings	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fastening	O
to	O
the	O
sash	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
patterns	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
's	O
coachman	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
parlour	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
great	O
coats	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
over	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
coach-house	O
;	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
not	O
fast	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
china	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
this	O
looks	O
like	O
the	O
same	O
china	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Halliburton	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
waiting	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Richards	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
china	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
two	O
coats	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
china	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
surtout	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
men	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
edged	O
with	O
silver	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
;	O
one	O
other	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shirt	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
dresser	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
ladder	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
stood	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
cistern	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
above	O
the	O
cistern	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
foot	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
ladder	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
hat	O
from	O
the	O
room	O
over	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
sash	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
cistern	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
coats	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
servants	O
coats	O
,	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
most	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
she	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
Isleworth	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
silver-laced	O
hats	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
no	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
candle	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
about	O
half	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
out	O
hand	O
bills	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
advertised	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
cloaths	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
two	O
livery	O
coats	O
and	O
three	O
hats	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
cloaths	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
mention	O
that	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Oliver	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
chair	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
from	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
a	O
pound	O
or	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
butter	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
candle	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
lighted	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
door	O
had	O
been	O
unbolted	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
from	O
that	O
yard	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
ladder	O
stand	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
cloaths	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
that	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
then	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
table	O
linen	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
over	O
night	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
we	O
carried	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
bits	O
of	O
candle	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
neither	O
candle	O
nor	O
candlestick	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
what	O
we	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
whole	O
candle	O
burnt	O
half	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
that	O
kitchen	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
windows	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
shutters	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tunbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
On	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
two	O
bundles	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
livery	O
cloaths	O
were	O
hanging	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
may	O
be	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
suit	O
you	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
nothing	O
but	O
livery	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
three	O
hats	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
brown	O
cloaths	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
hats	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
get	O
them	O
done	O
up	O
against	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
new	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bolton	O
's	O
and	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
his	O
livery	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
these	O
cloaths	O
are	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
wore	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
by	O
another	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
too	O
big	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
band	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
sat	O
down	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
bills	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stolen	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
cloaths	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
brown	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
concealing	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
297	O
,	O
298	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
rabbit	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
pilaster	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
dovetail	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
trying	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
bead	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Absalom	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Absalom	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joiner	O
,	O
so	O
are	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chesterfield-street	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
tools	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
nine	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
but	O
the	O
dovetail	O
saw	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
Rider	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
Marks	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
dovetail	O
saw	O
was	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
that	O
again	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
tools	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Hughes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Marks	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
articled	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
find	O
me	O
in	O
tools	O
;	O
and	O
work	O
ran	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
job	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
tools	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
work	O
with	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
tools	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
tools	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Hughes	O
is	O
my	O
partner	O
;	O
Marks	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
bound	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
partner	O
with	O
Hughes	B-pers
a	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
12	O
months	O
;	O
Hughes	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
find	O
Marks	O
in	O
tools	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
difference	O
between	O
Hughes	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
job	O
for	O
himself	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
settled	O
again	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
tools	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
;	O
Hughes	O
was	O
as	O
liable	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
tools	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
free	O
consent	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
299	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
