TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YATES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hollman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Power	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maple	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turvile	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Benstead	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jewson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blacknell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Eason	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
Barnard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
.	O
335.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
forty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
brick	O
building	O
belonging	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
did	O
rip	O
,	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Back-road	B-place
,	I-place
Islington	I-place
.	O
Three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
his	O
work	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
somebody	O
was	O
stealing	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
lost	O
lead	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
another	O
man	O
to	O
assist	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
Francis	B-pers
Danby	I-pers
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
under	O
a	O
bush	O
on	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
knees	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
shook	O
and	O
trembled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
come	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
cut	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
bush	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Danby	I-pers
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behind	O
a	O
bush	O
on	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
knees	O
,	O
skulking	O
about	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
first	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
here	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
shook	O
and	O
trembled	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
bush	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
matched	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
lead	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
from	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
St.	O
Albans	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
field	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
stirred	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
awaked	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
shook	O
and	O
trembled	O
because	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
for	O
business	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
336	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Marcellis	I-pers
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Anthony	B-pers
Marcellis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
'Change	O
,	O
when	O
by	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
Compter	I-place
I	O
found	O
something	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
two	O
steps	O
from	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
That	O
afternoon	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lad	O
makes	O
several	O
attempts	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
down	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
when	O
by	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
living	O
by	O
going	O
about	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
selling	O
hymns	O
and	O
spiritual	O
songs	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
but	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
337	O
,	O
338	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tramer	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
workman	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
loitering	O
about	O
upon	O
Ludgate	B-place
hill	I-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
elderly	O
gentleman	O
they	O
followed	O
;	O
just	O
facing	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
they	O
seeing	O
his	O
pocket	O
slap	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
as	O
I	O
walked	O
,	O
Walker	O
made	O
several	O
attempts	O
as	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
Tramer	O
pushed	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Walker	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Maynard	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Le-grand	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
following	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
;	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Maynard	O
took	O
Walker	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
.	O
Walker	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
this	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
(	O
assessing	O
his	O
fellow	O
prisoners	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Trainer	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
jack-ass	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
overjoy	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
Pain	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
can	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
339	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
James	I-pers
Coyne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
200	O
pounds	O
weights	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
brick	O
building	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
L'Heureux	I-pers
did	O
rip	O
,	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
.	O
Betwixt	O
the	O
14th	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Roe	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
imagined	O
somebody	O
was	O
stealing	O
lead	O
off	O
my	O
house	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Charlotte-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Pancras	I-place
;	O
)	O
there	O
are	O
five	O
new	O
houses	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
Jacob	B-pers
L'Heureux	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
above	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
lead	O
cut	O
and	O
thrown	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
from	O
off	O
Mr.	O
L'Heureux	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
's	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
labourer	O
with	O
as	O
fired	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
asleep	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
lead	O
thrown	O
down	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tiles	O
rattled	O
down	O
the	O
gutter	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
building	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
cocked	O
my	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
still	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Whitney	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
340	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
M'Girk	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
carpenter	O
's	O
ax	O
,	O
a	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
a	O
smoothing	O
plane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
turning	O
saw	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
;	O
a	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
compasses	O
three	O
hundred	O
tenpenny	O
nails	O
,	O
a	O
broad	O
chisel	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
pinchers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
stock	O
lock	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Skirrett	I-pers
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Skirrett	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
at	O
separate	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
building	O
just	O
by	O
Holywell-mount	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lives	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
in	O
Whitecross	O
street	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
West	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Whitecross	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
saw	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
old	O
ones	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
plenty	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
mine	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Skirrett	O
's	O
saw	O
and	O
plane	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
among	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
stones	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Skirrett	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
this	O
saw	O
and	O
plane	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
the	O
saw	O
was	O
lost	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plane	O
about	O
nine	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
together	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
pawned	O
this	O
saw	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Crouch	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
occasion	O
for	O
but	O
one	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
well	O
,	O
going	O
cross	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
case	O
myself	O
among	O
some	O
stones	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
plane	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
saws	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
341	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
five	O
lilach	O
plants	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
three	O
privet	O
plants	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
five	O
honeysuckle	O
plants	O
,	O
five	O
vine	O
plants	O
,	O
four	O
jasmine	O
plants	O
,	O
two	O
box	O
plants	O
,	O
one	O
sweet-briar	O
plant	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Crispin	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
nursery-ground	O
,	O
did	O
pluck	O
up	O
,	O
dig	O
up	O
,	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
*	O
Crispin	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
keeps	O
a	O
nursery	O
ground	O
on	O
Milbank	B-place
;	O
the	O
plants	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
worked	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Wyld	O
street	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
plants	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
two	O
honeysuckles	O
,	O
one	O
vine	O
,	O
and	O
sweet-briar	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powe	I-pers
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
set	O
in	O
his	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
342	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Hickey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
soup-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
eight	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
marrow-spoon	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Wallard	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Wallard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pool	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
glover	O
,	O
in	O
New	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
stole	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
plate	O
last	O
?	O
J.	O
Wallard	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
shelf	O
in	O
a	O
passage	O
between	O
two	O
rooms	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
within	O
12	O
months	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
tablecloth	O
was	O
locked	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
a	O
scrutoir	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
in	O
debt	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
creditors	O
arrested	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
promise	O
upon	O
her	O
confessing	O
?	O
J.	O
Wallard	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
bu	O
t	O
upon	O
my	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
(	O
the	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
spoons	O
,	O
salt	O
,	O
and	O
table-cloth	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Walker's-court	O
;	O
this	O
plate	O
was	O
pledged	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
1766	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
1767	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
J.	O
Wallard	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
has	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
child	O
to	O
nurse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
your	O
apartment	O
?	O
J.	O
Wallard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Sidgear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
this	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
oath	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
also	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
coffee-pot	O
was	O
pawned	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
produce	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
lay	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
counter	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Worsley	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
while	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
coffee-pot	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dixon	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
brought	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
none	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
Worsley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
when	O
Worsley	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
?	O
Dixon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
pawned	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
343	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
porridge	O
pot	O
,	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
four	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
four	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
china	O
bowl	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
flour-dredger	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
fender	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Paddington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Anne	B-pers
Paddington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Paddington	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
ready	O
furnished	O
of	O
me	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
lodgings	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pledged	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rotchford	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Frank	B-pers
Rotchford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
goods	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
March	O
(	O
producing	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
344	O
,	O
345	O
,	O
346	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
a	O
pistole	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lesley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
money	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lesley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
inst	O
.	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
;	O
I	O
met	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
pay	O
for	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
another	O
girl	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Smith	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
said	O
she	O
should	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
soon	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
searched	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Smith	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
Smith	O
confessed	O
the	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
was	O
changed	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
in	O
liquor	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
with	O
such	O
people	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Power	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
deside	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
a	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
took	O
It	O
for	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
.	O
Ingram	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
first	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Hill	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
to	O
get	O
changed	O
;	O
when	O
this	O
girl	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
this	O
back	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
lying	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pocket-piece	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
things	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Lesley	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
carroty	O
hair	O
,	O
Smith	O
by	O
name	O
,	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
347	O
,	O
348	O
,	O
349	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
,	O
thirty-one	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Neyen	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Rimington	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Frederick	B-pers
Neyen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
at	O
Saltpetre-bank	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
Sukey	O
Atherley	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
called	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
called	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
treated	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
together	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
is	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
drams	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
then	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Atherley	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
moment	O
Hicks	O
came	O
up	O
Atherley	O
flew	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
put	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
unbuttoned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
your	O
money	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
pretty	O
free	O
in	O
playing	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
rustle	O
towards	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
,	O
she	O
flew	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
immediately	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
sure	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
Fanny	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
was	O
not	O
up	O
stairs	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
thirty-one	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
stairs	O
the	O
Atherleys	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
only	O
Mary	O
Hicks	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
accuse	O
Rimington	O
of	O
?	O
Neyen	O
.	O
She	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Mary	O
Hicks	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
unless	O
the	O
false	O
witnesses	O
are	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
are	O
sent	O
out	O
of	O
court	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
these	O
young	O
woman	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
or	O
Rimington	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Susanna	O
Atherley	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sober	O
?	O
M.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
come	O
often	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
long	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Susanna	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
?	O
M.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
immediately	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brebrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
these	O
new	O
stays	O
,	O
clothes	O
,	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
hats	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
;	O
Rimington	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
new	O
clothes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
got	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
deputy-keeper	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
last	O
Sunday	O
se'nnight	O
Frances	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
observed	O
to	O
put	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
stocking	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
herself	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
sister	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
stocking	O
off	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
her	O
left	O
leg	O
stocking	O
off	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
pulling	O
off	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
she	O
hesitated	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
half	O
guinea	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
Neyen	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
half	O
guineas	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
fight	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Egan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Susanna	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
and	O
Rimington	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
in	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Atherley	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
watchmen	O
came	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
black	O
eyes	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
about	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dog	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
ribbons	O
Egan	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Susanna	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Frances	O
and	O
Rimington	O
acquitted	O
.	O
350	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Vertue	B-pers
Donavan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Jane	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leg-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Long-acre	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milliner	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
visit	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
we	O
spent	O
the	O
afternoon	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
any	O
other	O
people	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
lodges	O
above	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
a	O
guinea	O
reward	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
guinea	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
lie	O
down	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
Upon	O
two	O
chairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
abscond	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
not	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
live	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
reputed	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
visitor	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
J.	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
lives	O
in	O
Clare-street	O
,	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
says	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
without	O
any	O
constable	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
accused	O
of	O
stealing	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
351	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brocksop	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Brocksop	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
office	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
walking	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bovill	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
and	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
handing	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
drop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
in	O
'Change-alley	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
resistance	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bovill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Halloo	O
,	O
who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
handing	O
the	O
book	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
papers	O
sell	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
made	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
help	O
gather	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
while	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gathered	O
up	O
the	O
papers	O
and	O
book	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
resistance	O
when	O
in	O
'Change-alley	O
;	O
the	O
book	O
dropped	O
directly	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Post-office	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
about	O
the	O
gentleman	O
losing	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
not	O
for	O
why	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
he	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
post	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
at	O
Norwich	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
write	O
the	O
letter	O
?	O
Merryman	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
write	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
wrote	O
it	O
?	O
Merryman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
really	O
forgot	O
the	O
name	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Popham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Phoenix-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
lad	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Quaker-street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
his	O
church	O
constantly	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
352	O
,	O
353	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty-two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
Meal	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Biby	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
Esqrs	O
;	O
May	O
2	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
supervisor	O
of	O
the	O
London-bridge	B-place
water-works	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
under	O
me	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
iron	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
willing	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
laid	O
a	O
trap	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
Walter	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
the	O
proprietors	O
are	O
John	B-pers
Authony	I-pers
Meal	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Biby	O
Lake	O
,	O
Esqrs	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
bridge	O
about	O
five	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
iron	O
lie	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
a	O
good	O
look	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
works	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sack	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
Nicholls	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
arm	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
expected	O
the	O
iron	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
immediately	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
iron	O
from	O
the	O
platform	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
convenient	O
to	O
fetch	O
away	O
.	O
His	O
evidence	O
not	O
being	O
supported	O
by	O
any	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
354	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Flower-de-luce-court	B-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
going	O
from	O
Clifford's-inn	O
;	O
people	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
croud	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
fellows	O
fighting	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
recollecting	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
close	O
in	O
his	O
fist	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cork	O
cutter	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
fight	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
slipped	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
cork-cutter	O
,	O
he	O
works	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
between	O
17	O
and	O
18	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Delay	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
porter	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch-case	O
from	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
dropped	O
by	O
accident	O
from	O
my	O
side	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
se'nnight	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
prison	O
walking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
with	O
an	O
apron	O
on	O
;	O
hed	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
through	O
the	O
arch	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
beckoned	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
watch-case	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
Bow	O
and	O
Stepney	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
here	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
silversmiths	O
between	O
there	O
and	O
Duke's-place	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
can	O
say	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
suffer	O
the	O
law	O
;	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
advance	O
his	O
wages	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Fish-street-hill	B-place
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
above	O
the	O
Monument	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
lad	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
holding	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
hallooed	O
out	O
murder	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
twelve	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
draw-boy	O
to	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
357	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
sattin	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
four	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
four	O
long	O
lawn	O
frocks	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
comb	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
;	O
twenty-four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
plated	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crutched	B-place
friars	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
family	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
to	O
my	O
country-house	O
at	O
Putney	O
,	O
leaving	O
only	O
Rebecca	O
Brown	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
London	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
horse	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
use	O
to	O
carry	O
tobacco	O
into	O
carts	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
used	O
as	O
a	O
ladder	O
,	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
removed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
window	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
thereupon	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
china	O
closet	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
counting-house	O
a	O
gold	O
laced	O
hat	O
which	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
ride	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
several	O
kinds	O
of	O
goods	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
enumerate	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
things	O
I	O
could	O
recollect	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
he	O
sent	O
out	O
bills	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
early	O
in	O
April	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
silver	O
nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
two	O
years	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
servant	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
family	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
child	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
small-pox	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
double	O
locked	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
were	O
gone	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
linen	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
which	O
the	O
horse	O
stood	O
against	O
was	O
shoved	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
shut	O
down	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
In	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
's	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
footman	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
chest	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
at	O
Putney	O
,	O
(	O
two	O
aprons	O
produced	O
,	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
footman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
;	O
(	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
plated	O
spurs	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
several	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
surtout	O
coat	O
produced	O
,	O
)	O
these	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
my	O
coat	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Stratford	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Black-friars	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
gold	O
ring	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
it	O
occurred	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
handbills	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
ring	O
mentioned	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
bills	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
that	O
bill	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
still	O
it	O
ran	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
that	O
bill	O
which	O
described	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
ring	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
wait	O
till	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
sattin	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
she	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hemings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
and	O
pledged	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Simonds	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
gown	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Russel	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
together	O
at	O
Chelmsford	O
in	O
Essex	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
one	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
having	O
money	O
owing	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Cross	O
at	O
Stratford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
waited	O
,	O
but	O
Buck	O
never	O
came	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
was	O
this	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
sattin	O
gown	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
black	O
petticoat	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
brought	O
a	O
nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
swore	O
to	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
petticoat	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Russel	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
Simonds	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
some	O
goods	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
come	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
overtook	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
shirts	O
and	O
the	O
gold-laced	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
here	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
a	O
snare	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
no	O
person	O
could	O
hurt	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
farther	O
discovery	O
made	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
boots	O
and	O
spurs	O
belonging	O
to	O
White	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
the	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
bring	O
here	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
(	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Russel	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
was	O
seven	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
father	O
at	O
Stratford	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
Michael	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
in	O
Poorjury-lane	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
spare	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Cross	O
betwixt	O
Stratford	O
and	O
Bow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
18	O
d.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
Buck	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
which	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
Buck	O
never	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
things	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
more	O
convenient	O
for	O
him	O
that	O
we	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
bundle	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
and	O
kept	O
them	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
can	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
bad	O
character	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
dismissed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
never	O
to	O
come	O
within	O
my	O
gates	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
358	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Elliott	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
Airey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Shower	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Clarissa	B-pers
Airey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Airey	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Jane	B-pers
Shower	I-pers
's	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
purse	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Shower	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
which	O
lay	O
loose	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shower	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
servant	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
till	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
five	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Airey	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
her	O
money	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
not	O
quite	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
every	O
lock	O
up	O
stairs	O
had	O
been	O
tried	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
forks	O
had	O
their	O
tines	O
bent	O
,	O
I	O
strongly	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Shower	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	B-pers
Shower	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
many	O
things	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Willingham	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
to	O
pledge	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
called	O
herself	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
that	O
is	O
unborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
proper	O
person	O
?	O
Peacock	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
person	O
coming	O
and	O
asking	O
for	O
it	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
persons	O
in	O
your	O
way	O
are	O
often	O
called	O
upon	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
person	O
they	O
take	O
things	O
in	O
of	O
?	O
Peacock	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
careful	O
in	O
asking	O
where	O
people	O
live	O
and	O
their	O
name	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Willingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Peacock	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
pawned	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Peacock	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
woman	O
pawned	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
day	O
besides	O
one	O
?	O
Peacock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
woman	O
that	O
did	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
359	O
,	O
360	O
,	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
Susanna	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
coat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
horse	O
pistols	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
bullet-bag	O
,	O
a	O
powder-horn	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
cotton	O
night-gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
three	O
napkins	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
cheque-apron	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Shurel	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
David	B-pers
Shurel	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Sackville-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
on	O
Haverstock-hill	B-place
,	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
last	O
mentioned	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
all	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
places	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Sackville-street	O
:	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
3d	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
hall-door	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
my	O
clock-case	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
near	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
the	O
clock	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
pendulum	O
,	O
pullies	O
,	O
and	O
winder	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
grey	O
coat	O
lined	O
with	O
black	O
,	O
black	O
buttons	O
and	O
holes	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sussian	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
dark	O
dimity	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
dining-room	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
chimney	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
horse-pistols	O
made	O
by	O
Barber	O
,	O
a	O
powder-flask	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
bullet-bag	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
marked	O
D.	O
M.	O
S.	O
or	O
M.	O
R.	O
a	O
white	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
cotton	O
night-gown	O
,	O
printed	O
red	O
and	O
blue	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
a	O
flowered	O
muslin	O
toilet	O
cloth	O
,	O
two	O
bordered	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
with	O
flower	O
baskets	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
;	O
all	O
these	O
I	O
advertised	O
May	O
the	O
6th	O
:	O
the	O
following	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
chest	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
then	O
recollected	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
cheque-apron	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
ditto	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pillowbears	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
servants	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
discocovered	O
the	O
thief	O
had	O
broke	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
some	O
ladder	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
back	O
window	O
of	O
six	O
squares	O
of	O
glass	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
twenty-four	O
feet	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
they	O
had	O
free	O
liberty	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
five	O
apartments	O
;	O
the	O
chambers	O
,	O
closets	O
,	O
and	O
cupboard	O
doors	O
were	O
all	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
to	O
admit	O
of	O
free	O
air	O
;	O
the	O
rooms	O
I	O
found	O
were	O
all	O
over	O
with	O
tallow	O
,	O
candle	O
droppings	O
,	O
and	O
bits	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
and	O
pieces	O
of	O
matches	O
scattered	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
candle	O
had	O
been	O
stuck	O
upon	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
sash	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
burnt	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bottom	O
rails	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
candles	O
,	O
tinder	O
,	O
matches	O
,	O
steel	O
,	O
and	O
flint	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
whether	O
they	O
used	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
they	O
brought	O
candle	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
to	O
town	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
also	O
a	O
second	O
night	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Pollard	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
cow-keeper	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Heley	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
sheets	O
cut	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
shifts	O
of	O
(	O
several	O
pieces	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Shurel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
compared	O
these	O
pieces	O
with	O
some	O
sheets	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
safely	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Noaks	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
information	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lived	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
cloth	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
servants	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Duck-lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
Susanna	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
;	O
(	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bonnet	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Shurel	O
.	O
This	O
sheet	O
and	O
clock	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
green	O
bonnet	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
.	O
Noaks	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
Stapleton	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
show	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Stretton's-ground	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Curtis	O
;	O
the	O
husband	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Noaks	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
(	O
be	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
Noaks	O
.	O
)	O
Catherine	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
grey	O
coat	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pollard	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
cow-keeper	O
;	O
Stapleton	O
delivered	O
three	O
shift	O
bodies	O
cut	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
like	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
shift	O
bodies	O
again	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
habitation	O
in	O
Nag's-head-yard	O
by	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
about	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
declared	O
to	O
her	O
sister	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
pistols	O
and	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
all	O
hanged	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
cutting	O
some	O
sheets	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Stapleton	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
long	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
Hertfordshire	O
from	O
my	O
grandfather	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
landlady	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
grandfather	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
fowls	O
and	O
twenty-three	O
eggs	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
they	O
tied	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
very	O
contented	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
staid	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
start	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
362	O
,	O
363	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
twenty-six	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ringrose	I-pers
,	O
April	B-place
20	I-place
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Ringrose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White's-ground	O
near	O
Barnaby-street	O
,	O
Surry	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Horseshoe	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
except	O
I	O
give	O
her	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
she	O
fetched	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
watchman	O
some	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
undressed	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
pillow	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
my	O
clothes	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
held	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
watch	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
clothes	O
on	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Anne	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
candle	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
twenty-six	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
twenty-seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
intending	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
use	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
talking	O
about	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
breeches	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
gold	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
brew	O
house	O
all	O
the	O
day	O
from	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
but	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
take	O
your	O
breeches	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
?	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
startled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
lodging	O
?	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Redcross-street	O
,	O
No	O
19	O
,	O
near	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
a	O
fore	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
you	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
you	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Ringrose	O
.	O
She	O
enticed	O
me	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Moslin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
what	O
he	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
Tower-hill	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
Davis	O
)	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
it	O
wanted	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
of	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
turned	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
the	O
hill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
towards	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
home	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
your	O
way	O
is	O
my	O
way	O
you	O
may	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
putting	O
lights	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
they	O
do	O
that	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Wilkes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
you	O
please	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Horseshoe	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
together	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
afford	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
behaved	O
well	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
another	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
directly	O
;	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
Davis	O
,	O
lodges	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
she	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
lay	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
then	O
be	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
about	O
twelve	O
he	O
was	O
crying	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
several	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
presence	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Tower-hill	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
Smith	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
relation	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
reckoned	O
a	O
good	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
drawed	O
away	O
I	O
believe	O
by	O
very	O
bad	O
company	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Smith	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
when	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
now	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
364	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Taplin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
porridge-pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
St.	I-place
Anne's-lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
about	O
eleven	O
weeks	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
deserted	O
the	O
regiment	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
belonged	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
pledged	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sclater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Stretton's-ground	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
porridge-pot	O
,	O
blanket	O
,	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
all	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
January	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
mother	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
not	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
debt	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threatened	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
break	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
three	O
hundred	O
lashes	O
for	O
deserting	O
;	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Cold-stream	O
regiment	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
times	O
are	O
hard	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
and	O
porter	O
for	O
my	O
bread	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
365	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Paul	B-pers
William	I-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
ounce	O
of	O
human	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
eleven	O
ounces	O
of	O
horse-hair	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
toupee-irons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pinching-iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Bunyan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Windsor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
,	O
three	O
weeks	O
last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
cut	O
some	O
young	O
ladies	O
hair	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
clothes	O
being	O
but	O
indifferent	O
,	O
I	O
hired	O
him	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
breeches	O
and	O
stockings	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
other	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
upon	O
Hounslow-heath	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
abusive	O
people	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
satisfied	O
without	O
I	O
would	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
lent	O
me	O
these	O
clothes	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hair	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
366	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
500	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
being	O
disturbers	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
did	O
assemble	O
near	O
the	O
Mansion-house	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
there	O
continuing	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
making	O
great	O
noise	O
and	O
disturbance	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
many	O
stones	O
at	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
break	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
damage	O
the	O
furniture	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
divers	O
subjects	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
in	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
in	O
great	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
their	O
lives	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
at	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
hearing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
disturbance	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
election	O
at	O
Brentford	O
;	O
)	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
came	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Manlove	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
partner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Heath	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
mischief	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
and	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
report	O
true	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
vast	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
some	O
thousands	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
throw	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
break	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
windows	O
;	O
among	O
them	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
shouting	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Wilkes	O
for	O
ever	O
!	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
language	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
;	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
broke	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
windows	O
,	O
particularly	O
below	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
stones	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
Such	O
stones	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
pick	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
being	O
after	O
the	O
new	O
paving	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
little	O
stones	O
lying	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
stones	O
flying	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
bigness	O
of	O
an	O
egg	O
,	O
bigger	O
or	O
lesser	O
,	O
and	O
pieces	O
of	O
brick-bats	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
much	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
still	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
mistaken	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
behaviour	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
duty	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
every	O
Englishman	O
,	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
suppress	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
a	O
mob	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
Stevenson	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
that	O
villain	O
,	O
I	O
suspect	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
you	O
see	O
he	O
is	O
throwing	O
stones	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
watched	O
him	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
all	O
the	O
stones	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
up	O
a	O
passage	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
church	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry	O
below	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
lay	O
;	O
he	O
loaded	O
himself	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
and	O
broke	O
several	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
on	O
the	O
west	O
side	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
never	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
hardly	O
patience	O
to	O
forbear	O
taking	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
;	O
my	O
neighbour	O
Stevenson	O
believing	O
I	O
should	O
seize	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
murdered	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
afraid	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
leave	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
soldiers	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
mob	O
stopped	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
more	O
active	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
bayonee	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
drawed	O
round	O
in	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
soldiers	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
posture	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
several	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
several	O
windows	O
in	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
my	O
neighbour	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
advice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
agreeable	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
inclination	O
,	O
left	O
me	O
:	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
throwed	O
all	O
the	O
stones	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
west	O
side	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
more	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
broke	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
windows	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
considered	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
;	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
they	O
talked	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
;	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
mob	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
determined	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
mob	O
:	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
own	O
brains	O
,	O
I	O
concluded	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
how	O
dare	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
pick	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
in	O
this	O
the	O
mob	O
would	O
rather	O
be	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
than	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
body	O
very	O
near	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
body	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
his	O
companion	O
made	O
off	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
you	O
up	O
as	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
you	O
up	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
windows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
from	O
first	O
to	O
last	O
might	O
you	O
have	O
kept	O
your	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
a	O
full	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
broke	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
other	O
peoples	O
lamps	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
candles	O
in	O
every	O
window	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
perhaps	O
out	O
of	O
respect	O
,	O
the	O
mob	O
shouting	O
,	O
Wilkes	O
for	O
ever	O
!	O
then	O
a	O
stone	O
went	O
,	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
were	O
throwing	O
and	O
shouting	O
Wilkes	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
more	O
windows	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
than	O
any	O
ten	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
remarkable	O
for	O
throwing	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
inward	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
we	O
examined	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
very	O
much	O
soiled	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
handling	O
dirty	O
stones	O
:	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
mentioned	O
this	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
heard	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
women	O
would	O
give	O
evidence	O
that	O
his	O
hands	O
were	O
clean	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
went	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
twelve	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
coming	O
up	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dressed	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
own	O
dark	O
hair	O
,	O
a	O
coloured	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ragged	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
directly	O
followed	O
him	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
between	O
the	O
mob	O
and	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-gate	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
stop	O
at	O
the	O
Poultry-gate	O
to	O
watch	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
watching	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
jumped	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
the	O
Compter-gate	O
did	O
you	O
seize	O
him	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
Not	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
it	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
the	O
mob	O
reached	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
walking	O
together	O
a	O
good	O
middling	O
pace	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
three	O
miles	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
run	O
to	O
get	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
directly	O
fronting	O
the	O
gate	O
when	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
twenty	O
feet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
abide	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
He	O
shifted	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
and	O
front	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sometimes	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
a	O
particular	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
meant	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
see	O
they	O
are	O
muddy	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
dirty	O
;	O
his	O
hands	O
were	O
both	O
soiled	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
handling	O
dirty	O
stones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
hands	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
Nobody	O
but	O
the	O
turnkey	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
all	O
this	O
come	O
to	O
;	O
said	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
breaking	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
windows	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
scarcely	O
a	O
whole	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
walked	O
round	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
look	O
sharp	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
-	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
look	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
some	O
person	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
all	O
broke	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
)	O
people	O
were	O
throwing	O
stones	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
one	O
person	O
upon	O
earth	O
that	O
threw	O
a	O
stone	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
round	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
single	O
out	O
any	O
one	O
particular	O
person	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
mentioned	O
throw	O
a	O
stone	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
no	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
pieces	O
of	O
tiles	O
lying	O
there	O
;	O
said	O
Pain	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
picks	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
off	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
left-hand	O
side	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
walking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
;	O
said	O
Pain	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
afraid	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
left-hand	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
directly	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
among	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
50	O
l.	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
reward	O
offered	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
alluded	O
to	O
throw	O
a	O
stone	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
stones	O
thrown	O
while	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
throwed	O
them	O
near	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
after	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
servants	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
certainly	O
have	O
fired	O
at	O
the	O
mob	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
15	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
say	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
next	O
morning	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
him	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
remember	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Compter-gate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pushed	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
of	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
and	O
Pain	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
situation	O
in	O
the	O
mob	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
converse	O
together	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
He	O
walked	O
before	O
and	O
I	O
near	O
him	O
behind	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
converse	O
occasionally	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
point	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
throwing	O
stones	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
Pain	O
pointed	O
to	O
as	O
throwing	O
stones	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
Pain	O
pointed	O
at	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
Pain	O
pointed	O
throw	O
stones	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
throwing	O
stones	O
together	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
apprehend	O
Pain	O
had	O
some	O
nation	O
of	O
a	O
reward	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
arrive	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
?	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
About	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Wyld-street	O
,	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
his	O
business	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
comes	O
and	O
spends	O
his	O
evenings	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
lives	O
in	O
Jewin-street	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
watch-finisher	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
not	O
bailed	O
?	O
E.	O
Saxton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
his	O
bail	O
surrender	O
him	O
up	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
E.	O
Saxton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
so	O
?	O
E.	O
Saxton	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
another	O
troublesome	O
affair	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
Amelia	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
prisoner	O
there	O
for	O
debt	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
