TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ridgway	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Jerrard	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bate	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Welles	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Naire	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tawlks	I-pers
,	O
Sachever	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Juby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dakin	I-pers
,	O
Solomon	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hundley	I-pers
.	O
406	O
,	O
407	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Child	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lear	I-pers
;	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
Henry	B-pers
Lear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sugar	O
refiner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Water-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Black-friars	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
sugar-house	O
to	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Cox	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
speaking	O
to	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
run	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
people	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shirt	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
from	O
a	O
hook	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
me	O
first	O
put	O
my	O
hat	O
behind	O
the	O
street-door	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Child	O
had	O
the	O
shirt	O
;	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-woman	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
a	O
shilling	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Cox	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
both	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
hat	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
408	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
duffel	O
cardinal	O
trimmed	O
with	O
furr	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
cheque	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
||	O
Esther	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Leather-lane	B-place
,	O
he	O
is	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Stoughton	O
's	O
warehouse	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
,	O
she	O
cries	O
crabs	O
and	O
shrimps	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
room-door	O
open	O
,	O
two	O
drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
hat	O
missing	O
from	O
one	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
coloured	O
apron	O
from	O
the	O
bed-post	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
also	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lawn	O
apron	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
clothes-basket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
woman	O
as	O
I	O
described	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
Mutton-hill	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
duffel	O
cloak	O
and	O
coloured	O
apron	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
from	O
hanging	O
behind	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Sarah	O
Lake	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
(	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
apron	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Keden	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Needham	O
's	O
,	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
where	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
in	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
409	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Iveson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
hammering	O
in	O
a	O
lighter	O
that	O
lay	O
a	O
long	O
side	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
is	O
owner	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
belong	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
lighter	O
loaded	O
with	O
sugar	O
in	O
Shadwell-dock	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hammering	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
cask	O
;	O
he	O
throwed	O
down	O
the	O
hammer	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
containing	O
one	O
hundred	O
weight	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
feet	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
head	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
lighter	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
sugar	O
was	O
lying	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
hammering	O
the	O
cask	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
as	O
a	O
lighterman	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jollet	I-pers
.	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
otherwise	O
but	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
410	O
,	O
411	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cruise	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
;	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
live	O
ducks	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
my	O
men	O
secured	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
pond	O
where	O
the	O
duck	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hackney	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
pond	O
in	O
Mr	O
.	O
Speed	O
's	O
field	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
foot-path	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
Cruise	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
pond	O
washing	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
wiped	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
lappet	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
distance	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
ducks	O
in	O
the	O
pond	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
Cruise	O
with	O
two	O
ducks	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
running	O
cross	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Speed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Conway	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
that	O
way	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Cruise	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
that	O
day	O
which	O
he	O
says	O
the	O
ducks	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
For	O
Conway	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Robson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Conway	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
between	O
eighteen	O
and	O
nineteen	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Chart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Conway	O
betwixt	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine's-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
E.	O
Newland	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
boy	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Sumersell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
412.	O
Edward	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
413	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
store	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Marybone	B-place
parish	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pigs	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Oxlard	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Oxlard	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Dulwich	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pig	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
22	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Berier	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
bought	O
another	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
a	O
sty	O
at	O
Berier	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
kinsman	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Clark	O
.	O
My	O
kinsman	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Lisson-green	O
;	O
my	O
kinsman	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Oxlard	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
and	O
his	O
kinsman	O
too	O
.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
sent	O
my	O
kinsman	O
(	O
named	O
Ibord	O
)	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Oxlard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Reading	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berier	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
driving	O
the	O
two	O
pigs	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
at	O
Dulwich	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Sydenham	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Oxlard	O
came	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
sty	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
clips	O
on	O
the	O
shoulders	O
on	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
spotted	O
black	O
and	O
white	O
.	O
Clark	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
as	O
he	O
describes	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
pigs	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
fair	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
forty-seven	O
pigs	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
414.	O
John	B-pers
Jarret	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
a	O
pillow	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
called	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
415	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Conscollon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
glass	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Puncheon	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Puncheon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Meeting-house-court	O
,	O
Long-acre	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
business	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
in	O
walking	O
a	O
little	O
about	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
Jackson's-alley	O
,	O
by	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
women	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
working	O
man	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
woman	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
chose	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
leaning	O
my	O
arm	O
over	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
whom	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
quit	O
the	O
place	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
soon	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Broker's-alley	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
liquor	O
and	O
some	O
brandy	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
joined	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
followed	O
us	O
from	O
Jackson	O
's	O
alley	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
dared	O
not	O
detect	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
the	O
liquor	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
to	O
Chimney-sweeper's-alley	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
hoped	O
they	O
would	O
deliver	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
she	O
burst	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
beating	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
tore	O
my	O
clothes	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
?	O
Puncheon	O
.	O
In	O
Fenchurch-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
intent	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
Jackson's-alley	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
way	O
?	O
Puncheon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
frolick	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chimney-sweeper's-alley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
knocking	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
carpenter	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
bailiff	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
harbour	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
a	O
bailiff	O
's	O
following	O
dog	O
.	O
Puncheon	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
compound	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
than	O
they	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
France	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
||	O
Peter	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
at	O
Gun-dock	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
somebody	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
boy	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
draw	O
me	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
mug	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
imagine	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Etherington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
alarm	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
being	O
lost	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
some	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
some	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Milk-alley	O
with	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
intended	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
walking	O
or	O
running	O
?	O
Etherington	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
walking	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Cou	O
rt	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
prosecutions	O
for	O
drawing	O
in	O
silver	O
?	O
Duffey	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
use	O
it	O
for	O
my	O
customers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
mug	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Bromley	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Etherington	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
going	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Bromley	O
's	O
?	O
Etherington	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
seven	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
417	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Isaac	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
glass	O
globe	O
lamps	O
with	O
tin	O
rims	O
fixed	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
tin	O
burners	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
||	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Whitsun	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
eleven	O
globe	O
lamps	O
from	O
Spitalfields	O
where	O
I	O
contract	O
for	O
lighting	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
with	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
him	O
long	O
before	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Ruffey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Whitsun	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
and	O
shewed	O
three	O
globe	O
lamps	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
rims	O
on	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
these	O
lamps	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
on	O
Whitsun	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
rather	O
than	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
burner	O
on	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
alight	O
;	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
uncle	O
and	O
aunt	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
one	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
three	O
lamps	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
418	O
,	O
419	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Trubshaw	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
daughter	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
in	O
partnership	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
toy-shop	O
opposite	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
dinner	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
about	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
shew	O
glass	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
gold	O
rings	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
standing	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
on	O
suspicion	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
searching	O
found	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
Harris	O
's	O
hat	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
rings	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
Harris	O
's	O
hat	O
;	O
we	O
stripped	O
them	O
both	O
naked	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grafton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
these	O
two	O
rings	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
serve	O
her	O
with	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
rings	O
.	O
M.	O
Pearson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
my	O
rings	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Grafton	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
rings	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
Harris	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
wire	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagine	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
take	O
things	O
out	O
through	O
holes	O
in	O
windows	O
.	O
Harris	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Another	O
lad	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
hat	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Trubshaw	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
grandmother	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
lad	O
(	O
meaning	O
his	O
fellow	O
prisoner	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
asking	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Harris	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Harris	O
's	O
father	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
favour	O
)	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cripple	O
.	O
Trubshaw	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Maples	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Harris	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Trubshaw	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
420	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scotch	O
carpet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
five	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Maley	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Duke-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
flat	O
irons	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
and	O
pawning	O
some	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
's	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
seals	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	B-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Broadey	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Beckam	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
is	O
named	O
Gunston	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Jermyn-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
some	O
flat	O
irons	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
Banister	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
Scotch	O
carpet	O
of	O
Broadey	O
.	O
E.	O
Maley	O
.	O
The	O
carpet	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
sent	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Diarden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pecks	O
of	O
household	O
flour	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
miller	O
at	O
Hillingdon	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
flour	O
,	O
we	O
guessed	O
a	O
bushel	O
or	O
more	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
we	O
weighed	O
the	O
flour	O
we	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
a	O
bushel	O
and	O
a	O
peck	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
see	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
mill	O
window	O
,	O
by	O
flour	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
trod	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
account	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
flour	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
where	O
some	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
it	O
agreed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
five	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
near	O
lying	O
in	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brickman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hubbard	O
's	O
mill	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
flour	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Hubbard	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
flour	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
by	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
the	O
flour	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Shouler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe-buckle	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckle	O
from	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
window	O
in	O
Ratcliffe	B-place
highway	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
broke	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
into	O
Shadwell	O
church	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
break	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
buckle	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
coal-cart	O
going	O
by	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
box-maker	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
that	O
way	O
with	O
goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
and	O
Imp	O
.	O
423	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
ditto	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herrick	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Horse	I-place
and	I-place
Groom	I-place
in	I-place
Portland-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
from	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
from	O
my	O
room	O
over	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
return	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
mistake	O
;	O
he	O
fetched	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hay	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
plead	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
tried	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
your	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Vigars	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ransom	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
coloured	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-end	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chamber	O
and	O
closet	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
weekly	O
servant	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Shoreditch	O
work	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
her	O
father-in-law	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
absconded	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
that	O
person	O
gave	O
me	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
bonnet	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
wife	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
buckles	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bellamy	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
bonnet	O
and	O
cloak	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
425	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
426	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
coach	O
harness	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
bridle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
brechin	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
North	B-place
Audley-street	I-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
harness	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
coachmen	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
watchman	O
take	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
some	O
harness	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
harness	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
harness	O
,	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
for	O
who	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
what	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
well-dressed	O
man	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
harness	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Jourdan	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
two-pence	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
drink	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
once	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Mens	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
427	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bridget	B-pers
Bouston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackavoy	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Mackavoy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
stall	O
in	O
Covent-garden	B-place
;	O
on	O
Whitsun	O
Monday	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
stall	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cavenhan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-hart-yard	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
box	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
new	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
empty	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Mackavoy	O
.	O
This	O
box	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
empty	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fairlock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
M'Dougal	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
428	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Pipson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gangsman	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bear-key	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
sugar	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hogshead	O
of	O
sugar	O
near	O
him	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
pilfered	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
quality	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
warehouse	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
sugar	O
out	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
429	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Shute	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Shute	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
rents	O
a	O
shop	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
their	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Saturday	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back-door	O
into	O
Pope's-head-alley	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
four	O
spoons	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
trusted	O
with	O
six	O
to	O
clean	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kersill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Whitehouse	O
at	O
Islington	O
to	O
exchange	O
these	O
,	O
a	O
spoon	O
for	O
a	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
offer	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
of	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Gosling	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
there	O
appeared	O
an	O
advertisement	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
four	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
being	O
stolen	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
two	O
table	O
spoons	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
(	O
three	O
spoons	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
crest	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
St	O
.	O
Brides	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
assembled	O
together	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
I	O
buttoned	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
watch	O
chain	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sting	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
stoop	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
stooping	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
down	O
Black-horse-alley	O
into	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
going	O
into	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
striped	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boyden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
also	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
stooped	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
advantage	O
to	O
slip	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Black-house-alley	O
into	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Boyden	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
striped	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
stopped	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
out	O
against	O
me	O
made	O
me	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Boyden	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
directly	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Black-horse-alley	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
431	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
;	O
coming	O
this	O
way	O
on	O
the	O
right-hand	O
side	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
lower	O
than	O
the	O
green-market	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
has	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
both	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
green-market	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handke	O
rchief	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
turn	O
into	O
the	O
leather-market	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
people	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
prosecuting	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
is	O
a	O
mathematical	O
instrument	O
maker	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lamp-lighter	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
432	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kealing	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
the	B-place
Castle	I-place
and	I-place
Faulcon-yard	I-place
;	O
(	O
we	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
glass	O
bottles	O
)	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
warehouse	O
where	O
the	O
phials	O
lay	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
hay-loft	O
which	O
commands	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
crate	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
phials	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
crate	O
?	O
Mott	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
what	O
the	O
glass	O
bottles	O
are	O
brought	O
in	O
from	O
Staffordshire	O
and	O
Worcestershire	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
uncle	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
eight	O
phials	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
one	O
word	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crosier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Parry	O
,	O
gave	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
insanity	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
confined	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
433	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hogwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen-sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
left	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
434	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
new	O
bar-iron	O
,	O
the	O
weight	O
seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
bolt-iron	O
,	O
the	O
weight	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Invill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
at	O
Mile-end	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Ward	O
come	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
new	O
bar-iron	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
on	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
it	O
dropped	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
at	O
my	O
shop-door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
proper	O
opportunity	O
to	O
observe	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
again	O
by	O
a	O
crack	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
unlocked	O
the	O
old	O
iron	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
that	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
weigh	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
iron	O
under	O
her	O
counter	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
iron	O
;	O
at	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
five-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Smith	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
asked	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
no	O
such	O
iron	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
welcome	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
directly	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
throw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
weighs	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
;	O
Ward	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
my	O
master	O
two-pence	O
farthing	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
always	O
gave	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
Ward	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
face	O
she	O
never	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
but	O
three-farthings	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
this	O
iron	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
new	O
bar-iron	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
smiths	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
bolt-iron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
bar-iron	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
piece	O
of	O
new	O
bar-iron	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
piece	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
found	O
at	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
at	O
my	O
first	O
asking	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
Ward	O
's	O
name	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
none	O
of	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
still	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
Invill	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
immediately	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
new	O
bar-iron	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
evidence	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
were	O
examined	O
on	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
Ward	B-pers
a	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
five-pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
halfpence	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Rand	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hurdle	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Troop	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
M'Farling	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
436	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Rackley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
dowlas	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Winchmore-hill	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
daily	O
labour	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
stole	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
light	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
examine	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
last	O
Sunday	O
;	O
he	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
20	O
miles	O
beyond	O
Reading	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
old	O
clothes	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
hay-barn	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
key	O
in	O
a	O
barn	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
husband	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
back-side	O
my	O
house	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
back-door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
clothes	O
produced	O
here	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
hay-loft	O
where	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Newington	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Leadenhall-market	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
was	O
blue-grey	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
cape	O
and	O
black	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
a	O
stick	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Wakefield	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
coats	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
as	O
Frazier	O
has	O
described	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
starving	O
alive	O
for	O
want	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
437	O
,	O
438	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Craycraft	I-pers
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Robert	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
At	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
)	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Black-house-yard	B-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
seemingly	O
about	O
16	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
jacket	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
little	O
bastard	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
Craycraft	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
look	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
knocked	O
down	O
with	O
?	O
Nicholson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
or	O
his	O
fist	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
boy	O
before	O
?	O
Nicholson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
shorter	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Castleton	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
better	O
clothes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
no	O
other	O
people	O
going	O
along	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Nicholson	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Craycraft	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Nicholson	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
in	O
Distress	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Craycraft	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
any	O
house	O
where	O
were	O
women	O
?	O
Nicholson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
Jackson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
shipmate	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
next	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Black-boy	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
other	O
boys	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
pick	O
pockets	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
names	O
was	O
Terry	O
Tinley	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Craycraft	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
lewd	O
woman	O
's	O
company	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
searify	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
never	O
go	O
into	O
company	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
by	O
Craycraft	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
one	O
man	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
the	O
waiter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
's	O
daughter	O
;	O
Craycraft	O
called	O
me	O
Irishman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
Irishman	O
,	O
drink	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
,	O
Craycraft	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
nose	O
and	O
looked	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
signifying	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Blackboy-alley	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
after	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
also	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
down	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
Terry	O
Finley	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
Terry	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
down	O
the	O
bank	O
;	O
said	O
Craycraft	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Blackhorse-yard	O
;	O
there	O
Craycraft	O
told	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
and	O
searched	O
me	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
Terry	O
Finley	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
about	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Nicholson	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
said	O
Craycraft	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sucking	O
cull	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
drunken	O
gentleman	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
white	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
get	O
away	O
you	O
little	O
bastard	O
;	O
then	O
Craycraft	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
double	O
fist	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
dropped	O
,	O
Craycraft	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
Bourn	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
two-pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
then	O
Craycraft	O
said	O
,	O
hush	O
,	O
you	O
thief	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
your	O
throat	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
turning	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
bank	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
or	O
aniseed	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
three-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Craycraft	O
again	O
;	O
Craycraft	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
thief	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
man	O
they	O
robbed	O
)	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
Terry	O
Finley	O
?	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
Bourn	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Craycraft	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
,	O
Terry	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
this	O
towards	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
we	O
robbed	O
Nicholson	O
;	O
Craycraft	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
blast	O
you	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
their	O
throats	O
directly	O
;	O
Nicholson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
lad	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
both	O
their	O
hats	O
were	O
flapped	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
patch	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
his	O
check	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
singing	O
ballads	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
stopped	O
and	O
stood	O
talking	O
to	O
two	O
sailors	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Craycraft	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
are	O
hired	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
the	O
clothes	O
you	O
have	O
on	O
to	O
tell	O
this	O
story	O
?	O
Suilivan	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
shirt	O
to	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
vermin	O
;	O
these	O
clothes	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
out	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
worked	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
this	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Craycraft	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
constable	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
put	O
you	O
apprentice	O
.	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
Justices	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
mind	O
after	O
this	O
thing	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
boy	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
has	O
friends	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
country	O
,	O
send	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
live	O
at	O
Waterford	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
followed	O
picking	O
of	O
pockets	O
?	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
followed	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
six	O
years	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
country	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Quist	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
(	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Evans	O
)	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
Craycraft	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
named	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
came	O
in	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
be	O
quiet	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
more	O
beer	O
,	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
woman	O
,	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Etherley	I-pers
came	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
box	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bourn	O
said	O
she	O
has	O
tipped	O
you	O
the	O
double	O
,	O
to	O
Craycraft	O
;	O
Craycraft	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
holy	O
Jesus	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
mark	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
company	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
awaked	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
draw	O
them	O
any	O
more	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
seeing	O
this	O
boy	O
Sullivan	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
M.	O
Quist	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
served	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
aniseed	O
at	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gisby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Kennedy	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Gisby	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
two	O
husbands	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
before	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
one	O
pint	O
after	O
eleven	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
mistress	O
cleared	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
twelve	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
come	O
again	O
that	O
night	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
gin	O
?	O
Gisby	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
again	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
you	O
out	O
three-pence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
Gisby	O
.	O
I	O
give	O
change	O
to	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
very	O
seldom	O
take	O
notice	O
to	O
whom	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
M'Lean	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
ask	O
this	O
boy	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
boy	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
new	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
M.	O
Quist	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
Craycraft	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
;	O
Wapping	O
;	O
last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
this	O
lad	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
Saltpetre	O
bank	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
chair	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
said	O
some	O
bad	O
word	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
some	O
bad	O
work	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
into	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
hearing	O
no	O
disturbance	O
at	O
all	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
arm	O
upon	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
,	O
up	O
came	O
the	O
lad	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
crying	O
and	O
whining	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
words	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
these	O
people	O
have	O
done	O
something	O
amiss	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
twelve	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
watchmen	O
and	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
every	O
corner	O
about	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nobody	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
Well-street	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Nightingale-lane	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
running	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
lad	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
lad	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
hole	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
and	O
locked	O
him	O
up	O
about	O
three	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
was	O
named	O
Cassady	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
which	O
is	O
Craycraft	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
patch	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
cheek	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jack	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
as	O
you	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Sullivan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
sham	O
a	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
as	O
if	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
mistrust	O
us	O
.	O
Chambers	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Justices	O
how	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sucking	O
call	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Nicholson	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
tall	O
man	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
spoke	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
;	O
that	O
Nicholson	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
spare	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
about	O
his	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
two-pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
boy	O
taken	O
?	O
Chambers	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
Monday	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
singing	O
ballads	O
about	O
Wilkes	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
sent	O
my	O
apprentice	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
cutlace	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
blood-thirsty	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
unarmed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
to	O
some	O
paviours	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
with	O
assistance	O
secured	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
lad	O
tell	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
another	O
lad	O
being	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Chambers	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Terry	O
Finley	O
of	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
lad	O
follows	O
picking	O
of	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
Craycraft	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
blast	O
you	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
coloured	O
clothes	O
on	O
as	O
now	O
;	O
one	O
wore	O
lighter	O
clothes	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
with	O
flapped	O
hats	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-way	O
,	O
Black-horse-yard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
For	O
Craycraft	O
.	O
Honor	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Craycraft	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
from	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
from	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
at	O
another	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Deptford	O
,	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
London-bridge	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Quist	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Quist	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
turned	O
out	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
H.	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
At	O
whose	O
house	O
did	O
you	O
drink	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
H.	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Fenning	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Craycraft	O
?	O
H.	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
.	O
Mathew	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Newman	O
,	O
-	O
Sullins	O
,	O
Jerrat	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Dunn	O
,	O
appeared	O
for	O
Bourn	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
coal	O
cellar	O
in	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
native	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
439	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
shooting	O
off	O
a	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
hall	O
at	O
Phillis	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
garden	O
ground	O
of	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Phillis	O
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
Phillis	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brumpton-lane	B-place
,	I-place
opposite	I-place
the	I-place
Bell	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
garden-ground	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
for	O
bigamy	O
last	O
March	O
sessions	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
branded	O
(	O
see	O
his	O
trial	O
,	O
No	O
245	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
;	O
)	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
misfortune	O
of	O
falling	O
down	O
and	O
hurting	O
his	O
leg	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
his	O
leg	O
was	O
excessive	O
black	O
and	O
bad	O
;	O
all	O
his	O
discourse	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
repented	O
of	O
his	O
past	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
it	O
before	O
God	O
nor	O
man	O
:	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
condescend	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
utter	O
ruin	O
of	O
us	O
both	O
;	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
lodging	O
by	O
Nibes	O
's	O
pound	O
by	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
supper	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
flung	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
somebody	O
fly	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
son	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
man	O
among	O
the	O
gooseberry-bushes	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
voice	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
your	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
his	O
son	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
son	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
for	O
his	O
clothes	O
(	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
had	O
continued	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
)	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
desire	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
move	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
such	O
word	O
by	O
his	O
son	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
pushed	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
way	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
front-door	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
what	O
would	O
become	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
abrupt	O
manner	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
upbraid	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
his	O
bread	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
endeavour	O
for	O
his	O
bread	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
power	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
terror	O
,	O
something	O
seized	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
afterwards	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
as	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
what	O
answer	O
he	O
made	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
struggled	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
spare	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
his	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
strength	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
desired	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
spare	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
well	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
(	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
round	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
fired	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
me	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
left-side	O
of	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ball	O
came	O
out	O
on	O
my	O
right-side	O
;	O
it	O
went	O
through	O
my	O
neck	O
(	O
she	O
showed	O
the	O
scars	O
,	O
which	O
showed	O
the	O
ball	O
must	O
go	O
through	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
her	O
neck	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
arbour	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
another	O
pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
shot	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
.	O
with	O
his	O
throat	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
till	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
last	O
Friday	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
together	O
?	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
unhappy	O
life	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
apprehend	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
proposals	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
sooner	O
beg	O
my	O
bread	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
imagine	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
himself	O
?	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
must	O
imagine	O
justice	O
would	O
overtake	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
fall	O
when	O
he	O
shot	O
you	O
?	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
supported	O
by	O
two	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
as	O
other	O
drunken	O
men	O
are	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
apartment	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
below	O
murdering	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
down	O
they	O
will	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
listened	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
's	O
voice	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
wedding	O
at	O
Kensington	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
the	O
maid	O
cry	O
murder	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
pistol	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Ewen	O
's	O
hair	O
and	O
cap	O
all	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
,	O
hold	O
me	O
,	O
hold	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
wretch	O
(	O
or	O
that	O
poor	O
creature	O
)	O
has	O
murdered	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
fired	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
E.	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
fired	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Mrs.	O
Freeman	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
shot	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
shot	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
bullet	O
is	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
doctor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
blood	O
running	O
down	O
her	O
neck	O
:	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
heard	O
another	O
pistol	O
go	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fly	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
gone	O
into	O
Essex	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
she	O
that	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hospital	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
terror	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
planted	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
few	O
of	O
some	O
that	O
were	O
mine	O
when	O
I	O
married	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
over	O
some	O
houshold	O
goods	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
moment	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
made	O
over	O
some	O
houses	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
Hyde	O
park-corner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
that	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
P.	O
Ewen	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
my	O
houses	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
ladle	O
was	O
bought	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
firing	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
small	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
water	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
turn	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
till	O
she	O
turned	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
friends	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buss	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
mouth	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
snatched	O
her	O
head	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
went	O
off	O
accidentally	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
another	O
pistol	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
another	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
myself	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
carried	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
parted	O
from	O
me	O
26	O
or	O
27	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
married	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
his	O
trial	O
and	O
conviction	O
for	O
bigamy	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
receiving	O
his	O
punishment	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
440	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Wiggons	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
441	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
pounds	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Phebe	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
442	O
,	O
443	O
,	O
444	O
,	O
445	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
Isabella	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bell	I-pers
Mayor	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Shields	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
pounds	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
Phebe	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
All	O
five	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
446.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
His	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
447	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christiana	B-pers
Phinias	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
callimanco	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
19	O
++	O
Jane	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
silver	O
tankard	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
about	O
my	O
tankard	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
J.	O
Gee	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
law	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
tankard	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
in	O
King-street	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
son	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
reason	O
for	O
telling	O
my	O
mistress	O
the	O
tankard	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
that	O
cellar	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
myself	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
shoes	O
there	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
suspect	O
the	O
tankard	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
448	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
worsted	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Collin	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Collin	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
book-binder	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
long	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
afternoon	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
Why	O
with	O
company	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
past	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
past	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
stupid	O
in	O
liquor	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
did	O
she	O
carry	O
you	O
into	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
The	O
ground	O
floor	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
four	O
guineas	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
rest	O
again	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
She	O
dropped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
opposite	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
discovered	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
soon	O
discovered	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
all	O
over	O
for	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
had	O
you	O
visited	O
this	O
lady	O
before	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
your	O
going	O
there	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
army	O
last	O
was	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
serjeant	O
,	O
so	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
sure	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
lost	O
your	O
money	O
somewhere	O
else	O
.	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
four	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
working	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
quite	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
with	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
four	O
guineas	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
suffered	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
tote	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Boot	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
hot	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
evidence	O
once	O
swore	O
me	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
keeper	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
six	O
weeks	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
.	O
Burton	O
.	O
One	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
took	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
prosecuto	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
other	O
money	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
gone	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
this	O
woman	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
