TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
MANSFIELD	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	O
STAFFORD	O
SMYTHE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BATHURST	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Christop	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Galbreath	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harbridge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cafe	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Innes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pond	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sturdy	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
Will	B-pers
Fillingham	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Garey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Langfer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
.	O
591	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tyler's-court	B-place
,	I-place
Carnaby-market	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
Old	O
Michaelmas	O
day	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
alarmed	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
again	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
my	O
rounds	O
about	O
ten	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
my	O
constant	O
method	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
again	O
also	O
at	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
again	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
was	O
drawn	O
three	O
parts	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
could	O
hang	O
without	O
falling	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
waiting	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
masquerade	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
here	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
masquerade	O
is	O
not	O
kept	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
alarmed	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
he	O
rolled	O
himself	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davenport	O
,	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
as	O
if	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
halloo	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
the	O
pin	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
Pratt	O
.	O
The	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
is	O
a	O
square	O
pin	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
turned	O
round	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
iron	O
bars	O
above	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
air	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
trying	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
reach	O
down	O
and	O
unkey	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
tried	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davenport	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
shop	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
bars	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
keyed	O
the	O
windows	O
both	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
the	O
masquerade	O
was	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
sister	O
lives	O
in	O
Carnaby-market	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
shop-window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
shop	O
or	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
at	O
Richmond	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Curtis	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Curtis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
then	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Curtis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
burning	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
left	O
burning	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
592	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Duvall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
1	O
st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
the	B-place
Poultry	I-place
towards	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
593	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
and	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
laced	O
with	O
thread-lace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
glove	O
knots	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Waldon	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
related	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Bowman	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
discharged	O
her	O
for	O
leaving	O
my	O
house	O
door	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
for	O
her	O
wages	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
should	O
be	O
looked	O
over	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
all	O
was	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
come	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
things	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
brought	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Purlin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
this	O
bundle	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
594	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crees	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Creese	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
September	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	B-place
Almonry	I-place
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
women	O
came	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
offering	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
leave	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Glass-house-street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
nursing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
at	O
Robert	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Westminster	O
;	O
a	O
girl	O
that	O
works	O
plain-work	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
masters	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pledge	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
has	O
taken	O
no	O
pains	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Nanny	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
other	O
name	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
595	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Urquhart	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Francis	B-pers
Piggott	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Francis	B-pers
Piggott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
physician	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Colchester	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Winchester	O
in	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Reading	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
daughter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Cranford-bridge	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
tender	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
quick	O
,	O
quick	O
,	O
looking	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
also	O
from	O
me	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
King	O
Edward	B-pers
the	O
VIth	O
's	O
shilling	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
seemingly	O
towards	O
Maidenhead	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
driver	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
quick	O
,	O
the	O
driver	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
his	O
horses	O
were	O
tired	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
expedient	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
London	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
brother	O
at	O
Richmond	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
advise	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
being	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
watch	O
case	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Stevenson	O
had	O
been	O
negligent	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
word	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
watch-case	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
having	O
received	O
a	O
warning	O
bill	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
being	O
lost	O
;	O
this	O
only	O
being	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
justified	O
in	O
stopping	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
described	O
,	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
(	O
the	O
case	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Frank	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Piggott	O
.	O
That	O
evidence	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
with	O
him	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Rochford	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
gold	O
seal	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Rochford	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
pawned	O
things	O
in	O
that	O
name	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
(	O
the	O
seal	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
Curle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
What	O
can	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
time	O
for	O
my	O
evidence	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
trial	O
off	O
,	O
made	O
affidavit	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
a	O
material	O
witness	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
that	O
woman	O
passed	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
order	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
.	O
596	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Segware	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
coloured	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
yellow	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
white	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pink	O
and	O
black	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
white	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
striped	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
coloured	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
coloured	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
black	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
shoes	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
seven	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
two	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Catherine	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
the	O
Rolls	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
lame	O
of	O
the	O
palsy	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
nurse	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
left	O
that	O
door	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
smith	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
sheet	O
and	O
some	O
odd	O
things	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
West	O
Harding-street	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
above	O
twenty	O
different	O
times	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Wassells	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
her	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
597	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
between	O
the	B-place
Hole-in-the-wall	I-place
and	O
Cannonbury-house	B-place
;	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
rifling	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
arms	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
quite	O
moon-light	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
always	O
said	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Southgate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Hole-in-the-wall	O
by	O
Islington	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
twenty	O
rods	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Southgate	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
Hole-in-the-wall	O
from	O
Cannonbury-house	O
?	O
Southgate	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
walking	O
with	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Canonbury-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Southgate	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
Newington	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Dorril	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
took	O
his	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Dorril	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
lives	O
about	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
for	O
a	O
living	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
fighting	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxers	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
battle	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
second	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
wait	O
till	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
wait	O
six	O
hours	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
came	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
house-joiner	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spragg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
master	O
carpenter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
six	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
my	O
place	O
was	O
much	O
laid	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
and	O
missed	O
nothing	O
;	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
many	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
bricklayer	O
and	O
plaisterer	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
carpenter	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Spragg	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
evening	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
work	O
there	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
at	O
Waltham-abbey	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
when	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
English	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
near	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
work	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
her	O
gate	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Spragg	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Lamb	O
that	O
works	O
with	O
me	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
place	O
you	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
from	O
Islington	O
?	O
English	O
.	O
As	O
high	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
it	O
is	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
miles	O
,	O
that	O
place	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
eight	O
mile	O
stone	O
from	O
Shoreditch	O
church	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Spragg	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
supper	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
;	O
we	O
waited	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
bacon	O
and	O
potatoes	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
ten	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
my	O
labourer	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
into	O
Lancashire	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
company	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
Lamb	O
and	O
he	O
supped	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
Lamb	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
Pain	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
598	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Brittain	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
coach-hammer	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
French	I-place
Horn	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
stable-yard	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
hammer-cloths	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
from	O
the	O
carriages	O
;	O
my	O
ostler	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
two	O
Jews	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Jews	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
from	O
the	O
Thursday	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
let	O
out	O
upon	O
bail	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
the	O
cloths	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
lost	O
the	O
two	O
cloths	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
carriages	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
two	O
hammer-cloths	O
from	O
off	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
's	O
carriages	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
tried	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
very	O
readily	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Steel	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Steel	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
blame	O
an	O
innocent	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
want	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
599	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Lady	O
Anne	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Aug.	O
31	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowdell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Lady	O
Anne	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
wait	O
for	O
an	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
my	O
Lady	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
begging	O
letter	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
wait	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
pepper-castor	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
side-board	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
no-body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
besides	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
;	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
described	O
the	O
arms	O
on	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pepper-castor	O
and	O
one	O
spoon	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
on	O
Aug.	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
seven	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
pepper-castor	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
arms	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
advertisement	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
with	O
the	O
things	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
Lady	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
her	O
arms	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
caster	O
,	O
and	O
crest	O
on	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
crimes	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
.	O
600	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
forty-two	O
guineas	O
,	O
twelve	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
nine	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Two	I-place
Brewers	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
Long	I-place
ditch	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
on	O
February	O
22	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
maid	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
wentup	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chissel	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
trunk	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
turned	O
upside	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
club-box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
always	O
kept	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
safety	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
witness	O
here	O
will	O
inform	O
the	O
court	O
what	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
key	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
stewards	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
that	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
maid	O
that	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
odd	O
things	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
named	O
Collins	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
to	O
Tothill-fields	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
desire	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
received	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
guards	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
company	O
was	O
upon	O
duty	O
,	O
the	O
serjeant	O
told	O
us	O
Curtis	O
had	O
heard	O
we	O
were	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
Colonel	O
did	O
not	O
advertise	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
deserter	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
woman	O
here	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
286	O
it	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
for	O
another	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Curtis	O
the	O
soldier	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Collins	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
when	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
answered	O
she	O
had	O
ten	O
guineas	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
along	O
of	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
the	O
club-box	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Thames	O
by	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
bond	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
papers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
55	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
forty	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
particularly	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
small	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
Collins	B-pers
the	O
evidence	O
here	O
ten	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
?	O
Beckford	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
deserve	O
my	O
fate	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
more	O
accessary	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
inform	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
stood	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
clubs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
asked	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
club	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
his	O
money	O
last	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
club	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
warrant	O
you	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
booty	O
in	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
whereabouts	O
does	O
it	O
stand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
intelligence	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Tothill-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brown	O
box	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Tothill-fields	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
ten	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brown	O
canvass	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
guinea	O
was	O
an	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
set	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
S.	O
Collins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
purse	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
waterman	O
that	O
lives	O
by	O
Millbank	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Six	O
Bells	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
returned	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
fuddled	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
pieces	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
twenty-one	O
guineas	O
in	O
guineas	O
and	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
9	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
altered	O
his	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Oxford	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
from	O
for	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
fetch	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
it	O
down	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dangerous	O
to	O
travel	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
twenty-one	O
guineas	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
without	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
without	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
paid	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
except	O
when	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
;	O
I	O
left	O
20	O
guineas	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shirt	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
dimity	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
bead	O
necklace	O
with	O
silver	O
spreaders	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
601	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Leay	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
my	O
shew-glass	O
was	O
broke	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
dozen	O
and	O
two	O
stock-buckles	O
in	O
my	O
shew-glass	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
count	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
seventeen	O
remaining	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cartwright	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
take	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shew-glass	O
with	O
a	O
stock-buckle	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
reached	O
out	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
fling	O
the	O
buckles	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
three	O
lodged	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
our	O
journeyman	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
while	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
pick	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nigh	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
by	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
buckles	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
boy	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
chimney	O
sweeper	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
answerable	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
behaves	O
well	O
at	O
home	O
Mary	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
goes	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
a	O
sweeping	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
having	O
washed	O
his	O
face	O
after	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
persuade	O
himself	O
the	O
right	O
person	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
,	O
a	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
such	O
would	O
do	O
well	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
clean	O
before	O
committed	O
.	O
602	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Smellar	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Sinclare	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whitaker	O
's	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
.	O
there	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
603	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Roger	B-pers
M'Daniel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pork	O
chine	O
bones	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Abraham	B-pers
Law	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
goods	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
by	O
commission	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-market	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
while	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
unloading	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
undo	O
a	O
basket	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
four	O
chine	O
bones	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mess	O
.	O
Bell	O
and	O
Goff	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
bones	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
staff	O
cross	O
me	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
throw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
by	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bones	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
throwed	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
fellow	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
that	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
when	O
this	O
accident	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
604	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
,	O
September	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
605	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	B-place
Mansion	I-place
house	I-place
the	O
day	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Denmark	O
dined	O
there	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
taped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cund	I-pers
's	O
hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
o'clock	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Denmark	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
down	O
Cheapside	O
from	O
near	O
King-street	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
several	O
attempts	O
at	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
pocket-lid	O
being	O
in	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
coach-way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
quick	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cund	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
opposite	O
the	O
Mansion	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
honest	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
bread	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farrier	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
sessions	O
goes	O
over	O
Paine	O
's	O
head	O
but	O
he	O
transports	O
twenty	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
last	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
606	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Cain	I-pers
;	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Can	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
unknown	O
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16	O
th	O
September	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
the	O
hand	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
)	O
the	O
wife	O
said	O
that	O
's	O
my	O
husband	O
'	O
a	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
boys	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
but	O
walked	O
on	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
prosecute	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
expence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
other	O
boys	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
607	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Greaves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
street	O
called	O
South	B-place
Park	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
joining	O
to	O
divers	O
other	O
respective	O
dwelling-houses	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
and	O
voluntarily	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
it	O
was	O
burnt	O
down	O
and	O
consumed	O
.	O
+	O
Colonel	O
Edward	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
when	O
this	O
fire	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
execution	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
gave	O
her	O
notice	O
of	O
my	O
coming	O
8	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
clothes	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
burnt	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
lamentable	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
burnt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Col.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
believe	O
thirty-three	O
shirts	O
and	O
nine	O
waistcoats	O
at	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
fair	O
play	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Greaves	O
had	O
pawned	O
any	O
linen	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
seventeen	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jason	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
sixteen	O
shirts	O
and	O
eight	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
shirts	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
ruffled	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
burnt	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
pledging	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
made	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
notice	O
when	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
town	O
?	O
Col	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
that	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
notice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
given	O
any	O
direction	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
made	O
up	O
for	O
you	O
or	O
altered	O
?	O
Col.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
house	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
some	O
neckcloths	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
into	O
stocks	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
to	O
be	O
ruffled	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
treat	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
this	O
room	O
?	O
Col.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
herself	O
delivered	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
room	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
choice	O
of	O
three	O
rooms	O
;	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
except	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
my	O
shirts	O
were	O
all	O
callico	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
sixteen	O
shirts	O
and	O
eight	O
waistcoats	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
five	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
eight	O
months	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
her	O
property	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
all	O
brought	O
within	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
were	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
?	O
Jason	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
Colonel	O
that	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
name	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Jason	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
last	O
parcel	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Colonel	O
sent	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
coach	O
?	O
Jason	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
one	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Colonel	O
)	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
niece	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	B-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
shirts	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
17.	O
shirts	O
and	O
3	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Colonel	O
.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Stainsby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
possession	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
happened	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
sent	O
word	O
he	O
would	O
advertise	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
coming	O
and	O
coming	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
goods	O
advertised	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
set	O
them	O
on	O
fire	O
and	O
burn	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
that	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
possession	O
with	O
me	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
morning	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
her	O
room	O
was	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
forward	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
and	O
kill	O
her	O
cat	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
cat	O
ran	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
fire	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
cat	O
was	O
a	O
witch	O
and	O
would	O
haunt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
kill	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
one	O
day	O
we	O
must	O
kill	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
day	O
we	O
must	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
kill	O
her	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
found	O
fault	O
with	O
the	O
fluttishness	O
of	O
her	O
maid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
heard	O
her	O
talk	O
of	O
killing	O
the	O
cat	O
before	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Stainsby	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
mentioned	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
blowing	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bellows	O
to	O
blow	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
some	O
body	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
your	O
house	O
is	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
smother	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
by	O
the	O
people	O
washing	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
usual	O
to	O
smoke	O
so	O
at	O
such	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
blowing	O
the	O
fire	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
smother	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
some	O
body	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
your	O
house	O
is	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
the	O
fire	O
comes	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
window	O
;	O
it	O
broke	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
bed	O
chamber	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
any	O
fire	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fifteen	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
burst	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
nigh	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
smoke	O
and	O
sulphur	O
came	O
so	O
strong	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
George	B-pers
Dundass	I-pers
in	O
bed	O
above	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
leads	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
hallooed	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
you	O
can	O
run	O
through	O
smoke	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
through	O
fire	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
words	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
madam	O
has	O
set	O
this	O
house	O
on	O
fire	O
on	O
purpose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
fire	O
began	O
in	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
Stainsby	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
smoke	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
break	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
first	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
fire	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
kitchen	O
fire	O
I	O
light	O
up	O
myself	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Stainsby	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
money	O
lent	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
?	O
Stainsby	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
chimnies	O
were	O
situated	O
?	O
Stainsby	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
parlour	O
fire	O
is	O
forward	O
so	O
is	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
stack	O
of	O
chimnies	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
house	O
quite	O
burnt	O
down	O
?	O
Stainsby	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
burnt	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
fell	O
in	O
;	O
this	O
house	O
was	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Capt	O
.	O
Townsend	O
's	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dundass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
cat	O
would	O
run	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
fire	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
once	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
cat	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
kill	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
cat	O
would	O
haunt	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
talk	O
thus	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
fire	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
sulphur	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
thinking	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
lighting	O
the	O
fire	O
below	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
began	O
to	O
increase	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
got	O
my	O
clothes	O
on	O
;	O
Stainsby	O
called	O
out	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
fire	O
crack	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
smoke	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
down	O
through	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
cracking	O
in	O
?	O
Dundoss	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
forwards	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
garret	O
;	O
the	O
cracking	O
was	O
immediately	O
under	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Col.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
Dundass	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
the	O
sabbath-day	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
happened	O
she	O
expected	O
him	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
Sunday	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
burnt	O
out	O
once	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
first	O
about	O
fire	O
?	O
Dundass	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
cat	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Dundass	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
Dundass	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
wild	O
to	O
come	O
near	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
would	O
come	O
nigh	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
chimney	O
on	O
fire	O
?	O
Dundass	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Greaves	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
's	O
in	O
Shire-lane	O
,	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
letter	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
neither	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
nor	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
rooms	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Col	O
Hamilton	B-pers
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
things	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
message	O
from	O
the	O
Colonel	O
about	O
his	O
coming	O
home	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
message	O
came	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
return	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
that	O
message	O
come	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
back	O
when	O
your	O
mistress	O
sent	O
you	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
's	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
burnt	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
dining-room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
time	O
had	O
your	O
mistress	O
used	O
to	O
rise	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
She	O
sometimes	O
arose	O
by	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
chamber-windows	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
open	O
all	O
her	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
only	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
candle	O
left	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
errand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
candle	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
then	O
go	O
into	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
both	O
open	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
one	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
always	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
smoke	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
by	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
forward	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
fire	O
came	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
very	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
a	O
rush-light	O
burning	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
watch-light	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
it	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
soulness	O
of	O
the	O
chimnies	O
?	O
M.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
The	O
kitchen	O
and	O
parlour	O
chimnies	O
were	O
both	O
swept	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
open	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
,	O
directly	O
opposite	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
generally	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
windows	O
open	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
windows	O
shut	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
on	O
my	O
clothes	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
smoke	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
windows	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
windows	O
,	O
both	O
were	O
shut	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
general	O
a	O
very	O
early	O
riser	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
generally	O
open	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
smoke	O
when	O
the	O
shutters	O
were	O
shut	O
?	O
F.	O
Parker	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
crevices	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
inside	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
between	O
the	O
brickwork	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
;	O
Col.	O
Hamilton	O
never	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
leave	O
some	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
fellow	O
Stainsby	O
has	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
smoked	O
tobacco	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
all	O
this	O
is	O
spite	O
and	O
malice	O
entirely	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
none	O
more	O
cautious	O
of	O
fire	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
dreadfully	O
burnt	O
out	O
before	O
at	O
Wapping	O
wall	O
;	O
this	O
Bolland	O
wanted	O
to	O
arrest	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
bailiffs	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
and	O
appraise	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
two	O
fellows	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bolland	O
,	O
take	O
that	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
smokes	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Col.	O
Hamilton	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
workwoman	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
some	O
stocks	O
,	O
I	O
employed	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
garret	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
garret	O
that	O
opened	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
surely	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
days	O
:	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
my	O
trial	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
confusion	O
of	O
my	O
attorney	O
,	O
my	O
witnesses	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
500	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
an	O
undeniable	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
that	O
any	O
poor	O
woman	O
has	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
robbed	O
my	O
husband	O
of	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
wants	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
fire	O
came	O
,	O
unless	O
by	O
this	O
cat	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
under	O
the	O
grate	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
Stainsby	O
threatened	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
he	O
looks	O
so	O
like	O
a	O
thief	O
I	O
hated	O
him	O
,	O
every	O
word	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
;	O
Dundass	O
said	O
,	O
Bolland	O
offered	O
him	O
20	O
l.	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
farthest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dundass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Golding	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rotherhithe	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
reason	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
word	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rotherhithe	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
extremely	O
gay	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
as	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
honest	O
and	O
sober	O
to	O
the	O
greatest	O
degree	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
mean	O
and	O
piciful	O
by	O
her	O
appearance	O
and	O
character	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
gossiping	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
people	O
of	O
character	O
do	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
connected	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Whitewood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Rotherhithe	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wapping	O
Old-stairs	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wapping	O
Old-stairs	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Constable	O
Lamden	B-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
good	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Springle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
she	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-three	O
callico	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
608	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rice	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
||	O
Rice	O
Williams	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	B-place
Marquis	I-place
of	I-place
Granby	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
hire	O
myself	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
upon	O
other	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
wanted	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
men	O
began	O
to	O
hussel	O
gold	O
about	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
understand	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
put	O
down	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
would	O
answer	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
against	O
three	O
others	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
my	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
play	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
your	O
watch	O
is	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
his	O
friend	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Tyburn-road	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Soho	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
walked	O
on	O
to	O
Leicester-fields	O
and	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
deliver	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
hanged	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
,	O
unless	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
dangerous	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
me	O
then	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
did	O
you	O
consent	O
to	O
his	O
putting	O
your	O
watch	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
slipped	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
without	O
my	O
consent	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
you	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
out	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
hat	O
yourself	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
brother	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
by	O
force	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
why	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
brother	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
what	O
had	O
passed	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
fetched	O
down	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
brother	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	B-pers
the	O
constable	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
my	O
brother	O
the	O
guinea	O
that	O
my	O
brother	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
won	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
any	O
satisfaction	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
and	O
Major	O
Spinnage	B-pers
;	O
when	O
Major	O
Spinnage	B-pers
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
Price	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
hanged	O
ten	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
brother	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
delivered	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
any	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
obstreperous	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
bind	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
reading	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
;	O
Williams	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
name	O
Price	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
Welchman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
might	O
by	O
your	O
name	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
;	O
very	O
possible	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
gentleman	O
that	O
wanted	O
a	O
footman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
our	O
footman	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
I	O
may	O
enquire	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
direction	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
for	O
beer	O
,	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
cheese	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
than	O
of	O
the	O
farthest	O
person	O
living	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
gaming	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
their	O
money	O
;	O
said	O
Williams	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
soon	O
win	O
all	O
their	O
money	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
hiding	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
under	O
a	O
hat	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
won	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
together	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
win	O
all	O
these	O
mens	O
money	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
play	O
no	O
farther	O
under	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
lost	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
for	O
another	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
Williams	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
stake	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
's	O
watch	O
for	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
watch	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
Williams	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
men	O
will	O
come	O
upon	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
his	O
brother	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
speak	O
Welch	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
;	O
they	O
after	O
that	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
a	O
defraud	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
night	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
robbery	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
,	O
Member	O
of	O
Parliament	O
for	O
Berkshire	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
twice	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
nine	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
staid	O
nine	O
days	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
town	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
:	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
which	O
he	O
says	O
of	O
speaking	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
service	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Thomas	O
Levis	O
,	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
that	O
bound	O
him	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gravesbarg	I-pers
,	O
a	O
lapidary	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lyun	I-pers
,	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Huckle	O
,	O
that	O
served	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
lately	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
609	O
,	O
610	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Plymonth	B-pers
Jumboe	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
silver	O
tops	O
for	O
castors	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
principal	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
obtained	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
promise	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
law	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
received	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
611	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Paul	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
612	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Singer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barnham	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Barnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Isleworth	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
meadow-ground	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Isleworth	B-place
and	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gate	O
was	O
spiked	O
up	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
gelding	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spike	O
was	O
drawn	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
advertised	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Barnham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
that	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
gardens	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
Uxbridge-moor	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
confession	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
gate	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
consederate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
any	O
favour	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
?	O
Barnham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Barnham	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
him	O
to	O
Longford	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
adrift	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Lammas	O
meadow	O
just	O
by	O
Longford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
enquired	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
meadow	O
there	O
?	O
Barnham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Isleworth	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
bring	O
an	O
innocent	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
drawed	O
the	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
him	O
to	O
Long	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Lammas	O
field	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
confession	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
upon	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
farmer	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
liquor	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
sober	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
liquor	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
liquor	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
and	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
among	O
fix	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drank	O
two	O
glasses	O
of	O
wine	O
and	O
one	O
draught	O
of	O
porter	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Harmsworth	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
all	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
our	O
parts	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
behave	O
ill.	O
William	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Harmsworth	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
other	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
thirty	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
married	O
his	O
sisters	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
613	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilsham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
September	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
614	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Grimstone	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
worsted	O
stocking	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
alley	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
called	O
Chequer-alley	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
blue	O
like	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
hung	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
a	O
woman	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
hallooed	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
here	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
in	O
James	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
Featherstone-street	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
took	O
my	O
things	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lipsey	I-pers
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
above	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Abraham	B-pers
Frankmore	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kelsoy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	O
Stadall	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
615	O
,	O
616	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
with	O
three	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hopegood	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hackney	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Cambridge	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Botsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Foster	B-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hopegood	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
two	O
boys	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
at	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
confessed	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
's	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
named	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
Hopegood	O
's	O
mother	O
.	O
Betsworth	O
.	O
Hopegood	O
said	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
that	O
Andrews	O
gave	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brebrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Pell	O
:	O
Hopegood	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitte	O
d	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
evidence	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
that	O
Andrews	O
and	O
Cooper	O
broke	O
a	O
house	O
open	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
leading	O
to	O
Hackney	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
Andrews	O
said	O
Cooper	O
broke	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
much	O
about	O
dark	O
.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Bethnal-green	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
white	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
lying	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Hopegood	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hopegood	I-pers
,	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
whose	O
is	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
16	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Andrews	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Hopegood	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
See	O
Hopegood	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
No	O
288	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
617	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Hopegood	I-pers
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gilford	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
duffil	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Uriah	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Uriah	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Catherine-wheel-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
market	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
meat	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
my	O
drawer	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
gone	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
Gilford	O
came	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
thief	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
a	O
teaspoon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hopegood	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
Brebrook	O
had	O
Hopegood	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
