TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
[	O
Price-Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Heathfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burbridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Spendelow	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Ealey	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickles	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Mussen	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Snowden	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Town	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
James	O
Lock	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
.	O
495.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
four	O
iron	O
window-bars	O
,	O
the	O
weight	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
fixed	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
August	O
30	O
.	O
The	O
evidences	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
496	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
handing	O
my	O
wife	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
near	O
Bartlet's-buildings	B-place
;	O
I	O
felt-something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
carriageway	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
stand	O
of	O
hackney	O
coaches	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
moon	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
within	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Barbara	O
Crookshanks	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
not	O
Gay	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
call	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
497	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Offer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bigge	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Bigge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Salisbury-court	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
taking	O
it	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
left	O
shoulder	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
among	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
expecting	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Denmark	O
coming	O
by	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
498	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
callimanco	O
pumps	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parkhurst	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parkhurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
Hampton-court	B-place
,	I-place
called	I-place
the	I-place
Park-house	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
the	O
Park-keeper	O
;	O
his	O
usual	O
hour	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
is	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
help	O
,	O
being	O
infirm	O
;	O
we	O
imagine	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
were	O
helping	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
?	O
E.	O
Parkhurst	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
that	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
Anne	O
Watts	O
's	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
gown	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bullin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
pocket	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
cardinal	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
owned	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
companions	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Sir	O
Philip	B-pers
Musgrove	I-pers
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
Philip	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
read	O
against	O
her	O
in	O
court	O
if	O
she	O
signed	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Contents	O
.	O
``	O
That	O
she	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
listing	O
up	O
the	O
``	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
continued	O
there	O
till	O
three	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
499	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Dolling	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Dolling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Hodsden-green	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sirket	O
,	O
in	O
Wilsden	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
London	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
necessaries	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
on	O
Honey-pot-hill	B-place
,	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
foot	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
horse	O
's	O
bridle	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
moon-light	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
fourpence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
they	O
drew	B-pers
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
from	O
under	O
their	O
arm-pits	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
feet	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Dolling	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
and	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
Westburn-green	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
miles	O
or	O
more	O
from	O
Wilsden	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fork	O
and	O
a	O
rake	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
haymaking	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
fellow-servants	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
return	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
before	O
that	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
you	O
?	O
Dolling	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
sum	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
might	O
offer	O
you	O
that	O
rather	O
than	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
prison	O
?	O
Dolling	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Consider	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
depends	O
upon	O
your	O
evidence	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Dolling	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Dolling	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
lustier	O
man	O
than	O
he	O
a	O
considerable	O
deal	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
him	O
his	O
partner	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
we	O
offered	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
partner	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
either	O
at	O
the	O
Spotted	O
Dog	O
at	O
Westburn-green	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
;	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
liberty	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
places	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
enquired	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
houses	O
?	O
Dolling	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
barn	O
that	O
night	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
Clarey	O
his	O
partner	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Dolling	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Dolling	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Dolling	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
drank	O
his	O
beer	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
Dolling	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
Dolling	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
partner	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
presently	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
partner	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
body	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
Dolling	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Mention	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
Miller	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
his	O
bag	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
were	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
as	O
I	O
mentioned	O
before	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
Marybone	O
watch	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
his	O
bag	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
that	O
money	O
at	O
'Squire	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
bag	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
salmon	O
man	O
who	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
some	O
salmon	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
uneasy	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
presently	O
came	O
her	O
husband	O
crying	O
salmon	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
coming	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
before	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
robbed	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
his	O
purse	O
;	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
judge	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
500	O
,	O
501	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
quart	O
silver	O
tankards	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
:	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
cannister	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon-tray	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
butter	O
boats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
and	O
salt-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
nine	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
Spanish	O
dollars	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
coin	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
window	O
shutter	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
mahogany	O
desk	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
accounts	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
beaufet	O
except	O
a	O
punch-ladle	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
twelfth	O
year	O
of	O
my	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
father	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
and	O
lighter-man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
besides	O
this	O
lad	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
so	O
ill	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
brought	O
here	O
.	O
Martin	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
502	O
,	O
503	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walldock	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Dollanson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
china	O
punch-bowls	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
George	I-place
alehouse	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
generally	O
do	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
till	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
putting	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
them	O
they	O
flew	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
iron	O
bolt	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
halfpence	O
and	O
silver	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
each	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
eleven	O
china	O
bowls	O
,	O
my	O
books	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
brandy	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
brought	O
me	O
seven	O
of	O
my	O
china	O
bowls	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
break	O
of	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
also	O
my	O
two	O
till	O
drawers	O
empty	O
;	O
Dollanson	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
second	O
night	O
after	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
above	O
twice	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
They	O
,	O
Coward	O
,	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
forced	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
open	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
7	O
punch-bowls	O
and	O
halfpence	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
.	O
)	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
the	O
bowls	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
four	O
more	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
books	O
and	O
writings	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Light	O
Horseman	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Swan-alley	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
just	O
day-light	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
halfpence	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
each	O
18	O
d.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
nine	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Richardson	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
Walldock	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
four	O
china	O
bowls	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
Richardson	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
will	O
buy	O
some	O
china	O
bowls	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
an	O
Indiaman	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
might	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Houndsditch	O
to	O
Moses	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
my	O
brother	O
;	O
they	O
shewed	O
him	O
two	O
large	O
and	O
two	O
small	O
ones	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
given	O
into	O
Richardson	O
's	O
hands	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Red	O
Lion-street	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
a	O
question	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
people	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
robbery	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
about	O
any	O
bowls	O
that	O
were	O
sold	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
to	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
small	O
ones	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
partly	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bowls	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
on	O
the	O
edge	O
,	O
(	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
produced	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
easily	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
damaged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
Richardson	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
Richardson	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
above	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
when	O
Dollanson	O
was	O
there	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Elias	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ham	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
punch	O
bowls	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Anne	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
another	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
Price	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Darlin	I-pers
,	O
No	O
316	O
,	O
317	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
tried	O
with	O
Dollanson	O
by	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
No	O
128	O
,	O
129	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Elias	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
here	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
bowls	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
them	O
by	O
myself	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
price	O
they	O
asked	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
offered	O
them	O
6	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
bowls	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
of	O
the	O
bowls	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
stop	O
the	O
bowls	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
bowls	O
till	O
Aaron	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
told	O
me	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Moses	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
?	O
Elias	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
bowl	O
?	O
Elias	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
that	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
another	O
bowl	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
has	O
a	O
pea-hen	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
offered	O
both	O
these	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
bowls	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Good	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
's	O
window	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
light	O
his	O
pipe	O
by	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
another	O
man	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
lighting	O
his	O
pipe	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
*	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
once	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Pied	O
Bull	O
bench	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
cat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
seven	O
china	O
bowls	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
this	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
white	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
that	O
home	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
going	O
a	O
milking	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
another	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
that	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
gets	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
generally	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
usually	O
go	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
or	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
bowls	O
and	O
drawers	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
caution	O
to	O
watchmen	O
not	O
to	O
neglect	O
their	O
duty	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
strangers	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
took	O
you	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
Good	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
that	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
his	O
wig	O
was	O
Dollanson	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
darkish	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
smith	O
.	O
Walldock	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
goal	O
may	O
be	O
brought	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
bowls	O
.	O
Dollanson	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
five	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
Sir	O
John	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
clear	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
living	O
by	O
going	O
a	O
portering	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
goal	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
bowls	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
Of	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
In	O
Houndsditch	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
only	O
one	O
man	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
brother	O
to	O
Aaron	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
bowls	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
small	O
ones	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
lives	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
bowls	O
again	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Your	O
brother	O
says	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
people	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cavenban	I-pers
.	O
Walldock	O
gets	O
his	O
living	O
by	O
working	O
with	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
baker	O
live	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
E.	O
Cavenban	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
who	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mother	O
knew	O
Walldock	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
work	O
?	O
M.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Walldock	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
last	O
?	O
M.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
eight	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
.	O
Dollanson	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
carried	O
my	O
things	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dollanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lapidary	O
and	O
glass-man	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
gets	O
his	O
bread	O
by	O
working	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
by	O
portering	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
.	O
504	O
,	O
505	O
,	O
506	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Darlin	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
outside	O
Temple-bar	B-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
cheque	O
;	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
of	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
removed	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
cheque	O
;	O
they	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
last	O
parcel	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
Anne	B-pers
Darlin	I-pers
shuffle	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
pocket-hole	O
,	O
whether	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
or	O
under	O
her	O
coat	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
she	O
looked	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
Lewis	O
asked	O
what	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
1	O
s.	O
she	O
offered	O
me	O
11	O
d.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
Darlin	O
soon	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
recollected	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
looking	O
I	O
found	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
I	O
knew	O
their	O
persons	O
could	O
I	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Strand	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Southampton-street	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
York-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Chandler	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
;	O
Darlin	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
left	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
the	O
journeyman	O
,	O
they	O
three	O
women	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
many	O
questions	O
,	O
they	O
declared	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow-street	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
had	O
amongst	O
them	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
and	O
twenty-pence	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
so	O
young	O
,	O
why	O
they	O
should	O
take	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
;	O
Lewis	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
we	O
can	O
live	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
whoring	O
and	O
thieving	O
.	O
Their	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
Lewis	O
asked	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
cheque	O
for	O
an	O
apron	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
shewed	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
deal	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
muslin	O
there	O
.	O
Price	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
507	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
doll	O
's	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Anne	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Wapping-street	B-place
by	O
the	O
new	O
market	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
shop-window	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
striped	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
doll	O
's	O
petticoat	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
within	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
turn	O
of	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Hague	O
's	O
brother	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
shirt	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
coal	O
heaving	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
King	O
James's-stairs	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
ran	O
by	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
508	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Garton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
blue-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bread-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
a	O
yearly	O
servant	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
my	O
till	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
moidore	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
till	O
since	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
pull	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
scratch	O
over	O
the	O
nose	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
guineas	O
were	O
so	O
marked	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
constable	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
every	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
were	O
marked	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
till	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
unlocked	O
;	O
I	O
usually	O
kept	O
it	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
of	O
this	O
money	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
attempted	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bartlett	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Russell	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
lately	O
he	O
has	O
fallen	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
behaved	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
509	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joshua	B-pers
Chailer	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Chappelow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
dozen	O
of	O
worsted	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stonehewer	I-pers
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Stonebewer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
Talbot-court	B-place
,	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
my	O
uncle	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
a	O
pattern	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
twist	O
to	O
be	O
matched	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
moved	O
from	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
which	O
turns	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
crack	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
where	O
the	O
buttons	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
forwards	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
that	O
person	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
heart	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
person	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
sort	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
pocket	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
little	O
resistance	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
(	O
the	O
buttons	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
sowed	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
coloured	O
thread	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
in	O
that	O
hole	O
are	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
vacancy	O
between	O
two	O
bags	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
match	O
some	O
twist	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
pattern	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
match	O
against	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
nor	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
touch	O
a	O
button	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
buttons	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
at	O
Henley	O
upon	O
Thames	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
goods	O
now	O
,	O
the	O
buttons	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
stand	O
here	O
alive	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
bag	O
of	O
buttons	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Noye	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
shop	O
at	O
Henley	O
upon	O
Thames	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
.	O
-	O
Gibson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
hone	O
st	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Cumberland	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
510	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Christie	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
++	O
Andrew	B-pers
Christie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Red	O
Cow	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Long	B-place
lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
frequently	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Christie	O
's	O
house	O
after	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
Jewin	O
street	O
,	O
were	O
there	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
a	O
pewter	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
close	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
trade	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
something	O
like	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
shipwright	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
look	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
having	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
,	O
whispered	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
eye	O
to	O
his	O
silver	O
mug	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
close	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
whipped	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
left-hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
mug	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
beer	O
shine	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
this	O
mug	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
charge	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
wrong	O
mug	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
511	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seller	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Seller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
One	I-place
Tun	I-place
public-house	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
bottom	I-place
of	I-place
Holbourn-hill	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
drawed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
of	O
having	O
taken	O
a	O
pot	O
and	O
beer	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
that	O
drank	O
once	O
of	O
her	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
drank	O
her	O
beer	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
fore-door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
the	O
back-door	O
;	O
she	O
stood	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
pot	O
concealed	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
going	O
down	O
towards	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
from	O
her	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Another	O
woman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
drank	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
pot	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Seller	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
beyond	O
there	O
,	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
512	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Wallace	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
60	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Michael	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
High-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
grasing	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
hides	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
turn-over	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
60	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
bureau	O
locked	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
some	O
little	O
things	O
before	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
my	O
suspecting	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
freely	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
The	O
false	O
keys	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
unlocked	O
the	O
bureau	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
20	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
ill	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
you	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
brother	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
60	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bureau	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
James	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
sad	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
accuse	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
could	O
you	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
debts	O
which	O
he	O
owed	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mourning	O
coat	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
had	O
you	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Michael	O
's	O
bureau	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
my	O
brother	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
open	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
key	O
that	O
lay	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Michael	O
and	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Marsh	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
charge	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
acquaint	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
writing	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
wrote	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
the	O
letter	O
was	O
,	O
his	O
acknowledging	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
begging	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
must	O
die	O
according	O
to	O
law	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
letter	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
hand	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
officer	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
away	O
and	O
spent	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
47	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
the	O
mother	O
had	O
raised	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
assure	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
brother	O
agree	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
52	O
l.	O
7	O
s	O
5	O
1/2	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
away	O
of	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
as	O
he	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
offered	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
both	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
money	O
had	O
been	O
raised	O
they	O
never	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
513	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Moses	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
Jacob	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
;	O
the	O
paper	O
was	O
deposited	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
at	O
Clapton	B-place
,	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
as	O
we	O
know	O
of	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
what	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
by	O
any	O
means	O
to	O
be	O
destroyed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
labouring	O
gardener	O
,	O
employed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Keith	O
,	O
our	O
gardener	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
garden	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Keith	O
had	O
always	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
that	O
garret	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
laid	O
fruit	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Farro	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
old	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
was	O
my	O
uncle	O
;	O
this	O
paper	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
piece	O
)	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
the	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
with	O
some	O
butter	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
(	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
leaf	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
ledger	O
.	O
)	O
Elias	B-pers
Lindce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
garret	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
ledgers	O
and	O
a	O
journal	O
wanting	O
,	O
the	O
ledger	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
year	O
1744	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
customary	O
every	O
year	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
papers	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boxes	O
are	O
numbered	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
frequently	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
old	O
books	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
any	O
doubts	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
left	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
upon	O
missing	O
the	O
books	O
I	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shop-keeper	O
at	O
Hackney	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
this	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
's	O
power	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
one	O
Johnson	O
,	O
a	O
shop-keeper	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
our	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
back	O
113	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
of	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
79	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Erasmus	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
about	O
96	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
people	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
parcels	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
last	O
February	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
foreign	O
letters	O
,	O
invoices	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
either	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
upwards	O
of	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
him	O
all	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two-pence	O
farthing	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
delivered	O
these	O
two	O
bundles	O
of	O
paper	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
books	O
or	O
paper	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
ledgers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
books	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
sheet	O
here	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
this	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
piece	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
at	O
two-pence	O
or	O
two-pence	O
farthing	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Lindoe	O
.	O
This	O
leaf	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ledgers	O
that	O
was	O
deposited	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
years	O
1722	O
and	O
23.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
Hummerton	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
parcels	O
of	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
's	O
head	O
gardener	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Keith	O
,	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
98	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Keith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
,	O
the	O
garret	O
where	O
these	O
papers	O
lay	O
we	O
go	O
through	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
fruit	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
faithful	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
twenty-two	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Keith	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Keith	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
always	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
punctual	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
of	O
Clapton	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
Guilty	O
12	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
514	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ingledou	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ragget	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
six	O
cheque	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chiswick	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
three	O
children	O
's	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
four	O
cotton	O
bed	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stratton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stratton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
our	O
wash-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
have	O
it	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
oath	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
I	O
attended	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
things	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Ragget	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
left	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash-house	O
,	O
some	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chiswick	I-pers
,	O
some	O
Mr.	O
Stratton	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Blessbold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
breaking	O
open	O
this	O
wash-house	O
,	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Odley	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
shifts	O
,	O
sheets	O
,	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Odley	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Odley	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
offered	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
and	O
asked	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
20	O
d.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Finch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Cold	O
Bath-fields	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
all	O
these	O
which	O
are	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ragget	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
goods	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Stratton	O
's	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Chiswick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash	O
house	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
Old-street	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
which	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
515	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Jarrat	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lessey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lessey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	B-place
;	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
lodging	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
lett	O
with	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Needham	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
pledged	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
tea-kettle	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
pledged	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
516	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
five	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
reputation	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
resolution	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
and	O
others	O
boxes	O
,	O
which	O
occasioned	O
him	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
Zechariah	O
Stafford	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
false	O
entries	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
in	O
February	O
and	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
examining	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
Zechariah	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
lend	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
your	O
master	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Stafford	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
?	O
Stafford	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
tell	O
your	O
master	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Stafford	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
this	O
lad	O
has	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
examining	O
his	O
warehouse	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
lent	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
never	O
no	O
such	O
goods	O
taken	O
in	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
a	O
thing	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
watch-chain	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
presently	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shew-glass	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
master	O
should	O
see	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
his	O
three	O
brothers	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
517	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
when	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
sickness	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
delirious	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
come	O
about	O
again	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
about	O
the	O
21st	O
or	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
?	O
M.	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
She	O
fetched	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
till	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
I	O
enquired	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hospital	O
?	O
M.	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
seven	O
weeks	O
last	O
Thursday	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Baldwin's-gardens	O
;	O
this	O
tea-kettle	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
was	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
last	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
kettle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
another	O
woman	O
pledged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Belton-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
pro	O
duced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
aprons	O
and	O
a	O
napkin	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
full	O
seven	O
months	O
gone	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
young	O
child	O
but	O
fifteen	O
months	O
old	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
mercy	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
and	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bed-quilt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
china	O
bowl	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Sep.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Esther	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Bear	B-place
yard	I-place
,	I-place
Clare-market	I-place
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
lost	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
last	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
weeks	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Pursell	I-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
punch-bowl	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
produced	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
All	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
quitted	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
518	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
August	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
watch	O
maker	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
two	O
different	O
shops	O
,	O
I	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
daughter	O
if	O
we	O
sold	O
watches	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
servant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
More	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
pray	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
make	O
watches	O
and	O
sell	O
watches	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
pray	O
what	O
might	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
four	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
second-hand	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
through	O
the	O
kitchen	O
into	O
my	O
watch-making	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
second-hand	O
watch	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
step	O
backwards	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
name	O
so	O
pat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dyer	O
in	O
Fashion-street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
an	O
oil	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
very	O
lowest	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
it	O
go	O
well	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
ear	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
go	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
10	O
s.	O
worse	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
best	O
into	O
your	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
watch	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
recommend	O
I	O
hung	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
,	O
because	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
I	O
shall	O
want	O
another	O
for	O
a	O
brother	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
I	O
shall	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
another	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
some	O
silver	O
chains	O
or	O
silk	O
strings	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
much	O
deal	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
into	O
a	O
glass-case	O
,	O
there	O
hung	O
some	O
ladies	O
chains	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
several	O
watches	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
chains	O
that	O
hang	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
ladies	O
chains	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
unlocked	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
shew	O
enough	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
drawer	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
steel	O
chains	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
thought	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
this	O
chain	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
steel	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
18	O
d.	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
beat	O
you	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
you	O
shall	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
chain	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
I	O
shall	O
buy	O
one	O
for	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
better	O
customer	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
stand	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
by	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
watch	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
have	O
forgot	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
chain	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
catgut	O
string	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
lay	O
for	O
some	O
space	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
nor	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
thinking	O
him	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
elbow	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
me	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
follow	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
watch-maker	O
's	O
shop	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
space	O
where	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
at	O
going	O
out	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
More	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
you	O
keep	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
my	O
daughter	O
was	O
cutting	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
for	O
tea	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
stepped	O
into	O
my	O
watch-maker	O
's	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
the	O
chain	O
upon	O
the	O
board	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
this	O
rogue	O
has	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
myself	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
another	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
pray	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
watch	O
in	O
order	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
quite	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
it	O
to	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
wear	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
name	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
who	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dyer	O
that	O
recommended	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
up	O
stairs	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
house-door	O
open	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
advertise	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
meet	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
some	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
you	O
stopped	O
him	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bargained	O
for	O
with	O
some	O
shop-made	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
proposal	O
about	O
paying	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
by	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
made	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
make	O
an	O
offer	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
no	O
body	O
about	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
More	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
daughter-in-law	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
attend	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
sold	O
watches	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
More	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
father	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
servant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
More	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
make	O
watches	O
or	O
sell	O
watches	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
step	O
backwards	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
work-shop	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
cut	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
for	O
tea	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
lies	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
we	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
kitchen	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
opposite	O
the	O
shop-door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
father	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
in	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
removed	O
from	O
my	O
seat	O
till	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
workshop	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
father	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
father	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
upon	O
your	O
ringing	O
the	O
bell	O
?	O
S.	O
Cope	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
father	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
work-shop	O
as	O
he	O
always	O
does	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wondered	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bid	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
Mr.	O
More	O
's	O
name	O
over	O
his	O
door	O
?	O
S.	O
Cope	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
board	O
describing	O
his	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
situated	O
?	O
S.	O
Cope	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crown-alley	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
can	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
the	O
watches	O
are	O
kept	O
without	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
my	O
face	O
to	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
's	O
shop-door	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
two	O
different	O
shops	O
,	O
two	O
different	O
houses	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
's	O
shop	O
is	O
very	O
seldom	O
open	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
generally	O
bolted	O
and	O
locked	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
door-way	O
cut	O
through	O
a	O
party	O
wall	O
.	O
James	B-pers
March	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
deliver	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
into	O
trouble	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
countryman	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
Leeds	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
shop-mate	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
to	O
try	O
how	O
it	O
would	O
go	O
against	O
Mr.	O
More	O
's	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
More	O
's	O
again	O
?	O
March	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
More	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
accomptant	O
,	O
I	O
settle	O
accounts	O
for	O
merchants	O
and	O
trades-people	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Debarty	O
a	O
searlet	O
dyer	O
,	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
do	O
business	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
accused	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Debarty	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
knowing	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
character	O
was	O
so	O
fair	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
guilty	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
solemnly	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
not	O
complying	O
with	O
it	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
constable	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
where	O
Mr.	O
More	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
were	O
together	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
that	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
all	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Resback	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Debarty	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Leeds	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
diligent	O
;	O
he	O
lodges	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Resback	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
on	O
his	O
re-examination	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
recollection	O
he	O
mentioned	O
it	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Resback	I-pers
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
nights	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Norton	O
Falgate	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
cruel	O
man	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
depriving	O
and	O
keeping	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
confined	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
in	O
keeping	O
him	O
from	O
sending	O
for	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
Mr.	O
More	O
's	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
himself	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
blame	O
in	O
this	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
his	O
friend	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
friends	O
might	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
before	O
this	O
conversation	O
.	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
him	O
even	O
pen	O
,	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
paper	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
kept	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Resback	O
.	O
Mr.	O
More	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
friends	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
on	O
the	O
second	O
examination	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
;	O
Mr.	O
More	O
said	O
upon	O
his	O
oath	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
Mr.	O
More	O
owned	O
there	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
oil-shop	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
cheapen	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Mr.	O
More	O
say	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
oil-shop	O
was	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
at	O
an	O
oil	O
shop	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
Mr.	O
More	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Debarty	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
More	O
mention	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
?	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Resback	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
night	O
the	O
11th	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Mr.	O
More	O
to	O
cheapen	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
Mr.	O
More	O
lived	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
objection	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
More	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
Mr.	O
More	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
golden	O
letters	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
objection	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Mr.	O
More	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
about	O
his	O
buying	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
necessity	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
name	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
name	O
was	O
More	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
a	O
sign	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
golden	O
letters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
say	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
recovered	O
from	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
apothecary	O
and	O
his	O
friends	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
out	O
into	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
frequently	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Resback	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
deserving	O
character	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
diligent	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
discharge	O
you	O
of	O
calling	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
any	O
earnest	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
word	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Man	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Debarty	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
worked	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
watch	O
upon	O
trial	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
cheapened	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
Man	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
line	O
from	O
his	O
father	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
her	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
liked	O
her	O
we	O
should	O
agree	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
price	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
was	O
35	O
s.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
More	O
.	O
More	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
Sir	O
John	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Debarty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
scarlet	O
dyer	O
by	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
recommendation	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
diligent	O
man	O
as	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
family	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
an	O
extreme	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
very	O
diligent	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
dyer	O
and	O
clothier	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
here	O
to	O
improve	O
himself	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
desiring	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
his	O
son	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
pleased	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
Mr.	O
Debarty	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
More	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
that	O
Saturday	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
from	O
Leeds	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
clerk	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
improve	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
dyeing	O
business	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
an	O
upholstery	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Leeds	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
town	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black-friars	O
,	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Yorkshire-man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
recommendation	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Althwaite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
rope-maker	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Farrer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
distant	O
relation	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
well-behaved	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
519	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Anne	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Anne	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
Hyde-park-corner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
married	O
?	O
A.	O
Wingate	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
David	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
till	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
an	O
execution	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
quarrel	O
about	O
selling	O
fruit	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
served	O
a	O
writ	O
upon	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
;	O
they	O
kicked	O
down	O
my	O
fruit	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
my	O
husband	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
an	O
execution	O
for	O
the	O
cost	O
,	O
and	O
Taylor	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
Hart	O
a	O
Jew	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Smith	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
Taylor	O
's	O
follower	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
Smith	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
roll	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
an	O
ague	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
Taylor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Wingate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
Mr.	O
Hounslow	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
execution	O
against	O
your	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
hither	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
on	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Hart	O
got	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
to	O
Taylor	O
,	O
he	O
to	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
Head	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
one	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
coachman	O
that	O
Taylor	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
goal	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Taylor	O
's	O
spunging-house	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
stopped	O
at	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
Charlotte-street	O
,	O
Taylor	O
was	O
allowed	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
very	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
when	O
it	O
stopped	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
served	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
spoke	O
two	O
words	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
goal	O
immediately	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
discharged	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Colvill-court	O
,	O
near	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
;	O
instead	O
