TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
MARCH	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Chruch-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
Will	B-pers
Hanscombe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anstead	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Noys	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Francis	O
Noys	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
Abrah	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hulme	I-pers
,	O
Job	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Worthy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hurford	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sheredine	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
Silvester	B-pers
Langfield	I-pers
,	O
Rob	B-pers
Winkworth	I-pers
,	O
Alex	B-pers
.	I-pers
John	I-pers
Gagnon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Head	I-pers
,	O
+	O
+	O
Isaac	B-pers
Butterfield	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
Richard	O
Head	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Brain	I-pers
.	O
155	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Webberton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
January	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	B-place
Tuns	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
in	I-place
Fetter-lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
scavenger	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
three	O
children	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
having	O
broken	O
victuals	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
pewter	O
pots	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Seller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Holbourn-hill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
perceived	O
his	O
pocket	O
to	O
stand	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
one	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
turned	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
he	O
made	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
pots	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pots	O
lying	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
door	O
in	O
Flower-de-luce	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
156	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1766	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
cheesemonger	B-place
's	I-place
and	I-place
grocer	I-place
's	I-place
shop	I-place
in	I-place
Chiswell-street	I-place
last	O
June	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
fastened	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
my	O
shutters	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
two	O
with	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
help	O
,	O
help	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Samuel	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
my	O
brother	O
in-law	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
tumbling	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
struggled	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
chamber	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
murder	O
or	O
thieves	O
;	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
our	O
clothes	O
on	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
flap	O
,	O
by	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
wooden	O
frame	O
of	O
a	O
cellar	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
opened	O
while	O
I	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
cellar	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
drawn	O
the	O
staples	O
,	O
and	O
cracked	O
the	O
bolt	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
some	O
iron	O
instrument	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
wrenched	O
open	O
;	O
in	O
searching	O
my	O
till	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
my	O
loose	O
halfpence	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
a	O
drawer	O
on	O
the	O
grocery	O
side	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
farthings	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
reward	O
for	O
taking	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
till	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
boarded	O
and	O
lodged	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
like	O
the	O
shutting	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
again	O
:	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
breeches	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
flung	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
fall	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
catch	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
alarm	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
opening	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
hold	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
on	O
but	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
three	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
looking	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
sun	O
up	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
without	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
toe	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
frame	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
had	O
been	O
wrenched	O
quite	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
comes	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
was	O
wrenched	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
chisel	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
mark	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
will	O
be	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Gilbert	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
before	O
sun-rising	O
?	O
Horn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
yet	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
neighbour	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
rose	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
murder	O
and	O
thieves	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
wits	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
struggle	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Swede	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Judah	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
iron	O
pokers	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
Abraham	B-pers
Judah	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
colour-maker	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	B-place
;	O
we	O
having	O
been	O
robbed	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
people	O
sitting	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
with	O
firearms	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
who	O
came	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
one	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
two	O
iron	O
pokers	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
at	O
a	O
large	O
oven	O
in	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
three	O
yards	O
long	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
weekly	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pokers	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
from	O
me	O
one	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
these	O
two	O
iron	O
pokers	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
pitch	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
pokers	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
beadle	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
pockers	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
pokers	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
manufactory	O
,	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Uriah	B-pers
Judah	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Our	O
house	O
having	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
sat	O
up	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
nights	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
instant	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
bustling	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
stands	O
up	O
a	O
yard	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
father	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
bustle	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
gate	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
pokers	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
,	O
confessed	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
before	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
pokers	O
?	O
Judah	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
;	O
Conway	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
perhaps	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Judah	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
pokers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
work-shop	O
where	O
the	O
pokers	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
join	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
I	O
behaved	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
when	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
china	O
bowls	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
green-stall	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Turnagain-lane	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
garret	O
stairs	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
,	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lodges	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
presently	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
garret	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gardener	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
ask	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
158	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blinkhorn	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blinkhorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hat-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Change	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Selfe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blinkhorn	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
push	O
in	O
our	O
sash-window	O
,	O
the	O
groove	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
hat	O
out	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
Trigg-stairs	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
lighter	O
and	O
laid	O
himself	O
down	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Lambeth-hill	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
toward	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
lad	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
lad	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
jump	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
stairs	O
into	O
a	O
lighter	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
himself	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
downwards	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blinkhorn	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
that	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blinkhorn	O
also	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
own	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
coat	O
running	O
with	O
two	O
hats	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
into	O
a	O
lighter	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bliss	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Bliss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	B-place
in	I-place
White's-alley	I-place
,	I-place
Little	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
pots	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
this	O
pot	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
seeing	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
(	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
King's-head-court	O
out	O
of	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
hustled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
threw	O
this	O
pot	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
moments	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
myself	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
use	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Little	O
Moorfields	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pot	O
lying	O
under	O
a	O
wall	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
washed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixty	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Prince	B-place
's	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
warehouse-man	O
;	O
we	O
having	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
missed	O
goods	O
on	O
mornings	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
counting-house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
watch	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
shut	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
neighbours	O
upon	O
hearing	O
her	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
counting-house	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
cross	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
up	O
from	O
a	O
pile	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
thief	O
;	O
when	O
help	O
came	O
and	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
call	O
it	O
quilted	O
everlasting	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
,	O
nobody	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
stood	O
half	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
there	O
,	O
nobody	O
came	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shut	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
161	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
bushels	O
of	O
green	O
peas	O
in	O
the	O
shells	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
six	O
pecks	O
of	O
French	O
beans	O
in	O
the	O
shells	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Cosgrove	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
390	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Braine	I-pers
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
,	O
1766	O
.	O
+	O
A	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
and	O
conviction	O
of	O
Haines	O
and	O
Braine	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
their	O
trial	O
No	O
262	O
,	O
263	O
,	O
in	O
April	O
sessions	O
1766	O
.	O
)	O
Ralph	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
the	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1766	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
tobacco	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
Haines	O
,	O
Braine	O
,	O
and	O
Smither	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
fact	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
were	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
convicted	O
,	O
Smither	O
was	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
tobocconist	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
against	O
him	O
than	O
what	O
Smither	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smither	I-pers
.	O
Betwixt	O
the	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
1766	O
,	O
Haines	O
,	O
Braine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hamburgh	O
Arms	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
's	O
yard	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
7	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
drink	O
my	O
health	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
done	O
within	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Smither	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
but	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
duty	O
is	O
six-pence	O
halfpenny	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Smither	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
us	O
all	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
Haines	O
,	O
Braine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
camen	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
we	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
up	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Smither	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
evidences	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
servants	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
here	O
they	O
could	O
clear	O
up	O
my	O
innocency	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
they	O
are	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
promised	O
faithfully	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Arthur	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
worsted	O
maker	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
in	O
Wheeler	O
street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
a	O
brewer	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
dyer	O
in	O
Prescot-street	O
,	O
Goodman's-fields	O
;	O
Hugh	B-pers
Pitchcroft	I-pers
,	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Morlimar	I-pers
,	O
a	O
shop-keeper	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Billingly	I-pers
,	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
163	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
Moses	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Moses	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Highgate	B-place
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
55	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
he	O
looked	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
nobody	O
passing	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
collar	O
and	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
from	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
it	O
against	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
holding	O
his	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Solomon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
two	O
miles	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Solomon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
again	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Solomon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
twice	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
a	O
powder-horn	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
several	O
slugs	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Solomon	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
demand	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Solomon	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
silver	O
buckles	O
or	O
spoons	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
other	O
watches	O
in	O
my	O
bags	O
,	O
I	O
trade	O
in	O
nothing	O
but	O
watches	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
watch	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
watch	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
very	O
good	O
hours	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
?	O
Wentworth	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Wentworth	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
twenty	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stationer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Birchin-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1765	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
;	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
behaved	O
in	O
all	O
respects	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
last	O
April	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
employ	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
Stamford-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
his	O
living	O
since	O
last	O
Christmas	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
fourteen	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
worked	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
and	O
industrious	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
six	O
months	O
ill	O
of	O
an	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
greatly	O
distressed	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
carpenters	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Hugh	B-pers
James	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hugh	O
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Hugh	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
near	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
chariot	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
lady	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
road	O
in	O
Islington	B-place
parish	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
rather	O
modestly	O
in	O
his	O
situation	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
chariot	O
without	O
any	O
imprecations	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
saw	O
none	O
but	O
women	O
,	O
I	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
money	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
his	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
down	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
alarm	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
for	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
down	O
my	O
fore-glass	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
coachman	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
towards	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
coachman	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
chariot	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
in	O
sight	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
out-ran	O
me	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
stopt	O
by	O
Dobney	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
ever	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sight	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
for	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopped	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
a	O
powder-horn	O
with	O
powder	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
slugs	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Bucar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stopped	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Islington	O
back	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
first	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
master	O
deliver	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
stept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chariot	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
our	O
country-house	O
with	O
the	O
chariot	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Palmer	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
James	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
a	O
powder-horn	O
,	O
some	O
slugs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
164	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
pimento	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Paumier	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Wyld	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
bag	O
of	O
pimento	O
cut	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
in	O
all	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
small	O
bag	O
,	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Paumier	I-pers
;	O
my	O
partner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
him	O
walk	O
;	O
we	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
legs	O
,	O
he	O
kicked	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Wyld	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pimento	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
pepper	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
five	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
bags	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
pepper	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
about	O
five	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
bag	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paumier	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
bags	O
not	O
above	O
six	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
right	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
cut	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
but	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
passage	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
walking	O
along	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
what	O
they	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
165	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
'Change	B-place
on	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
having	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
boys	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
carry	O
a	O
hod	O
for	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
166	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	B-place
in	I-place
Salisbury-court	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
which	O
before	O
had	O
been	O
hanging	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
.	O
Urban	B-pers
Doterman	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
standing	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
without	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
coat	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
lad	O
,	O
he	O
chucked	O
my	O
hat	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
167	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Callagan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
of	O
Botolph-lane	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Haywood	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Haywood	O
ran	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Haywood	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
following	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
tallest	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
a	O
gate-way	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
twelve	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
packthread-ground	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
168	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
ox	O
hides	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
four	O
cow	O
hides	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Kyke	I-pers
Van	I-pers
Mieup	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lighter	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	B-place
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Goat-yard	O
,	O
Horsleydown	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
ten	O
hides	O
in	O
my	O
skittle-ground	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
hides	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Irish	O
hides	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
lighterman	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
wharfinger	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
hides	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
ten	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
letters	O
B	O
,	O
C	O
,	O
and	O
D	O
,	O
some	O
one	O
letter	O
some	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
's	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
porters	O
bring	O
those	O
hides	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
skittle-ground	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
got	O
up	O
there	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
hides	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Liscoe	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wharfinger	O
at	O
Hays	O
's	O
wharf	O
,	O
in	O
Shad	O
Thames	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
delivered	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
ten	O
hides	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
particularly	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
A	O
,	O
B	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
horn	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
quality	O
of	O
the	O
hides	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
which	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
is	O
Hays	O
's	O
wharf	O
?	O
Liscoe	O
.	O
That	O
and	O
Horsleydown	O
are	O
both	O
in	O
Southwark	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
vessel	O
lay	O
when	O
the	O
hides	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
hides	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
?	O
Liscoe	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
a	O
day	O
and	O
a	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
from	O
?	O
Liscoe	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
from	O
Cork	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
the	O
vessel	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
stream	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
hides	O
ever	O
on	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
?	O
Liscoe	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
hides	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
the	O
lighter	O
was	O
carried	O
over	O
to	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
being	O
Sunday	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
hides	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
all	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
branding-irons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
raw	O
hides	O
,	O
salted	O
and	O
tied	O
up	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
lighter	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
lay	O
in	O
Hanover-hole	O
;	O
the	O
lighter	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Porter	O
's	O
key	O
near	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
Hays	O
's	O
wharf	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
wharfinger	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
lighter	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
hides	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
in	O
Goat-yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
the	O
lighter	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
Porter	O
's	O
key	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
proof	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
hides	O
were	O
delivered	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
to	O
the	O
lighter	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Kyke	I-pers
Van	B-pers
Mieup	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
hides	O
when	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
joint	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
and	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
skift	O
that	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
row	O
by	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
crossed	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
boat	O
and	O
pursued	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
in	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
board	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
lumbering	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
man	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
watch	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
men	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
job	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
hides	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
lay	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
skift	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
porters	O
six-pence	O
each	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
hard	O
job	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Goat	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
skittle-ground	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
on	O
his	O
duty	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
skift	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Shaw	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
on	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
break	O
of	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
hides	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
employed	O
besides	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
clandestinely	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
speak	O
in	O
any	O
disrespect	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
and	O
flung	O
them	O
down	O
facing	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
happened	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
daily	O
labour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Seething-lane	O
,	O
by	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Any	O
where	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
the	O
skins	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
In	O
an	O
alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Very	O
likely	O
you	O
can	O
tell	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
that	O
alley	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
no	O
questions	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twelve	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
with	O
honesty	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
employments	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
169	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
||	O
David	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Crutched-friars	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
spent	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
very	O
freely	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
accosted	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
company	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Corn-hill	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gracechurch-street	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
down	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
disengage	O
myself	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
still	O
persisted	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fenchurch-street	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
address	O
enough	O
to	O
continue	O
by	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Fenchurch-street	O
;	O
sometimes	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
disengaged	O
myself	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
quit	O
her	O
hold	O
;	O
she	O
continued	O
importuning	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
some	O
where	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
at	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
mere	O
curiosity	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
woman	O
could	O
mean	O
;	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
amorous	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
one	O
arm	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
loving	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
fumbling	O
about	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
art	O
enough	O
to	O
address	O
me	O
for	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
disengaged	O
myself	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pocket-piece	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
two	O
moidores	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
guineas	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
like	O
slight	O
of	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
all	O
she	O
could	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
absolutely	O
refused	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
just	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
he	O
knowing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
went	O
directly	O
away	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
must	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
other	O
woman	O
never	O
touched	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
really	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
when	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
felt	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
her	O
hand	O
within	O
side	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
this	O
affair	O
brought	O
me	O
more	O
to	O
myself	O
than	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
that	O
other	O
woman	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shillings	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
first	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
first	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
excuse	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
3	O
d.	O
to	O
buy	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
brandy	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
find	O
3	O
d.	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
talk	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
another	O
night	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
talking	O
to	O
this	O
lady	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
stood	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
something	O
;	O
we	O
stood	O
talking	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
talking	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
about	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
seven	O
guineas	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stripped	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
smock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
say	O
you	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
real	O
invention	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
tittle	O
of	O
it	O
true	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
magistrate	O
a	O
different	O
story	O
;	O
I	O
neither	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
not	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
really	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
simple	O
curiosity	O
in	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
served	O
her	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
serve	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
She	O
served	O
me	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
M.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life-time	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Magleshan	I-pers
.	O
In	O
live	O
in	O
Holywell-lane	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Magleshan	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
and	O
surgeon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
bring	O
home	O
work	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
?	O
Magleshan	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
many	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
city	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
street-walker	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
prisons	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
before	O
for	O
a	O
fact	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	O
Cluse	O
,	O
No	O
98	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
170	O
,	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Blessett	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
called	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Wyld-street	I-place
,	I-place
Lincoln's-inn-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
at	O
night	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
knock	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
candlestick	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
rushed	O
in	O
;	O
Blessett	O
came	O
foremost	O
into	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
following	O
him	O
;	O
Blessett	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
scuffle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
candle	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lately	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
,	O
happened	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
wrenched	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
Blessett	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
Massey	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
this	O
large	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
cried	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
and	O
got	O
other	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
Round-house	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Blessett	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
was	O
Massey	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
cried	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
back	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
candle	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
pistol	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
.	O
David	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
his	O
bed-side	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
call	O
,	O
thieves	O
,	O
thieves	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
hands	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
David	B-pers
James	I-pers
had	O
secured	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
a	O
candle	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
taken	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Blessett	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
swears	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
rob	O
or	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Haseldine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Blessett	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
apprentice	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
lad	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
when	O
examined	O
there	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
muttered	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
Blessett	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
this	O
evidence	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
young	O
youths	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Massey	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Patley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Massey	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pestel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Blessett	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
Massey	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
good	O
characters	O
of	O
each	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
Massey	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
Massey	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Blessett	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
172	O
,	O
173	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Buller	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee-buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
half	O
pound	O
weight	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walsingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
White's-alley	O
,	O
Little	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Buller	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
night	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Buller	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
buckle	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Cox	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
brass	O
weight	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
Buller	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Walsingham	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
Cox	O
lived	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
upon	O
Cox	O
's	O
mother	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
cock-lost	O
;	O
his	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
11	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
being	O
with	O
Buller	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
the	O
weight	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
at	O
last	O
where	O
that	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
bought	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Margaret	O
his	O
wife	O
deposed	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
shop	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
imagined	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
finding	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
a	O
dirty	O
shoe	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
she	O
described	O
the	O
boys	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
mentioned	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hederly	I-pers
a	O
brass-founder	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Buller	O
brought	O
the	O
weight	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
mother	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
potatoes	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
that	O
business	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
the	O
weight	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
three-pence	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gallier	I-pers
a	O
lad	O
of	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
knee-buckle	O
of	O
Cox	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
gave	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckle	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Buller	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
has	O
been	O
passed	O
to	O
his	O
settlement	O
in	O
Lancashire	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
.	O
Cox	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
Buller	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
.	O
T	O
Cox	O
Acq	O
.	O
174	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mulliner	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mulliner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Holbourn	B-place
opposite	I-place
Staple's-inn	I-place
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
drawing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
pick	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
ran	O
through	O
Staple's-inn	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
frighted	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
175	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Dennis	B-pers
Caffery	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Capery	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
ton	O
of	O
Scotch	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Rymer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Grimes	O
and	O
Holmes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
partners	O
in	O
the	O
coal	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
water-side	B-place
at	I-place
Durham-yard	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
boat	O
with	O
some	O
Scotch	O
coals	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
shoved	O
her	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
another	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shillings	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round-house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
500	O
weight	O
of	O
coals	O
in	O
his	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
our	O
craft	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
Scotch	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
craft	O
there	O
had	O
any	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
craft	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
market	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
the	O
porter	O
unloaded	O
my	O
boat	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
were	O
coals	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
throwing	O
them	O
out	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
bear	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
176	O
,	O
177	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toole	I-pers
and	O
Paul	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toole	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
two-feet	O
rule	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
my	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Toole	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
called	O
Irish	O
Jack	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
fellow	O
prisoner	O
to	O
write	O
it	O
.	O
Produced	O
and	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
Clerkenwell	O
Prison	O
.	O
``	O
Sir	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
or	O
``	O
two	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
something	O
to	O
your	O
advantage	O
;	O
I	O
``	O
am	O
taken	O
prisoner	O
on	O
your	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
``	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
``	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
``	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toole	I-pers
.	O
``	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
stays	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
order	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
and	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
had	O
broke	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
my	O
stays	O
and	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
going	O
back	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
the	O
keeper	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
irons	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Matthews	O
and	O
Hart	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Black-boy-alley	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
women	O
in	O
another	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stays	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Stonecutter-street	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotterill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Patterson	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Stonecutter-street	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
pawned	O
these	O
stays	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Toole	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
wrongfully	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brick-maker	O
,	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
lad	O
.	O
Toole	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Matthews	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
178	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
stays	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
179	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coomes	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
hat	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
errand	O
up	O
stairs	O
whether	O
we	O
would	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hat-box	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
shirt	O
of	O
mine	O
out	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
;	O
she	O
receives	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
month	O
of	O
Whitechapel	O
parish	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
when	O
she	O
received	O
her	O
money	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
hat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
sell	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
peace	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
180	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
hempen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
man	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
four-pence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
French	I-pers
;	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
January	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
a	O
brewer	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
sacking	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
within	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
four	O
aprons	O
tied	O
about	O
his	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shoes	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
nights	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
wrote	O
by	O
the	O
maker	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
aprons	O
and	O
shoes	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
's	O
wife	O
has	O
owned	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
wet	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tompkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
liquor	O
was	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
disordered	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
181	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Christy	I-pers
,	O
a	O
letter-carrier	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
merchant	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
receive	O
4	O
d.	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
postage	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
embezzle	O
and	O
apply	O
the	O
said	O
money	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
comptroller	O
of	O
the	O
Post-office	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
appointed	O
a	O
letter-carrier	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1765	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
the	O
letter-carriers	O
appointed	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
No	O
other	O
way	O
than	O
being	O
entered	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
as	O
a	O
letter-carrier	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
into	O
security	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brathwaite	I-pers
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
book	O
the	O
supernumerary	O
letter-carriers	O
names	O
are	O
in	O
;	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Christy	I-pers
,	O
supernumerary	O
letter-carrier	O
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
,	O
1765	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
broke	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
letters	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
receive	O
letters	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Bristol	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
in	O
it	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Cockhill	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
a	O
groat	O
for	O
the	O
postage	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
letter	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bill	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
find	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
attempt	O
to	O
negotiate	O
the	O
bill	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Halliburton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
the	O
letter	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
letter	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
ascertain	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
delivered	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Post-office	O
;	O
what	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
were	O
380	O
odd	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
letters	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
above	O
300	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
Post-office	O
to	O
deliver	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
delivered	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
unopened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Potts	O
.	O
Whether	O
fourpence	O
for	O
a	O
double	O
letter	O
was	O
sufficient	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
We	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
wrote	O
upon	O
it	O
more	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
forwarded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
be	O
received	O
where	O
delivered	O
.	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
window-man	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Post-office	O
to	O
receive	O
letters	O
;	O
we	O
mark	O
them	O
first	O
with	O
the	O
office	O
mark	O
with	O
red	O
ink	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
paid	O
;	O
this	O
letter	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
having	O
no	O
post	O
mark	O
wrote	O
in	O
red	O
ink	O
was	O
never	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
always	O
mark	O
them	O
before	O
we	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
assistant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
looked	O
at	O
this	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
ever	O
was	O
accounted	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
ever	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
usual	O
mark	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
letter-carrier	O
to	O
the	O
Post-office	O
;	O
I	O
walk	O
Stepney	O
and	O
Ratcliffe	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mascall	O
lives	O
in	O
that	O
district	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
letter	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
that	O
walk	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
doctor	O
's	O
bill	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
administered	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
four	O
weeks	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
walk	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
that	O
walk	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
letters	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
gave	O
a	O
right	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
another	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
inspect	O
the	O
letters	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
they	O
are	O
double	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
a	O
groat	O
received	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
letter-carriers	O
except	O
we	O
pay	O
the	O
full	O
money	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Middle-row	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
the	O
betwixt	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Lady	O
Anne	B-pers
Connolly	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
served	O
my	O
lady	O
upwards	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
faithful	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
son	O
Mr.	O
Connolly	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
his	O
travels	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hurt	O
his	O
leg	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
him	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Post-office	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Besborough	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
at	O
my	O
lady	O
's	O
for	O
eighteen	O
years	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Potts	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
must	O
have	O
paid	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
pocket	O
,	O
for	O
letters	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
delivered	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
No	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
upon	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
182	O
,	O
183	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collop	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Calwin	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hulme	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Stapler	I-pers
,	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Watling-street	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
36	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
to	O
a	O
printer	O
's	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
;	O
each	O
piece	O
contains	O
about	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
is	O
named	O
Robert	B-pers
Bulpink	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Quaker	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
town-clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Calwin	O
and	O
Foster	O
,	O
callico-printers	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
collecting	O
the	O
duty	O
for	O
the	O
excise	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
cart	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
these	O
goods	O
in	O
Watling-street	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
went	O
with	O
Bulpink	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
36	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
count	O
them	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
missed	O
two	O
.	O
John	B-pers
M'Namara	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
my	O
fourteenth	O
year	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
with	O
a	O
jack-ass	O
selling	O
greens	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
help	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
cooper	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clempson	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
one	O
Saturday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Clark	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
jumped	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
cart	O
(	O
which	O
had	O
three	O
horses	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
)	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
handed	O
one	O
to	O
Collop	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Gordon	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
cut	O
the	O
marks	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
figures	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
black	O
;	O
she	O
cut	O
one	O
piece	O
in	O
halves	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
one	O
piece	O
we	O
gave	O
to	O
a	O
lame	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
Gordon	O
we	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Collop	O
should	O
have	O
laid	O
at	O
Gordon	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
cotton	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Hulme	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
cottons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Hulme	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
deliver	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
cease	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
property	O
till	O
they	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
printer	O
is	O
accountable	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
horses	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
?	O
Hulme	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
broad-wheel	O
cart	O
with	O
three	O
horses	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brebrook	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
lame	O
fellow	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
whole	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
M	O
'	O
Namara	B-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
had	O
gave	O
him	O
this	O
piece	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
went	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
,	O
to	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
M'Namara	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Collop	O
and	O
Clark	O
were	O
some	O
where	O
on	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
cotton	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cart	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
to	O
Gordon	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
tea	O
on	O
her	O
dresser	O
(	O
about	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
tea	O
produced	O
,	O
)	O
it	O
being	O
directed	O
for	O
Matthew	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
at	O
Bow	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
imagined	O
they	O
got	O
this	O
cloth	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
callico-printers	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
yourself	O
out	O
of	O
trouble	O
;	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Jenny	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
her	O
maid	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
two	O
short	O
pieces	O
;	O
there	O
wants	O
about	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
still	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
maid	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
picking	O
pockets	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
greater	O
discovery	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morrison	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
named	O
Jane	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
pieces	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
till	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
came	O
,	O
herself	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
printed	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
:	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
Jane	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
a	O
customer	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Collop	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
from	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
wrongfully	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Gordon	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
One	O
Susannah	B-pers
Etherly	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
cotton	O
as	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
till	O
summer	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
servant	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Etherly	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
one	O
Williams	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
myself	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
by	O
my	O
maid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gordon	O
above	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
Gardener	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
character	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
her	O
getting	O
her	O
living	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Farran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Farran	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
her	O
character	O
is	O
.	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Gordon	O
in	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
necessary-house	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mill-yard	O
by	O
Goodman's-fields	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
less	O
than	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
she	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
or	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Collop	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Gordon	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
184	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
French	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
;	O
two	O
woollen	O
rugs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
and	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Beech	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
and	O
lighterman	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
close	O
bodied	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vessel	O
at	O
Wapping	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
with	O
my	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
vessel	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
as	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
close	O
bodied	O
one	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
things	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
mine	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
vessel	O
lay	O
near	O
my	O
back	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
185	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ayre	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Ayre	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
vessel	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
foremast	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
fact	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Irongate	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
oats	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
cargo	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
150	O
quarters	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Truss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
;	O
a	O
porter	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Irongate	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
sweepings	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
which	O
lay	O
near	O
Lady	O
Parson	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
's	O
company	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
sacks	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
officer	O
had	O
detected	O
this	O
evidence	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
three	O
sacks	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
clean	O
oats	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Bristol	O
alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
lighter	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
one	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
cook	O
,	O
the	O
