TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
OF	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SIDNEY	B-pers
STAFFORD	I-pers
SMYTHE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BATHURST	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Please	O
+	O
;	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
||	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Whitchurch	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Snape	I-pers
,	O
Gyles	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Benwell	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Aires	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vardy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fladgate	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edmonson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Box	I-pers
.	O
251	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELizabeth	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Alves	I-pers
,	O
April	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Alves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Portuguese	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bristow	O
;	O
we	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hennington	O
,	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
at	O
Charing-cross	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hennington	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
seven	O
guineas	O
last	O
Thursday	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
it	O
all	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hennington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Alves	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
Thursday	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bureau	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
for	O
his	O
advice	O
;	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Betty	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
as	O
easy	O
as	O
we	O
can	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bristow	O
;	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
very	O
strongly	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
about	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
we	O
called	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
about	O
six	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
purse	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
bureau	O
,	O
she	O
likewise	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
We	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
cloth	O
for	O
shifts	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
guineas	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
abroad	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
252	O
,	O
253	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Gibson	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
tenon	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pannel	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pilaster	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
ogee	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
;	O
one	O
tenon	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
long	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
trying	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
one	O
smoothing	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
one	O
pilaster	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
rabbet	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Bignall	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
William	O
Turner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
tools	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
building	O
in	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
(	O
mentioning	O
the	O
tools	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
)	O
we	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
;	O
Gibson	O
Bignall	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
said	O
she	O
pawned	O
some	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coulter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Williams	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
charged	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
receiving	O
some	O
carpenter	O
's	O
tools	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
a	O
building	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
(	O
meaning	O
Bignall	O
)	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Bignall	O
her	O
husband	O
?	O
Coulter	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
married	O
,	O
she	O
herself	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
tools	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
to	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Gibson	O
Bignall	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
as	O
they	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
went	O
round	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
Bignall	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
building	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Bignall	O
work	O
in	O
that	O
building	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Coulter	O
.	O
Did	O
,	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
tools	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
?	O
Coulter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
custody	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
her	O
confess	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
master	O
carpenter	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
others	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bignall	O
.	O
Williams	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
254	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Stothers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
coverlid	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
baize	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
brass	O
flour-dredger	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dornford	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Anne	B-pers
Dornford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Dornford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
iron	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
shaken	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
could	O
put	O
their	O
hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
two	O
saucepans	O
at	O
Richard	B-pers
Best	I-pers
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
two	O
saucepans	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
yesterday	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
person	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
days	O
till	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
having	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
others	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
made	O
strict	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Best	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
saucepans	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
bread	O
for	O
her	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
at	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
she	O
did	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Best	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
cock	O
and	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopped	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
sold	O
these	O
saucepans	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
together	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bosley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
brought	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
and	O
pawned	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
we	O
believe	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
yet	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
my	O
husband	O
bid	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
255	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Udith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
dye	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Long	B-place
lane	I-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Rag	O
fair	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
cloak	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
Eaton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
dyer	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
line	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
256	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
plough	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
;	O
one	O
gouge	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
chisels	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
square	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Murrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
saw	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
Great	O
Wild-street	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat-sheaf	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
thirteen	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
257	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
petticoat	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
absconded	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
till	O
last	O
Friday	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hopcraft	I-pers
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hopcraft	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
petticoat	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
petticoat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
absconded	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
staid	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
258	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Costelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
twibill	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
paviour	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
tools	O
,	O
spades	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
this	O
twibill	O
is	O
an	O
instrument	O
with	O
which	O
we	O
get	O
up	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
twibill	O
from	O
the	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
walking	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
work	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
W.	O
Brook	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brook	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
twibill	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
work	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
King's-road	O
near	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn-lane	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Canler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
paviours	O
and	O
bricklayers	O
as	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
borrowed	O
money	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
such	O
a	O
tool	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
an	O
honester	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
safeguard	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
tool	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
Canler	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
bought	O
one	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Macdaniel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
259	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Quenter	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Peter	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Quenter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
and	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Duke-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
27	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
some	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
silver	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Le	O
Quenter	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
almost	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
some	O
silver	O
lace	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
silver	O
lace	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
himself	O
opened	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Le	O
Quenter	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
nineteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
and	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
greatly	O
surprized	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
Newman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
silversmith	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
acquaint	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
carrying	O
some	O
silver	O
lace	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
260	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Lotan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
louis	O
d'ors	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Panchau	I-pers
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Isaac	B-pers
Panchau	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
five	O
louis	O
d'ors	O
;	O
another	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
I	O
found	O
but	O
three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Panchau	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
country	O
man	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Panchau	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
constable	O
coming	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
two	O
louis	O
d'ors	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
co	O
nfessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Panchau	O
.	O
At	O
different	O
times	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
often	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
abroad	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Rummer	O
in	O
Mortimer-street	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
my	O
wife	O
a	O
louis	O
d'or	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
French	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Panchau	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
five	O
louis	O
d'ors	O
in	O
his	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
bag	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
three	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
change	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
publican	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lost	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
he	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
a	O
hatter	O
brought	O
a	O
hat	O
home	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lent	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
3	O
s.	O
that	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
of	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
that	O
my	O
wife	O
washed	O
for	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
louis	O
d'or	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
I	O
offered	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
wife	O
that	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
served	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Prince	O
Charles	O
of	O
Lorrain	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
here	O
to	O
buy	O
horses	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
261	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Pump	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
money-till	O
made	O
of	O
deal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Shotton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Mark	B-pers
Shotton	I-pers
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Butcher-row	B-place
in	I-place
East-smithfield	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
money	O
rattle	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
till	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
my	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
S.	O
Shotton	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
flung	O
the	O
till	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
18	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
S.	O
Shotton	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
pork-shop	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
coming	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
first	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Pump	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
without	O
,	O
I	O
soon	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
running	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Pump	O
throw	O
the	O
till	O
down	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
through	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
expecting	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
lead-mill	O
for	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
262	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Green	B-pers
Jemmit	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
duffil	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hulbart	I-pers
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hulbart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
matross	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout	O
coat	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
from	O
the	B-place
Brown	I-place
Bear	I-place
in	I-place
Devonshire-street	I-place
,	I-place
Queen's-square	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
hanging	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barclow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
us	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
the	O
prisoner	O
do	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
?	O
Barclow	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Barclow	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
tap	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Goal	O
,	O
Southwark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-square	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
Turner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
263	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Greggs	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pattens	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
to-bed	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
washed	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
quitted	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
abroad	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
from	O
her	O
bed	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
sheet	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
to	O
Thomasin	O
Dodd	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
since	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
sheet	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
my	O
partner	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
)	O
she	O
pledged	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Devonshire	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
right	O
name	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
pattens	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
pattens	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
feet	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Warren	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
sheet	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
(	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
must	O
pawn	O
something	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
pawned	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
wearing	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
pattens	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
the	O
nurse	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
pattens	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
instead	O
of	O
her	O
pattens	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
264	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Eastland	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Eastland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
them	O
according	O
to	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
your	O
bed	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
by	O
my	O
bed-side	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Benjamin-street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Eastland	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
formerly	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
neighbours	O
said	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
your	O
watch	O
as	O
usual	O
?	O
Eastland	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
once	O
pawn	O
my	O
watch	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
wanting	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
did	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Eastland	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
,	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
Eastland	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
base	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
had	O
she	O
pledged	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
She	O
pledged	O
it	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
1766	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1767	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
whose	O
watch	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Eastland	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
25	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
enquired	O
after	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
above	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Nancy	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
put	O
your	O
child	O
on	O
a	O
clean	O
shift	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
children	O
I	O
had	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
directly	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
be	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
make	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
now	O
,	O
Billy	O
,	O
consider	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
through	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
cash	O
runs	O
very	O
short	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
do	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
lend	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
then	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
apron	O
and	O
cardinal	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
arrested	O
my	O
husband	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
leave	O
my	O
husband	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
three	O
children	O
by	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
265	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Church	I-pers
Callen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
brick	O
building	O
,	O
did	O
rip	O
,	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	O
Church	O
Callen	O
.	O
The	O
building	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
frequently	O
lost	O
lead	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
set	O
Hildey	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hildey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
this	O
building	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
lead	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
parted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
each	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
upwards	O
of	O
an	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
After	O
Hildey	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
building	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacco-cutter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
jobs	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
brickfields	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
;	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
bustle	O
;	O
said	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
stir	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
dead	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
266	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Church	I-pers
Callen	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
,	O
did	O
rip	O
,	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	O
Church	O
Callen	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
houses	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
lost	O
lead	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
Beck	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
thinking	O
that	O
might	O
fright	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
gutter	O
,	O
taking	O
lead	O
off	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
down	O
;	O
Beck	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
and	O
called	O
Charles	B-pers
Hildey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
drew	B-pers
both	O
sash	O
and	O
frame	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
backwards	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
is	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
round	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
strong	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
under	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sword	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
stabbed	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
several	O
parts	O
of	O
my	O
body	O
;	O
Beck	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
Hildey	O
's	O
coming	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
both	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
Tom	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
)	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
but	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Callen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
moon	O
light	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
;	O
he	O
seeing	O
two	O
men	O
walking	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
by	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
gutter	O
;	O
they	O
shifted	O
from	O
that	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
joist	O
of	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
lead	O
fall	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
dead	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
gun	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
sword	O
;	O
I	O
whispered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
to	O
walk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
building	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
move	O
;	O
he	O
clapt	O
his	O
feet	O
upon	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
that	O
and	O
frame	O
all	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
under	O
the	O
frame	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
board	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
joists	O
,	O
that	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
fell	O
through	O
,	O
I	O
jumped	O
down	O
,	O
thinking	O
of	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
recovered	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
frame	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
down	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
stood	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
's	O
sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
bustle	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
my	O
sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
resolute	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
recovered	O
both	O
the	O
swords	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
great	O
difficulty	O
to	O
manage	O
him	O
;	O
had	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Hildey	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
both	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hildey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
assist	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
and	O
Beck	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
gun	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
listened	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
or	O
hear	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
soon	O
heard	O
something	O
jump	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
over	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
lead	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
clapt	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
surrender	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
surrender	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
can	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
wait	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
law	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Callen	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
dram	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
how	O
could	O
that	O
be	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
only	O
joists	O
and	O
no	O
boards	O
to	O
sleep	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
who	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
perhaps	O
he	O
might	O
save	O
himself	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
Nugent	O
that	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
this	O
building	O
,	O
and	O
Nugent	O
threw	O
the	O
lead	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
staid	O
below	O
to	O
watch	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
received	O
the	O
lead	O
they	O
stole	O
,	O
lived	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
named	O
Martin	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
,	O
that	O
sells	O
old	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
warrant	O
out	O
for	O
Nugent	O
and	O
Bridgman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Bridgman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
then	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
Bridgman	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
entirely	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
Bridgman	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
lead	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
Martin	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
any	O
lead	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
son	O
lived	O
at	O
Barnet	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
between	O
two	O
waggons	O
at	O
Redburn	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
next	O
Sunday	O
will	O
be	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
buried	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
tired	O
and	O
fatigued	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
in	O
the	O
chimney	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
alarming	O
about	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
catch	O
them	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
foot	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
joist	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
another	O
story	O
higher	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
or	O
two	O
and	O
threw	O
stones	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
coming	O
down	O
I	O
trod	O
upon	O
a	O
window	O
frame	O
that	O
canted	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
with	O
swords	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
well	O
since	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
267	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lewis	B-pers
Gwillim	I-pers
,	O
clerk	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pint	O
silver	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Salutation	I-place
in	I-place
Tavistock-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
pint	O
mug	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
remaining	O
liquor	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
mug	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
go	O
out	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
scrupulous	O
of	O
apprehending	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
too	O
many	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haliburton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
constables	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
my	O
watch	O
night	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
persons	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
night-houses	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
.	O
268	O
,	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Tipple	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Slavin	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
five	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
green	O
grocer	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
above	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
somebody	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
turned	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cardinal	O
and	O
two	O
white	O
aprons	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
stairs	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
C.	O
Sparkes	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
Edward	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pushed	O
them	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
Slavin	O
's	O
bosom	O
,	O
seeing	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
t	O
wo	O
double	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
5	O
caps	O
and	O
a	O
topknot	O
;	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Tipple	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
stays	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Sparkes	O
's	O
calling	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
she	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
having	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
drop	O
from	O
Tipple	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
stairs	O
were	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
5	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
double	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
topknot	O
,	O
taken	O
from	O
Slavin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
dropt	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
C.	O
Sparkes	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
bed-basket	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
upon	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
fore-room	O
,	O
that	O
door	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
Tipple	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Slavin	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
answered	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
270	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Beezer	I-pers
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Beezer	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Cannon-street	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
touched	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
another	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
fetch	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
fetched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
go	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Ludgate-hill	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fellow	O
singing	O
of	O
ballads	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
companions	O
,	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
mob	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
as	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
visible	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eyed	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
mob	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
let	O
go	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
holiday	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
Hermitage-yard	O
,	O
Wapping	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
liberty	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
holiday	O
making	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
companion	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
advice	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
dutiful	O
child	O
till	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
pretty	O
near	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
some	O
baker	O
's	O
boy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
271	O
,	O
272	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Elrey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spratley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Spratley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
election	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Guildhall	B-place
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
boys	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
Guildhall	O
were	O
moving	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
were	O
moving	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
kept	O
very	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
poll	O
,	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
visible	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
Elrey	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
to	O
Haywood	O
;	O
I	O
tapped	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
collars	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Haywood	O
dropt	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Haywood	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
see	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
voting	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
that	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
make	O
muffins	O
,	O
Haywood	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
account	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Liquorpond-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
child	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
a	O
husband	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
another	O
child	O
,	O
two	O
as	O
good	O
children	O
as	O
ever	O
were	O
born	O
.	O
Elrey	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
that	O
gentleman	O
took	O
me	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
picking	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairmaker	O
in	O
Leicester-street	O
;	O
Elrey	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
money	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
errand-boy	O
at	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
apprentice	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
husband	O
works	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
with	O
200	O
l.	O
in	O
goods	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
273	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Shooler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Axford	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Axford	I-pers
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
farther	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
church	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
believed	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
absolutely	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
among	O
the	O
mob	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Notzall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
trade	O
a	O
box-maker	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
his	O
time	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
journey-work	O
at	O
the	O
trade	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Notzall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perfumer	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
distant	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
274	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Maack	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Francis	B-pers
Maack	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barry	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
into	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Deputy	O
Wilson	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Lombard	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
came	O
by	O
together	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
these	O
two	O
dogs	O
come	O
by	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Belchier	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
follow	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
his	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
boy	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
it	O
going	O
in	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Serle	I-pers
.	O
A	O
man	O
tossed	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
carry	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
tossed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
bricklayers	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
Borough	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
welcome	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
275	O
,	O
276	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pummall	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vantandilo	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
barber	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
pretty	O
near	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
in	O
Flower	O
and	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
my	O
friend	O
went	O
up	O
St.	B-place
Michael's-alley	I-place
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
these	O
girls	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
fond	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
kissed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
snatch	O
at	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
chain	O
gone	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Vantandilo	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
fought	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
at	O
the	O
'Change	O
,	O
they	O
fought	O
the	O
watchman	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
me	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
call	O
another	O
watchman	O
to	O
assist	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
searched	O
?	O
Raymond	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
seal	O
or	O
money	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
cost	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Raymond	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
your	O
friend	O
assist	O
you	O
?	O
Raymond	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
into	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
Raymond	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
ways	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
Upper	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
you	O
continue	O
there	O
?	O
Raymond	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
much	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Geter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
charge	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
after	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
lost	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
mentioned	O
about	O
the	O
seal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Geter	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
prisoners	O
searched	O
?	O
Geter	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
search	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
signify	O
.	O
Raymond	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
never	O
talked	O
of	O
searching	O
them	O
.	O
Geter	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
losing	O
his	O
seal	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Pummall	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Vinegar-yard	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
a	O
little	O
later	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
that	O
gentleman	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
cane	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
pass	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
lady	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
her	O
fellow	O
prisoner	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
past	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
in	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
Pummall	O
is	O
an	O
engine	O
winder	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
employed	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
no	O
honester	O
woman	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
six	O
months	O
since	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
single	O
?	O
Kelly	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Jeggot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
clean	O
industrious	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
.	O
Vantandilo	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
my	O
child	O
of	O
three	O
months	O
old	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
(	O
meaning	O
Pummall	O
)	O
was	O
stopped	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
judge	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
assaulting	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
277	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
man	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
ells	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
.	O
+	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
at	O
Wilsden	B-place
;	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
till	O
night	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
brick-work	O
was	O
pulled	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
broke	O
through	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
person	O
had	O
crept	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
this	O
brick-work	O
joined	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chamber-door	O
was	O
burst	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
ells	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
binding	O
of	O
hay	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
from	O
that	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
clear	O
himself	O
before	O
his	O
master	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
,	O
named	O
Bodymead	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ealey	I-pers
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cloth	O
and	O
shoes	O
there	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
the	O
shoes	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
the	O
brick-work	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
place	O
broke	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
chamber-door	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
six	O
ells	O
of	O
dowlas	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
stockings	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
binding	O
hay	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
thought	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
come	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
cloth	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
(	O
showing	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
my	O
son	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
jun	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
six	O
sets	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
looks	O
upon	O
the	O
mark	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Harrow	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Nicoll	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
stockings	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
both	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Ealey	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Edgware	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
young	O
lad	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
278	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Trippit	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crothers	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Crothers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Carlisle	B-place
alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
melted	O
down	O
all	O
his	O
old	O
silver	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crothers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
clock-maker	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
clock	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
tea	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
day	O
long	O
cleaning	O
the	O
clock	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
tea-spoons	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
own	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
279	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
weather	O
sheep	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
I	O
live	O
at	O
Clapham	B-place
in	O
Surry	O
;	O
last	O
Friday	O
I	O
lost	O
ten	O
sheep	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
from	O
an	O
inclosed	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
advertised	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
last	O
?	O
Tilbury	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
that	O
a	O
sheep	O
with	O
my	O
mark	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
turnpike	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
parish	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
of	O
my	O
sheep	O
alive	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tilbury	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
five	O
of	O
his	O
sheep	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
had	O
his	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
alive	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
killed	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Borough	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
fat	O
sheep	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
Dartford	O
or	O
Deptford	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
sheep	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
near	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
beyond	O
the	O
bridge	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Tilbury	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
a	O
little	O
land	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Tilbury	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
first	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
much	O
business	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
universal	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Yorkshire	O
;	O
he	O
married	O
unknown	O
to	O
his	O
parents	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
very	O
honourable	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
any	O
land	O
for	O
sheep	O
to	O
graze	O
in	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
five	O
women	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
skins	O
?	O
Tilbury	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
sheep	O
skinned	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
horns	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
unusual	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
280	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
other	O
earrings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
garnet	O
and	O
other	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
pair	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
:	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
journey-work	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
from	O
the	O
guards	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
dine	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
another	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
dine	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
for	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
recommendation	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
stepped	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
the	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
containing	O
an	O
uncertain	O
number	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fully	O
convinced	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
him	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
notices	O
out	O
to	O
pawnbrokers	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
offered	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
intelligence	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
had	O
deserted	O
from	O
the	O
guards	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Tooley-street	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
window	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
make	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
making	O
,	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
making	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
two	O
odd	O
ones	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
the	O
party	O
,	O
named	O
Matthew	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
only	O
satisfaction	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
generous	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
earrings	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
account	O
from	O
him	O
of	O
six	O
pair	O
,	O
first	O
pawned	O
,	O
then	O
sold	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
;	O
five	O
pair	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
in	O
Joiner-street	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
three	O
pair	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
;	O
three	O
pair	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
Noble-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
on	O
Tower	O
hill	O
delivered	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gatey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
in	O
Tooley-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
earrings	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
he	O
pledged	O
three	O
pair	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
larger	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clare	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clare	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Clare	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
lost	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
281	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Philip	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
seeing	O
several	O
people	O
round	O
the	O
Mansion	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
breeches	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
looking	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
pocket	O
;	O
his	O
pocket	O
lid	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
appeared	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
turn	O
about	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
282.	O
William	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty-one	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
brimstone	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kingscole	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Kingscole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
we	O
are	O
druggists	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
with	O
us	O
seventeen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
trusted	O
as	O
a	O
manufacturer	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
to	O
deliver	O
any	O
thing	O
without	O
our	O
order	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
brimstone	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
counting-house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
outstanding	O
debt	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
money	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
accounted	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
all	O
clandestinely	O
but	O
one	O
parcel	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
road	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Kingscole	O
brought	O
a	O
bill	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
brimstone	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
parcel	O
you	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
in	O
January	O
1764	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Kingscole	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
order	O
the	O
brimstone	O
in	O
October	O
1764	O
;	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
brimstone	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
bill	O
against	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ought	O
to	O
account	O
to	O
his	O
masters	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
283	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
serge	O
sailors	O
jackets	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Tough	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Tough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Sally	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
jackets	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
vessel	O
with	O
an	O
armful	O
of	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
by	O
the	O
New-road	O
turnpike	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
four	O
old	O
jackets	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
old	O
breeches	O
,	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
clothes	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
to	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
George	O
,	O
what	O
vessel	O
do	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Joiner	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
old	O
ship-mate	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
robbing	O
any	O
body	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Harwich	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
284	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Sheridan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brickinshaw	I-pers
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Brickinshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
twenty	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
an	O
inn	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
baker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
single	O
or	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
one	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
or	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
shop	O
and	O
ask	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
beer	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
catched	O
me	O
round	O
my	O
waist	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
houses	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
lying	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
legs	O
between	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
your	O
petticoats	O
on	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
particular	O
.	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
He	O
drawed	O
my	O
petticoats	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
more	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
thing	O
into	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prevent	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
thing	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
blood	O
came	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
as	O
much	O
noise	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
or	O
pull	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
dragged	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
lane	O
into	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
nearer	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
or	O
farther	O
off	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
nearer	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
houses	O
there	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
no	O
body	O
come	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
in	O
that	O
lane	O
,	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
lying	O
with	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
strength	O
left	O
to	O
struggle	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
coment	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
lie	O
down	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
legs	O
between	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
down	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
then	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
kiss	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
kiss	O
him	O
nor	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
then	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
our	O
house	O
full	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
my	O
mistress	O
directly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
company	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
mistress	O
ask	O
you	O
where	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
coming	O
home	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
my	O
staying	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
tell	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
company	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
your	O
master	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Brickinshaw	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
M.	O
