TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
COMMISSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
OYER	O
and	O
TERMINER	O
,	O
and	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
GOAL	O
DELIVERY	O
FOR	O
THE	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILKIE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bible	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Before	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARLEY	I-pers
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YATES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
character	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ascough	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Holford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
MIDDLESEX	O
JURY	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hancox	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Neves	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cossens	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carrier	I-pers
.	O
101	O
,	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sadd	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
horse-whip	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sadd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Marybone	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Essex	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
between	O
Islington	B-place
and	O
Old-street	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
walking	O
before	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
foot-path	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
rather	O
taller	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
(	O
such	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
lamps	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
turnpike	O
on	O
the	O
Islington	O
side	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
together	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
footpath	O
;	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
bridle	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
repeated	O
his	O
blows	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
my	O
horse	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
presented	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
still	O
kept	O
beating	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
my	O
belly	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
ceased	O
my	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
tore	O
the	O
lappet	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
quite	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
wild	O
sowl	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
turned	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Crawley	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
kept	O
beating	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
I	O
being	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
to	O
attend	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
there	O
described	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
hand-whip	O
;	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'enight	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Burnet	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
produced	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
hat	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
being	O
my	O
watch	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Creswell	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
disputing	O
about	O
the	O
reckoning	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
concern	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
fire-arms	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
Crawley	O
's	O
breast	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
horse-whip	O
in	O
Swinney	O
's	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
told	O
that	O
a	O
pistol	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
Crawley	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
Swinney	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
some	O
paper	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
turnpike	O
ticket	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
contents	O
W.	O
Midd	O
.	O
Essex	O
28	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
ticket	O
in	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
Rumford	O
turnpike	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
fort	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
that	O
carries	O
through	O
Mile-end	O
turnpike	O
;	O
the	O
figures	O
28	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Burnet	O
.	O
That	O
watch	O
I	O
found	O
then	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Crawley	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
sob	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
silver	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
confined	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
watches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
whip	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
also	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
from	O
Swinney	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
upon	O
Crawley	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
at	O
past	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
wrangling	O
about	O
the	O
reckoning	O
;	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
she	O
wished	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Swinney	O
struck	O
with	O
his	O
heel	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
hearing	O
a	O
bustle	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
fire-arms	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
then	O
assistance	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burnet	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
horsewhip	O
out	O
of	O
Swinney	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
some	O
powder	O
,	O
some	O
little	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
turnpike	O
ticket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
two	O
watches	O
out	O
of	O
Crawley	O
's	O
breeches-pocket	O
;	O
the	O
pistol	O
had	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
powder	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
(	O
a	O
horse-pistol	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
horsewhip	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
found	O
upon	O
Crawley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whip	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
servant	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
any	O
liquor	O
without	O
their	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopenny	O
,	O
they	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
hot	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
another	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
third	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Crawley	O
began	O
to	O
struggle	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
Swinney	O
fell	O
upon	O
Stevens	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
Crawley	O
.	O
Swinney	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
watch	O
at	O
Barnet	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
whip	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
about	O
two	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
ticket	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
hat	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Crawley	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
pain	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
Dec.	O
21	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
to	O
London	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
the	O
tallest	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
,	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
Crawley	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
this	O
watch	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
his	O
two	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Swinney	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Crawley	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
.	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
Hoxton	B-place
field	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
ten	O
rods	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
moon	O
light	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
path	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
suspicious	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
going	O
on	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tallest	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
watches	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
Burnet	O
.	O
That	O
watch	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Swinney	O
's	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
searched	O
them	O
.	O
Hewett	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
especially	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Crawley	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Creswell	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trials	O
.	O
Swinney	O
's	O
defence	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
watch	O
at	O
Barnet	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
.	O
Crawley	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Scolar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Du	I-pers
Burg	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Du	O
Burg	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Du	I-pers
Burg	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
on	O
Hounslow-heath	B-place
,	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
horse-back	O
,	O
who	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
repeater	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
blue	O
colour	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
immediately	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
seal	O
to	O
be	O
advertised	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
seal	O
and	O
chain	O
were	O
also	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
as	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
many	O
such	O
steel	O
chains	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
seal	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Hounslow-heath	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
pistol	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
post-boy	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
on	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
master	O
let	O
down	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
man	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
.	O
Sweet	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
my	O
money	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
for	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
matter	O
how	O
particular	O
;	O
master	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
lode	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Sweet	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
fresh	O
complexion	O
;	O
(	O
such	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
master	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
we	O
received	O
a	O
hand	O
bill	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
describing	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
a	O
single	O
highwayman	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
ten	O
guineas	O
over	O
and	O
above	O
the	O
reward	O
allowed	O
by	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
;	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
that	O
afternoon	O
my	O
apprentice	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
watch	O
and	O
the	O
hand-bill	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
dial-plate	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
with	O
gold	O
hours	O
and	O
gold	O
hands	O
;	O
by	O
looking	O
it	O
through	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
answered	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
wanted	O
ten	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
coach	O
come	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
an	O
advertisement	O
,	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
highway	O
on	O
Christmaseve	O
;	O
he	O
again	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
insist	O
upon	O
your	O
going	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
there	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
watch	O
as	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
till	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
for	O
farther	O
examination	O
:	O
my	O
apprentice	O
having	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
called	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
ago	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
boots	O
and	O
spurs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
on	O
horseback	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
boots	O
,	O
spurs	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
whip	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
;	O
the	O
hand-bill	O
came	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner-came	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
after	O
the	O
was	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
ten	O
guineas	O
upon	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
it	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
in	O
the	O
handbill	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
bill	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
ten	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Master	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner/	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
horse	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
held	O
his	O
horse	O
while	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
boots	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
shirt	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
he	O
once	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
a	O
whip	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
plated	O
spurs	O
,	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
examined	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
leave	O
a	O
message	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
Exchange-court	O
by	O
Exeter-exchange	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Street	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
goal	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
that	O
woman	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
who	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
we	O
had	O
information	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-lane	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
shewed	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
which	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
landlady	O
shewed	O
us	O
one	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
it	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
slugs	O
and	O
slints	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
concerning	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
vault	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
loaded	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pocket-pistol	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Street	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
seal	O
in	O
Sarah	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
's	O
box	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
scate	O
on	O
the	O
ice	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
seal	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
seal	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
brought	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Street	O
,	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
with	O
my	O
scates	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
ice	O
would	O
bear	O
in	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
and	O
scated	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
Kensington	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
seal	O
of	O
this	O
watch	O
lying	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
covered	O
with	O
dirt	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Middleton	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
distressed	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
say	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Middleton	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
alone	O
on	O
Christmas-eve	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Middleton	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
on	O
Christmaseve	O
?	O
S.	O
Middleton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
jury	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Luke	B-pers
Ranger	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
silk	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
seventy-six	O
pair	O
of	O
other	O
silk	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
wove	O
silk	O
for	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Eltington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Israel	O
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Israel	O
Eltington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
sundry	O
parcels	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
mention	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
of	O
his	O
extravagant	O
life	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
having	O
missed	O
goods	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
could	O
charge	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
apartment	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
in	O
his	O
landlady	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
wife	O
lodged	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
manufactory	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
every	O
workman	O
's	O
goods	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
those	O
goods	O
were	O
never	O
sold	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Eltington	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
such	O
goods	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
,	O
this	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
farther	O
enquiry	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
goods	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
bound	O
for	O
Jamaica	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
Collins	O
down	O
to	O
Portmouth	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
goods	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
papers	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
had	O
my	O
writing	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
invoice	O
in	O
Luke	B-pers
Ranger	I-pers
's	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
64	O
l.	O
consisting	O
of	O
stocking	O
and	O
breeches	O
pieces	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
manufactory	O
;	O
the	O
invoice	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
invoice	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
ship	O
lay	O
at	O
Mother-Bank	O
(	O
the	O
invoice	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
Lenton	O
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Corland	I-pers
commander	O
,	O
dated	O
October	O
25th	O
,	O
1767	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
which	O
agrees	O
with	O
the	O
invoice	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
short	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
letter	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
handwriting	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
letter	O
read	O
)	O
``	O
wherein	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
``	O
he	O
had	O
wronged	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
begs	O
for	O
``	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
if	O
the	O
ship	O
is	O
not	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
``	O
makes	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
the	O
goods	O
will	O
be	O
delivered	O
``	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
hopes	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
``	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
punished	O
;	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
himself	O
``	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
only	O
transgressor	O
,	O
signed	O
Luke	O
``	O
Ranger	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
received	O
27	O
l.	O
after	O
his	O
commitment	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
adventure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
out	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Granades	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Eltington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
quantity	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
?	O
Eltington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
tot	O
he	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
parcels	O
very	O
considerable	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
and	O
mother	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
dealt	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
last	O
summer	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
dispose	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
pair	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
sold	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
shop	O
price	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
some	O
at	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
6	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Eltington	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
much	O
confused	O
,	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
lived	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
J.	O
Walters	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
when	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benny	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
38	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
wooden	O
tubs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Mordecai	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mordecai	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Elias	B-pers
Mordecai	I-pers
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Shoemaker	B-place
row	I-place
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
butter	O
,	O
flour	O
,	O
oats	O
,	O
and	O
barley	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walking	O
about	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
daughter	O
cry	O
,	O
somebody	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
two	O
tubs	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
yourself	O
uneasy	O
,	O
Daniel	O
has	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Mordecai	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
stood	O
wringing	O
her	O
hands	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
two	O
tubs	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
with	O
two	O
tubs	O
;	O
we	O
enquired	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
with	O
others	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
shewed	O
me	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
wife	O
run	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
wicked	O
creature	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
rob	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
girl	O
to	O
run	O
for	O
a	O
proper	O
officer	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
one	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
butter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
bring	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
butter	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tub	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tub	O
,	O
all	O
dirty	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
letters	O
M	O
O	O
scratched	O
on	O
the	O
tub	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
three	O
nights	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mordecai	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
tubs	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
about	O
four	O
doors	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
tubs	O
,	O
one	O
full	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
half	O
full	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
woman	O
complained	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
Daniel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
running	O
past	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
butter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
about	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Mordecai	O
.	O
Did	O
these	O
tubs	O
stand	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
or	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
S.	O
Mordecai	O
.	O
They	O
stood	O
behind	O
my	O
counter	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
open	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Markas	O
Garrick	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
baker	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Blackmoor's-head	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
tell	O
his	O
mother	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
then	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Marks	O
Marks	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
about	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
three	O
farthings	O
to	O
his	O
penny	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
Cowen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Garrick	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Shoemaker-row	O
with	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
that	O
wants	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
presently	O
after	O
there	O
came	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
he	O
follows	O
the	O
baking	O
business	O
,	O
in	O
selling	O
cakes	O
about	O
Duke	O
's	O
place	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Roney	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Rachel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Roderegous	I-pers
,	O
Herian	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
Abigail	B-pers
Roderegous	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
106	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
gate	O
stood	O
,	O
towards	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Artillery-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
stood	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
there	O
,	O
looking	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
walking	O
;	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
hat	O
go	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
then	O
passing	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
moderate	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
with	O
equal	O
pace	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
very	O
moderately	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
not	O
play	O
the	O
fool	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
hat	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
words	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
continuing	O
the	O
same	O
pace	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
hastened	O
his	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoued	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
,	O
crying	O
the	O
same	O
running	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
ground	O
of	O
me	O
something	O
.	O
During	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
people	O
moving	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
distinguish	O
him	O
clearly	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
continued	O
my	O
run	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
turning	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
Artillery-lane	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
called	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
a	O
little	O
loud	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
said	O
there	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
have	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
towards	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
,	O
five	O
,	O
or	O
six	O
persons	O
together	O
standing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
them	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
have	O
taken	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
charge	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hat	O
besides	O
that	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
coat	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
matter	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
;	O
they	O
hustled	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
Artillery-lane	O
,	O
the	O
croud	O
still	O
increasing	O
;	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
intreated	O
very	O
earnestly	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
kneeling	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
those	O
about	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Bishopsgate	O
watch-house	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
appear	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
while	O
this	O
was	O
carrying	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
croud	O
that	O
my	O
hat	O
had	O
been	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
in	O
Artillery-lane	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
(	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Artillery-lane	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
fire-side	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
gentleman	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
combustion	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
talking	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
coach	O
man	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Smith	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
hat	O
lying	O
just	O
by	O
that	O
post	O
facing	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
says	O
he	O
has	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
carry	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
gentleman	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
?	O
A.	O
Smith	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
six	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
person	O
here	O
that	O
knows	O
how	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
began	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Hyams	O
Lazarus	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
regular	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
makes	O
a	O
point	O
of	O
it	O
never	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
without	O
his	O
leave	O
;	O
that	O
evening	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Admiral	O
Vernon	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
going	O
home	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
pushed	O
against	O
us	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
pushing	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
accident	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
continued	O
scolding	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
presently	O
stop	O
thief	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
hat	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Lazarus	O
Levi	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
works	O
for	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
diamond	O
polisher	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
his	O
indentures	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
three	O
years	O
to	O
serve	O
;	O
my	O
uncle	O
trusts	O
him	O
with	O
thousands	O
of	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
diamonds	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roaper	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
this	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
very	O
grossly	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
prudent	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
six	O
sons	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
goes	O
out	O
without	O
leave	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
always	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
good	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
an	O
apprentice	O
?	O
Levi	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lies	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Lady	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Lady	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
some	O
time	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
silver	O
plates	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bread	O
basket	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
according	O
to	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
informed	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spindler	O
,	O
a	O
silver-refiner	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Ducket	I-pers
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
.	O
This	O
day	O
fortnight	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Ducket	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Ducket	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
plates	O
of	O
Patterson	O
;	O
when	O
Ducket	O
and	O
Patterson	O
were	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
they	O
accused	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ducket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Patterson	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
two	O
plates	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
or	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
lay	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
expences	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
plates	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Latham	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lady	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
)	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
These	O
plates	O
were	O
stopt	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
Ducket	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
advertise	O
the	O
plates	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
three	O
papers	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
custody	O
about	O
eight	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
appeared	O
to	O
claim	O
the	O
plates	O
,	O
the	O
Alderman	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
party	O
and	O
discharge	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
plates	O
were	O
left	O
them	O
by	O
their	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
recommended	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
;	O
Ducket	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
advertisements	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
their	O
expences	O
;	O
the	O
plates	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
7	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
11	O
d.	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
the	O
butler	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
plates	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
what	O
circumstances	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
plates	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Patterson	O
his	O
aunt	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Emory	O
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
108	O
,	O
109	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
December	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
court	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
carried	O
a	O
dozen	O
silver	O
watches	O
packed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
box	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
the	O
bookkeeper	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Leeds	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
an	O
order	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Storer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
ten	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
accountable	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Storer	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
carrier	O
was	O
answerable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cooley	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
watches	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Storer	O
and	O
book	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
waggoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
pack	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
hamper	O
;	O
Stamp	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
near	O
the	O
hamper	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
waggoner	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
small	O
box	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
charge	O
about	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hamper	O
cut	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
parcel	O
advertised	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
advertising	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
or	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
clerks	O
,	O
acquainting	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
stopt	O
in	O
offering	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Gregory	O
pulled	O
this	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
that	O
Stamp	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
seven	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
Stamp	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
watches	O
between	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
and	O
Islington	O
.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plated	O
buckles	O
;	O
then	O
Gregory	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plated	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Storer	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
inn	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
stones	O
end	O
with	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
on	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
going	O
I	O
think	O
along	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Stamp	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
inn	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Islington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
Bunce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Hats	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
waggoner	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
waggoner	O
had	O
a	O
cadet	O
that	O
went	O
forward	O
with	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
Stamp	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
still	O
in	O
your	O
place	O
?	O
Bunce	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Marsden	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
Stamp	O
's	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
Gregory	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
)	O
then	O
Gregory	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
seven	O
were	O
buried	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
buried	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
hat	O
,	O
under	O
ground	O
,	O
in	O
Feather-bed-row	O
,	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
seven	O
watches	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Stamp	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
these	O
watches	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
hat	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Islington	O
.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Stamp	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
hobble	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moffet	I-pers
gave	O
Stamp	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
Benj	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Gregory	B-pers
the	O
same	O
.	O
Stamp	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Gregory	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
110	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Leggate	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
French	O
plate	O
extinguisher	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
nozel	O
of	O
French	O
plate	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Letecher	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Letecher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Anthony	B-pers
Letecher	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
sea	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
divers	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
disturbance	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
drunken	O
frolic	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
when	O
sober	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
seafaring-man	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Letecher	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodger	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publichouse	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
that	O
lodger	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
left	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
on	O
the	O
shelf	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Archihald	O
Mautslan	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
joke	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Peter	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Webber	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
three	O
masters	O
of	O
small	O
vessels	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
chequed	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
bed-gowns	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nunnery	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Nunnery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cold-bath-field	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
only	O
two	O
nights	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
in	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
houses	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
bed-gown	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sharpe	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
shirt	O
,	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Chandler	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Baldwin's-gardens	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Fox	O
's	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
smith	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
greatly	O
distressed	O
for	O
want	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
these	O
thing	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
own	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
112	O
,	O
113	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
and	O
Maximilian	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
live-guards	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
late	O
,	O
I	O
light	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
soldier	O
,	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Hedge-lane	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
sign	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
by	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sober	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
I	O
fuddled	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Coventry-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
all	O
of	O
smallish	O
stature	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Grosvenor-square	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
their	O
company	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
together	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
lower	B-place
Grosvenor-street	I-place
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
walked	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
sell	O
by	O
my	O
left	O
leg	O
;	O
he	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
pushed	O
me	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sell	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Burford	O
that	O
was	O
under	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
stood	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
accidental	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
be	O
advertised	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
to	O
come	O
immediately	O
to	O
his	O
office	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
Miller	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stood	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
Burford	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
he	O
said	O
when	O
or	O
where	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
perfectly	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
information	O
brought	O
against	O
Miller	O
,	O
concerning	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
Burford	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
Burford	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
the	O
clerk	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
watch	O
,	O
seal	O
and	O
chain	O
,	O
were	O
described	O
to	O
them	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
watch	O
last	O
?	O
Phipps	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Falcon	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
Burford	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Miller	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Miller	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Jemmy	O
Boswell	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ruins	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Burford	O
there	O
;	O
Bond	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brazier	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
For	O
Miller	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
Miller	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Burford	O
?	O
M.	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
son	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
son	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
?	O
M.	O
Miller	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Miller	O
's	O
mother	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
court	O
when	O
Burford	O
made	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hewlin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Miller	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Burford	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Miller	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Burford	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
364	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
No	O
273.	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
he	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bert	I-pers
.	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
and	O
slaying	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fisherman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fishing	O
just	O
below	O
Barnes	O
;	O
Ellis	O
and	O
Mr	O
Goodchild	O
,	O
with	O
I	O
believe	O
seven	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
nets	O
,	O
my	O
nets	O
were	O
not	O
fair	O
nets	O
;	O
I	O
mean	O
they	O
were	O
unlawful	O
,	O
the	O
mashes	O
were	O
too	O
small	O
;	O
those	O
people	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
water-bailiff	O
,	O
Goodchild	O
is	O
his	O
deputy	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
nets	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Strand-bridge	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
manned	O
two	O
boats	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
stones	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
river	O
to	O
board	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
nets	O
again	O
;	O
a	O
battle	O
ensued	O
;	O
Ellis	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
water-bailiff	O
's	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
struck	O
Thorne	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
boat-stern	O
;	O
we	O
attacked	O
them	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
own	O
we	O
did	O
wrong	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
fish	O
with	O
foul	O
nets	O
no	O
more	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
and	O
stabbing	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Windmill	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
upon	O
Hadley-green	O
,	O
near	O
Barnet	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Sawyers	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
White-lion	O
,	O
Kitt's-end	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
beer	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
draw	O
us	O
none	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Ward	O
say	O
behind	O
us	O
,	O
how	O
they	O
walk	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
causeway	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
clear	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
threw	O
Langford	O
off	O
against	O
the	O
pales	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
knocked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
and	O
some	O
blows	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
kicked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
again	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
cut	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stabbed	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
in	O
my	O
body	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
blood	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
Langford	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
call	O
murder	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
horse-keeper	O
named	O
Jennings	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
finding	O
me	O
bloody	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
murder	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
blood	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Langford	O
,	O
my	O
landlord	O
had	O
washed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
complained	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
we	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
his	O
bowels	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cut	O
under	O
his	O
eye	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
utter	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
passed	O
between	O
us	O
before	O
he	O
pushed	O
us	O
off	O
the	O
causeway	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Carol	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Sawyers	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
this	O
evidence	O
called	O
in	O
for	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
any	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
along	O
side	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
Harman	O
were	O
one	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Two	O
Sawyers	O
and	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
upon	O
the	O
causeway	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
behind	O
Harman	O
;	O
Ward	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
see	O
how	O
he	O
walks	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
on	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
them	O
both	O
off	O
the	O
causeway	O
;	O
Langford	O
sell	O
against	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
and	O
Harman	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Harman	O
recovered	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
yard	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
fellow-servants	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
Ward	O
ran	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
fellow-servants	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
behind	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
fighting	O
;	O
Jennings	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
Harman	O
's	O
hands	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
wrist	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
hand	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
together	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Couch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
lay	O
down	O
;	O
Ward	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
fighting	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
shut	O
up	O
his	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
murder	O
done	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
tumbled	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
fellow-servants	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
fight	O
two	O
against	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
blood	O
on	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
spot	O
on	O
my	O
cap	O
;	O
Ward	O
called	O
to	O
his	O
fellow-servants	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
not	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
will	O
you	O
let	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
before	O
Jennings	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
fighting	O
with	O
Ward	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Carol	I-pers
went	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
all	O
three	O
standing	O
up	O
pulling	O
one	O
another	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Harman	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Carol	O
,	O
here	O
will	O
be	O
murder	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
mischief	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
standing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Ward	O
came	O
through	O
my	O
room	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
there	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
throw	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
pond	O
,	O
or	O
put	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
ice	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
bailiff	O
to	O
General	O
Keppel	B-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kitt's-end	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Edward	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
either	O
sit	O
or	O
lie	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
hurt	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
very	O
much	O
disabled	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bloody	O
condition	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
horse-keeper	O
,	O
or	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
that	O
had	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
water	O
and	O
washed	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
very	O
much	O
hurt	O
about	O
about	O
his	O
eye	O
,	O
his	O
hands	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
bleed	O
about	O
the	O
eye	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Harman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
languishing	O
condition	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
examined	O
a	O
wound	O
within	O
two	O
inches	O
of	O
the	O
navel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
abdomen	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
occasion	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
wound	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
left	O
eye	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
occasioned	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
an	O
inch	O
in	O
depth	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
wounds	O
were	O
given	O
by	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Imp	O
.	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Asgood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
;	O
he	O
stood	O
also	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
not	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
in	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
him	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
Robert	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	B-place
the	I-place
Last	I-place
and	I-place
Sugar	I-place
Loaf	I-place
,	I-place
Water-lane	I-place
Black-friars	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
five	O
bargemen	O
or	O
lightermen	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
stank	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
contradict	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
our	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
each	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
penny	O
glass	O
each	O
;	O
without	O
any	O
provocation	O
the	O
prisoner	O
swore	O
and	O
blasted	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
called	O
me	O
booger	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
two	O
others	O
of	O
them	O
sell	O
to	O
beating	O
Edward	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
,	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
expected	O
murder	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
mischief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
passed	O
me	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
;	O
I	O
said	O
run	O
quick	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
expect	O
murder	O
will	O
be	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
farther	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
watchman	O
passed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
run	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
pulled	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
sits	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
heard	O
me	O
say	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
bargemen	O
had	O
came	O
out	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
beating	O
Crowther	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
received	O
his	O
hurt	O
abroad	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
came	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
Bartene	O
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
most	O
cruelly	O
used	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
up	O
his	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
some	O
blood	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
ear	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
little	O
finger	O
in	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
clot	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
deceased	O
been	O
a	O
watchman	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
watchman	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
very	O
likely	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
heard	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
hearing	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
or	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
breed	O
a	O
riot	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
is	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
you	O
brought	O
us	O
here	O
on	O
purpose	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
heard	O
me	O
say	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
welcome	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
paying	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knew	O
of	O
my	O
sending	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
five	O
men	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
11	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
they	O
found	O
fault	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
stank	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
abuse	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
used	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
fire	O
and	O
broil	O
him	O
;	O
Duncomb	O
said	O
what	O
can	O
be	O
your	O
reason	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
no	O
provocation	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
many	O
blasphemous	O
oaths	O
and	O
vile	O
expressions	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
have	O
this	O
usage	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
no	O
customer	O
shall	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
immediately	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
maid	O
out	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
stay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
strock	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
twice	O
on	O
the	O
ribs	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Newton	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
cried	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
Duncomb	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
sender	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
stop	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
was	O
out	O
calling	O
the	O
watch	O
they	O
quitted	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
almost	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
calling	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
watchmen	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
their	O
slaves	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bargemen	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
by	O
the	O
house	O
corner	O
,	O
towards	O
Fleetditch	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
went	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
steps	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
had	O
secreted	O
themselves	O
under	O
the	O
houses	O
by	O
Fleet-ditch	O
;	O
they	O
jumped	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
watchmen	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
returned	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
ill	O
used	O
enough	O
before	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bartene	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
called	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Ridley	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
watchman	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Paved	O
Alley	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
Ridley	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
run	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
broker	O
his	O
lanthorn	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Catlin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bargeman	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
fault	O
with	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
some	O
gin	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
served	O
us	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Duncomb	O
was	O
in	O
discourse	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Duncomb	O
up	O
in	O
discourse	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
sent	O
his	O
servant	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
none	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
going	O
out	O
without	O
paying	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
pay	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
Mr.	O
Duncomb	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
pay	O
to-morrow	O
;	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
blame	O
will	O
be	O
laid	O
upon	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
known	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Duncomb	O
being	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
the	O
watchmen	O
coming	O
down	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
steps	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
and	O
draw	O
the	O
watchman	O
's	O
staff	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
hit	O
him	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
with	O
the	O
staff	O
;	O
as	O
Thompson	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
Thompson	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
gentlemen	O
do	O
not	O
kill	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
your	O
husband	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
prisoner	O
off	O
from	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
watchman	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
almost	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
lanthorns	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
-	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coal	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Paved	O
Alley	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
neighbour	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
ditch	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
men	O
standing	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
just	O
turning	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
that	O
side	O
near	O
the	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
helping	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
struck	O
by	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
about	O
four	O
feet-long	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
to	O
escape	O
the	O
blows	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
stick	O
with	O
my	O
two	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
haling	O
me	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
ing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bidding	O
me	O
let	O
the	O
stick	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
m	O
his	O
blood	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
hit	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
enough	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Catlin	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
struck	O
me	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
widow	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
led	O
home	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
badly	O
used	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
beat	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
cruel	O
manner	O
,	O
by	O
five	O
villainous	O
fellows	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
staff	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
his	O
staff	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
his	O
right	O
ear	O
,	O
running	O
down	O
with	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
right	O
nostril	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
bed	O
and	O
compose	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
bed	O
;	O
with	O
persuasion	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
Hannah	O
,	O
my	O
head	O
!	O
Hannah	O
!	O
my	O
head	O
!	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
Lord	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
!	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
fatal	O
stroke	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
upon	O
his	O
poor	O
children	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
!	O
was	O
I	O
but	O
sit	O
to	O
die	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
opened	O
his	O
eyes	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
cried	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
prodigiously	O
;	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
senseless	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
surgeon	O
opened	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
feel	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
attend	O
St.	O
Bartholemew's-hospital	O
;	O
Ridley	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
sensible	O
,	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
eyes	O
,	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
ears	O
,	O
the	O
right	O
ear	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Young	B-pers
the	O
surgeon	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
am	O
pupil	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
examined	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
sclap	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
find	O
a	O
fracture	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
orders	O
to	O
blend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
what	O
was	O
necessary	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
upon	O
visiting	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
death	O
;	O
upon	O
representing	O
the	O
case	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
head	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
examine	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
fracture	O
from	O
the	O
hind	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
orbit	O
of	O
the	O
eye	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
depression	O
of	O
the	O
bone	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
discover	O
with	O
what	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
given	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
impossible	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
struck	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
escape	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coal-merchant	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
sober	O
young	O
fellow	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
an	O
honester	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
humaner	O
man	O
in	O
that	O
employ	O
living	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
frequent	O
instances	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
employ	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
bargeman	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
extremely	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
recommendation	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
executed	O
all	O
orders	O
given	O
him	O
with	O
great	O
punctuality	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lime-merchant	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
assiduous	O
in	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
frequently	O
to	O
Northfleet	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
drunk	O
or	O
negligent	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
and	O
dealer	O
in	O
coals	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
things	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
time	O
;	O
was	O
he	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
cruel	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
sooner	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
what	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
tempered	O
civil	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
company	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
after	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
him	O
disposed	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsome	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chaterton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
dutiful	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
quarrel	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
sailed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
sailed	O
in	O
one	O
barge	O
together	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
Friday	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
sentence	O
immediately	O
afterwards	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
body	O
to	O
be	O
dissected	O
and	O
anotomized	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
executed	O
accordingly	O
.	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Luke	I-pers
Kenchelow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
silk	O
cap	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jarrard	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Jarrard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Jarrard	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Hat	I-place
and	I-place
Bonnet	I-place
in	I-place
More-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Soho	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
arm	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
where	O
a	O
gown	O
had	O
hung	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
sung	O
the	O
gown	O
into	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
gown	O
had	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
pinned	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
pinned	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
deposed	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
began	O
and	O
finished	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
call	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
look	O
as	O
other	O
people	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
118	O
,	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
duffil	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
callimanco	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
grogram	O
cardinal	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tyley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Tyley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Worcester-street	B-place
,	I-place
Old	I-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
pawnbroking	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
till	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
from	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
of	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
one	O
night	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
pulley	O
into	O
an	O
entry	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
backwards	O
;	O
Casey	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
duffil	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
half	O
mourning	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
cardinal	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
Jew	O
a	O
barber	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
23	O
s.	O
for	O
our	O
part	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
came	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
clothes	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
them	O
three	O
young	O
fellows	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
one	O
Jacobs	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
young	O
fellows	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
paid	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
callimanco	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
cardinal	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
