TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hollyer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eastwick	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Custins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Killbeck	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicoll	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lott	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brambley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
*	O
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mash	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
,	O
Tuffin	O
Hobbs	O
,	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Timberlake	I-pers
.	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
containing	O
nineteen	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
44	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Milk-Street	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
piece	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
London	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Ewer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
into	O
our	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
London	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
worth	O
two	O
pounds	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
eight-pence	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Meymott	I-pers
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Meymott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Milk-Street	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
with	O
some	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
stay	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Bow	O
Church	O
.	O
He	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Jew	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bread-Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ewer	O
's	O
shop	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Milk-Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Ewer	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
also	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Chamberlain	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
it	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Bread-Street	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twenty	O
yards	O
walking	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
bag	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Ewer	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
linen	O
?	O
Meymott	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
times	O
before	O
on	O
different	O
days	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
changed	O
a	O
word	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
does	O
this	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Pembroke	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
evidence	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
old	O
bawd	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
.	O
Meymott	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
every	O
word	O
false	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
saying	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
270	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Tully	I-pers
,	O
grocer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
pomenta	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
ship	O
on	O
the	O
navigable	O
river	O
of	O
Thames	O
,	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
bags	O
of	O
pomenta	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	B-place
Henrietta	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
empty	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
pomenta	O
hanging	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
captain	O
of	O
the	O
vessel	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
captain	O
being	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
deprived	O
of	O
his	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
271	O
,	O
272	O
,	O
273	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Sykes	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Best	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogony	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
three	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
and	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
;	O
and	O
Winifred	B-pers
Carryl	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Titchbourn-Street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Great-Turnstile	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
at	O
near	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Spanish	O
ambassador	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
come	O
home	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
found	O
our	O
door	O
which	O
opens	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
lett	O
the	O
other	O
rooms	O
.	O
The	O
outward	O
door	O
we	O
always	O
leave	O
open	O
for	O
the	O
lodgers	O
.	O
The	O
bolt	O
was	O
burst	O
open	O
from	O
the	O
staple	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
(	O
Mentioning	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
things	O
advertised	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
by	O
Catharine	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Running	O
Horse	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
ever	O
acknowledge	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Never	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
shillings	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
my	O
lock	O
drove	O
from	O
its	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
.	O
The	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
where	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
night	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
men	O
's	O
names	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
Catharine	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
S.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milk-woman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Titchbourn-Court	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Best	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
brought	O
you	O
here	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Best	O
,	O
God	O
blast	O
her	O
!	O
what	O
does	O
she	O
want	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
my	O
beer	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
Best	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
and	O
stood	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
gate-way	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
feet	O
from	O
Saunders	O
's	O
door	O
:	O
she	O
jumped	O
from	O
thence	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Saunders	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
Best	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Sykes	O
followed	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
that	O
covered	O
her	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
C.	O
Keith	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
They	O
lodged	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
people	O
with	O
milk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Saunders	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
C.	O
Keith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Saunders	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
serve	O
my	O
customers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
needle-maker	O
that	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
things	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
?	O
C.	O
Keith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
cloth	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Sykes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
last	O
evidence	O
before	O
;	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
.	O
Best	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
Sykes	O
and	O
Best	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Carryl	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Best	O
tried	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
465	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Kite	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
160	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
274	O
,	O
275	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Medley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Maughlin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Winifred	B-pers
Carryl	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Archibald	B-pers
Maughlin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	B-place
,	I-place
East-Smithfield	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
get	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
guinea	O
reward	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
offer	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
find	O
it	O
without	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
Angel-alley	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
Carryl	O
's	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
sheets	O
of	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
bottom	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Medley	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
mug	O
cost	O
me	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Maughlin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
drawed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
engraved	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
his	O
liquor	O
in	O
one	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
beer	O
he	O
never	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
put	O
the	O
pint	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
a	O
customer	O
with	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
the	O
night	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
some	O
houses	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
supposed	O
Medley	O
frequented	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Esther	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	O
that	O
Winifred	B-pers
Carryl	I-pers
had	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
twenty-two	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Angel-court	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
Carryl	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Whinny	O
Madding	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Whinny	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
!	O
Here	O
is	O
this	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
come	O
to	O
light	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
the	O
mug	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
walked	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
coverlid	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
proper	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Medley	I-pers
came	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
where	O
I	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
shew	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
this	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
where	O
Carryl	O
lived	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
dispute	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
twenty-two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
twenty-two	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
hand	O
.	O
Medley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
mug	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
evidence	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
.	O
Carryl	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
here	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Pierpoint	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Carryl	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
good	O
.	O
Medley	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Carryl	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
Years	O
.	O
See	O
Medley	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
525	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
276	O
,	O
277	O
,	O
278	O
,	O
279	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Mallows	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pajolas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
blue	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
ermine	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
brown	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
is	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
And	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
three	O
gowns	O
,	O
the	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pajolas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Margaret-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
was	O
told	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
odd	O
things	O
,	O
some	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Martha	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
's	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warrant	O
granted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spinnage	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mallows	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
repairing	O
a	O
house	O
just	O
by	O
mine	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
Bush	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
Mallows	O
's	O
master	O
,	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
questions	O
;	O
Mallows	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
what	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
impeached	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
had	O
Bush	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
another	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
except	O
Waters	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
declared	O
themselves	O
innocent	O
except	O
Mallows	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Our	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
black	O
stuff	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
M.	O
Dean	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
surveyor	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Asylum	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
her	O
in	O
cloaths	O
;	O
so	O
have	O
laid	O
her	O
things	O
as	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Crooksbanks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Silver-Street	O
,	O
Golden-square	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
black	O
stuff	O
gown	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Hegath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
This	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
were	O
pledged	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
called	O
herself	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
Moses	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fifteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
eighteen	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
Bush	O
,	O
Mallows	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Bush	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
walked	O
about	O
till	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Bush	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
window	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
empty	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
ladder	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
the	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
moon	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
chucked	O
the	O
clothes	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
them	O
.	O
Mallows	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
Bush	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
He	O
got	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
leads	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
garret	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
found	O
open	O
.	O
They	O
stayed	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
gowns	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pledge	O
them	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
had	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Farrington	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
serve	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
some	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
Major	O
Spinnage	B-pers
came	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
Mallows	O
.	O
Mallows	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Moses	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
in	O
Cranbourn-alley	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
younger	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Bush	O
in	O
Tothill	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
evidence	O
Waters	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Austin	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
garret	O
fastened	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
it	O
myself	O
betwixt	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
fastening	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Bush	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
evidence	O
,	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
seeing	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
brother	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Waters	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
quarrelled	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
trouble	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
this	O
robbery	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
.	O
Mallow	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
lad	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Waters	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
night	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
came	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
leave	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
lodging	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Bush	O
,	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
Mallows	O
,	O
all	O
three	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Ann	O
Waters	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Bush	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
570	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
280	O
,	O
281	O
,	O
282	O
,	O
283	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hines	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Mundy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
remonsterance	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
challace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
Excellency	O
Count	B-pers
Salvre	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Imperial	O
Ambassador	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
steward	O
to	O
his	O
Excellency	O
Count	O
Salvre	O
.	O
The	O
chapel	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James's-square	O
,	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
between	O
fourteen	O
and	O
fifteen	O
feet	O
high	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
upon	O
a	O
post	O
where	O
his	O
Excellency	O
goes	O
in	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
part	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
trod	O
was	O
dirty	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
think	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
it	O
gave	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
noble	O
families	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
lay	O
dormant	O
till	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Stapleton	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
concerned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
surplice	O
,	O
which	O
contained	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
these	O
girls	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
six	O
persons	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Stapleton	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
women	O
.	O
Bush	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
admitted	O
him	O
and	O
a	O
girl	O
evidence	O
.	O
Bush	O
is	O
now	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
on	O
another	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Ann	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
All	O
four	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
284	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
St.	O
David	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
,	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
C.	O
Chambers	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
before	O
you	O
or	O
behind	O
you	O
?	O
C.	O
Chambers	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
with	O
the	O
breeches	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Alms	O
Houses	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
!	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
dead-drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Richard	O
Row	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
breeches	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
and	O
hallooed	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
clothes	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
swore	O
the	O
robbery	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Creswick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
285	O
,	O
286	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Waldin	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Nicholi	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Christian	B-pers
Nicholi	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
somebody	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
chamber	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
about	O
half	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
toy	O
and	O
silver	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
They	O
produced	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
by	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
me	O
assistance	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
case	O
with	O
aqua-fortis	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
man	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
10	O
l.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
This	O
Jew	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
white	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Gray	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Gray	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
two	O
days	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
with	O
a	O
vessel	O
for	O
Captain	O
Johnson	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
young	O
fellow	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
young	O
fellows	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
park	O
tossing	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
this	O
watch	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Pinchbeck	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
seal	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
white	O
stone	O
seal	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
afternoon	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
seal	O
was	O
gold	O
;	O
he	O
tried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
and	O
put	O
that	O
seal	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
is	O
on	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
all	O
spent	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
spend	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
us	O
both	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
prison	O
.	O
Waldin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Gray	O
buy	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
seal	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
money	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
us	O
both	O
.	O
Levi	O
.	O
Walden	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Gray	O
asked	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shave	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Friday	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
park	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Gray	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
people	O
tossing	O
up	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
asked	O
Gray	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
gone	O
down	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
walk	O
he	O
called	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Gray	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
seal	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Shave	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
justly	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
Gray	O
doing	O
there	O
Shave	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
Shave	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Shave	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
some	O
meat	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
287	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
metal	O
box	O
and	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Virgina-Street	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
On	O
April	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
merry	O
making	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
continued	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
noise	O
or	O
resistance	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
searched	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
metal	O
box	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fluttered	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
niece	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
rather	O
darkish	O
than	O
light	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
very	O
clear	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
both	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
voice	O
and	O
stature	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
three	O
had	O
blue	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
or	O
surtout	O
coats	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
hats	O
flapped	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
shorter	O
than	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
named	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Leynard	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
company	O
there	O
from	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
till	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
wore	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout	O
coat	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Leynard	O
's	O
wife	O
's	O
wake	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
White	O
Lion-Street	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
a	O
wake	O
?	O
M.	O
Conner	O
.	O
They	O
sit	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
wanted	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stayed	O
there	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
Virginia-Street	O
?	O
M.	O
Conner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
from	O
this	O
Court	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
corpse	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
by	O
themselves	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Derwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
coffee-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
person	O
can	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
backwards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hollis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
night	O
the	O
election	O
was	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Leynard	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Leynard	O
lay	O
dead	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
wake	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
Sullivan	O
was	O
sitting	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Hollis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
and	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
Mrs.	O
Leynard	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
not	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
continued	O
up	O
stairs	O
till	O
twelve	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
evidences	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
;	O
the	O
jury	O
thought	O
it	O
needless	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
thirteen-and-sixpenny	O
piece	O
,	O
twelve	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
Just	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
an	O
alley	O
I	O
met	O
Sullivan	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
way	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	B-place
of	I-place
Plough-Alley	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
White	O
Lion-Street	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hundred	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
Sullivan	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Another	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
squatted	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
Sullivan	O
about	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
and	O
a	O
thirteen-and-sixpenny	O
piece	O
,	O
guineas	O
,	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
a	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
seven	O
guineas	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
near	O
a	O
lamp	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
sort	O
out	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
close	O
blue	O
coat	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
girl	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hermitage-Street	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
robbed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
Plough-Alley	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
tw	O
enty	O
yards	O
from	O
Plough-Alley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cornwell	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Watermens	O
Arms	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
his	O
ship	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
robbed	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
mate	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bailiff	O
's	O
follower	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
right	O
under	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
while	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
bailiff	O
that	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
arrested	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
the	O
mate	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
another	O
did	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
bear	O
him	O
a	O
grudge	O
on	O
his	O
arresting	O
you	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
witnesses	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
husband	O
to	O
Mary	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Leynard	O
's	O
from	O
eleven	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
night	O
till	O
three	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Magee	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
assist	O
as	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
wake	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
continued	O
there	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
till	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
deposed	O
she	O
helped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
clothes	O
on	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
up	O
again	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
room	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
stayed	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
made	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
just	O
struck	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
passed	O
over	O
the	O
Hermitage	B-place
bridge	I-place
about	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stepped	O
from	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
!	O
and	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
,	O
above	O
a	O
hundred	O
times	O
.	O
He	O
passed	O
for	O
a	O
bailiff	O
's	O
follower	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
lamp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
and	O
metal	O
buttons	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
him	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
person	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
!	O
Thieves	O
!	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
a	O
smack	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
obstinate	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
a	O
dozen	O
robberies	O
thereabouts	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
trouble	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
sworn	O
in	O
a	O
bailiff	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
287	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Manton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
printed	O
book	O
bound	O
in	O
leather	O
,	O
entitled	O
,	O
The	O
Book	O
of	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
and	O
Administration	O
of	O
the	O
Sacraments	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Rites	O
and	O
Ceremonies	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Dean	B-pers
and	I-pers
Chapter	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
church	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Paul	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	I-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
vergers	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
church	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
vergers	O
go	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
a	O
book	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
touch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
dropped	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
(	O
Two	O
folio	O
Common	O
Prayer	O
Books	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Dean	O
and	O
Chapter	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defences	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
distressed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
promised	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
mercy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
printed	O
books	O
bound	O
in	O
leather	O
,	O
intitled	O
,	O
The	O
Book	O
of	O
Common-Prayer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Dean	O
and	O
Chapter	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Christopher	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Pater-noster-row	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
3d	O
or	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
two	O
books	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
two	O
folio	O
Common-Prayer	O
Books	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
a	O
pension	O
annually	O
from	O
the	O
Trinity-house	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
and	O
others	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
and	O
another	O
verger	O
.	O
As	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
books	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
enquiring	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
these	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
lettered	O
on	O
the	O
St	O
outside	O
P	O
C	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Dean	O
and	O
Chapter	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
288	O
,	O
289	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
dealer	O
with	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
gentlemen	O
pretty	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
live	O
honest	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
and	O
Ship	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
Lion	O
soon	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
meaning	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
Cook	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Lion	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
opened	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Cook	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
Cook	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Bull	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Keys	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
a	O
Kick	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
this	O
language	O
?	O
Key	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
deputy-keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
pretty	O
much	O
used	O
to	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
gentry	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six-and-forty	O
yards	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
of	O
different	O
colours	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
staff	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
applied	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
for	O
leave	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
which	O
he	O
granted	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
.	O
Cook	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Morris	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Duke's-place	O
to	O
sell	O
among	O
the	O
Jews	O
.	O
Then	O
Morris	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
Cook	O
's	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
made	O
it	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
an	O
owner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
superfine	O
black	O
cloth	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
After	O
that	O
Morris	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
watch	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
four	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
this	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
abroad	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
cloth	O
worth	O
a	O
yard	O
?	O
Keys	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Lazrous	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lion	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
cloth	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
but	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Raven	O
and	O
Ship	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
drinking	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
then	O
in	O
came	O
Lion	O
and	O
Keys	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
and	O
Keys	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Cook	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Cook	O
say	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
at	O
Kensington	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
evidence	O
as	O
Keys	O
had	O
said	O
before	O
.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Red-Lion-square	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
half	O
a	O
day	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
cloth	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Lion	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
cloth	O
.	O
Lion	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
safe	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
synagogue	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
Lion	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
there	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
turn	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
children	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
cost	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
coarse	O
;	O
and	O
first	O
bid	O
me	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
then	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Then	O
Keys	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
staff	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
examined	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
here	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
then	O
Sir	O
John	O
committed	O
us	O
for	O
farther	O
examination	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
we	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
advertised	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
owner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
none	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
Morris	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
watch	O
at	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
cloth	O
of	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Cook	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
the	O
cloth	O
and	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
290	O
,	O
291	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bluckfield	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Snow-hill	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
King's-Arms	I-place
inn	I-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
walking	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
very	O
close	O
behind	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
then	O
walked	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
they	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
We	O
pursued	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stop	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
gone	O
past	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
you	O
have	O
.	O
They	O
declared	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
we	O
meant	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
us	O
stop	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
from	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
they	O
resisted	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
dangerous	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
alehouse	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
search	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
mine	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
this	O
yours	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
of	O
itself	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
dropped	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
their	O
impudence	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
violent	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Pool	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
bought	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
at	O
Rag-fair	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
till	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Bluckfield	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
cutler	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
home	O
with	O
some	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Pool	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Going	O
down	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
me	O
but	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
all	O
nasty	O
,	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
292	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
weight	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Queen-hithe	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
cheese	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
cheese	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
eleven	O
cheeses	O
on	O
a	O
table	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcel	O
under	O
the	O
uppermost	O
cheese	O
,	O
hanging	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
lying	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
uppermost	O
cheese	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
marked	O
T	O
M	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
sack	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
cheese	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
here	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
293	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
Eaves	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Jans	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
.	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Jans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wardor-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
I	O
reserve	O
to	O
myself	O
the	O
upper	O
floor	O
and	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
lett	O
out	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
business	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
The	O
staple	O
to	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
forced	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
things	O
;	O
amongst	O
which	O
were	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
again	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Major	O
Spinnage	B-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
hand-bills	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
stopt	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dubury	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Carnaby-street	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
clothes	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
pawned	O
the	O
coat	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
pledge	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
offered	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Bedfordbury	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
jeweller	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
so	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
commiting	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jervis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jervis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
gave	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
each	O
a	O
ticket	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
.	O
Through	O
persuasion	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
master	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
his	O
maid	O
come	O
to	O
rock	O
the	O
child	O
while	O
they	O
drank	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rodenhurst	O
,	O
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
boy	O
from	O
the	O
apothecary	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
within	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
phial	O
of	O
stuff	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
this	O
will	O
do	O
my	O
cold	O
good	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
saw	O
me	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
bottle	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
clergyman	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Oxford	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
cross	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
keeping	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
to	O
rock	O
the	O
cradle	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
home	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
nine	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
cradle	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
just	O
awake	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
light	O
me	O
a	O
candle	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Was	O
I	O
alone	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
a	O
sweetheart	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
arm	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
and	O
kissed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
candle	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
lose	O
your	O
ma	O
idenhead	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
took	O
my	O
candle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
this	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
about	O
my	O
waist	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
fetched	O
me	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
and	O
flung	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
upon	O
a	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
fell	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
lay	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
up	O
my	O
petticoats	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
arm	O
cross	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
scrambling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
my	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
you	O
shall	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
ravished	O
me	O
without	O
my	O
will	O
or	O
consent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
resist	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
He	O
ravished	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
.	O
No	O
Answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
tell	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
With	O
his	O
tool	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
something	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
my	O
petticoats	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
wet	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
blood	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
this	O
story	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
you	O
and	O
he	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
mistress	O
from	O
the	O
play	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
together	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ravish	O
you	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
study	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
came	O
home	O
first	O
,	O
your	O
master	O
or	O
mistress	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
Master	O
came	O
home	O
first	O
.	O
Mistress	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
tavern	O
to	O
order	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
.	O
Master	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
tavern	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
home	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
mention	O
this	O
to	O
first	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
spoke	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
houses	O
joining	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
that	O
joins	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
was	O
empty	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
there	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
When	O
mistress	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
looks	O
very	O
poorly	O
;	O
has	O
the	O
child	O
cried	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
I	O
have	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Master	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
kept	O
up	O
past	O
her	O
hour	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
staying	O
alone	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
good	O
parson	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
as	O
rude	O
as	O
the	O
devil	O
.	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
for	O
the	O
supper	O
.	O
I	O
staying	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
mistress	O
came	O
down	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
for	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
parson	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill.	O
Master	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
supper	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
no	O
more	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
warming	O
the	O
bed	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Has	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
too	O
.	O
Master	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
said	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
your	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
both	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
of	O
a	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
what	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
your	O
mistress	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
breakfast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
came	O
by	O
then	O
breakfast	O
was	O
ready	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
introduce	O
it	O
after	O
breakfast	O
?	O
E.	O
Jervis	O
.	O
Mistress	O
hearing	O
me	O
tell	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
for	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Jervis	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
gentleman	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
?	O
Jervis	O
.	O
Because	O
we	O
had	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
related	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
as	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
all	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
apothecary	O
's	O
boy	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
tavern	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
study	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Heabendle	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
me	O
deliver	O
the	O
phial	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
crime	O
for	O
which	O
a	O
man	O
must	O
lose	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
justice	O
some	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
shame	O
;	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
poor	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
mentioned	O
the	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
when	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
shut	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
attempted	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
her	O
other	O
arm	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
arm	O
lay	O
upon	O
her	O
breast	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
people	O
speak	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
quarters	O
of	O
Spital	O
Field	O
clock	O
go	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
quarters	O
the	O
last	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
go	O
the	O
half	O
hour	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
flung	O
her	O
across	O
,	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
her	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
careful	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
fearing	O
it	O
should	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
some	O
hurt	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
noise	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
mouth	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
cried	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rodenburst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mistress	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
ticket	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
of	O
The	O
Fair	O
Penitent	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
saw	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
stayed	O
till	O
the	O
play	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
tavern	O
to	O
order	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
so	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
looks	O
very	O
pale	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sleep	O
,	O
being	O
kept	O
up	O
past	O
her	O
hour	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
cross	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
cried	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wished	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
stayed	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Her	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
Was	O
you	O
afraid	O
to	O
stay	O
alone	O
?	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
good	O
parson	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
as	O
rude	O
as	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
hurt	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Her	O
master	O
said	O
,	O
Has	O
he	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
been	O
rude	O
?	O
has	O
he	O
hurt	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
I	O
shall	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
ashamed	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
was	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
supper	O
ready	O
.	O
She	O
staying	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
crying	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asking	O
her	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
master	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
;	O
so	O
nothing	O
farther	O
passed	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
warming	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Has	O
the	O
parson	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
too	O
.	O
Her	O
master	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
girl	O
stepped	O
after	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
something	O
before	O
eight	O
)	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
think	O
of	O
a	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
what	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
slapped	O
the	O
door	O
too	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
between	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
being	O
sent	O
down	O
for	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
stayed	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
parson	O
has	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
she	O
does	O
nothing	O
but	O
crawl	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cried	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
After	O
breakfast	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
washing	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
began	O
asking	O
her	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
out	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
seemed	O
so	O
uneasy	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
a	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
hear	O
your	O
husband	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
lawyer	O
's	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
ashamed	O
of	O
himself	O
?	O
M.	O
Rodenburst	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
only	O
pulling	O
and	O
hawling	O
her	O
about	O
,	O
as	O
young	O
persons	O
do	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
flung	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
laid	O
with	O
you	O
!	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sure	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
!	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
indeed	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
justice	O
done	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
her	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
shocked	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
then	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
manner	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
that	O
evening	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cradle	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
letting	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
and	O
lighted	O
his	O
candle	O
,	O
which	O
generally	O
stands	O
there	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
tap	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
see	O
this	O
room	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
and	O
dragged	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
again	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
carried	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
cried	O
and	O
screamed	O
prodigiously	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
arm	O
somewhere	O
upon	O
her	O
breast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
describe	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
laying	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
M.	O
Rodenburst	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
;	O
as	O
men	O
have	O
conversation	O
with	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
against	O
her	O
consent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Rodenburst	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
is	O
empty	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
is	O
a	O
china	O
shop	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
high	O
brick	O
wall	O
between	O
,	O
higher	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
reach	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
.	O
That	O
house	O
and	O
ours	O
are	O
both	O
double	O
brick	O
houses	O
;	O
and	O
ours	O
is	O
lined	O
with	O
wainscot	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
apothecary	O
's	O
boy	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
phial	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
rock	O
the	O
cradle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
excuse	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
make	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Rodenburst	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
from	O
about	O
eight	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
said	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
tavern	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tavern	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
judgment	O
she	O
believed	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
did	O
lie	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
will	O
;	O
that	O
although	O
there	O
are	O
children	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
hears	O
any	O
noise	O
there	O
from	O
that	O
parlour	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
first	O
applied	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
character	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
mother	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
peaceable	O
manner	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
directed	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
lived	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
dragged	O
her	O
about	O
and	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
character	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
nor	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
modest	O
girl	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
girl	O
examined	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
her	O
examined	O
here	O
?	O
J	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
varied	O
in	O
any	O
circumstance	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
particularly	O
requested	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
cautious	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
here	O
and	O
hereafter	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
charge	O
him	O
wrongfully	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
did	O
not	O
inquire	O
so	O
particularly	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
then	O
how	O
it	O
would	O
turn	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
give	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
committed	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
had	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
absolutely	O
for	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
would	O
have	O
bound	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
examined	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
detainer	O
was	O
sent	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
material	O
difference	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
circumstances	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
has	O
said	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
two	O
persons	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
company	O
some	O
hours	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
from	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
bottle	O
at	O
the	O
tavern	O
door	O
of	O
an	O
apothecary	O
's	O
boy	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Heabendle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
rock	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
cradle	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
bring	O
something	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
M.	O
Heabendle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
unhappy	O
circumstance	O
for	O
any	O
man	O
,	O
much	O
more	O
for	O
a	O
clergyman	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
conscientious	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
every	O
word	O
sworn	O
against	O
me	O
is	O
false	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
innocence	O
will	O
be	O
sufficiently	O
proved	O
before	O
this	O
honourable	O
court	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
God	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
judge	O
of	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Freemont	I-pers
.	O
The	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Three	O
Tun	O
tavern	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
there	O
eating	O
some	O
salmon	O
.	O
I	O
remained	O
there	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
past	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
if	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
never	O
quitted	O
our	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
he	O
quitted	O
it	O
a	O
moment	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
did	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
merry	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
stirred	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
florried	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
eat	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
and	O
raddishes	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
very	O
agreeable	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
naturally	O
chatty	O
and	O
merry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Freemont	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
wheeler	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
with	O
precision	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
nine	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
quarters	O
at	O
the	O
church	O
went	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
act	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
on	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
Tun	O
tavern	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
eight	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
reading	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
lobster	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
bought	O
a	O
lobster	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
salmon	O
,	O
and	O
supped	O
there	O
together	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Freemont	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
never	O
parted	O
company	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
new	O
cheese	O
and	O
raddishes	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
called	O
upon	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
since	O
recollect	O
he	O
was	O
