TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
George	B-pers
Perrot	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Willes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hatt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Sampson	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Turverwell	I-pers
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Billing	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fanton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Silk	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wetherell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Angell	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chippendale	I-pers
||	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilmott	I-pers
||	O
,	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vigure	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilmott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Woolbridge	I-pers
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chippendale	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dearlove	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
twenty-one	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
August	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Milk-Street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
reason	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robing	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
mentioning	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
till	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
confession	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
for	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
What	O
past	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
uncle	O
can	O
inform	O
you	O
.	O
M.	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
asked	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
questions	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
three	O
to	O
him	O
myself	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
secreted	O
it	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
tears	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
There	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
proposed	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
ample	O
discovery	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
encouragement	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
would	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
be	O
favourable	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
417	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lowton	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
near	O
Epping	O
forest	O
.	O
On	O
Easter-Monday	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Feathers	I-place
at	I-place
Charing-Cross	I-place
,	O
to	O
refresh	O
myself	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gill	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
yard	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
Who	O
he	O
was	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Then	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
,	O
one	O
held	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
more	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
searched	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
dawning	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
within	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
?	O
Chappel	O
.	O
I	O
begged	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
fearing	O
they	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Chappel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
return	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
alarm	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Chappel	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
passage	O
?	O
Chappel	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
that	O
used	O
you	O
thus	O
ill	O
,	O
go	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Chappel	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gandal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
that	O
comes	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Sun	O
Fire-Office	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Feathers	O
is	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
is	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
backwards	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
could	O
he	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
mentioned	O
two	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
public-house	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
son	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
licence	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
many	O
robberies	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Almonry	O
:	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
Mr.	O
Chappel	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
that	O
conclusion	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
own	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
if	O
pawned	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
redeem	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Powes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
on	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
another	O
girl	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
this	O
gentleman	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
us	O
into	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
connections	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
something	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
present	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
already	O
?	O
He	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
penny	O
for	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
his	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
together	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
black	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
black	O
silk	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
*	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
safe	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
window	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
cut	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
groove	O
away	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
shutter	O
slides	O
,	O
taken	O
the	O
shutter	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
above	O
five	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dadget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
his	O
mother	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
Charterhouse-lane	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
the	O
things	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
nor	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Cann	O
's	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
:	O
he	O
there	O
owned	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
others	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cann	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
companions	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
named	O
James	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
as	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
their	O
names	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
Blower	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
here	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Catherine-wheel	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
by	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hilyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
82	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
and	O
enameller	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
put	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
waterman	O
;	O
but	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
the	O
watch-case	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
his	O
character	O
impeached	O
before	O
.	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dorton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
in	O
Charterhouse-lane	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rawley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-case	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Charterhouse-lane	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Poppin	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
Fleet-Street	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
419	O
,	O
420	O
,	O
421	O
,	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pissey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwellinghouse	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Knipe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
musical	O
table	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Deelvy	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dailey	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Knipe	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
facing	O
Chapel	O
Street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
clock	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
clock	O
;	O
likewise	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
work	O
basket	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gauze	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
clock	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Kenderis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
fastened	O
all	O
the	O
back	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
danger	O
of	O
the	O
fore-room	O
windows	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
the	O
clock	O
;	O
likewise	O
the	O
ruffles	O
and	O
gauze	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
's	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
work	O
basket	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
some	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
table	O
clock	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
.	O
They	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
M'Mahon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Plume	O
of	O
Feathers	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
and	O
salesman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
by	O
Red	O
Lion-street	O
;	O
Stapleton	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
iron	O
rails	O
,	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
gauze	O
and	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
David	O
Price	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
Stapleton	O
followed	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
They	O
found	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
Stapleton	O
handed	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
:	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
gave	O
Stapleton	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
candle	O
:	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
Stapleton	O
for	O
Dailey	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
Dailey	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Caton	O
and	O
Stapleton	O
rent	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
Dailey	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
clock	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
our	O
lodging	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
chimes	O
would	O
strike	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
fore-room	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
disorderly	O
persons	O
:	O
I	O
and	O
Stapleton	O
got	O
clear	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
twelve	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Dailey	O
went	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
clock	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
Caton	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
off	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
clock	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
servant	O
maids	O
,	O
as	O
their	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bambury-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
M'Mahon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
M'Mahon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Caton	O
and	O
Stapleton	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
also	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
much	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Price	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
me	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
M'Mahon	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Red	O
Lion-street	O
,	O
leaning	O
over	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Red	O
Lion	O
passage	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Galaway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
a	O
search	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Dailey	O
's	O
rents	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
M'Mahon	O
,	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
Caton	O
:	O
Stapleton	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
the	O
rooms	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
lodging	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
;	O
M'Mahon	O
was	O
cleared	O
:	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Dailey	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Dailey	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
M'Mahon	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
clock	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
whose	O
clock	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
informed	O
us	O
that	O
Stapleton	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linen	O
and	O
gauze	O
in	O
Dailey	O
's	O
necessary	O
house	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Burnett	I-pers
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
several	O
houses	O
of	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Dailey	O
's	O
rents	O
we	O
found	O
M'Mahon	O
,	O
Caton	O
and	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
M'Mahon	O
was	O
cleared	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
Justices	O
he	O
never	O
lay	O
in	O
Dailey	O
's	O
rents	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Price	O
was	O
also	O
discharged	O
.	O
Caton	O
was	O
detained	O
by	O
reason	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
pick	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Stapleton	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
here	O
to-day	O
.	O
After	O
Dailey	O
had	O
told	O
of	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
M'Mahon	O
at	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
's	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
necessary	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
has	O
been	O
mentioned	O
already	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Red	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
maids	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
clock	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
Stapleton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
for	O
other	O
offences	O
.	O
Caton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
one	O
morning	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
more	O
beer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Stapleton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
shuffle	O
board	O
.	O
M'Mahon	O
said	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
accuse	O
yourself	O
.	O
Stapleton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Price	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Red	O
Lion	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
M'Mahon	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
came	O
by	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
clock	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
father	O
would	O
lock	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
M'Mahon	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
.	O
Dailey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
M'Mahon	O
never	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
bargain	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
then	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
there	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
the	O
clock	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
brought	O
till	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Galaway	O
Dailey	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
.	O
The	O
boys	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
long	O
before	O
.	O
Dailey	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
Turnmill	O
Street	O
;	O
Margaret	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Dondin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
lately	O
deals	O
in	O
old	O
clothes	O
and	O
linen	O
rags	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
honest	O
in	O
his	O
dealings	O
.	O
Caton	O
,	O
Stapleton	O
and	O
Price	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
Dailey	O
guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
423	O
,	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Caton	I-pers
(	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Hugh	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Dean	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
Caton	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
one	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
July	O
7	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Murry	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
This	O
old	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
never	O
comes	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
takes	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
belated	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
till	O
morning	O
.	O
Murry	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
You	O
fool	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
your	O
room	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
blame	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
in	O
Maynard-street	B-place
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
undress	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pulling	O
off	O
my	O
gown	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
dram	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
yet	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
the	O
breeches	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
Immediately	O
up	O
came	O
Murry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
They	O
rushed	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
string	O
in	O
getting	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
Murry	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hampton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
about	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
received	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fell	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
;	O
there	O
this	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
invited	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
bed	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
bed	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
gin	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
others	O
rifled	O
my	O
pockets	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
ventured	O
my	O
life	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
425	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-road	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
cut	O
in	O
single	O
yards	O
for	O
a	O
particular	O
use	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
the	O
9th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
shewed	O
five	O
pieces	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
identical	O
pieces	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
(	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
brought	O
out	O
three	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
one	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
out	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
in	O
six	O
pieces	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
packthread	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Irish	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Flyn	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
her	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
known	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
wash	O
them	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
yard	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Flyn	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flyn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Jones	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
worth	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Flyn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
wash	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
this	O
Jones	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
drank	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Flyn	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
this	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Jones	O
.	O
What	O
door	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
back-door	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
426	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
September	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
Trinity-monday	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Swift	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
hawled	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
clandestinely	O
carried	O
my	O
watch	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
a	O
stout	O
woman	O
?	O
Donaldson	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
dapper	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
such	O
woman	O
here	O
?	O
(	O
He	O
looks	O
about	O
.	O
)	O
J.	O
Donaldson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
about	O
again	O
.	O
J.	O
Donaldson	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
(	O
Pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
got	O
both	O
her	O
arms	O
round	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
J.	O
Donaldson	O
.	O
Because	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
was	O
near	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hawl	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
in	O
Wapping	O
parish	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
facing	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
watch-string	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Stribley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
deliver	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
small-beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
427	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thread	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thread	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Roebuck	O
in	O
Grafton-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
leatherseller	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
that	O
worked	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
conversation	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
upon	O
a	O
furloe	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
friends	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
fife	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
in	I-place
Pye-street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
touched	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
snatched	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Core	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Gun-yard	O
.	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Hunks	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
was	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
a	O
drummer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
little	O
estate	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
habit	O
of	O
a	O
drummer	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
that	O
worked	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
upon	O
a	O
furloe	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
journey	O
and	O
safe	O
return	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
learn	O
him	O
the	O
fife	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
gratis	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
appearance	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Serjeant	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
drum-major	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
428	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
Holmes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
just	O
as	O
my	O
servant	O
had	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vanham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mould	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
variety	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
directly	O
say	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
till	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
hang	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
shewed	O
her	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
stolen	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
had	O
them	O
close	O
up	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
good	O
woman	O
wanted	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
more	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
but	O
eight	O
weeks	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
the	O
eight	O
weeks	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
She	O
comes	O
from	O
Nottinghamshire	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
knew	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
but	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
sick	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
429	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
featherbed	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Parson	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Bride-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
live	O
joins	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
its	O
reaching	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
my	O
goods	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
now	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
bed	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
fetched	O
that	O
bed	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
bed	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Islington	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hodson	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Holder	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
had	O
a	O
bed	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
people	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
bed	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
yet	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
to	O
what	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
who	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
follow	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
answers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
all	O
unanimous	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
charge	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
order	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Worthy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
twenty-one	O
years	O
;	O
David	B-pers
Mophet	I-pers
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
the	O
same	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
sixteen	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
fifteen	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	O
,	O
sixteen	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Dolby	I-pers
,	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
Lauff	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Edmund	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
Louff	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
,	O
just	O
entering	O
Ludgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
about	O
half-way	O
down	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
My	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Oliver	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Arms	O
tavern	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
follow	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
run	O
along	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
afterwards	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
In	O
walking	O
along	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
dutiful	O
son	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
him	O
at	O
school	O
from	O
three	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
last	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
two	O
voyages	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
sea	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
at	O
seven	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Havannah	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
431	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
old	B-place
Bridewell	I-place
before	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
burnt	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
out	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
man	O
up	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
apprehended	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
hill	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
myself	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
better	O
acquainted	O
with	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
my	O
cook	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Lobb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
offering	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge-foot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
apprehended	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
at	O
Bridewell	O
precinct	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
in	O
Tooley-street	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
copper	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
different	O
in	O
his	O
story	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
hill	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Sharpe	O
's	O
cook	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leek	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offering	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
that	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
down	O
Tooley-street	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
King's-head	O
tavern	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
farther	O
down	O
Tooley-street	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
in	O
Tooley-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
offer	O
a	O
copper	O
pottage-pot	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
he	O
set	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sharpe	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
my	O
daily	O
using	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
tin	O
shop	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tin	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
tin	O
shop	O
by	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
hill	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
trouble	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
S.	O
Metcalf	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
get	O
our	O
goods	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
we	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
from	O
Newgate-street	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
turner	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
on	O
Snowhill	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
live	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nearer	O
the	O
fire	O
than	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Snowhill	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
.	O
Lobb	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
his	O
master	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stir	O
a	O
step	O
to	O
save	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
432	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gutteridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
coffee	O
at	O
Fresh	B-place
wharf	I-place
,	O
in	O
casks	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
oyl	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
watching	O
for	O
a	O
merchant	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
coffee	O
,	O
rather	O
heavy	O
for	O
sleep	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
watchman	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
his	O
lanthorn	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
casks	O
;	O
going	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
casks	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hole	O
bored	O
in	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
inches	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
in	O
the	O
bulge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coffee	O
was	O
running	O
out	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
apron	O
under	O
to	O
catch	O
it	O
;	O
whose	O
apron	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
coffee	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
cask	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
there	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
to	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
black	O
man	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
coffee	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
pity	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
some	O
for	O
our	O
wives	O
breakfasts	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
black	O
man	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
occasions	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
some	O
coffee	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
black	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
something	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
some	O
coffee	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
cask	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
433	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Currant	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
of	O
wheaten	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
1/2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
;	O
and	O
another	O
ditto	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
434	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
repeating	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
York-Buildings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Berkeley-Square	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
accosted	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
your	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
you	O
home	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Bond-Street	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
thieves	O
and	O
pick-pockets	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
thieves	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
very	O
genteely	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
York-Buildings	B-place
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
pushed	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Jeffery	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
immediately	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
towards	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
who	O
described	O
the	O
watch	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
my	O
blood	O
boiled	O
in	O
my	O
veins	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
handsome	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Brush	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Brush	O
till	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
the	O
number	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Levi	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
Levi	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
some	O
questions	O
about	O
a	O
brother-in-law	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
struck	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bill	O
lying	O
which	O
described	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
lost	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
names	O
were	O
Reeve	O
and	O
Cotton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
before	O
you	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Levi	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
that	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
names	O
were	O
Reeve	O
and	O
Cotton	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1217	O
,	O
last	O
April	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
capped	O
and	O
jewelled	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
eighteen	O
guineas	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
was	O
in	O
white	O
clothes	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
white	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
,	O
genteel	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
dressed	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
bail	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
accused	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
this	O
Levi	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
what	O
motive	O
he	O
could	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
intimate	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
ungrateful	O
in	O
not	O
giving	O
me	O
something	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
can	O
do	O
nothing	O
without	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
find	O
no	O
bill	O
without	O
me	O
:	O
money	O
is	O
now	O
very	O
acceptable	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
declare	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
concerned	O
himself	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
,	O
thin	O
young	O
fellow	O
in	O
white	O
clothes	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
prated	O
like	O
a	O
magpye	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
voice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
said	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
Who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
attorney	O
's	O
clerk	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hubert	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Whitters	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mess	O
.	O
Hussey	O
and	O
Whitters	O
,	O
August	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Templar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Hussey	O
and	O
Whitters	O
,	O
linen-drapers	O
in	O
Gerrard-Street	B-place
.	O
About	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
with	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
from	O
that	O
to	O
many	O
other	O
articles	O
.	O
She	O
saw	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
she	O
applied	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
convey	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
or	O
under	O
her	O
child	O
's	O
clothes	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
bought	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
with	O
other	O
customers	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
privately	O
told	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
seen	O
her	O
take	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
fall	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
walk	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
lawn	O
fall	O
.	O
(	O
Five	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
the	O
lawn	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hubert	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Whitters	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
lawn	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
some	O
caps	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
child	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
:	O
he	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
under	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
petticoats	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
child	O
,	O
in	O
High-Street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
High-Street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
near	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
March	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
March	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
436	O
,	O
437	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
,	I-pers
Picklley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abigail	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
438	O
,	O
439.	O
John	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
Venables	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
wooden	O
blocks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
long	O
rope	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
runner	O
,	O
with	O
proper	O
tackle	O
thereto	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Heyman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
was	O
given	O
in	O
evidence	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
partners	O
in	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
omitted	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
merchant	O
and	O
planter	O
at	O
the	O
Granades	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
,	O
merchant	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
not	O
being	O
laid	O
right	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
440	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Kenzie	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Lyons	I-pers
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Israel	O
Lyons	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
near	O
Ludgate-hill	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
tavern	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
inn	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
in	O
Bridges-Street	B-place
.	O
She	O
conducted	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
What	O
silver	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
extremely	O
tired	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
to	O
sleep	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
wound	O
my	O
watch	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
by	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
woman	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
gold	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
round-house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
very	O
number	O
of	O
pieces	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
tape	O
tied	O
round	O
her	O
body	O
over	O
her	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
purse	O
fastened	O
to	O
it	O
behind	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
money	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
all	O
along	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
money	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
stormed	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	O
;	O
he	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shillings	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bruised	O
me	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
:	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
or	O
intended	O
to	O
use	O
him	O
ill	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
441	O
,	O
442	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
M'Mahone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
443	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Snarbo	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
gold	O
fringe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Parys	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Michael	O
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
request	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
by	O
a	O
jury	O
of	O
half	O
foreigners	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
interpreter	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Parys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hotel	O
in	O
Suffolk-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
all	O
foreign	O
nobility	O
that	O
come	O
over	O
resort	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
in	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
before	O
:	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
spoke	O
bad	O
English	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Speak	O
German	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
cards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
this	O
yours	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
from	O
a	O
merchant	O
who	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
gentleman	O
?	O
He	O
mentioned	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
this	O
gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
his	O
compliments	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
favour	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
or	O
employ	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
great	O
trust	O
till	O
I	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
honour	O
of	O
knowing	O
the	O
gentleman	O
he	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
and	O
behaviour	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
charity	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
very	O
pitiful	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
country	O
seat	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
business	O
that	O
required	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
answer	O
.	O
A	O
note	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Cousmaker	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
exceeding	O
thankful	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
country	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
late	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
come	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
late	O
that	O
night	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
dark	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
come	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
sweat	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
pitched	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
lay	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
cook	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
cook	O
made	O
an	O
objection	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
up	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
shewed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
his	O
box	O
into	O
the	O
cook	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
trunk	O
carried	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
trimmed	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
some	O
account	O
of	O
hereafter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
company	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
lazy	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
away	O
my	O
victuals	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
missing	O
:	O
having	O
lost	O
one	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lose	O
another	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
a	O
through	O
search	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
spoon	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
seen	O
since	O
dinner	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
wife	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
Here	O
he	O
is	O
!	O
Here	O
he	O
is	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
parlour	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
?	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
here	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
?	O
He	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
though	O
his	O
breeches	O
were	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
got	O
him	O
towards	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
run	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
?	O
Pull	O
your	O
breeches	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
seeing	O
some	O
shifts	O
.	O
He	O
replied	O
,	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
cook	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
strip	O
.	O
My	O
cook	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
wits	O
to	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
rogue	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nine	O
shirts	O
on	O
,	O
besides	O
several	O
shifts	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
He	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
throw	O
out	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
from	O
his	O
pockets	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
by	O
,	O
Take	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
proper	O
inventory	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
long	O
list	O
of	O
rich	O
things	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
look	O
upon	O
myself	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
villain	O
as	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
locked	O
in	O
a	O
bureau	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
D'Eon	O
's	O
trunk	O
broke	O
.	O
The	O
silver	O
hilt	O
of	O
the	O
sword	O
I	O
found	O
broke	O
from	O
the	O
blade	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
hook	O
of	O
the	O
scabbard	O
.	O
The	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
sword	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
D'Eon	O
's	O
secretary	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
my	O
store	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
crimson	O
silk	O
damask	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
gold	O
fringe	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
breeches	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
crammed	O
them	O
so	O
full	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
four	O
witnesses	O
in	O
court	O
that	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
me	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
thought	O
it	O
needless	O
to	O
examine	O
any	O
other	O
witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
shirt	O
to	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
for	O
turning	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
that	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
what	O
they	O
called	O
a	O
foreigner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
shifts	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
fringe	O
was	O
till	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
his	O
sister	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
444	O
,	O
445	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stackhouse	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Litchfield	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sampson	B-pers
Jessop	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sampson	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Sampson	B-pers
Jessop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hoxton	O
Square	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Pinner	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Harrow-road	B-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Padington	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
(	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
moonlight	O
night	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Litchfield	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
walked	O
about	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
from	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
He	O
replied	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
pistol	O
.	O
Then	O
Stackhouse	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
my	O
horse	O
:	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
horse	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
was	O
behind	O
came	O
and	O
jumped	O
upon	O
the	O
shafts	O
of	O
my	O
carriage	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
hands	O
down	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
reins	O
and	O
whip	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
hold	O
your	O
hands	O
down	O
for	O
?	O
Hold	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
watch	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Litchfield	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
pulling	O
off	O
my	O
gloves	O
.	O
Stackhouse	O
said	O
,	O
Blast	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
quick	O
,	O
clap	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
patience	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
they	O
clapped	O
their	O
hands	O
on	O
the	O
cut-side	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
jumped	O
from	O
my	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
towards	O
Harrow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
intelligence	O
to	O
all	O
I	O
met	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Foundling	O
Hospital	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
going	O
upon	O
the	O
Harrow	O
road	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
three	O
men	O
had	O
just	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
Sir	O
John	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
particular	O
number	O
on	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
different	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
particularly	O
the	O
dress	O
and	O
persons	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
such	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
persons	O
and	O
cloathing	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Stackhouse	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
ten	O
days	O
.	O
After	O
Litchfield	O
and	O
Temple	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
card	O
and	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
shewed	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
attended	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
admitted	O
Temple	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
on	O
my	O
carriage	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
watch	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
when	O
Stackhouse	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cotrell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
where	O
I	O
generally	O
do	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
looked	O
at	O
if	O
wanted	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stackhouse	I-pers
came	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
private	O
boxes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
private	O
boxes	O
?	O
Cotrell	O
.	O
These	O
boxes	O
are	O
private	O
places	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
ladies	O
who	O
do	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
when	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Cotrell	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
our	O
lane	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
lives	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
examine	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
in	O
came	O
Temple	O
and	O
Litchfield	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
breeches	O
that	O
would	O
suit	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sure	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
then	O
to	O
loiter	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Stackhouse	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
a	O
ticket	O
.	O
He	O
wrote	O
upon	O
it	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Bow-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ticket	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Bow-Street	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
The	O
moment	O
he	O
wrote	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
getting	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
watch	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
it	O
answered	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
milkman	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
slopman	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
first	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
then	O
Titchfield-street	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
mentioned	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
highway	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
near	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
As	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Litchfield	O
and	O
Temple	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
either	O
of	O
those	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
denied	O
knowing	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
myself	O
;	O
Litchfield	O
and	O
Temple	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
my	O
bringing	O
Stackhouse	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Tothill-field	O
bridewell	O
for	O
farther	O
examination	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
thigh	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
near	O
Vauxhall	O
.	O
Temple	O
was	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
court	O
thought	O
proper	O
not	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
Stackhouse	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
Temple	O
.	O
Litchfield	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
Litchfield	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Litchfield	O
near	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
milkman	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cow-keeper	O
and	O
farmer	O
at	O
Hyde-park	O
Corner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bears	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Hyde-park	O
Corner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
better	O
than	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
446	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
ruffle	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Duff	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
duffil	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Hannah	B-pers
Man	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
One	B-place
Tun	I-place
in	I-place
little	I-place
Poultney-street	I-place
,	I-place
Knave	I-place
's	I-place
Acre	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
red	O
cardinal	O
and	O
linen	O
shirt	O
in	O
July	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
red	O
cardinal	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
and	O
ask	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
pledge	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
As	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
your	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
your	O
other	O
things	O
are	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
get	O
in	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
the	O
key	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
and	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
red	O
cardinal	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
two	O
shillings	O
upon	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
447	O
,	O
448	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Paul	B-pers
Caustin	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Caustin	I-pers
,	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
dwelling	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
+	O
Paul	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
William	O
acquitted	O
.	O
449	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
450	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Repton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Repton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waggoner	O
.	O
My	O
waggon	O
goes	O
from	O
Shrewsbury	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
lighted	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
gateway	O
of	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Faulcon	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
's	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
high	O
loaded	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
a	O
wicker	O
basket	O
(	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
:	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Eastlander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bird	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Faulcon	O
yard	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
wicker	O
basket	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
desiring	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
basket	O
go	O
away	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
the	O
direction	O
off	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
cloth	O
over	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
leather	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
.	O
The	O
basket	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
in	O
Shropshire	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
M.	O
Carver	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
not	O
being	O
proper	O
evidence	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Repton	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
?	O
Repton	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
10	O
d.	O
or	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
waggoner	O
delivered	O
only	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
fowls	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
wicker-basket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
451	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gibons	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Otridge	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Simon	B-pers
Otridge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
towards	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
before	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
turned	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
immediately	O
and	O
brushed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shoulder	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
why	O
I	O
jostled	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
oath	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whose	O
hand	O
.	O
My	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
turn	O
short	O
round	O
upon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
