TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	O
TURNER	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Place	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
and	O
++	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Wintle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Luntley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chawner	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
Silvanous	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
Silver	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Braithweight	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gouland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
De	I-pers
Rippe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holgate	I-pers
.	O
*	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Holgate	O
.	O
79	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Purney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
December	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
preceding	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Cheapside	O
into	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
le	I-place
Grand	I-place
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
disturb	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
discovered	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
apprehended	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
associate	O
,	O
saying	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
Here	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
or	O
Take	O
it	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
which	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
seeing	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
,	O
refused	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
effrontery	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
seized	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
80	O
,	O
81	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
inland	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
subscribed	O
J.	O
Adams	O
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
18	O
l.	O
directed	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Baldero	O
and	O
Co.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
December	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Thornley	O
's	O
in	O
Russell-Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
bookcase	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
principal	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
papers	O
,	O
quite	O
empty	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
cash	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
two	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
coin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
servant	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
double	O
house	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
Clark	O
in	O
thro	O
'	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
Clark	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
in	O
Old-Bedlam	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
two	O
messengers	O
to	O
Harwich	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Gravesend	O
tilt-boats	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Wilson	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
intimate	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Swanston	O
and	O
my	O
son	O
to	O
Dover	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
they	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
me	O
four	O
of	O
my	O
bills	O
.	O
That	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
is	O
laid	O
in	O
another	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
in	O
question	O
produced	O
and	O
road	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
purport	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
conversed	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Swanston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smallwood	O
's	O
son	O
to	O
Dover	O
.	O
One	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
not	O
going	O
so	O
fast	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
horseback	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
They	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
proposed	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
Calais	O
,	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
bill	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smallwood	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
London	O
Inn	O
at	O
Dover	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
desired	O
the	O
waiter	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
box	O
to	O
put	O
their	O
clothes	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Deal	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
an	O
India	O
ship	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Smallwood	O
's	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
such	O
persons	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
assist	O
them	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
horse	O
to	O
be	O
saddled	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Deal	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Folkstone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
mayor	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
was	O
suspected	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
them	O
.	O
Clark	O
delivered	O
the	O
bills	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
their	O
masters	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
very	O
little	O
answer	O
;	O
one	O
delivered	O
up	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
29	O
l.	O
in	O
cash	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
Dover	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Swanston	O
was	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoners	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smallwood	O
.	O
82	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
making	O
and	O
forging	O
a	O
certain	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
subscribed	O
thereto	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
Halford	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
12th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
1768	O
.	O
Pay	O
``	O
to	O
Mr.	O
J	O
.	O
Hall	O
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
18	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
John	O
``	O
Smith	O
.	O
''	O
And	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
John	B-pers
Barbe	I-pers
,	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Barbe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
working-silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bargained	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
silver	O
sauce-boats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
laddle	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
deliver	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
clean	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Soho-Square	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
bill	O
against	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
In	O
what	O
name	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
Fuller	O
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
18	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Vaughn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
Halford	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
draft	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Barbe	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
he	O
presented	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
payment	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forgery	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
in	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
some	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
hand-writings	O
of	O
two	O
persons	O
,	O
named	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
only	O
two	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
that	O
keep	O
cash	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
material	O
difference	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
refused	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barbe	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Halford	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
partners	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
know	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Halford	O
brought	O
the	O
bill	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
bill	O
I	O
received	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
balance	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
step	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
note	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
balance	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
6	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
the	O
change	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
two	O
John	B-pers
Smiths	I-pers
write	O
,	O
who	O
keep	O
cash	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
:	O
one	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
junior	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
senior	O
;	O
one	O
lives	O
in	O
Bucklersbury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
St.	O
Helen	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
writing	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
cheque	O
on	O
the	O
bill	O
the	O
cheque	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
our	O
customers	O
lost	O
several	O
blank	O
cheques	O
belonging	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
for	O
his	O
change	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
call	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
To	O
Mess	O
.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
Halford	O
,	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1768	O
.	O
Pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
J	O
.	O
Hall	O
,	O
bearer	O
,	O
18	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
draft	O
for	O
goods	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
not	O
trying	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
now	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
informed	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
intelligence	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
wrote	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
in	O
Gloucester	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
from	O
thence	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
lived	O
in	O
Hand-Court	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
in	O
lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
owed	O
me	O
29	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
conveniently	O
pay	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
navy	O
all	O
the	O
last	O
war	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
twenty-three	O
years	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
week	O
to	O
support	O
myself	O
,	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
money	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
certain	O
day	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
can	O
satisfy	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
a	O
banker	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
banker	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Fuller	O
and	O
Halford	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
bills	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
for	O
18	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
persons	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
named	O
Abraham	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
Smith	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
a	O
different	O
banker	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
on	O
Fuller	O
and	O
Son	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
one	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barbe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tho	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
having	O
been	O
purser	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
articles	O
for	O
sea	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
debt	O
was	O
contracted	O
,	O
at	O
stone-buckles	O
that	O
Smith	O
had	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Quaker	O
's	O
Buildings	O
,	O
near	O
Smithfield	O
Bars	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
absent	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
near	O
Porter	O
's	O
Block	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
she	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
frequently	O
in	O
September	O
and	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
may	O
you	O
have	O
breakfasted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
times	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
before	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
draft	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
live	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Quaker	O
's	O
Buildings	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
lives	O
now	O
by	O
Porter	O
's	O
Block	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
him	O
this	O
draft	O
for	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
demand	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
note	O
given	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
two	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
notes	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
young	O
Smith	O
give	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
notes	O
,	O
all	O
payable	O
to	O
Jonathan	O
Hall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
wrote	O
Jonathan	O
,	O
or	O
J	O
.	O
Hall	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
which	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
frequently	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
notes	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
of	O
four	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
two	O
of	O
18	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
of	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
10	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
or	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Smith	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Smith	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
kept	O
cash	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
this	O
note	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
(	O
he	O
takes	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
Smith	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
he	O
write	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
breakfast-time	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
my	O
brother	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
note	O
given	O
single	O
,	O
or	O
another	O
given	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
given	O
single	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
note	O
given	O
before	O
this	O
(	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
)	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
they	O
were	O
chequed	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
on	O
one	O
banker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
dealings	O
between	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
pretty	O
much	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
hard-ware	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
About	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Hall	O
say	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
Shall	O
we	O
settle	O
?	O
They	O
got	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
up	O
some	O
account	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
settle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
draft	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
notes	O
were	O
given	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Shall	O
we	O
settle	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
is	O
Smith	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
twenty-five	O
,	O
or	O
twenty-six	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
size	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
About	O
my	O
size	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
middling	O
size	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
black	O
,	O
or	O
fair	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
last	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
ago	O
:	O
since	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
subpoened	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
coming	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
sum	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Smith-give	O
Hall	O
bills	O
for	O
different	O
sums	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
different	O
bankers	O
;	O
some	O
for	O
twelve	O
guineas	O
,	O
some	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
eighteen	O
.	O
One	O
time	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
bills	O
for	O
eighteen	O
guineas	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
connections	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
one	O
another	O
bills	O
.	O
Smith	O
has	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
bill	O
that	O
Hall	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Hall	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
such	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
Smith	O
write	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Hall	O
write	O
also	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
bill	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
The	O
body	O
of	O
this	O
draft	O
is	O
Hall	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
signing	O
is	O
Smith	O
's	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
Smith	O
wrote	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
speaking	O
to	O
the	O
name	O
Smith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
wrote	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bareau	I-pers
.	O
That	O
is	O
Hall	O
's	O
writing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
another	O
Forgery	O
.	O
83	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
carcase	O
of	O
a	O
dead	O
ewe	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
or	O
persons	O
,	O
unknown	O
.	O
December	O
23	O
.	O
||	O
Tho	B-pers
Milley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
watchman	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
venison	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
come	O
this	O
way	O
?	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
ewe	O
sheep	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
skin	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
guts	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fat	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
wollen	O
rag	O
within	O
the	O
belly	O
of	O
the	O
sheep	O
.	O
The	O
belly	O
was	O
quite	O
warm	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
this	O
direction	O
tied	O
on	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
,	O
Newberry	O
,	O
Barkshire	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Newbury	O
Stage	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
steel	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Canarvan	O
's	O
servants	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
Knightsbridge	O
.	O
We	O
advertised	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
brand	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
skin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
Milley	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
meat	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Milley	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
father	O
at	O
Southgate	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Canarvan	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Southgate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
basket	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
venison	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
a	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
without	O
going	O
round	O
.	O
Coming	O
over	O
Finchly	O
Common	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
way	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
84	O
,	O
85	O
,	O
86	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Witchcraft	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Dickes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Landaway	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
thirty-two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
but	O
Joseph	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
87	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
David	I-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
beaver	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Rodbard	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
December	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Rodbard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Blackfryers	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bureau	O
,	O
to	O
lend	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Wyld	I-pers
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
locking	O
the	O
bureau	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
doors	O
bang	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
whether	O
somebody	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
reached	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
back-way	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
would	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
came-up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
hat	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
one	O
,	O
lined	O
with	O
white	O
silk	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
well	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
crime	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
.	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
David	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Mills	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
When	O
in	O
Black-fryars	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
running	O
across	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
mine	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stop	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
88	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
five	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
9	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fawcett	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
4	O
:	O
||	O
Eliz	B-pers
Fawcett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Fawcett	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
(	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	B-place
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
very	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
reaching	O
down	O
a	O
neck	O
of	O
mutton	O
.	O
I	O
cast	O
my	O
eye	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
apron	O
was	O
removed	O
from	O
my	O
pocket-apron	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
nothing	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
meat	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Isaac	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
name	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Mentioning	O
the	O
pieces	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
still	O
held	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
while	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
concealed	O
betwixt	O
his	O
legs	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Toone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
I	O
assisted	O
Mrs.	O
Fawcett	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
charged	O
,	O
denyed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
search	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
from	O
betwixt	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
May	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
purse	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
against	O
Mrs.	O
Fawcett	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
stooped	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
between	O
my	O
legs	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
89	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
December	O
17	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
90	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counteirfeting	O
an	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
Halford	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
October	O
``	O
2	O
l	O
,	O
1768	O
.	O
Pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
or	O
``	O
bearer	O
,	O
15	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
G	O
.	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
''	O
And	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
October	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
near	O
Aldgate	B-place
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
buy	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
dozen	O
of	O
house	O
,	O
of	O
23	O
or	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
Berry	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
used	O
him	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
customer	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
out	O
five	O
dozen	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
name	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Robinson	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
presented	O
a	O
draft	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
draft	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hesitating	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
reputable	O
country	O
shop-keeper	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
inclinable	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
precaution	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
immediately	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
draft	O
upon	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
with	O
the	O
5	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
made	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
bill	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
's	O
house	O
being	O
but	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
's	O
four	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Skinner	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
withdraw	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
do	O
his	O
business	O
now	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
my	O
draft	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Gompy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
was	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
about	O
selling	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
before	O
an	O
Alderman	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
was	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
there	O
acknowledged	O
another	O
fraud	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Sheffield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Gompy	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
Gompy	O
taken	O
.	O
John	O
Vaughn	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Halford	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
lately	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
from	O
Sheffield	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
draft	O
of	O
one	O
Gompy	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
could	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
town	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Nuns	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
nights	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
laid	O
at	O
the	O
Fleece	O
Goodman's-fields	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
consistent	O
in	O
the	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
G.	O
Humphrys	O
keep	O
cash	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Vaughn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
draft	O
is	O
a	O
blank	O
cheque	O
of	O
ours	O
that	O
has	O
seen	O
filled	O
up	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
to	O
the	O
purport	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
drafts	O
of	O
Gompy	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
off	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
any	O
bad	O
design	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Saunders	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
Robinson	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Kennet	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Matthew	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Alderman	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
confused	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Geter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prison	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
after	O
Gompy	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Nuns	O
,	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
turnkeys	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
told	O
we	O
were	O
too	O
late	O
by	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
,	O
Gompy	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Golden-Fleece	O
,	O
in	O
Goodman	O
's	O
Fields	O
;	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
Skinner	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
Gompy	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Waddington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Nuns	O
,	O
White-Chapel	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
sevennight	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Brentwood-Fair	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Skinner	O
rode	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
on	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
staid	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
or	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
this	O
horse	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
thought	O
Skinner	O
was	O
servant	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
lusty	O
man	O
,	O
two	O
Jews	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
Skinner	O
to	O
Burntwood-Fair	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Jew	O
was	O
named	O
Gompy	O
Humphrys	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
Jew	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
and	O
Skinner	O
's	O
victuals	O
and	O
drink	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
and	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
Skinner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
what	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
scissars-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Ironmonger-Row	O
,	O
Old-Street	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
from	O
Sheffield	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
scissars	O
grinder	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
at	O
Sheffield	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
come	O
up	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Sheffield	O
not	O
seven	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
about	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
:	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
learn	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Sheffield	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
certain	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
this	O
Gompy	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Gloucester	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eglinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Abdy	I-pers
's	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
in	O
Oat-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Goldsmiths-Hall	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
Sheffield	O
nine	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
last	O
Easter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
case-maker	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
write	O
or	O
read	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Throgmorton-Street	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
sixteen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
years	O
at	O
Sheffield	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
laborious	O
,	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
commonly	O
understood	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
,	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
a	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
draft	O
,	O
drawn	O
on	O
Mess	O
.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
Halford	O
,	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
signed	O
G.	O
Humphrys	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
October	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
near	O
Cripple-gate	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
green	O
tea	O
.	O
He	O
agreed	O
for	O
twenty-four	O
pounds	O
,	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
marked	O
Matthew	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Doncaster	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
two	O
Necks	O
,	O
in	O
Lad-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
again	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
to	O
7	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
draft	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
satisfied	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
remainder	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
8	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
draft	O
was	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
note	O
before	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
kept	O
cash-there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
This	O
draft	O
was	O
presented	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
near	O
Criplegate	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
kept	O
cash	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
``	O
To	O
Mess	O
.	O
Fuller	O
,	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
Halford	O
,	O
bankers	O
,	O
``	O
&	O
c.	O
Oct.	O
19	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
``	O
Brown	O
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
15	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
``	O
G	O
.	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
''	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Kennet	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
received	O
one	O
draft	O
of	O
Gompy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
named	O
Bonner	O
,	O
snuff-makers	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
pounds	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
for	O
paying	O
the	O
bill	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
very	O
much	O
desired	O
Gompy	O
might	O
be	O
inquired	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Geter	I-pers
and	O
George	O
Washington	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
trial	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
91	O
,	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hinchley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	B-place
publick-house	I-place
in	I-place
Church-street	I-place
,	I-place
Edmonton	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
key	O
by	O
some	O
accident	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
Hinchley	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
)	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
about	O
two	O
pounds	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
accused	O
the	O
girl	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
and	O
mentioned	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
had	O
inticed	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
inticed	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
care	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
,	O
she	O
received	O
three	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
ever	O
seeing	O
any	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Rowin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
girl	O
confess	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
drawers	O
,	O
two	O
large	O
pieces	O
and	O
two	O
small	O
ones	O
of	O
gold	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
inticed	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
continued	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
several	O
quarrels	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
you	O
have	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
Mother	O
White	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
?	O
Upon	O
their	O
examination	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
always	O
declared	O
her	O
innocence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
tipple	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Witaker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
brought	O
three	O
guineas	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
put	O
three	O
guineas	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
put	O
three	O
guineas	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Hinchley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
bid	O
me	O
rob	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
White	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hinchley	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Walburn	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Matthew	B-pers
Walburn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	B-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
publick-house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Great	I-place
Marlborough-Street	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
mist	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
changed	O
that	O
piece	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
clothes	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Spinage	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
piece	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
honestly	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
his	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
fifteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
94	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Bartram	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Free	I-pers
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Free	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Vine-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
The	O
girl	O
lived	O
facing	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
use	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
drink	O
.	O
Betwixt	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
change	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
bureau	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
what	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
then	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
mix	O
three	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
upwards	O
of	O
four	O
pounds	O
missing	O
from	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
justly	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
four	O
pounds	O
gone	O
.	O
Whoever	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
stair-foot-door	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
six	O
feet	O
ten	O
inches	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
wood	O
away	O
over	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
wrenched	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
sevennight	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Marybone-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
confederate	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
imagining	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
without	O
somebody	O
lifting	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
This	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
under	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
the	O
shutter	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
upon	O
that	O
first	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Glasshouse-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Marybone-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
table-spoon	O
and	O
strainer	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
wanted	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dane	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
mother	O
lived	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
,	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
chamber-milliner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
her	O
mother	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crest	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
my	O
sending	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
soon	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
went	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
a	O
relation	O
,	O
that	O
lived	O
at	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
man	O
for	O
her	O
mistress	O
when	O
the	O
mistress	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
surprized	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
stopt	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
;	O
she	O
accused	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
way	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
again	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
released	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
All	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
ingenuous	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
you	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
charge	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
you	O
here	O
.	O
It	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
option	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
will	O
charge	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
neither	O
father	O
nor	O
mother	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
seventeen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
95	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
containing	O
seven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
September	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
,	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
by	O
Charing-cross	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
pieces	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
silk	O
ones	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
two	O
pieces	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
less	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
handkerchifs	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
but	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
that	O
price	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Buckingham-court	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
delivering	O
it	O
:	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
round	O
us	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
twenty	O
pence	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Cozins	I-pers
,	O
Lucy	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Marsden	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
96	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Green-park	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Robert	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
December	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
Debenture-office	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Green-park	O
,	O
towards	O
Lord	O
Bath	O
's	O
gate	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bason	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
came	O
past	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
stick	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
back	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
much	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
in	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
mirey	O
clay	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
gravel	O
walk	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
attacked	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
said	O
:	O
they	O
pulled	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
made	O
off	O
cross	O
the	O
field	O
towards	O
the	O
Grove	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
leave	O
me	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
they	O
threw	O
me	O
my	O
hat	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
washed	O
myself	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
bloody	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
idea	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
behind	O
me	O
I	O
hardly	O
saw	O
;	O
he	O
that	O
attacked	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
surtout-coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twenty	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Popard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
corporal	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
inlisted	O
but	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
advance	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
raise	O
more	O
upon	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
lent	O
him	O
only	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
them	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hallburton	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
carrying	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
bills	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
Clay	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
number	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
orders	O
to	O
attend	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
with	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Rees	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
soldier	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
?	O
Rees	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Green-park	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
man	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
Park	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
only	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
eight	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
directly	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
this	O
story	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
battalion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
quartered	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
did	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
soldiers	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Rees	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
corporals	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
on	O
this	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
robbery	O
,	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
four	O
or	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
Corporal	O
Hudson	O
used	O
to	O
lend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
admitted	O
as	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
swore	O
falsely	O
against	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haliburton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
countryman	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
Long-field	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
information	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
Drew	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
one	O
Burrow	O
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
:	O
accordingly	O
Burrow	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
this	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
another	O
man	O
's	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Devonshire	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
belong	O
to	O
Col.	O
Gore	B-pers
's	O
company	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
97	O
,	O
98	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
box-iron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
++	O
Isaac	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ironmonger-Row	B-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
yesterday	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
front	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
broke	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
can	O
give	O
the	O
best	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
hard	O
at	O
work	O
a	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
got	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
sound	O
sleep	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
)	O
and	O
my	O
line	O
striped	O
of	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
:	O
I	O
mist	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
box-iron	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
rooms	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
we	O
lie	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
your	O
door	O
and	O
window	O
fastened	O
?	O
I.	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
fork	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
door	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wire-drawer	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pemberton	O
's	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
boys	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
Wilkes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
stood	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Pemberton	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
distance	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
lad	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
boys	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
believe	O
slipt	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
three	O
boys	O
all	O
together	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
join	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
Wilkes	O
had	O
this	O
green	O
apron	O
on	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
linen	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
dragged	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
White	O
's	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
boys	O
tried	O
to	O
kick	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
Cooper	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
Wilkes	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
shirts	O
,	O
shifts	O
,	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lefeavor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
called	O
watch	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Cooper	O
making	O
off	O
,	O
in	O
White	O
's	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
with	O
Cooper	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
box-iron	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
White's-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
?	O
Lefeavor	O
.	O
Wilkes	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
Adams	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
that	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
box-iron	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
found	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
)	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
Ben	O
,	O
that	O
sells	O
trotters	O
and	O
neats-feet	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Wilkes	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
together	O
.	O
Wilkes	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
to	O
case	O
himself	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
Wilkes	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Wilkes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
jump	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Adams	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
after	O
the	O
boy	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
followed	O
him	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
Wilkes	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
then	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
then	O
running	O
down	O
Whitecross-Street	O
.	O
They	O
ran	O
down	O
very	O
near	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
before	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
slip	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Cooper	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
you	O
saw	O
first	O
?	O
Or	O
was	O
it	O
him	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
whoever	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
were	O
looking	O
one	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
99	O
,	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Walter	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Memory	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
bed-quilts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
mahogany	O
fire-screen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
)	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
a	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
came	O
with	O
Terrin	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
Joseph	O
Terrin	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
conveyed	O
my	O
things	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
carried	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Terrin	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Watt	O
Watkins	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Terrin	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
there	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Watkins	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
quilts	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
screen	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
101	O
,	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Tirpinder	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
another	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stirrop-irons	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
girths	O
and	O
a	O
saddle-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
||	O
Peter	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
the	O
election	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
saddles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
plated	O
stirrops	O
,	O
and	O
girths	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
saddle-cloth	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
had	O
stirrops	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
girth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
stable	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
At	O
the	B-place
Castle	I-place
at	I-place
Brentford	I-place
.	O
The	O
saddles	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sadler	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
saddle	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Parker	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
full	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mantle	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
countryman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
hay	O
cart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Christmas-eve	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Demain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sadler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
saddle	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
A	O
Guinea	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
busy	O
now	O
,	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
have	O
looked	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
saddle	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Parker	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
saddle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
gentleman	O
thinks	O
we	O
have	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
come	O
together	O
?	O
Demain	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
.	O
Mantle	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
we	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
can	O
produce	O
the	O
owner	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
us	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
Sent	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
us	O
?	O
Demain	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Tirpinder	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
that	O
?	O
Demain	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
.	O
Mantle	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Going	O
through	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
the	O
saddle	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
saddle	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
stable	O
.	O
Tirpinder	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mantle	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
sadler	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
saddle	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mantle	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Tirpinder	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
surtout	O
Bath	O
beaver	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dignam	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dignam	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Bath	O
beaver	O
coats	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fore	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Terrin	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Dignam	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Dignam	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
.	O
Terrin	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ince	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Ince	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
surtout	O
Bath	O
beaver	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Ince	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russell	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Terrin	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Running	O
Horse	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
Richard	O
Row	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
coat	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Boot	O
,	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
or	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
him	O
not	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
two	O
coats	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
my	O
coat	O
on	O
again	O
:	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
coat	O
too	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
evidence	O
Terrin	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Ince	O
.	O
Terrin	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
in	O
taking	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
taking	O
Dignam	O
's	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Terrin	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
(	O
Terrin	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Ward	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Terrin	O
.	O
Ward	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
to	O
Dignam	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
shoved	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
back	O
the	O
blind	O
,	O
and	O
Ward	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
coats	O
:	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ince	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
coats	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
coat	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
fell	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
clothes	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Holborn	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
dog	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Pidgeon	O
's	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
indict	O
Tiney	O
Roach	O
,	O
a	O
prisoner	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
all	O
your	O
robberies	O
.	O
Terrin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
this	O
bill	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Richard	O
Row	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
Terrin	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Terrin	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
coats	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ince	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Boot	O
,	O
in	O
Cross-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stayed	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
running	O
.	O
Assistance	O
came	O
up	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Row	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Boot	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
clothes	O
on	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
wear	O
Mr.	O
Ince	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round-house	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
,	O
Terrin	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
coat	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Fletcher	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
coats	O
,	O
said	O
this	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
your	O
property	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
wear	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
fit	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
it	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
it	O
is	O
advertised	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
stand	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
106	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
ten	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Chigwell	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
came	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
coach	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
rode	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
coach-box	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
box	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
ten	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
white	O
coloured	O
one	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
.	O
My	O
box	O
and	O
bundle	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
boot	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
wet	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
stayed	O
at	O
the	O
inn	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
so	O
did	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
brought	O
my	O
things	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
.	O
The	O
coach	O
brought	O
a	O
hamper	O
of	O
fowls	O
,	O
as	O
Wise	O
told	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
hamper	O
shipped	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
my	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
assistance	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
hamper	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
bundle	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Wise	O
would	O
carry	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
Inn	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
Groves	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
after	O
my	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
A	O
tallow-chandler	O
from	O
Stratford	O
came	O
up	O
accidentally	O
.	O
Wise	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hill	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
tallow-chandler	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
hot	O
.	O
Wise	O
had	O
my	O
box	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
place	O
.	O
Wise	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
or	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
place	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
accept	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
's	O
carrying	O
my	O
box	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
London	O
Bridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
place	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
was	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
Groves	O
took	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
entirely	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
that	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
Well-close-square	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
kept	O
walking	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
are	O
we	O
going	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
?	O
His	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
Groves	O
walked	O
behind	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
drest	O
in	O
a	O
livery	O
.	O
Wise	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
footman	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Wise	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
cross	O
my	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
we	O
were	O
wrong	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Groves	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
towards	O
London-bridge	O
?	O
Groves	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
lived	O
somewhere	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
staid	O
behind	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Groves	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
staid	O
behind	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
my	O
box	O
to	O
Wise	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
whisper	O
'd	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
somewhat	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
Wise	O
gave	O
Groves	O
my	O
box	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
Groves	O
kept	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
cross	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
Wise	O
walked	O
a	O
great	O
pace	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
set	O
to	O
running	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
cross	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
were	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
by	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bread-street	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
Wise	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Bread-Street	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
heard	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
A	O
footman	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
account	O
I	O
gave	O
;	O
he	O
stept	O
forwards	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Groves	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
strong	O
sits	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
word	O
for	O
word	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
made	O
an	O
appointment	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
Wise	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
London	O
last	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
four	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
play	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
fowls	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Dunn	O
's	O
wharf	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
hamper	O
.	O
The	O
porter	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
them	O
in	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Wise	O
hired	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
porter	O
went	O
before	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Dunn	O
's	O
wharf	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
fowls	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
drink	O
plentifully	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
by	O
agreement	O
,	O
somewhere	O
by	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
where	O
else	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
any	O
place	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
hear	O
Groves	O
and	O
he	O
talk	O
about	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
tallow-chandler	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
little	O
quarrel	O
between	O
Wise	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
coming	O
along	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
person	O
is	O
my	O
witness	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
dispute	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
Wise	O
's	O
coat	O
;	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
catched	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr	O
.	O
Wise	O
make	O
str	O
ong	O
love	O
to	O
you	O
coming	O
up	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
propose	O
to	O
make	O
love	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refused	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
walk	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
arm	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
dragged	O
me	O
along	O
,	O
when	O
Groves	O
was	O
behind	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Groves	O
?	O
M.	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
we	O
seemed	O
to	O
meet	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
opposite	O
Bow-church	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Wise	O
,	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
almost	O
backwards	O
;	O
his	O
elbow	O
came	O
against	O
my	O
stomach	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
elderly	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
shoved	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
ask	O
him	O
his	O
reason	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bread-Street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
cuff	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
livery	O
,	O
laced	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
for	O
running	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
scoundrels	O
and	O
rascals	O
he	O
could	O
think	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
terrible	O
manner	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
impudent	O
fellow	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
send	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Computer	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
You	O
!	O
I	O
can	O
buy	O
20	O
such	O
scoundrels	O
as	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Armiger	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
came	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
catched	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
box	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
run	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Armiger	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
,	O
in	O
Bread-Street	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
He	O
abused	O
every	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
