TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Evre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Pyner	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Faulkland	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shrubb	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hackney	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Spratling	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bodley	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Churchman	I-pers
,	O
Dormer	B-pers
Heiford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Daves	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Turkey	O
oil-stone	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
one	O
other	O
Turkey	O
oil-stone	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
carpenter	O
's	O
plough	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
new	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
a	O
builder	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
day	O
week	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
building	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Turkey	O
stones	O
and	O
the	O
plough	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
last	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Ruins	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
would	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
constable	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
saw	O
and	O
oil-stone	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
for	O
liquor	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
tools	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
their	O
respective	O
owners	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
of	O
his	O
stealing	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
building	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
October	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
David	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hackney-Road	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
.	O
My	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
and	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
,	O
when	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
came	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
stole	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Geary	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Sun-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Long-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Moor-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
Harris	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
frock	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
that	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Sun-Street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
gown	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
down	O
Hackney-Road	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
frock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
dark	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
people	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
fields	O
near	O
Islington-Road	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
barn	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
into	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
gown	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Geary	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
John	B-pers
Pullin	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
of	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
fun	O
.	O
As	O
Mrs.	O
Geary	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
some	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
picked	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
confessed	O
to	O
him	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
speaks	O
very	O
wrong	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Lady	B-pers
Albany	I-pers
,	I-pers
Viscountess	I-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
table-clock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
ten	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
thirteen	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
lady	O
;	O
a	O
woollen	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hobourn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Hobourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Lady	O
Middleton	O
,	O
in	O
Albemarle-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
made	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bells	O
put	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
windows	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
.	O
My	O
lady	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
so	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
lady	O
hires	O
by	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
is	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
watch	O
went	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
imagining	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
making	O
fires	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
air	O
the	O
rooms	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
lady	O
was	O
expected	O
home	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
bells	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
poker	O
fall	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
noise	O
of	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
which	O
shook	O
the	O
bed	O
I	O
lay	O
upon	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
iron	O
chest	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
water	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
removed	O
there	O
by	O
one	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
rather	O
before	O
me	O
(	O
this	O
noise	O
continued	O
till	O
almost	O
seven	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
fires	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
robbed	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
opened	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
below	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
bells	O
all	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
(	O
the	O
kitchen	O
is	O
below-stairs	O
)	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
that	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
press	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
strewed	O
about	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
was	O
broke	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
rather	O
under	O
the	O
area	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
inside	O
shutter	O
:	O
the	O
screws	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarry	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
.	O
The	O
screws	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
outside	O
shutter	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bar	O
goes	O
down	O
across	O
the	O
inside	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
thing	O
that	O
turns	O
round	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
must	O
pull	O
their	O
clothes	O
off	O
to	O
put	O
their	O
hand	O
in	O
to	O
turn	O
that	O
thing	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
table	O
linen	O
and	O
fine	O
sheets	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
own	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
one	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
My	O
buckles	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
there	O
;	O
where	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
table-clock	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
tea	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
bent	O
up	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
iron	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
it	O
contained	O
only	O
writings	O
,	O
they	O
opened	O
it	O
no	O
further	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
cleaned	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
clock	O
described	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
hand-bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
among	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
anything	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
following	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Milliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Lady	O
Middleton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
(	O
Thirteen	O
napkin	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
such	O
napkins	O
of	O
my	O
lady	O
's	O
missing	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
These	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
marks	O
,	O
a	O
coronet	O
with	O
seven	O
balls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
letter	O
M	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
date	O
underneath	O
when	O
made	O
.	O
These	O
have	O
1752	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Such	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
are	O
missing	O
.	O
These	O
I	O
think	O
must	O
be	O
my	O
lady	O
's	O
.	O
Hobourn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
lady	O
's	O
linen	O
was	O
marked	O
as	O
these	O
are	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
employed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
repeated	O
informations	O
concerning	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
Lady	O
Middleton	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
hearing	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
we	O
acquainted	O
Sir	O
John	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
that	O
comes	O
out	O
into	O
Bedfordbury	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
jeweller	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
ordered	O
Wright	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
watch	O
both	O
ends	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Lady	O
Middleton	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Wright	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
about	O
one	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
people	O
went	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
court	O
,	O
all	O
people	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
We	O
waited	O
till	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
We	O
set	O
two	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
Cave	O
lived	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
like	O
a	O
porter	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
We	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
thirteen	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
:	O
searching	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
a	O
dark	O
lantern	O
,	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
matches	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
napkins	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
when	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
watching	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
napkins	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
dark	O
lantern	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
Jews	O
frequent	O
the	O
passage	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
bargain	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
cornelians	O
to	O
work	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
offering	O
these	O
napkins	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
the	O
napkins	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
dozen	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
ten	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
clouts	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dawson	O
's	O
Alley	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Youd	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
therese	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Youd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hemmings	B-place
's	I-place
Row	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
My	O
family	O
was	O
all	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
nine	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
fasten	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
fastened	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
that	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
bolt	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
cracked	O
across	O
,	O
and	O
burst	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
)	O
Out	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wooden	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
beyond	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
lost	O
all	O
our	O
clothes	O
that	O
we	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
two	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
a	O
work-basket	O
with	O
new	O
work	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
deal	O
box	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
large	O
pier	O
glass	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
we	O
left	O
open	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
to	O
them	O
but	O
through	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
two	O
pillows	O
and	O
pillow-cases	O
on	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
work-basket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
trifling	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Youl	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
pillows	O
and	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
work-basket	O
,	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
therese	O
,	O
are	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
pillows	O
were	O
on	O
our	O
bed	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
t	O
hings	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
husband	O
fastened	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
forced	O
open	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
going	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Youl	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
pillows	O
on	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
therese	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
found	O
these	O
pillows	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
forty	O
guineas	O
that	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
pillows	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
.	O
Bond	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
that	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
concern	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
mentioned	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
money	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
were	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
dressing	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
indeed	O
mention	O
some	O
money	O
when	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
money	O
there	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nine	O
guineas	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
received	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
butter	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
except	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
five-and-threepenny	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
:	O
but	O
that	O
money	O
was	O
delivered	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
cornelians	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
cutting	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tyas	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Tyas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chandois-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Grosvenor	I-place
Square	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
to	O
attend	O
there	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
I	O
saw	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
pushed	O
up	O
,	O
we	O
imagined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
at	O
first	O
going	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
hanging	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
his	O
bed	O
side	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
clothes	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Jew	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
wear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
box	O
and	O
case	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great-Poultney-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
sevennight	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
squares	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
show	O
glass	O
where	O
my	O
watches	O
were	O
was	O
removed	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cases	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
near	O
home	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
(	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
show-glass	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
show-glass	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
from	O
the	O
Public-Office	O
at	O
Bow-Street	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
advertised	O
one	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Cave	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
showed	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
This	O
watch	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
On	O
that	O
Friday	O
morning	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
watch-case	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
jeweller	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
waistcoat	O
has	O
no	O
pockets	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
Jew	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sattin	O
saque	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
November	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
53	I-place
in	I-place
Bow-Lane	I-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
silk-dyer	O
in	O
the	O
garment	O
way	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
flowered	O
saque	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pink	O
sattin	O
night-gown	O
,	O
a	O
gray	O
watered	O
tabby	O
gown	O
,	O
all	O
unripped	O
and	O
put	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
dying	O
;	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
blossom-coloured	O
silk	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
dye	O
with	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
to	O
match	O
in	O
colour	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
that	O
had	O
some	O
cracks	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
shop	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
instrument	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
draw	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
shop	O
was	O
left	O
without	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
my	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
backwards	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
under	O
where	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
in	O
part	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
upright	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dye-house	O
from	O
me	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
apprentice	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Sam	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
watching	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
put	O
their	O
hands	O
into	O
your	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
immediately	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
panes	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
things	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
soon	O
missed	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
only	O
missed	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
had	O
them	O
advertised	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
goods	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
silk	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
shot	O
with	O
a	O
violet	O
or	O
blossom	O
colour	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
remnants	O
of	O
silk	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
front	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
off	O
from	O
this	O
very	O
same	O
silk	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
puts	O
the	O
silk	O
to	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
cut	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
the	O
front	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
indented	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
,	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
swear	O
it	O
very	O
safely	O
,	O
the	O
fronts	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
cut	O
from	O
those	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
silk	O
in	O
Cave	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
's	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
register	O
down	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
also	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
great	O
misfortune	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
silk	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
taylor	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
:	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
first	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
a	O
tavern	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
lodge	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
going	O
on	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
decent	O
manner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
bed	O
by	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
October	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Mrs.	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Dr.	O
Cherrington	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Paradise-Row	O
,	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
rushing	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
thrown	O
down	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
brute	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
push	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
He	O
went	O
forwards	O
a	O
dog	O
's	O
trot	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
active	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
breast	O
,	O
supported	O
by	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
-	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
-	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Immediately	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
bundle	O
that	O
is	O
dropped	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
motion	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
towards	O
the	O
water-side	O
.	O
In	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Greenwood	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
linen	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
headborough	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
linen	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
publick	O
offender	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
punished	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirts	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
on	O
the	O
North	O
side	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
another	O
little	O
boy	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
very	O
well	O
knew	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
attempt	O
to	O
pick	O
several	O
pockets	O
between	O
there	O
and	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
Just	O
by	O
the	O
crossing	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
attempted	O
to	O
pick	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
very	O
visible	O
.	O
He	O
not	O
being	O
quick	O
enough	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stepped	O
forward	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turning	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
between	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
owns	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
crowd	O
.	O
The	O
Alderman	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
show	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
nose	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wyre	I-pers
,	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
with	O
Wyre	O
the	O
last	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
of	O
wheaten	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
bread	O
basket	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
124	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
into	O
Castle-yard	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pigg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
three	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
loaves	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
baker	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
basket	O
and	O
take	O
three	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
basket	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
Pigg	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
opposite	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
as	O
he	O
described	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
mistress	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
cloth	O
,	O
called	O
chintz	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	B-pers
united	I-pers
company	I-pers
of	I-pers
merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
October	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
India	O
warehouse	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
weighing	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Helen	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
there	O
with	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
chintz	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
working	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Hush	O
!	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
another	O
man	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Rudock	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rudock	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bale	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
surveyed	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
opened	O
before	O
they	O
are	O
surveyed	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Rudock	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Rudock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
regular	O
account	O
taken	O
and	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
officer	O
,	O
whose	O
business	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
attend	O
there	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
deficiency	O
in	O
these	O
chintzs	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
account	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
five	O
or	O
six-and-twenty	O
pieces	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Milbank	O
told	O
me	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Sir	O
Eglin	O
Alstone	O
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hulston	I-pers
,	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
,	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ewen	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Batten	I-pers
,	O
three	O
King	O
's	O
officers	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Gerton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Cosden	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maiden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
labourers	O
in	O
the	O
warehouses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
china-ware	O
basons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
twelve	O
china	O
tea-cups	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
other	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	B-pers
united	I-pers
company	I-pers
of	I-pers
merchants	I-pers
,	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
also	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Rudock	O
sent	O
me	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
china-ware	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
with	O
this	O
china-ware	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pockets	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
in	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Seething-lane	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
officers	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
here	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Smith	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
my	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
report	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
china-ware	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Rudock	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
abundance	O
of	O
china-ware	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
with	O
certainty	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
such	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
that	O
china	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
called	O
the	O
Sea-horse	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Iron-gate	O
by	O
water	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lose	O
my	O
call	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
officer	O
should	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bunning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Rose-street	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
Sea-horse	O
.	O
She	O
lay	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
bought	O
some	O
china	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
my	O
white	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
my	O
notice	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
that	O
I	O
liked	O
.	O
He	O
bought	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
china	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Bunning	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
cups	O
and	O
some	O
basons	O
,	O
odds	O
and	O
ends	O
he	O
called	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
they	O
were	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
I	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
for	O
a	O
boat	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
on	O
shore	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
si	O
de	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
river	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
his	O
work	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
call	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
bargain	O
?	O
Bunning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
each	O
?	O
Bunning	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ring	O
them	O
?	O
Bunning	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
examine	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pockets	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
packed	O
in	O
some	O
India	O
paper	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
boat	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Falcon-court	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
him	O
that	O
morning	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
walked	O
together	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remainder	O
part	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
we	O
took	O
boat	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Rudock	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
over	O
your	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
warehouses	O
?	O
Rudock	O
.	O
We	O
call	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bunning	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
on	O
board	O
?	O
Bunning	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
on	O
board	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
better	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hewen	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
King	O
's	O
officers	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Boutell	I-pers
,	O
labourers	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
.	O
William	O
Hill	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lovegrove	O
,	O
all	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Rothwell	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
china-ware	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Rothwell	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
reason	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
in	O
answer	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
The	O
alderman	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
first	O
?	O
Rothwell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Sea	O
Horse	O
?	O
Rothwell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Rudock	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
china	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
syllable	O
of	O
having	O
bought	O
them	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Sea	O
Horse	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Boutell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
elder	O
took	O
a	O
general	O
survey	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
chests	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
that	O
had	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Rudock	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
this	O
china	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
Rudock	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
twenty-five	O
or	O
twenty-six	O
shillings	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
china	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
having	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Sea	O
Horse	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
to	O
prosecute	O
Bunning	O
for	O
perjury	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Newport	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Guildhall	B-place
,	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
drawing	O
the	O
lottery	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
his	O
together	O
.	O
His	O
companion	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
keeping	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
follow	O
a	O
country	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
:	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Newport	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
pick-pocket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
several	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
yet	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
a	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
putting	O
something	O
between	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Newport	O
appeared	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
not	O
appeared	O
since	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
the	O
bill	O
at	O
our	O
own	O
expence	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
pardon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
words	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bagnell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Valentine	B-pers
Anshutz	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
130	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
soup-spoon	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
a	O
pistole	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Valentine	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Valentine	O
Anshutz	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clock-case	O
maker	O
,	O
rather	O
in	O
the	O
fine	O
way	O
,	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
fast	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
better	O
.	O
My	O
child	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
naked	O
sword	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
;	O
overnight	O
the	O
sword	O
was	O
hanging	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
130	O
ounces	O
of	O
chippings	O
of	O
silver	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
mahogany	O
bureau	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
with	O
the	O
sword	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
four	O
common	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
soup-ladle	O
,	O
a	O
mother-of-pearl	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
mourning-rings	O
and	O
some	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
morocco	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
was	O
wrenched	O
open	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
a	O
dirty	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
marks	O
of	O
feet	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
carpet	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
chisels	O
found	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
wrenched	O
open	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
bills	O
dispersed	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
:	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
pistol	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
deposed	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
informations	O
lodged	O
with	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
of	O
houses	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sir	O
John	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Graham	O
lived	O
,	O
in	O
Leicester-Street	O
,	O
by	O
Lickapond-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Leather-Lane	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
first	O
secured	O
Underwood	O
and	O
Burton	O
,	O
having	O
watched	O
their	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
found	O
Bagnell	O
in	O
bed	O
there	O
.	O
In	O
Underwood	O
's	O
pocket	O
were	O
found	O
twenty-seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
chisel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
center-bit	O
and	O
stock	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
Burton	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
center-bit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stock	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
bit	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
bits	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
table	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
,	O
a	O
match	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
some	O
gunpowder	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pistols	O
(	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
)	O
.	O
Graham	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
till	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
two	O
watchmen	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
seeing	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
Denmark-Street	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
their	O
faces	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
any	O
charge	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Graham	B-pers
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Bagnell	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
487	O
.	O
See	O
also	O
Bagnell	O
and	O
Graham	B-pers
both	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
477	O
.	O
For	O
Underwood	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Clifford	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
522.	O
all	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
,	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
three	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Popjoy	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
15.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wosley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Christopher	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Cowen	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
flowered	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
three	O
coloured	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
bays	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Frances	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
being	O
very	O
illegally	O
obtained	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
gold	O
pendants	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
pendants	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
enamelled	O
dial-plates	O
for	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
forty-eight	O
balances	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Upjohn	I-pers
and	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Wirgman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
,	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Upjohn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Wirgman	I-pers
in	O
the	O
watchmaking	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Cuthert	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
brought	O
John	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
pendants	O
,	O
and	O
enamelled	O
dial-plates	O
,	O
as	O
suspecting	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
lad	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
his	O
younger	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
our	O
errand	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
examined	O
them	O
separately	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
confessed	O
he	O
got	O
at	O
them	O
by	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
from	O
the	O
shutters	O
to	O
a	O
mahogany	O
drawer	O
where	O
we	O
keep	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
drawer	O
we	O
keep	O
enamelled	O
dial-plates	O
.	O
We	O
always	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
also	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
receiving	O
them	O
of	O
his	O
brother	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
dial-plates	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Red	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
pendant	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
suspecting	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
change	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
telling	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
pendant-maker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
maker	O
in	O
the	O
wholesale	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
complete	O
an	O
order	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
pendant	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
till	O
his	O
order	O
was	O
compleat	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
know	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brother	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Upjohn	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
,	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
four	O
gold	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
pendants	O
,	O
and	O
fifty-four	O
watch	O
dial	O
plates	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
and	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trimble	I-pers
.	O
At	O
his	O
first	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dial-plate-maker	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
learn	O
enamelling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
formerly	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
for	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Ufford	I-pers
the	O
headborough	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
watch	O
balances	O
,	O
four	O
watch	O
glasses	O
and	O
one	O
dial	O
plate	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
searching	O
his	O
box	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Aylesbury-street	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoners	O
both	O
confess	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
receiving	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
paper	O
.	O
William	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
John	O
guilty	O
.	O
T.14	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
window	O
blind	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old-street	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
has	O
been	O
twice	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lowe	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lowe	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
day-light	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
shoved	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
window-blind	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
alarmed	O
,	O
having	O
lost	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
some	O
nights	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
inside	O
shutters	O
were	O
not	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
them	O
secure	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
bells	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
's	O
staff	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
beadle	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
watch	O
there	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
was	O
ordered	O
ot	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
having	O
brought	O
a	O
window-blind	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
odd	O
for	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
blind	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
beadle	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
ask	O
after	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
knocked	O
at	O
his	O
room	O
door	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
blind	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
also	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
tools	O
set	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
houses	O
with	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lowe	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
being	O
alarmed	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
master	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window-blind	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
carpenter	O
was	O
mending	O
the	O
shutter	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
and	O
stood	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
told	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
watchman	O
's	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
master	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
blind	O
.	O
We	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
blind	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
not	O
making	O
him	O
hear	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
snore	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
.	O
We	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
blind	O
stood	O
against	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
chisels	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
in	O
bricks	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
candle	O
in	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
beadle	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
I	O
sit	O
up	O
every	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seven	O
watchmen	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
vacancy	O
I	O
put	O
one	O
in	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
vacancy	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
staid	O
so	O
late	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
his	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
staff	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mahogany	O
blind	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
Master	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
is	O
proper	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
honestly	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lowe	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
watchman	O
went	O
Old-street	O
beat	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
any	O
thing	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
The	O
servant	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Has	O
he	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
mahogany	O
window	O
blind	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
watchman	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
watchman	O
that	O
went	O
Old-street	O
beat	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
when	O
a	O
vacancy	O
has	O
been	O
)	O
we	O
could	O
make	O
nobody	O
hear	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
found	O
somebody	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
we	O
forced	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blind	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
watchmen	O
's	O
staves	O
,	O
lanthorns	O
,	O
and	O
caps	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
watchmen	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
New-prison	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
also	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
tools	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
worsted	O
yarn	O
,	O
mohair	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
lady	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
every	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
beat	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
My	O
fellow	O
watchman	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Wind-mill	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
blind	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
My	O
beadle	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
thinking	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
an	O
owner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
other	O
goods	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
apartment	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
(	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
)	I-pers
Heskett	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
November	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
March	I-pers
,	O
without	O
Temple-bar	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
two	O
parcels	O
,	O
none	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
cloaths	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
rather	O
doubled	O
up	O
not	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grafton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
by	O
her	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
industrious	O
young	O
woman	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Allcock	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	O
.	O
*	O
Stephen	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black-Swan	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
High-Holborn	I-place
.	O
About	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
by	O
the	O
barking	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
dog	O
that	O
I	O
keep	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
crying	O
out	O
among	O
my	O
geese	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
kill	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
lumber	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
gallery	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
outward	O
door	O
stood	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
windows	O
and	O
door	O
open	O
into	O
the	O
gallery	O
.	O
The	O
geese	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
under	O
my	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
inn-yard	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
bottom	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
leads	O
to	O
some	O
workshops	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
file-cutter	O
and	O
grinder	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
whole	O
inn	O
and	O
yard	O
upon	O
lease	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
reserve	O
these	O
apartments	O
to	O
myself	O
.	O
Great	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
lett	O
to	O
a	O
hackneyman	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
stabling	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
horses	O
.	O
This	O
lumber	O
room	O
is	O
under	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
gallery	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
voices	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
called	O
my	O
bitch	O
by	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
catch	O
a	O
goose	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
flutter	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
They	O
killed	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
-	O
Stop	O
thieves	O
!	O
having	O
nobody	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
out	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
composure	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
gallery	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
stealing	O
my	O
geese	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
words	O
were	O
well	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
snap	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hands	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
another	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
shoot	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
more	O
men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
ride	O
that	O
shaded	O
that	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
cold	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
almost	O
naked	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
two	O
little	O
boys	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
among	O
the	O
geese	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
killed	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
missing	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
only	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
voice	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
disorderly	O
apprentice	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
outward	O
door	O
fast	O
at	O
your	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Kendrick	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
observed	O
no	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
upon	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
unlocked	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
week	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
boots	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
outran	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
-	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
every	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
give	O
the	O
account	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
geese	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
his	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
examined	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Houghton	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Field-Lane	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
either	O
primed	O
a	O
pistol	O
or	O
loaded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
determined	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
geese	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
how	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
coach-houses	O
,	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
gallery	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
himself	O
and	O
Houghton	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Simms	O
called	O
my	O
bull-bitch	O
by	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
heard	O
Houghton	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
words	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
geese	O
to	O
Blackboy-Alley	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
has	O
Simms	O
served	O
?	O
Kendrick	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
came	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
February	O
1762	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
parish	O
apprentice	O
from	O
Dorsetshire	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
weeks	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
Houghton	O
persuaded	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
rob	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Houghton	O
were	O
together	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Field-Lane	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
down	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
into	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
stop	O
somebody	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
gunpowder	O
into	O
the	O
pan	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
through	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
gallery	O
rails	O
into	O
the	O
gallery	O
:	O
Houghton	O
lifted	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
unlocked	O
the	O
bottom	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
bull-bitch	O
began	O
to	O
bark	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
quiet	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Houghton	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
geese	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Houghton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
killed	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
they	O
disturbed	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Houghton	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
with	O
master	O
:	O
he	O
bade	O
master	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
absolutely	O
shoot	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
The	O
outward	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
yard	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
inn	O
yard	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
geese	O
lay	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Houghton	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Randall	B-pers
the	O
other	O
.	O
Houghton	O
tied	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
warrants	O
against	O
Randall	O
and	O
Houghton	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
apprehend	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
evidence	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
Randall	O
in	O
Field-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
did	O
not	O
differ	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
in	O
the	O
account	O
they	O
gave	O
of	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
to	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
assisting	O
to	O
lift	O
the	O
evidence	O
over	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
killing	O
the	O
geese	O
,	O
one	O
taking	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
to	O
Blackboy-Alley	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
free	O
and	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
,	O
with	O
only	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
immediately	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
false	O
oaths	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
fuddled	O
.	O
Houghton	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
agreement	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
agreed	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
Houghton	O
lifted	O
the	O
evidence	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
then	O
fetched	O
the	O
two	O
geese	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
Houghton	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Blackboy-Alley	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Timothy	B-pers
Erwin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
called	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Camage	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Devis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
now	O
Dorothy	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridle	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Ridle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
last	O
cherry-time	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
or	O
week	O
.	O
She	O
behaved	O
well	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
staid	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
children	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
Bridge-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
this	O
gown	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
,	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
sits	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
has	O
been	O
twelve	O
months	O
last	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
children	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
things	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
wear	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
give	O
her	O
liberty	O
to	O
wear	O
your	O
things	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
liberty	O
to	O
wear	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
caps	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Timothy	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Maulton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
280	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
old	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Kindar	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Stephen	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutors	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
in	O
Mark-lane	O
,	O
Kindar	O
Mason	O
and	O
Arthur	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
they	O
are	O
partners	O
and	O
merchants	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
their	O
business	O
these	O
seven	O
years	O
as	O
a	O
ship-broker	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
old	O
iron	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Storehouse-yard	B-place
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
to	O
watch	O
yesterday	O
fortnight	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
warehouse	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Drury	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
wharf	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Ashington	I-pers
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
hid	O
myself	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
Ashington	O
lifted	O
Drury	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
shoved	O
a	O
wooden	O
bolt	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
three	O
iron	O
bolts	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
for	O
three	O
more	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
who	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
throw	O
those	O
three	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ashington	O
threw	O
three	O
bolts	O
under	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
wood	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Drury	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
logs	O
.	O
Drury	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Maulton	O
acquitted	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winford	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Vane	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
Argyll-buildings	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Argyll-street	B-place
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
conversed	O
together	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winford	I-pers
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
last	O
man	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
We	O
pursued	O
into	O
Carnaby-street	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
in	O
that	O
street	O
hearing	O
me	O
call	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
conducting	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Argyll-street	O
,	O
turning	O
round	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
something	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
stones	O
which	O
jingled	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
clasp-knife	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
sharp-pointed	O
clasp-knife	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
inches	O
long	O
)	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
a	O
stab	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
clasped	O
my	O
hand	O
against	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
point	O
in	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabbed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
kept	O
playing	O
away	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
stabbing	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
knife	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
one	O
cut	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cut	O
across	O
my	O
coat	O
at	O
my	O
left	O
hip	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
cuts	O
in	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
cut	O
the	O
knife	O
went	O
through	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
cut	O
a	O
slant	O
cut	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
blood	O
run	O
to	O
my	O
ear	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
small	O
scratch	O
with	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
knife	O
on	O
my	O
forehead	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
temple	O
.	O
(	O
he	O
showed	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
cuts	O
in	O
his	O
flesh	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
cloaths	O
)	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
drop	O
his	O
knife	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
hit	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
drop	O
his	O
knife	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
wherever	O
we	O
pleased	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spinnage	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
clerk	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
matches	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Gascoyne	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
but	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
feet	O
between	O
our	O
doors	O
.	O
Her	O
house	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
season	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
shoes	O
on	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
see	O
by	O
marks	O
of	O
their	O
making	O
water	O
against	O
the	O
wainscot	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
nastiness	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
as	O
usual	O
with	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
:	O
Coming	O
past	O
this	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
three	O
men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
thieves	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
He	O
pursued	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
began	O
stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stabbed	O
me	O
through	O
my	O
watch-coat	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
.	O
(	O
he	O
shewed	O
the	O
cuts	O
)	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
till	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Carnaby-Street	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
directly	O
made	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
immediately	O
dropped	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
running	O
so	O
fast	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
tumbled	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
carrying	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
it	O
was	O
these	O
two	O
keys	O
(	O
producing	O
two	O
small	O
stocklock	O
keys	O
)	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
spot	O
afterwards	O
.	O
He	O
after	O
that	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
clasp-knife	O
,	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
stabbing	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gascoyne	O
cried	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
stabbed	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
so	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
without	O
hurting	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
his	O
hand	O
back	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
stick	O
the	O
knife	O
into	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
immediately	O
.	O
We	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
further	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
locksmith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
these	O
keys	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
street-door	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mather	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
prodigious	O
knocking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Spinnage	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gascoyne	O
there	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
bag	O
,	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
matches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cord	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
with	O
the	O
cord	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Torey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Marlborough	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
call	O
of	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
enough	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
street	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
scuffle	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
collar	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gascoyne	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
Marlborough-street	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
upon	O
a	O
bench	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
buckles	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
Marlborough-street	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Diggot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
keys	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
's	O
house	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
's	O
house	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
some	O
furniture	O
from	O
that	O
house	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
some	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
.	O
When	O
Mrs.	O
Winford	O
went	O
out	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
door	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
which	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
this	O
last	O
witness	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
ordered	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
key	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
custody	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
work	O
in	O
gardens	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
Hyde-Park-Corner	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
What	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
here	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
shoes	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
not	O
mine	O
:	O
mine	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
bag	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
matches	O
;	O
which	O
latter	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
selling	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
something	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
Wilkes	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
sold	O
the	O
matches	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
How	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
matches	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
my	O
shoes	O
they	O
used	O
me	O
worse	O
and	O
worse	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
Light	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
a	O
distiller	O
,	O
at	O
Moregate	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Corral	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
trunk	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
All	O
were	O
very	O
safe	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
my	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
.	O
The	O
trunk	O
I	O
found	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Corral	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
left	O
her	O
trunk	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
week	O
before	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
trunk	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
till	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
stay	O
no	O
