TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Sidney	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Smythe	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
and	O
++	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Key	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kidman	I-pers
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
James	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Cowling	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Hearsay	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Elger	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Slaney	I-pers
John	B-pers
Trift	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Singer	I-pers
*	O
*	O
Andrew	B-pers
Pursell	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Singer	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
ill.	O
James	B-pers
Juery	I-pers
.	O
216	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
eighteen	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Tho	B-pers
Everett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cateaton-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
Blackwell-hall	O
factor	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Monksfield	I-pers
,	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
from	O
dinner	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
had	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
Wm	O
Monksfield	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Everett	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
at	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
just	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
prevented	O
my	O
seeing	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
foot	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
superfine	O
crimson	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
that	O
cloth	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
dropt	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
cloth	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
near	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
before	O
?	O
Monksfield	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Switt	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
earn	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
earn	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afrighted	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
willingly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
delivered	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
me	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Monksfield	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
Monksfield	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
Josiah	B-pers
Hodgkin	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
At	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Hodgkin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
Virginia-street	B-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
from	O
a	O
corner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
large	O
horse	O
pistol	O
at	O
my	O
breast	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
I	O
believe	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
himself	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
a	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
ribban	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Hodgkin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
moonlight	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
just	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
the	O
descriptions	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
words	O
?	O
Hodgkin	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Make	O
haste	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
by	O
a	O
Romish	O
chapel	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Virginia-street	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
center	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
Said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
New	O
Ragfair	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Hodgkin	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
seal	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
cap	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tyrawley	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
with	O
other	O
clothes	O
on	O
?	O
Hodgkin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
wide	O
on	O
his	O
cheek	O
bones	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
thin	O
,	O
meager	O
face	O
downwards	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lacon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
knew	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
spirit	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
guineas	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
heard	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
clothes	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout	O
coat	O
with	O
a	O
cape	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
neckcloth	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
:	O
his	O
face	O
very	O
broad	O
over	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
thin	O
downwards	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
several	O
houses	O
till	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
turn	O
to	O
find	O
a	O
minister	O
for	O
Wapping	O
church	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
church	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
brought	O
me	O
word	O
they	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
highwayman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
arms	O
.	O
He	O
fetched	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
.	O
I	O
loaded	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
desperate	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
armed	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
court	O
in	O
Parrot-Alley	O
;	O
we	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
pointed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
shoulder	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
instrument	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
an	O
instrument	O
made	O
of	O
lignumvita	O
,	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
stail	O
,	O
the	O
handle	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
inches	O
long	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
fastened	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
strong	O
silk	O
cord	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
I	O
made	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
defend	O
myself	O
against	O
the	O
cole-heavers	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
stir	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
watchmen	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
standing	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
latch	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Lacon	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
fast	O
.	O
I	O
burst	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
my	O
shoulder	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
pistol-bullets	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout	O
coat	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
coat	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
headbrough	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
beadle	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
highwayman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
joining	O
to	O
Parrot-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lacon	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
if	O
he	O
moved	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
beadle	O
searched	O
him	O
for	O
firearms	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
is	O
claimed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
bullets	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lacon	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
church	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
watchman	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
thief	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
he	O
lodged	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lacon	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
surrender	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
ten	O
leaden	O
bullets	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Tyrawley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
betwixt	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
nine	O
guineas	O
.	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
guineas	O
were	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Hodgkin	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
is	O
No	O
.	O
272	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
Green	I-pers
the	O
maker	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
paper	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
a	O
heart	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
silver	O
cap	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
Tyrawley	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
twice	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
he	O
brought	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
shank	O
of	O
a	O
seal	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
cheated	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
the	O
seal	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
or	O
not	O
(	O
thinking	O
to	O
direct	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
coming	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkin	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
him	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
the	O
seal	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
impression	O
of	O
the	O
seal	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
from	O
my	O
seal	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
family	O
coat	O
of	O
arms	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Tyrawley	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dressed	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Tyrawley	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
surtout	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
?	O
Tyrawley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
single	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
persons	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
I	O
could	O
rob	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
just	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
both	O
have	O
swore	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Scott	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
their	O
oaths	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Dison	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
fish	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
shipmate	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Harlequin	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
girls	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
nine	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
E.	O
Dison	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
husband	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Greenland	O
in	O
the	O
Weymouth	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
from	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Broadwater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wind	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
and	O
her	O
daughter	O
,	O
named	O
Bowers	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
East-Smithfield	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
woman	O
before	O
?	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
locked	O
us	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
watch	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sister	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
she	O
buried	O
?	O
Broadwater	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
buried	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
facing	O
the	O
Shovel	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
George	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
young	O
woman	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
she	O
is	O
called	O
Nancy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
before	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
Williams	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
lower	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
thing	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
sister	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
sister	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Sarah	B-pers
Michael	I-pers
.	O
Lacon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
bullets	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
bullets	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
watches	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
watches	O
?	O
M.	O
Michael	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
positive	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
one	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	O
,	O
Belamp	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Belamp	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
teakettle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Widowes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Widowes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
I	O
miss	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
direction	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbrokers	O
produced	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
want	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
Milliams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Jane	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
220	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crocker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
carcasses	O
of	O
two	O
dead	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
market	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
carcasses	O
of	O
two	O
dead	O
sheep	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
whole	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Garner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leach	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
carcasses	O
cut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
packed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
that	O
basket	O
any	O
meat	O
in	O
it	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Garner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fever	O
and	O
ague	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
shelter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
this	O
boy	O
came	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
washball	O
boxes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
flower	O
kits	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
bottle	O
stands	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Laco	I-pers
n	O
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lacon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
tongue	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Then	O
I'turned	O
her	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
dishonesty	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
ago	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
greatly	O
wronged	O
by	O
this	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
person	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
quarrel	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
turner	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Those	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
222	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Abraham	B-pers
Church	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
and	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bowing	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
stove	O
grate	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
fender	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
stove	O
grate	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
's	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
How	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
grate	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
is	O
named	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
224	O
,	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
superfine	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
shaloon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
hair	O
shag	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Chamberlayne	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pippen	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
hair	O
shag	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
superfine	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
shaloon	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well-knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Chamberlayne	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hoglane	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
dyer	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
George	O
Farmer	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pippen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
If	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
some	O
cloth	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stopt	O
some	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
wife	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
wife	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
failed	O
in	O
the	O
dying	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Davis	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
Davis	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
us	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
lost-man	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
white	O
goods	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
fort	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
goods	O
at	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
shaloon	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Marshalls	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
's	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
scarlet	O
hair	O
shag	O
,	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
Pompadour	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
orange	O
coloured	O
shaloon	O
;	O
at	O
Esther	B-pers
Shorey	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
Pompadour	O
cloth	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Play-House-Yard	O
,	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
orange	O
coloured	O
shaloon	O
,	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
black	O
amen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
scarlet	O
hair	O
shag	O
;	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Dyson	O
's	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
orange	O
coloured	O
shaloon	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Alefounder	O
's	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
advertised	O
things	O
stopped	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
remnant	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
Davis	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
inquired	O
Andrews	O
's	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
.	O
He	O
delivered	O
them	O
very	O
readily	O
without	O
asking	O
for	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
Davis	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Davis	O
ever	O
send	O
you	O
with	O
any	O
?	O
E.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Davis	O
was	O
never	O
by	O
but	O
once	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
piece	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
E.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
piece	O
or	O
shaloon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
orange	O
coloured	O
shaloon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
here	O
?	O
E.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
found	O
at	O
Andrews	O
's	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
Had	O
Davis	O
's	O
wife	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
brought	O
some	O
black	O
amen	O
and	O
green	O
amen	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
talked	O
with	O
Davis	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
darker	O
cloth	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
beadle	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
difficulty	O
at	O
Andrews	O
's	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Ellis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
them	O
readily	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dyson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
girl	O
pledged	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
shaloon	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rose-alley	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
wife	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
cloth	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
very	O
fuddled	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
knowing	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mordant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
parcels	O
of	O
goods	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
three	O
different	O
women	O
.	O
E.	O
Taylor	O
brought	O
one	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
16	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
four	O
parcels	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
several	O
parcels	O
back	O
that	O
Davis	O
's	O
wife	O
brought	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
ways	O
privy	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Andrews	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
under	O
fictitious	O
names	O
.	O
Two	O
pieces	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
daytime	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
candlelight	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
discern	O
the	O
colour	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
discovered	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
stopt	O
her	O
.	O
E.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
her	O
mother	O
;	O
one	O
by	O
daylight	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
candlelight	O
.	O
Davis	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Andrews	O
acquitted	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
,	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
calimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
stannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
.	I-pers
Rebecca	I-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Han	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
in	O
Bartholomew-close	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
should	O
I	O
call	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
should	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
but	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
inquired	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
clothes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
back	O
garret	O
and	O
front	O
garret	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
clean	O
but	O
the	O
table	O
cloths	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
woman	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Sept.	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
near	O
my	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
deserted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
distressed	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
willingly	O
.	O
Though	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
's	O
in	O
Bartholomew-close	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
My	O
room	O
door	O
was	O
never	O
opened	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
recommended	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
227	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Giltspur-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Feb.	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
partners	O
told	O
me	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
rails	O
sawed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
set	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
any	O
success	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
one	O
Ackerley	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
turned	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
we	O
lost	O
five	O
baskets	O
of	O
raisins	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Ackerley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
went	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
sawed	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
bars	O
across	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
five	O
baskets	O
of	O
raisins	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Giltspur-street	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
in	O
Jacob	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Cow-Cross	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
disposed	O
of	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lamb	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
disposed	O
of	O
without	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
by	O
trade	O
?	O
Ackerley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perukemaker	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
effect	O
of	O
intoxication	O
with	O
liquor	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
proposed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Ackerley	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
crane	O
at	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
tap	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
where	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
basket	O
in	O
Davis	O
's	O
lodging	O
in	O
Jacob	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Cow-Cross	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
Davis	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Fleming	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
ours	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
twenty	O
baskets	O
with	O
raisins	O
weighed	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
where	O
the	O
bars	O
were	O
found	O
cut	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
fifteen	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Among	O
the	O
twenty	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
baskets	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
kind	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
that	O
very	O
basket	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
that	O
at	O
seeing	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
woman	O
lived	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
cohabit	O
with	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
raisins	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
from	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
day	O
allowed	O
me	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
lighter	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
raisins	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
confirm	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
accomplice	O
Ackerley	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
229	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
,	O
March	O
,	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
facing	O
the	O
Mansion-house	B-place
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
want	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
from	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
tapt	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
church	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
attempting	O
to	O
pick	O
several	O
pockets	O
as	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
.	O
There	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
turning	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
pretty	O
much	O
on	O
a	O
crowd	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
coat	O
was	O
unbuttoned	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
or	O
purple	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
hit	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
marks	O
on	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
letter	O
A	O
upon	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
I	O
see	O
your	O
Lordship	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
woman	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
my	O
eyes	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mordica	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Bluecoat	O
boys	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
Cornhill	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
mob	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
through	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
my	O
pocket	O
pulled	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
one	O
,	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
M	O
upon	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
We	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
another	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
oranges	O
and	O
lemons	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Soloman	O
Mordica	O
,	O
No	O
176.	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
231	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Missin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
of	O
Feb.	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Wood-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
suppose	O
as	O
a	O
common	O
woman	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
stood	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
short	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Wildman	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Wildman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Wildman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Wildman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coppersmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
wife	O
?	O
Wildman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
children	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
concern	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
I	O
wanted	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
chose	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
called	O
you	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Wildman	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
account	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Wildman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
the	O
hour	O
one	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
that	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
along	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
together	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
beat	O
the	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
stand	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
232	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
960	O
halfpence	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brough	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Brough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Enfield	B-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
40	O
s.	O
worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
compting	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
a	O
dunghill	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Brough	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Brough	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
has	O
worked	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
thirty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brough	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Stephen	B-pers
Byne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Causton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
four	O
mourning	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
Bristolstone	O
girdle	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwellinghouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Causton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Highgate	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
my	O
servant	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
study	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
drawers	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
mourning	O
rings	O
,	O
medals	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
also	O
a	O
tea	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
workman	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
inquiring	O
,	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
gold	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
medals	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
.	O
He	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
circumstantial	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Tent	O
in	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
,	O
Southwark	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
inquire	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
lodging	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
trunk	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
His	O
landlady	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
lodger	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
my	O
opening	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
sealed	O
up	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
concerning	O
the	O
trunk	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
justices	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Crisp	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
crests	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
with	O
no	O
mark	O
.	O
The	O
rings	O
with	O
the	O
mottoes	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
medals	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
medals	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
others	O
like	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
sealed	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Causton	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
near	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
built	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
good	O
workman	O
,	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sherry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Causton	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
then	O
?	O
Sherry	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
all	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
shut	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
hands	O
.	O
Two	O
bolts	O
were	O
slipt	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
hall	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
medals	O
and	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
small	O
leather	O
trunk	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
locket	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
rings	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
the	O
mottoes	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
gold	O
coins	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
which	O
are	O
found	O
.	O
Sherry	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
plate	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
,	O
Southwark	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
Tent	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
hospital	O
.	O
Crisp	O
.	O
The	O
right	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
is	O
the	O
Tenter	O
,	O
having	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
supposed	O
,	O
been	O
a	O
tenter	O
ground	O
.	O
Parker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
but	O
eight	O
nights	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
this	O
trunk	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
locked	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
civil	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
to	O
prison	O
eight	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Causton	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
deliver	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ardine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
got	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
who	O
opened	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
this	O
little	O
red	O
trunk	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
medals	O
and	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
lockets	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
a	O
locket	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Caustin	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
stone	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
writing	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
medals	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
writing	O
is	O
when	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Th	O
.	O
C.	O
born	O
1st	O
Feb.	O
1694-5.	O
Mary	B-pers
Greillam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
,	O
deposited	O
this	O
trunk	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
one	O
evening	O
open	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
before	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
locket	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
writing	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
vastly	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Humphry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
diligent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alderslade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Wheatsheaf	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
:	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Humphry	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
paid	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Hackney	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
medals	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
to	O
excess	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
:	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
medals	O
?	O
Blackwell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Standing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
years	O
:	O
his	O
character	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
35	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
234	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
skins	O
of	O
shammy	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
Russia	O
drab	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stanser	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Stanser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bedfordberry	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
twelve	O
shammy	O
skins	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
Russia	O
drab	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-Horse-Yard	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
two	O
shammy	O
skins	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
dark	O
canvas	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Russia	O
drab	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
skins	O
and	O
some	O
Russia	O
drab	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
notice	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
12	O
d.	O
each	O
for	O
the	O
skins	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
the	O
Russia	O
drab	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
,	O
expecting	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
slipt	O
them	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
attempting	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
left	O
that	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stanser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
blue	O
stuff	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
dusk	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
.	O
They	O
kept	O
telling	O
me	O
to	O
reach	O
down	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
feared	O
the	O
y	O
were	O
upon	O
some	O
bad	O
design	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Two	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
he	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
skins	O
and	O
drab	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Madan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jourday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Story	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchimer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
235	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Sweetlove	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
bolster	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
fender	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
frying-pan	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
trevit	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griggs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gray	B-place
's	I-place
Inn-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
lett	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
about	O
Christmas	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
paid	O
his	O
rent	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
carried	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
candle	O
standing	O
without	O
a	O
candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
your	O
candlestick	O
?	O
The	O
wife	O
said	O
she	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
bedstead	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
fetch	O
your	O
sheets	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
bedstead	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blanket	O
,	O
bolster	O
case	O
and	O
sheets	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
mist	O
a	O
brass	O
fender	O
and	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
proposed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
tell	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
prosecute	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
at	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
but	O
the	O
frying-pan	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
fender	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
about	O
7	O
s.	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dobery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Careless	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fox-court	O
,	O
Gray's-Inn	O
lane	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
a	O
frying	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
trevit	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
about	O
6	O
s.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
these	O
but	O
the	O
frying-pan	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
summer	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
getting	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
month	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
work	O
for	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hadwen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
thirty	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
me	O
constantly	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
frequently	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
236	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
copper	O
boilers	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brazier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	B-place
.	O
One	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
my	O
back	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
coppers	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
somebody	O
in	O
a	O
carpenter	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
fired	O
off	O
two	O
horse	O
pistols	O
and	O
waited	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
quiet	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
call	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
!	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
again	O
!	O
the	O
thief	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
your	O
coppers	O
dropt	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
We	O
surrounded	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
form	O
in	O
a	O
wash-house	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
neighbour	O
's	O
apprentice	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Ever	O
since	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ewers	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
coppers	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
by	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
five	O
I	O
heard	O
these	O
coppers	O
fall	O
into	O
Bedshire-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
lying	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
concealed	O
between	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
parapet	O
wall	O
behind	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
concealed	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
key	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
within	O
that	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
smith	O
's	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
me	O
that	O
alarmed	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
first	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
blowing	O
the	O
fire	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
coppers	O
lying	O
:	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
we	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
daylight	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pales	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Accourt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
rumbling	O
of	O
the	O
coppers	O
.	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
clothes	O
on	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
coppers	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
they	O
fell	O
from	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
these	O
coppers	O
had	O
been	O
concealed	O
between	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
a	O
sugarbaker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
fetching	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
imagine	O
they	O
fed	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
master	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
somebody	O
just	O
turn	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
coppers	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asleep	O
under	O
a	O
washing	O
stool	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
robbery	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
where	O
there	O
have	O
been	O
seisures	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
These	O
coppers	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
carried	O
above	O
a	O
story	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
high	O
.	O
How	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
conceive	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
.	O
The	O
coppers	O
were	O
near	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
washing	O
stool	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
a	O
proper	O
place	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
?	O
Ewer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
concealed	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bill	O
's	O
other	O
apprentice	O
pulled	O
the	O
washing	O
tub	O
from	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
pulled	O
it	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
conceal	O
himself	O
.	O
Though	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
from	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bills	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Bills	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
the	O
Monday	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
suffer	O
servants	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
such	O
lengths	O
of	O
time	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
Bills	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
as	O
much	O
pains	O
as	O
most	O
people	O
do	O
with	O
apprentice	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
237	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
,	I-pers
Dowland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
,	O
1768	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bethnall	B-place
Green	I-place
parish	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Kingstand-Road	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Bethnall-Green	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
hat	O
last	O
January	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
gown	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Dowland	I-pers
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
her	O
any	O
promise	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gown	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
oysters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
behave	O
ill	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
appeared	O
always	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Culbert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Clare-Market	B-place
.	O
We	O
hang	O
the	O
sheep	O
carcasses	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
the	O
air	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
carcase	O
taken	O
away	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
carcase	O
of	O
mutton	O
at	O
Hay-Hill	O
,	O
near	O
Berkeley	O
Square	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
dead	O
dog	O
.	O
He	O
attempted	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
buildings	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Brudenell	O
Muse	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Berkeley-Square	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
there	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
carcase	O
of	O
mutton	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
that	O
employed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
spoil	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
by	O
the	O
Muse	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
bread	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sopped	O
in	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
about	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
mad	O
.	O
I	O
by	O
enquiring	O
found	O
the	O
mutton	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jolley	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jolley	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
mutton	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
in	O
our	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
239.	O
George	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
240	O
,	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sorrel	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
sorrel	O
gelding	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
locked	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
our	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
correction	O
of	O
Adgiam	O
,	O
in	O
Hampshire	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
a	O
sorrel	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
an	O
old	O
sack	O
,	O
marked	O
with	O
T.	O
R.	O
in	O
a	O
ring	O
with	O
a	O
star	O
.	O
He	O
informed	O
me	O
Dyer	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
such	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Dyer	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
lit	O
of	O
Dobbins	O
at	O
the	O
election	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
mob	O
took	O
his	O
part	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Crookham	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Dyer	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
Dobbins	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
charged	O
Dobbins	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
to	O
Dyer	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gunner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Crookham	O
,	O
near	O
Crundal	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
Crookham	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
my	O
son	O
how	O
far	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
Reading	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
them	O
about	O
sixteen	O
miles	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
50	O
s.	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
they	O
allowed	O
him	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
My	O
son	O
telling	O
me	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
examine	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Dyer	O
is	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
sorrel	O
gelding	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
and	O
four	O
white	O
feet	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Dyer	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
worse	O
is	O
my	O
misfortune	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
so	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
apprentice	O
boys	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Guildford	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
but	O
sixpence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Guildford	O
and	O
back	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
on	O
for	O
Farnham	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Farnham	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
enquired	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
for	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
sell	O
his	O
horse	O
to	O
bear	O
his	O
charges	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
without	O
his	O
two	O
boys	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
At	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
how	O
old	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
trot	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
then	O
to	O
gallop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Six-and-twenty	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
stole	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
very	O
honestly	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
questioned	O
him	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
and	O
clear	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
five-and-twenty	O
shillings	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
At	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
next	O
Whitsun-Tuesday	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Perhaps	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
fault	O
in	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
see	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
'll	O
just	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
farmer	O
that	O
has	O
more	O
judgement	O
that	O
I.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
opinion	O
they	O
have	O
stole	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
He	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
Dyer	O
the	O
road	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
Dobbins	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
foot	O
way	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
at	O
Sir	O
Harry	B-pers
St	I-pers
.	O
John	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
his	O
steward	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
two	O
fellows	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Sir	O
Harry	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
them	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
hear	O
of	O
an	O
owner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
horse	O
five	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Evans	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Dyer	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
bridle	O
and	O
sack	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
rider	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
his	O
rider	O
.	O
We	O
enquired	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
we	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
Shepperton	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
owner	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
through	O
Guildford	O
and	O
Farnham	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
owner	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
very	O
hard	O
drove	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
work	O
.	O
Dobbin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
together	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
horse	O
near	O
Sunbury	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
and	O
bridle	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
an	O
owner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
rode	O
to	O
Guildford	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
work	O
.	O
Dyer	O
then	O
proposed	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
we	O
had	O
best	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
resolved	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
friends	O
are	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Dyer	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Dobbins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
seventeen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
age	O
.	O
242	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Geo	B-pers
Hardin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peace	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
apartment	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
now	O
lies	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Hardin	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
living	O
by	O
charing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
243	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burger	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
tobacco-box	O
made	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
7.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
Last	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
Penitent-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cannon	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
latish	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
young	O
women	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
a	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pipe	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ryder	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
for	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to-bed	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
sixpennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
desired	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
girl	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
liquor	O
in	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
blowed	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
thieves	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
on	O
a	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
or	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Ryder	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
stockings	O
behind	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
came	O
swearing	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
?	O
Ryder	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
s.	O
My	O
watch	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
paper	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
for	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
woman	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
so	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
from	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
observed	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
where	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
then	O
but	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
searched	O
well	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Ryder	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
bed	O
all	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
are	O
got	O
clear	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
clear	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
things	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Ryder	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
liquor	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thorburn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
a	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sober	O
or	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Thorburn	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
judgment	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whereabouts	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
watch-house	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
prisoners	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
She	O
swore	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
girl	O
call	O
down	O
not	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
hanging	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
girl	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
his	O
things	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
except	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Summerfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Thorburn	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
they	O
have	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
's	O
.	O
Coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
pipe	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
pipe	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
directly	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
May-pole	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
It	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
offered	O
him	O
the	O
farthing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
at	O
Saltpetre-Bank	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
turned	O
the	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friends	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
my	O
friends	O
live	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
miles	O
off	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
beds	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
people	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
other	O
beds	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
