TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Termine	O
.	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clive	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Perrott	I-pers
+	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Willes	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
and	O
++	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caslon	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Stamp	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Motley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tenniswood	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sheridine	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
Silvester	B-pers
Langfield	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Head	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hillam	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
.	O
143	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bulcock	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Downer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
of	O
hats	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bulcock	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
just	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bullock	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
cut	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
window	O
several	O
times	O
trying	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
our	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
hole	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
inches	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
diamond	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
a	O
boy	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bulcock	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
inches	O
,	O
drawn	O
through	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
glass	O
was	O
whole	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
detected	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
compleated	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
by	O
getting	O
the	O
piece	O
into	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
144	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Esther	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Grub-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
lay	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
The	O
bell	O
being	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
come	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
for	O
goods	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
We	O
always	O
put	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
day	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
utterly	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
about	O
among	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
by	O
inquiring	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
by	O
using	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
linen	O
gown	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
something	O
later	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
goout	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
exact	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
well	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
order	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
be	O
looked	O
for	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
gown	O
for	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
145	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Woodthey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Dominique	B-pers
Angelo	I-pers
Jermamondo	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
japan	O
dressing-boxes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dominique	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Flanagen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dominique	B-pers
Angelo	I-pers
Jermamondo	I-pers
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
country	O
house	O
at	O
Acton	B-place
;	O
I	O
always	O
lie	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
round	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
then	O
locked	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
noise	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
softly	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
cats	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
noise	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
heard	O
?	O
Flannagen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
as	O
if	O
something	O
was	O
rustling	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
fall	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
packing	O
up	O
several	O
things	O
.	O
Taking	O
the	O
dressing	O
glass	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
attempt	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
fought	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
moon	O
shone	O
bright	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
fought	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
mastered	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
ladder	O
standing	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
drawed	O
that	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
gun	O
till	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
ladder	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bristow	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Bristow	O
's	O
ladder	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
bent	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
place	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
with	O
the	O
shutters	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
shoved	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
broke	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
throwed	O
two	O
japan	O
dressing	O
boxes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
throwed	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
long	O
iron	O
scure	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
window	O
was	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
fastened	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
constables	O
at	O
Acton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
about	O
nine	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Flanagan	O
bring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
bloody	O
and	O
scratched	O
about	O
their	O
heads	O
and	O
faces	O
.	O
Flanagan	O
had	O
a	O
gun	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broken	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
dressing	O
boxes	O
lying	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
ladder	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
bloody	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
the	O
cieling	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
bloody	O
(	O
The	O
two	O
dressing	O
boxes	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Flanagan	O
.	O
)	O
Flanagan	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
by	O
pushing	O
the	O
ladder	O
against	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
ladder	O
stand	O
against	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
fourteen	O
cuts	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
146	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
light	O
coloured	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
two	O
scarlet	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
black-silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Bath	O
flannel	O
great-coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
eleven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Pompadour	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
brewhouse	O
is	O
in	O
Dukestreet	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
and	O
my	O
apartment	O
is	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
only	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
,	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
kinsman	O
,	O
that	O
lie	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
two	O
bedchambers	O
there	O
;	O
mine	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
apartment	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
gone	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
and	O
clothes	O
press	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
locked	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
window	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
feet	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
had	O
twelve	O
pains	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
frame	O
that	O
contained	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
sash	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
get	O
through	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
got	O
bills	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
constables	O
and	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
my	O
Pompadour	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
by	O
five	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
worked	O
at	O
our	O
brew-house	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
your	O
window	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
ladder	O
upon	O
a	O
parapet	O
wall	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
new	O
building	O
.	O
The	O
ladder	O
stood	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
ladder	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
to	O
a	O
leaden	O
gutter	O
which	O
joins	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
that	O
window	O
fast	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
missed	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
described	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
was	O
pushed	O
open	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
hospital	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
bill	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
suit	O
of	O
Pompadour	O
clothes	O
in	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
not	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Tho	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
taphouse	O
at	O
Esquire	O
Hucks	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
was	O
robbed	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
take	O
a	O
key	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
his	O
lodgings	O
were	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
sick	O
at	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
hospital	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
M'Cardell	O
,	O
in	O
Church-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Gyles	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
clothes	O
littered	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dumbleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
)	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
that	O
key	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
clothes	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
M'Cardell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
(	O
a	O
woman	O
hired	O
the	O
room	O
which	O
past	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
)	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
but	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
The	O
key	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
constable	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
The	O
clothes	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
E.	O
M'Cardell	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
denomination	O
of	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
some	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
fire	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
place	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
victuals	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
drinking	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
bear	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
bundles	O
of	O
clothes	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
could	O
leave	O
their	O
bundles	O
till	O
the	O
morrow	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morrow	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
suits	O
of	O
clothes	O
in	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
carry	O
my	O
wife	O
a	O
little	O
wine	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
weak	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
in	O
bed	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
M'Cardell	O
knows	O
.	O
M'Cardell	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
goal	O
distemper	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
his	O
bed	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
how	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
go	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
?	O
M'Cardell	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
at	O
night	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
and	O
very	O
fatigued	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
tired	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
M'Cardell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
light	O
his	O
candle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
30	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stop	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
shirts	O
had	O
been	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
dirty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
one	O
man	O
could	O
break	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
man	O
might	O
,	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
not	O
so	O
heavy	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
man	O
might	O
carry	O
them	O
with	O
ease	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
147	O
,	O
148	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Baynam	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Lockinton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lockhart	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
175	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
indico	O
,	O
value	O
52	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
107	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
Andrew	B-pers
Curvan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
vessel	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
indico	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
cask	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
175	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
indico	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
worth	O
a	O
pound	O
?	O
Curvan	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
389	O
lb	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
,	O
cask	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
Mr.	O
Scofield	O
,	O
the	O
broker	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
107	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
sort	O
of	O
indico	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
which	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
cask	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
particular	O
coat	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
French	O
indico	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
indico	O
in	O
London	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
as	O
that	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
all	O
French	O
indico	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
it	O
?	O
Curvan	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
indico	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Curvan	O
,	O
for	O
exportation	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sample	O
shewed	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
in	O
change	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
400	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
indico	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Curvan	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
most	O
particular	O
kind	O
of	O
indico	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
indico	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
(	O
but	O
perhaps	O
that	O
is	O
immaterial	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Curvan	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
indico	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
108	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
question	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
such	O
in	O
London	O
besides	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Curvan	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
(	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
indico	O
produced-in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
are	O
very	O
few	O
casks	O
of	O
indico	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
kingdom	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
indico	O
you	O
bought	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Curvan	O
?	O
Scofield	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
indico	O
manufactured	O
?	O
Scofield	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
weed	O
;	O
by	O
fermenting	O
it	O
with	O
lime	O
they	O
bring	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
stone	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Scofield	O
sent	O
some	O
indico	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Curvan	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
remainder	O
in	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
which	O
certainly	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Lime-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
shewed	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
indico	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
like	O
this	O
one	O
cask	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
positively	O
this	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
indico	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
such	O
indico	O
in	O
England	O
before	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
indico	O
on	O
board	O
my	O
lighter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
stowed	O
among	O
some	O
cotton	O
.	O
My	O
lighter	O
lay	O
off	O
Porter	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Curvan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
lighter	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
alongside	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
the	O
captain	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
lighter	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
almost	O
half	O
the	O
indico	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
indico	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
lighter	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
heard	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pilfered	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Curvan	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
moved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
head	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
indico	O
gone	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Wapping	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
named	O
Hunter	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
some	O
indico	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pieces	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
indico	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dear	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
any	O
body	O
for	O
their	O
trouble	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lockhart	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
the	O
Watermens	O
Arms	O
and	O
Black	O
Boy	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
indico	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Sharp	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
coffee	O
of	O
a	O
captain	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
as	O
good	O
for	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
buy	O
it	O
for	O
eighteen	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
danger	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
that	O
appearance	O
,	O
in	O
buying	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Buy	O
it	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
money	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Hunter	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Gordon	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
delivered	O
23	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
indico	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
it	O
themselves	O
to	O
Lockhart	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Lockhart	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
inquired	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
change	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
note	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
nine	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
Baynam	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
Baynam	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
82	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Baynam	O
before	O
?	O
Sharp	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
that	O
to	O
Lockhart	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
three	O
guineas	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
a	O
farthing	O
to	O
Baynam	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Baynam	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
being	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
went	O
and	O
borrowed	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Baynam	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
four	O
guineas	O
for	O
that	O
parcel	O
.	O
Wm	O
Strange	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
correction	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
Baynam	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Sharp	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
Sharp	O
was	O
charged	O
as	O
a	O
principal	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Baynam	O
,	O
Sharp	O
has	O
been	O
charging	O
you	O
with	O
stealing	O
this	O
indico	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
it	O
is	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
you	O
are	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Baynam	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
fellow	O
,	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
side	O
to	O
the	O
Surry	O
side	O
.	O
The	O
lighter	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Surry	O
side	O
,	O
near	O
Rotherhithe	O
church	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
alongside	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
boat	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rowed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
side	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Sharp	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
149	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hennings	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Henning	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
,	O
going	O
towards	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
jirk	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
being	O
not	O
at	O
at	O
home	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
through	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
till	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mason	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Robert	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
James	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
150	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
January	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bazing-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
detected	O
that	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
stockings	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
dozen	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
miss	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
quantity	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
miss	O
two	O
pair	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
No	O
.	O
17.	O
in	O
Bazing-lane	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
clean	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
maid	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
when	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
nursed	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
her	O
lying	O
in	O
,	O
about	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
these	O
stockings	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
Bazing-lane	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
151	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Isaac	B-pers
Loach	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rammell	I-pers
,	O
February	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rammell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
:	O
going	O
towards	O
Cheapside-Conduit	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Woodstreet	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
turned	O
round	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Somebody	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
interim	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
channel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
have	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
accusing	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shewed	O
him	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
dropt	O
it	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
feet	O
in	O
the	O
channel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
152	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Charter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridgewater-square	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
watch-case	O
maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
silver	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
amount	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
landlord	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodges	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
charcoal	O
,	O
sea-coal	O
,	O
and	O
wood	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
fire	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
alarmed	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
neighbours	O
;	O
they	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
something	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
some	O
pearl	O
ash	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
imparted	O
this	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
about	O
some	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
what	O
silver	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
from	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
about	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
his	O
clothes	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
in	O
the	O
fob	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
in	O
it	O
and	O
being	O
bent	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
earning	O
so	O
little	O
and	O
spending	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
silver	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
before	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sits	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
fob	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Strutley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
master	O
first	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
silver	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
strongly	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
desired	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
fob	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
an	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Redrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Pearsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Park	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
just	O
and	O
upright	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
as	O
honest	O
and	O
upright	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Oliver	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
excuse	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
when	O
the	O
silver	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Oliver	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
stagnated	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
searched	O
him	O
forcibly	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
silver	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
found	O
?	O
Oliver	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
after	O
he	O
pulled	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Snow-hill	B-place
:	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
some	O
houses	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
halloo	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
dropped	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
halloo	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
door	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
pardon	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
felt	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
coming	O
through	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Honey-lane-market	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
to	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
when	O
he	O
called	O
stop-thief	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dean	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
le	O
Grand	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
sword-hilt	O
and	O
buckle	O
cutter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Blue-court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
spectacle-maker	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
poultering	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
behave	O
amiss	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
557.	O
in	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
154	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
not	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
women	O
's	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
December	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
promises	O
of	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
155	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
February	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Isaac	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
at	I-place
Uxbridge	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
instant	O
,	O
February	O
,	O
we	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
:	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
marked	O
I.	O
H.	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
instant	O
,	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
James	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Boar	O
's	O
Head	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
upon	O
the	O
heath	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	O
was	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Lane	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
James	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
spoon	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hayes	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hillington	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
156	O
,	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tite	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
February	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tite	I-pers
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
Ironmonger-row	B-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
parlour	O
sash	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
lost	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
a	O
watch	O
stand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
instant	O
,	O
February	O
,	O
Smithson	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
before	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
silk	O
gown	O
to	O
pledge	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
16	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Walmsley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bridgewater-square	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
linen	O
gown	O
brought	O
by	O
Reuben	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
in	O
Smithson	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Reuben	O
Biggs	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
impeached	O
five	O
men	O
:	O
four	O
of	O
whom	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
since	O
.	O
Reuben	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Stead	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Smithson	O
five	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
Smithson	O
is	O
an	O
ivory	O
spoon	O
maker	O
.	O
Lads	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
:	O
such	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
gentlemens	O
pockets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
Stead	O
?	O
Biggs	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sawyer	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
he	O
gets	O
his	O
living	O
by	O
thieving	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
above	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
particular	O
day	O
.	O
Steed	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Ironmonger-row	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
no	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
a	O
little	O
gate	O
which	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
parlour	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Stead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
about	O
a	O
robbery	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
information	O
of	O
several	O
robberies	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
engaged	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
this	O
bag	O
?	O
Biggs	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
cloth	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
making	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
yard	O
wide	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
Stead	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
black	O
bag	O
.	O
)	O
Biggs	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
watch-stand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
that	O
away	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Smithson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Smithson	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
the	O
silk	O
gown	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
I	O
find	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
Stead	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
Biggs	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
(	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
together	O
two	O
nights	O
)	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
might	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
bag	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
unfortunately	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Barbican	O
when	O
he	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Biggs	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
night	O
Stead	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tool	O
we	O
had	O
made	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
break	O
houses	O
,	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Smithson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
broke	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
trade	O
with	O
people	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
sold	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
has	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
To	O
Smithson	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Little-Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
an	O
ivory	O
brush	O
maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Smithson	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
done	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
many	O
times	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
for	O
me	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
living	O
since	O
?	O
Metcalf	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
works	O
at	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hibert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brush	O
maker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Boswell-court	O
,	O
Charterhouse-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
apprentice	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Robinhood's-court	O
,	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Smithson	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
paid	O
off	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Spruing	I-pers
.	O
Smithson	O
was	O
a	O
shipmate	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
since	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
it	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
poultry	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
bought	O
rabbits	O
and	O
fowls	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Stead	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Smithson	O
guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Negus	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
Ruben	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
See	O
Smithson	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
16.	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
342.	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Nelson	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
158	O
,	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
January	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Cross-lane	B-place
.	O
They	O
wanted	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
bringing	O
beer	O
they	O
brought	O
six-pennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
stuff	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
it	O
they	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
backwards	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
I	O
perceived	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
on	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
names	O
she	O
could	O
think	O
of	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
their	O
assistance	O
,	O
threatening	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
immediately	O
:	O
I	O
declared	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
quit	O
the	O
place	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
recompence	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
M'Gray	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
carver	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
lives	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
;	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
I	O
heard	O
watch	O
called	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
Rothery	O
,	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
somebody	O
came	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
my	O
latch	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
feather-bed	O
among	O
the	O
feathers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
's	O
servant	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
the	O
feathers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
together	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
M.	O
M'Gray	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Brumwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
among	O
the	O
feathers	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Hen	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
glad	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
me	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
with	O
that	O
woman	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
)	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
the	O
man	O
up	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
desire	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
gentleman	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
intrude	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Best	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
saffron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
8	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
cantharides	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
forty-eight	O
boxes	O
of	O
plaster	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bignel	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Wm	B-pers
Berson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
three	O
weeks	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
people	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
timber	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Going	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
come	O
by	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
here	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Coney	O
,	O
Gascoyne	O
,	O
and	O
Wilson	O
,	O
druggists	O
and	O
dry	O
salters	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
the	O
carman	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pint	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
packed	O
up	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
by	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
:	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
clerk	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
tied	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
rope	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
smell	O
of	O
drugs	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
found	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Gunthorp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
packed	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
saffron	O
,	O
some	O
plaster	O
,	O
and	O
cantharides	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
carman	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
box	O
at	O
Glascow	O
wharf	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
that	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
saffron	O
and	O
the	O
cantharides	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
box	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gunthorp	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
to	O
Wapping	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
through	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
sign	O
hanging	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
stood	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
answered	O
him	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
guess	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
hand	O
with	O
this	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shilling	O
and	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
sometimes	O
before	O
and	O
sometimes	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plasterer	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
earn	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Benson	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
off	O
?	O
Benson	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
coming	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Abrahams	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Best	O
.	O
Abrahams	O
is	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
evidence	O
against	O
Castle	O
and	O
Reed	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Esquire	O
Bond	O
's	O
planks	O
.	O
Abrahams	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
John	O
Abrahams	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
they	O
stopt	O
me	O
.	O
Benson	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
came	O
about	O
.	O
Abrahams	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
underkeeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Benson	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Burton	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
161	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
oak	O
timber	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
fir	O
planks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Row	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Row	I-pers
.	O
We	O
lost	O
oak	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
several	O
fir-planks	O
,	O
inch	O
thick	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
February	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
then	O
stripped	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
pieces	O
,	O
six	O
of	O
oak	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
deal	O
and	O
one	O
oak	O
plank	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
cart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
's	O
wood	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
The	O
fir	O
was	O
sawed	O
into	O
feather	O
edge	O
,	O
from	O
round	O
fir	O
;	O
none	O
such	O
was	O
ever	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
oak	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
had	O
used	O
in	O
scaffolding	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
without	O
planing	O
the	O
wood	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
mortar	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
cart	O
was	O
standing	O
before	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
house	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
orchard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
Shrove	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
oak	O
and	O
fir	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
We	O
value	O
the	O
oak	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
fir	O
at	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cart	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
That	O
will	O
come	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
that	O
timber	O
which	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
we	O
used	O
for	O
scaffolding	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
working	O
there	O
about	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cart	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
premises	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
oak	O
scaffolding	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
fir	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
oak	O
board	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	O
Row	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
the	O
timber	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
with	O
a	O
stock	O
lock	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
cart	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
stuff	O
that	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
making	O
the	O
cart	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
finished	O
yet	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
making	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
Christmas	O
?	O
Groom	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
New	O
Year	O
's	O
Day	O
?	O
Groom	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
New	O
Year	O
's	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
making	O
it	O
?	O
Groom	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
making	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
his	O
garden	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
labourer	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
we	O
used	O
the	O
oak	O
in	O
scaffolding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
making	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
or	O
night	O
?	O
Groom	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
's	O
people	O
might	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
in	O
their	O
orchard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
inhabited	O
?	O
Groom	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
cart	O
of	O
what	O
stuff	O
my	O
landlord	O
left	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
repaired	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Richard	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
landlord	O
has	O
sold	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Flannegell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty-eight	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hanmer	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Hanmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Hog-lane	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
till	O
pulled	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
there	O
usually	O
sticks	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Hanmore	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
till	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
night	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
search	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Hanmore	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
might	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
Hanmore	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
with	O
halfpence	O
,	O
there	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
not	O
so	O
many	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
backwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
half-pence	O
?	O
Hanmore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
163	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
five	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
linnen	O
pillowbier	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
M'Kowl	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Ann	B-pers
M'Kowl	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
M'Kowl	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Wyld-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
somebody	O
wanted	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Cotton	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
linen	O
lay	O
strewed	O
about	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
again	O
,	O
except	O
four	O
napkins	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
within	O
ten	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
quart	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
passage	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
near	O
pushing	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
drop	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pat	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
side	O
pocket	O
at	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
something	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
napkins	O
:	O
I	O
ordered	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
else	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
linen	O
dropt	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
half	O
out	O
and	O
half	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
within	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Pesau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
market	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Cotton	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
this	O
looking	O
glass	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
small	O
glass	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
M'Kowl	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cotton	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
channel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
channel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
and	O
Diana	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lion	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
his	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
mason	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
industrious	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
164	O
,	O
165	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
and	O
Hardel	B-pers
Handlan	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
stocking	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mattock	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Mattock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
Slater	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
four	O
boys	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
(	O
my	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
stockings	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
immediately	O
:	O
I	O
mist	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
fellow	O
stocking	O
in	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
confessed	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
stockings	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
At	O
first	O
the	O
woman	O
denied	O
having	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
odd	O
stocking	O
matched	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
damaged	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
four	O
boys	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
alight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
George	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
worsted	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
matching	O
the	O
worsted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
boys	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
biggest	O
of	O
them	O
blowing	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
asked	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
whether	O
the	O
others	O
belonged	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
one	O
stocking	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
dropt	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
the	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
silk	O
and	O
worstead	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
again	O
?	O
M.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Wall	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
people	O
fling	O
at	O
oranges	O
near	O
our	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
hold	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
boys	O
that	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
boys	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
William	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hardel	B-pers
Handlan	I-pers
.	O
Stapleton	O
is	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
held	O
Wall	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
held	O
Waters	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Handlan	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
;	O
Wall	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
hollow	O
tree	O
in	O
the	O
Bird-Cage-Walk	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Stapleton	O
mentioned	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
another	O
tree	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Handlan	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
worsted	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
difficult	O
in	O
chusing	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Stapleton	O
made	O
a	O
sham	O
cough	O
and	O
blowed	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
these	O
stockings	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Wall	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Waters	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Spencer	O
's	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Stapleton	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Wall	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Handlan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
At	O
their	O
request	O
they	O
were	O
branded	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
with	O
Stapleton	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
provided	O
for	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
most	O
excellent	O
useful	O
plan	O
.	O
166	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Leo	I-pers
,	I-pers
Delanty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chalon	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Chalon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Germain-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
plain	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
mend	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
things	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
a	O
petticoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
Chalon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
shirt	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Beauchamp	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
not	O
that	O
shirt	O
to	O
make	O
less	O
in	O
the	O
wrist	O
?	O
Chalon	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
takes	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
business	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
petticoat	O
less	O
in	O
the	O
waist	O
.	O
Chalon	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chalon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirt	O
and	O
petticoat	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
and	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
employed	O
in	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
mend	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
always	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
my	O
mistress	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
home	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
this	O
shirt	O
and	O
petticoat	O
were	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
home	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
167	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Bocket	I-pers
,	O
February	O
6	O
.	O
||	O
Francis	B-pers
Bocket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
at	O
Acton	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
'Squire	O
Wegg	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
saucepan	O
often	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
victuals	O
ready	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
heat	O
milk	O
and	O
potatoes	O
often	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
East-Acton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
saucepan	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
bogs	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
432.	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Kite	O
.	O
168	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
edged	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Panshard	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Panshard	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
banker	O
at	O
Paris	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
property	O
Mr.	O
Panshard	O
's	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
coach	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
A	O
chairman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
Greek-street	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
joke	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
quietly	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
off	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
seen	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
recommended	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
169	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
streak	O
of	O
iron	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
cart	O
wheel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
Richard	B-pers
Gravit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
wheelwright	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Bethnal-Green	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Gravit	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
iron	O
streak	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Gravit	O
.	O
He	O
drives	O
a	O
cart	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Reve	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
dropped	O
the	O
streak	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
170	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
25	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
February	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
Philip	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
garret	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
some	O
lead	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
two	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
chissel	O
I	O
found	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
chissel	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
in	O
cutting	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
cut	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
sell	O
and	O
pawn	O
all	O
my	O
tools	O
.	O
-	O
Yates	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
before	O
this	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
lad	O
come	O
up	O
for	O
business	O
.	O
His	O
friends	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
at	O
Coventry	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
consider	O
his	O
youth	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
punishment	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
expence	O
,	O
see	O
that	O
he	O
shall	O
return	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
friends	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
B	O
.	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Simon	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
chattels	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Michael	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
||	O
Michael	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Francis	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
there	O
?	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
!	O
Then	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
knocking	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
,	O
your	O
house	O
is	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
front	O
window	O
was	O
brok	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
iron	O
bar	O
being	O
bent	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
sash	O
broke	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Be	O
careful	O
at	O
entering	O
your	O
kitchen	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
and	O
abetting	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
stood	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Loseby	I-pers
broke	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
believe	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
window	O
so	O
fastened	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
hand	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
to	O
unfasten	O
it	O
?	O
Dale	O
.	O
The	O
screw	O
of	O
the	O
sash	O
that	O
fastens	O
it	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
undone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hand	O
must	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
to	O
unscrew	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
ascertain	O
that	O
that	O
screw	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
?	O
Dale	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
putting	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
an	O
entering	O
as	O
walking	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
.	O
Here	O
not	O
being	O
proof	O
in	O
this	O
particular	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
172	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Deborah	B-pers
Tash	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
Bath	O
stove	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
ironmonger	O
and	O
brazier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
on	O
Holbourn-hill	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
calling	O
out	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
stove	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
apprentice	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apprentice	O
stopped	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
turning	O
into	O
Shoe-lane	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
begged	O
my	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
:	O
she	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Bath	O
stove	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lesure	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
stealing	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
stove	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
after	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Auld	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
stove	O
from	O
her	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
stove	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
mittens	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
worsted	O
for	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
thirty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Wade	B-pers
Cuel	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Wade	B-pers
Cuel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
Inn	I-place
by	I-place
Holborn-bridge	I-place
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
porter	O
had	O
weighed	O
off	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Southampton	O
;	O
among	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
a	O
paper	O
parcel	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
at	O
Southampton	O
.	O
The	O
porter	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
shed	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
proceeded	O
to	O
weigh	O
another	O
parcel	O
for	O
another	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
uncommon	O
talking	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
