TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
*	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Blackstone	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Judges	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Churchill	I-pers
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Eddis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Robt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Carrington	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Rober	I-pers
George	B-pers
Lyall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Roson	I-pers
1st	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sheridine	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tuffnal	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Langstaff	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
2d	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hasleton	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Hallmarke	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Tett	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hilliam	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Gruyer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Tomalm	I-pers
John	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
129	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smithers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cottrell	O
,	O
a	O
founder	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	B-place
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
behind	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
window	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
,	O
had	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
assisting	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
dropped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
?	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
One	O
ran	O
up	O
Church-yard-alley	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
up	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
when	O
in	O
New-street	O
square	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
against	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stop	O
thief	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Going	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
some	O
wet	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dukey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fellow-apprentice	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
gave	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cottrell	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
girl	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
catched	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
She	O
ran	O
down	O
Shoe-lane	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
apprentice	O
have	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
by	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
he	O
dropped	O
this	O
wet	O
linen	O
.	O
My	O
apprentice	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
searched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
him	O
which	O
were	O
dry	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
linen	O
that	O
he	O
dropped	O
was	O
wet	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
They	O
must	O
get	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
eight	O
feet	O
high	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
unbolted	O
the	O
gate	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
to	O
secure	O
a	O
retreat	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
bolted	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
maid	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
wet	O
linen	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
This	O
linen	O
may	O
,	O
or	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
marked	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
linen	O
is	O
marked	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
dropping	O
the	O
wet	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
finding	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
claiming	O
them	O
only	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
that	O
linen	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
duffil	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
December	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Jer	O
.	O
Neal	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Wyn	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wyn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
ship	O
in	O
Yarmouth-roads	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
in	O
a	O
creditable	O
manner	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
this	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
never	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
would	O
know	O
better	O
what	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
seven	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Neal	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
man	O
comes	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
the	O
shirt	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wyn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
bed-gown	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirt	O
,	O
cloke	O
and	O
gown	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coal-heaver	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
four	O
nights	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Im	O
.	O
131	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Coningham	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
again	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Spenton	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Spenton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
White	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Well-close-square	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barlow	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
the	O
gown	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
husband	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
that	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
December	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
stuff	O
gown	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
shillings	O
upon	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
this	O
gown	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
if	O
her	O
husband	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
use	O
her	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Newson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
china	O
ware	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
sixteen	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
eighteen	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
eighteen	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Tadmarsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
china	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
several	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
uncle	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
confessed	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
resort	O
at	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
china	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
china	O
mentioned	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
plates	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	O
Row	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
some	O
china	O
.	O
My	O
maid	O
bought	O
these	O
of	O
him	O
towards	O
house-keeping	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
him	O
forty-six	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Coombs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Row	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
china	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
forty-six	O
shillings	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
,	O
facing	O
Whitechapel	O
Church	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
half	O
dozen	O
china	O
plates	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
china	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Archibald	O
Fryer	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Godby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Chief	I-pers
,	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sumner	I-pers
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
thickset	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Summer	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Summer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Stepney-fields	B-place
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
two	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
named	O
Maden	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
He	O
rifled	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
person	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Maden	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
bougre	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
serve	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
on	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
laid	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
;	O
then	O
Maden	O
took	O
my	O
coat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
bougre	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
your	O
neck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
assist	O
?	O
Summer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
?	O
Summer	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
words	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
when	O
Maden	O
was	O
pulling	O
my	O
boats	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Pull	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
make	O
no	O
words	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
I	O
met	O
Maden	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
boots	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
stripped	O
himself	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
jacket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Maden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
us	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
this	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
shoes	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
boots	O
on	O
your	O
legs	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
boots	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
by	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Maden	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
disputing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
his	O
boots	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Maden	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
bougre	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
tongue	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
somebody	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
sailor	O
a	O
punch	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Justice	O
Camper	O
admitted	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
against	O
Nicholls	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Leviston	I-pers
being	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
divers	O
robberies	O
.	O
Nicholls	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
laid	O
claim	O
to	O
.	O
One	O
Clarey	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
boots	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
walked	O
three	O
yards	O
with	O
Maden	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M	B-pers
.	I-pers
1st	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
worsted	O
night-cap	O
;	O
value	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
Stepney-fields	B-place
,	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
boots	O
on	O
:	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
blasphemous	O
words	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
rifled	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
ink-bottle	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
nothing	O
again	O
but	O
my	O
knife	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
before	O
Justice	O
Camper	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
Nicholls	O
was	O
delivering	O
this	O
knife	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
sat	O
fronting	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Maden	I-pers
.	O
We	O
got	O
some	O
money	O
from	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
an	O
ink-bottle	O
,	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
or	O
hat	O
.	O
We	O
committed	O
another	O
robbery	O
before	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
robbery	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Horseshoe	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
with	O
Maden	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
his	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Maden	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
knife	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
calld	O
Thomas	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Adam	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
Seymour	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
each	O
known	O
him	O
seventeen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
years	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
parents	O
were	O
honest	O
,	O
reputable	O
people	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M	B-pers
.	I-pers
1st	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
pennies	O
,	O
one	O
six-pence	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
two-pence	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
crystal	O
stone	O
studs	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Ed	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Stepney	B-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
moon-light	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
clapped	O
it	O
across	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
look	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
six-pence	O
.	O
He	O
searched	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
two-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
pennies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol-stone	O
studs	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
many	O
bitter	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
bougre	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
money	O
yet	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
chink	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
some	O
cash	O
here	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Nicholls	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
search	O
me	O
.	O
Nicholls	O
took	O
one	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
plated	O
buckles	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
bid	O
Nicholls	O
take	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Nicholls	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
mine	O
on	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
Nicholls	O
pulled	O
one	O
sleeve	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Nicholls	O
doubled	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
of	O
buck-skin	O
breeches	O
on	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
Nicholls	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
Then	O
Maden	O
said	O
to	O
Nicholls	O
,	O
Deliver	O
me	O
my	O
pistol	O
.	O
Whether	O
they	O
had	O
one	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
blue	O
jackets	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
fifty	O
yards	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
over	O
a	O
bank	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
at	O
Justice	O
Camper	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Maden	I-pers
.	O
We	O
committed	O
another	O
robbery	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
robberies	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
did	O
you	O
commit	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
We	O
committed	O
three	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
taking	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
with	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
taking	O
a	O
coat	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
Nicholls	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
taking	O
any	O
buckles	O
from	O
shoes	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
buckles	O
from	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
leather	O
breeches	O
?	O
Maden	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
came	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
Nicholl	O
's	O
hat	O
.	O
(	O
Holding	O
the	O
bat	O
they	O
changed	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
behaved	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
will	O
find	O
mercy	O
.	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
evidence	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
robbed	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
or	O
a	O
drinking	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Shewring	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Shewring	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
bed-gown	O
and	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
.	O
She	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
late	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
no	O
view	O
of	O
keeping	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
136	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Michells	I-pers
,	O
broker	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
worsted	O
coverlid	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
walnut-tree	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
another	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
painted	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mylam	I-pers
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Wil	O
.	O
Mylam	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
work-shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
search	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
time	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
things	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
on	O
a	O
counter	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Camper	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
his	O
mittimus	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
liberty	O
to	O
leave	O
two	O
looking-glasses	O
and	O
a	O
cover-lid	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
old	O
clothes	O
about	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Old-Gravel-lane	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bedstead	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
there	O
they	O
took	O
and	O
searched	O
me	O
:	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Never	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
was	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Israel	O
Joseph	O
and	O
Betty	B-pers
Lazrous	I-pers
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
137	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Agett	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Agett	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
these	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
upon	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
wholesale	O
and	O
retail	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
Go	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
She	O
understood	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
showed	O
them	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
The	O
magistrate	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
days	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
138	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
walking-cane	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tremlett	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Tremlett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
hard-ware	O
and	O
canes	O
.	O
My	O
goods	O
are	O
all	O
exposed	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phipp	I-pers
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
cane	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phipp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
bookseller	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
cane	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
bend	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
halloed	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
up	O
Catherine-street	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
139	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Divett	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
And	B-pers
.	I-pers
Divett	I-pers
.	O
Whether	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
weeks	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
only	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
lay	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
140	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty-five	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Kennet	O
Dixon	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Galley-key	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
47	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
's	O
agent	O
and	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
water-side	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
warehouse	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
lose	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
;	O
my	O
window	O
looks	O
directly	O
on	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
Pomerania	O
linen	O
,	O
or	O
narrow	O
German	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
detected	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
May	O
and	O
Cothoi	O
,	O
merchants	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Brian	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lodged	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
sober	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
141	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
January	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Jewin-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
party	O
of	O
pleasure	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
's	O
clerk	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
apartment	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
those	O
things	O
missing	O
that	O
are	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
somebody	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
on	O
her	O
legs	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
over	O
my	O
kitchen	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
utterly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
alderman	O
Harley	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
little	O
consequence	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
discharged	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
a	O
particular	O
friend	O
's	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
mother	O
's	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
farther	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
stockings	O
on	O
her	O
legs	O
,	O
two	O
soosee	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
napkins	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
?	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
trying	O
at	O
the	O
padlock	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
and	O
undid	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
confusion	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
wood	O
of	O
my	O
closet	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
at	O
my	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
have	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
but	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shift	O
.	O
She	O
produced	O
one	O
shift	O
and	O
two	O
napkins	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
drawers	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
found	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
she	O
produced	O
.	O
Wil	O
.	O
Windsor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
new	O
cloth	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
other	O
pawnbrokers	O
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
other	O
goods	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
showed	O
her	O
my	O
stockings	O
on	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
re-examined	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
money	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
bundle	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
promised	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
bundle	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
142	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dakley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
deal	O
board	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Ed	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
a	O
building	O
in	O
Fan's-alley	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
there	O
as	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Belas	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
deal	O
board	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
building	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
but	O
three	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Belas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
Pick-ax-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
board	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
this	O
new	O
building	O
in	O
Fan's-alley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
breach	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
board	O
loose	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
out	O
my	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
come	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
boards	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
jobb	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
143	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nineteen	O
fathom	O
of	O
buoy-rope	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
sheet-ropes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
ten	O
fathom	O
of	O
tack-rope	O
,	O
and	O
thirty-six	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
vessel	O
called	O
,	O
The	B-place
Prince	I-place
of	I-place
Brazil	I-place
,	I-place
lying	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
river	I-place
Thames	I-place
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
second	O
mate	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vessel	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
absconded	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
144	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
discharged	O
her	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
this	O
gown	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
now	O
lies	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Virginia-row	O
,	O
Bethnal-green	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
prison	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
since	O
conveyed	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
145	O
,	O
146	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
New	B-place
Brentford	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
my	O
warehouse	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
your	O
warehouse	O
join	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
cross	O
the	O
yard	O
from	O
my	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
joins	O
to	O
my	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
body	O
sleep	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
cheeses	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
seeing	O
mark	O
of	O
feet	O
upon	O
some	O
coals	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
myself	O
;	O
they	O
led	O
to	O
the	O
hole	O
where	O
the	O
jack-weight	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
warehouse	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
marks	O
of	O
feet	O
on	O
some	O
cheeses	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Wild	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
but	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
about	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
before	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
boy	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
with	O
Wild	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
a	O
hole	O
and	O
get	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
nutmegs	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
w	O
ith	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
where	O
Wild	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
cryed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
backwards	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
cheese	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
cut	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
declared	O
his	O
innocence	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
cheese	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
bed-room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Wild	O
charged	O
her	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
find	O
a	O
secret	O
place	O
to	O
put	O
what	O
he	O
brought	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
Wild	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
two	O
cheeses	O
.	O
Stevens	O
junior	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
cheeses	O
.	O
Wild	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Boyce	O
acquitted	O
.	O
147	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Will	I-pers
.	I-pers
Gomur	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
callimanco	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Millas	I-pers
,	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Feild	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
148	O
,	O
149	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Duncken	I-pers
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Carral	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
two	B-place
Turnstiles	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
A	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
home	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
but	O
with	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
word	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
Duncken	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
knocked	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
Carral	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
Duncken	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
full	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamps	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
very	O
few	O
people	O
stirring	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Duncken	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
says	O
you	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Said	O
Duncken	O
,	O
You	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
hat	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
then	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
stop	O
and	O
clear	O
yourself	O
.	O
Then	O
a	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
run	O
or	O
walk	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
a	O
pretty	O
quick	O
pace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
hat	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
This	O
might	O
be	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
minutes	O
from	O
first	O
to	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
and	O
Carral	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
called	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
towards	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
another	O
parish	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
dispute	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threatned	O
to	O
dash	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Duncken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Duncken	O
owned	O
Carral	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Carral	O
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stripped	O
to	O
fight	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
hat	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
coming	O
up	O
Holborn	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
evidence	O
against	O
Duncken	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
clear	O
Duncken	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
also	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Carral	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
together	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Brown	O
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
Chapman	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
both	O
prisoners	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Duncken	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
along	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Carral	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
hat	O
accidentally	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
bold	O
to	O
wear	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
150	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
throwing	O
at	O
oranges	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Southampton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
two	O
women	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
jumped	O
up	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
going	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
watch-chain	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
give	O
a	O
tug	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
my	O
pocket	O
inside	O
cut	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
prevented	O
him	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
women	O
immediately	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
quite	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
?	O
Bush	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
prevented	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
151	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Rail	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Rail	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Rail	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
softly	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
she	O
had	O
take	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
M.	O
Rail	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
stairs	O
;	O
my	O
room	O
is	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
belonging	O
to	O
Ann	O
Mayner	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
caps	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Mayner	I-pers
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mayner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Rail	O
pulled	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
this	O
shirt	O
and	O
cloke	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
caps	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bundle	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
152	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woolham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
December	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Woolham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fox-court	B-place
,	I-place
Southampton-row	I-place
.	O
I	O
let	O
Samuel	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
a	O
lodging	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
sevenight	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
threatned	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Botomly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Purple-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
these	O
sheets	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
eight	O
pence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
M'Cloudy	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
robe	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
clout	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
January	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
154	O
,	O
155	O
,	O
156	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitely	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Walt	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Carry	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
walking	O
cane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Silvester	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Silvester	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
Dyer	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
home	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Peter-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
awake	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
cane	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
two	O
houses	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
second	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
Carey	O
lodged	O
,	O
the	O
Duck	O
,	O
in	O
Duck-lane	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
Whitely	O
.	O
There	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
cane	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
soldier	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
husband	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Rook	O
,	O
the	O
soldier	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
girls	O
?	O
Coyle	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Duck	O
in	O
Duck-lane	O
:	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
a	O
cane	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
them	O
examined	O
before	O
Justice	O
Miller	O
;	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
re-examined	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
reported	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
soldier	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Pye-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bell	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
together	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
,	O
cane	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Whitely	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Carey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
nor	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Whitely	O
and	O
Carey	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Rook	O
acquitted	O
.	O
157	O
,	O
158	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
perukes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
six	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Tatenham	B-place
's	I-place
court	I-place
;	O
he	O
deposed	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
between	O
the	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Memory	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
M'Duff	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
account	O
not	O
being	O
supported	O
by	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Berridge	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
character	O
to	O
corroborate	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Memory	O
,	O
Memory	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Memory	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
100	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Kipling	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
silver	O
castors	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
salt	O
cellars	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
marrow-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
sauce-pans	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Henry	B-pers
Kipling	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Southampton-Row	B-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
confined	O
in	O
my	O
chamber	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
this	O
alarmed	O
me	O
greatly	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
New-Year	O
's	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
got	O
down	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
beauset	O
and	O
closet	O
broke	O
open	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back-room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bureau	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
letters	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kipling	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
on	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
street-door	O
open	O
that	O
was	O
locked	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
I	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
left	O
shut	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
beauset	O
was	O
open	O
:	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
and	O
door	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
found	O
turned	O
upside	O
down	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
table-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
waiter	O
missing	O
from	O
there	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kipling	O
.	O
The	O
plate	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
salts	O
,	O
a	O
pepper-castor	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
table-spoons	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
all	O
missing	O
on	O
New-Year	O
's	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
tumbled	O
about	O
and	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
also	O
a	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
waiter	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
ever	O
found	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crookhall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
this	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
Murphy	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
standing	O
along	O
with	O
Gypsey	O
George	O
,	O
his	O
right	O
name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
,	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
(	O
See	O
Gypsey	O
George	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
589	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Colbeck	I-pers
sold	O
it	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
for	O
twenty-four	O
guineas	O
in	O
Turnmiss-street	O
;	O
Colbeck	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
aquainted	O
with	O
Murphy	O
?	O
Crookhall	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Underwood	O
tried	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nightengall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
repeating	O
table	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
twenty	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-strainers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt	O
cellar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt-shovel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Nightengall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
parish	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
myself	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
,	O
after	O
going	O
round	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
commonly	O
do	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
fast	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
several	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
Mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
advertised	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
confessed	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
sold	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
they	O
get	O
in	O
?	O
Nightengall	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
I	O
found	O
split	O
down	O
from	O
top	O
to	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
beauset	O
and	O
the	O
cupboard	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
clock	O
spring	O
maker	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
five	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
a-jar	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
father	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
lights	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
ransacked	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
my	O
master	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nightengall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
father	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
observed	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crookhall	I-pers
.	O
Colebeck	O
,	O
Murphy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
this	O
house	O
open	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
Colebeck	O
and	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
wrench	O
open	O
the	O
shutter	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
and	O
wrenched	O
open	O
a	O
shutter	O
there	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
hand	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
burner	O
from	O
the	O
lamp	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Murphy	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
;	O
then	O
Colebeck	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
six	O
guineas	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
Murphy	O
some	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
break	O
the	O
shutter	O
and	O
place	O
open	O
with	O
?	O
Crookhall	O
.	O
We	O
broke	O
them	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
all	O
iron	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
this	O
information	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
another	O
indictment	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
North-Audley-street	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Holloway-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
searched	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
informed	O
so	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
with	O
one	O
Bush	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
accomplice	O
of	O
his	O
before	O
;	O
under	O
his	O
pillow	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
)	O
under	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
now	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
was	O
this	O
hand	O
crow	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
inches	O
long	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
claws	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
this	O
stock	O
and	O
two	O
center	O
bits	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bits	O
bigger	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
brass	O
box	O
with	O
tinder	O
,	O
flint	O
and	O
steel	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
my	O
toggs	O
(	O
meaning	O
his	O
clothes	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
buttons	O
were	O
all	O
plate	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
matter	O
of	O
evidence	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
clothes	O
were	O
returned	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
clothes	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
both	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
said	O
to	O
Crookhall	O
,	O
Now	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knows	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nightengall	O
's	O
house	O
being	O
robbed	O
.	O
Crook-hall	O
asked	O
him	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
also	O
had	O
two	O
guineas	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
clock	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nightengall	O
's	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
examined	O
but	O
was	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
He	O
gets	O
his	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
in	O
no	O
visible	O
way	O
of	O
getting	O
his	O
bread	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
swearing	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
carpenter	O
named	O
Jack	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
lay	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
might	O
put	O
my	O
clothes	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
his	O
tools	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stick-maker	O
:	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
Hedge-lane	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
since	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
Crookhall	O
evidence	O
against	O
Bush	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
570	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Catharina	B-pers
Chrastor	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
wires	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Catharina	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Crookhall	O
deposed	O
he	O
,	O
Colebeck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
to	O
corraborate	O
his	O
testimony	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
six-penny	O
worth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
was	O
missing	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sober	O
.	O
Job	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
bason	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
asking	O
people	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
A	O
shoe-black	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
spoon	O
out	O
publickly	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
was	O
quite	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
161	O
,	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linsey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bichards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Gropas	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
January	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Bichards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Well-street	B-place
Shoreditch	I-place
.	O
Linsey	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
for	O
these	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
I	O
have	O
continually	O
missed	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
my	O
dining-room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
to	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
we	O
missed	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
locked	O
into	O
the	O
closet	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
can	O
best	O
give	O
the	O
court	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
happened	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bichards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
daughter	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
locked	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
closet	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
father	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
key-hole	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
Linsey	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
shook	O
it	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
stopped	O
a	O
little	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
key-hole	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
shook	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
flew	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
knocked	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
examined	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
four	O
shillings	O
that	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
twice	O
before	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roaper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Linsey	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
four	O
shillings	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
money	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
two-pence	O
halfpenny	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Linsey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
lock	O
neither	O
the	O
times	O
before	O
not	O
that	O
neither	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
Linsey	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Gropas	O
acquitted	O
.	O
163	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Scott	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
potage	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
is	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winkworth	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
left	O
by	O
contract	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
in	O
Marybone	B-place
parish	O
;	O
he	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
lodgings	O
ready	O
furnished	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
absconded	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
be	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Several	O
articles	O
were	O
found	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Francis	B-pers
Milstead	I-pers
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
M'Donald	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
working	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
164	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Birtue	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Susanna	B-pers
Birtue	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Drury-lane	B-place
play-house	I-place
with	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
cap	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
croud	O
in	O
going	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
two-shilling	O
gallery	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
play-house	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gandle	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Rose	O
passage	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
robbing	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
:	O
the	O
book	O
and	O
cap	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
card	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
card	O
in	O
your	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gandle	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
play-house	O
passage	O
before	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
croud	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Garrick	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
house	O
this	O
being	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
birth-day	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
this	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
apprehension	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
and	O
trod-upon	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
snuff	O
box	O
produced	O
;	O
he	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
box	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
lobby	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
in	O
the	O
play	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
cap	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
and	O
the	O
snuff-box	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Gandle	O
.	O
First	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
play-house	O
with	O
the	O
croud	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Gandle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stoop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
towards	O
the	O
lady	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
Mr.	O
Gandle	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
pockets	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
under	O
a	O
mistake	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
agreeable	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
before	O
all	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
gentlemen	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
man	O
has	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Gandle	O
sent	O
away	O
immediately	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whitehouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cold-Bath-Field	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Norman's-Buildings	O
in	O
Old-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
china	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
Old-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
horn-button	O
maker	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
him	O
once	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cutler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holloway-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
intimately	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
worthy	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
did	O
lett	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
letts	O
small	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
out	O
to	O
use	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
cause	O
to	O
think	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
deals	O
with	O
sailors	O
that	O
come	O
from	O
India	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
132	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
alderman	O
Janssen	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
59	O
,	O
in	O
Bethell	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
72	O
,	O
in	O
Kite	O
's	O
.	O
165	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joaichim	B-pers
Saint	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
containing	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
53	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saxby	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
W.	O
Saxby	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Linen	O
Draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
My	O
warehouse	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
under	O
my	O
dwelling	O
house	O
and	O
kitchen	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
eight	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
people	O
in	O
my	O
warehouse	O
.	O
They	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stole	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
had	O
escaped	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
footboy	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
stamp	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
pattern	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
no	O
other	O
Draper	O
has	O
the	O
pattern	O
but	O
myself	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
real	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
stands	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
is	O
fifty-three	O
shillings	O
and	O
four	O
pence	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Saxby	I-pers
.	O
We	O
opened	O
shop	O
about	O
seven	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
eight	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
halloed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
piece	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Emanuel	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
old	O
clothes	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
fellows	O
run	O
past	O
Mr.	O
Saxby	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
or	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
did	O
swear	O
before	O
Mr.	O
alderman	O
Crosby	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
this	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
such	O
an	O
account	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
?	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
family	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
your	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
family	O
cause	O
you	O
to	O
forget	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
so	O
lately	O
?	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
sometimes	O
.	O
W.	O
Lovit	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
Jew	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
he	O
goes	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
he	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
trod	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
this	O
Emanuel	O
;	O
the	O
Jew	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Saxby	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
The	O
Jew	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sworn	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
declare	O
it	O
as	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
166	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leather	O
shoe	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
pump	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cow-lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Langden	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Snow-hill	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
walking	O
just	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hales	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
pump	O
from	O
the	O
grate	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
walking	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
that	O
pump	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hale	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
with	O
it	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
steps	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
pump	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
that	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
167	O
,	O
168	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Could	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blunder	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
three	O
stockings	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift-sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Tucker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
High-street	I-place
,	O
to	O
assist	O
a	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
brother	O
that	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
club-room	O
,	O
that	O
joins	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
a	O
fire	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ironing	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
ratthng	O
at	O
the	O
sash	O
in	O
Harrow-alley	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
sash	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
earthen	O
dish	O
;	O
the	O
dish	O
was	O
gone	O
also	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
soon	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
dish	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
accountable	O
for	O
them	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
lost	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bruit	I-pers
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
distant	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Aytiffe-street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
immediately	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Blunder	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
Gould	O
were	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
saw	O
the	O
sash	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
169	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
Blackfryars	O
workhouse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
work-house	O
,	O
and	O
trusted	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
people	O
's	O
linen	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
they	O
wear	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
all	O
again	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
170	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Rose	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Gog	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
quart	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Milk-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
:	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
some	O
bottles	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cellar	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
cries	O
about	O
for	O
kitchen-stuff	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
thirteen	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
persisted	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
implored	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
necessitated	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
l	O
tempted	O
her	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
bottles	O
.	O
That	O
door	O
is	O
usually	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
old	O
glass	O
bottles	O
and	O
hare-skins	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
woman	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
