TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Barlow	B-pers
Trecothick	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1770	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
,	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BARLOW	B-pers
TRECOTHICK	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Varnham	I-pers
Hen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Clemt	I-pers
.	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
John	B-pers
Heathfield	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Burbridge	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Willcox	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Day	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lambo	I-pers
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
Jabez	B-pers
Bloxham	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickles	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
George	B-pers
Mussen	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Frisby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
*	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Neild	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
498	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Aaron	B-pers
Cohen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
ounces	O
of	O
nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	B-pers
Burrough	I-pers
,	I-pers
Sealy	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15th	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
499	O
,	O
500	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pap	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt-seller	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
nutmeg	O
grater	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
leather	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
ten	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Goswell-street	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
13th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
ten	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
bag	O
containing	O
about	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
tea-cup	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
nutmeg	O
grater	O
,	O
a	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
salt-seller	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
myself	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
kinsman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bottom	O
hinge	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
was	O
forced	O
off	O
by	O
drawing	O
the	O
nails	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
half	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
the	O
preceding	O
night	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
plate	O
there	O
(	O
the	O
plate	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
the	O
three	O
table	O
spoons	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
J	O
.	O
A.	O
P.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cupboard	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
cup	O
board	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
all	O
this	O
plate	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
excepting	O
the	O
three	O
table	O
spoons	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
nephew	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
sash	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bottom	O
hinge	O
was	O
wrench	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
plate	O
produced	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
uncle	O
and	O
aunt	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
about	O
business	O
;	O
Henry	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
inner	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
plate	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
turnkeys	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
Dickenson	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Bunce	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
Bunce	O
;	O
Dickenson	O
tempted	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
.	O
Dickenson	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Bunce	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
boards	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pistols	O
,	O
three	O
chissels	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pincers	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Wood	O
,	O
Kingman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Bunce	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
pistols	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
horse	O
pistol	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
two	O
slugs	O
,	O
the	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
three	O
chissels	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pincers	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
Bunce	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
pistols	O
and	O
chissels	O
buried	O
under	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
slugs	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Bunce	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
walking	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Darby	O
has	O
an	O
impediment	O
in	O
his	O
speech	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
here	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
Darby	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
;	O
guilty	O
to	O
value	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Bunce	O
acquitted	O
.	O
501	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
M'Mullen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
August	O
11th	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
to	O
the	B-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
raffle	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
won	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
a	O
raffle	O
,	O
afterwards	O
that	O
a	O
cousin	O
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
he	O
there	O
told	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
different	O
stories	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
label	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
insensible	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
holding	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
and	O
take	O
some	O
money	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
penny	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
a	O
roll	O
and	O
butter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
request	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
penny	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
roll	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
502	O
,	O
503	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
bowl	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
made	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
16th	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Taylor	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
504	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
And	O
Ann	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
15th	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
defect	O
in	O
the	O
evidence	O
on	O
this	O
indictment	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
505	O
,	O
506	O
,	O
507	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Guines	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
508	O
,	O
509	O
,	O
510	O
,	O
511	O
,	O
512	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Flanagan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coleby	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lum	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
four	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
soop	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
twelve	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
twenty	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
stand	O
,	O
with	O
five	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
three-prong	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
snuffer-stand	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver-salts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Michael	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather-shoes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
twelve	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
twenty	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stand	O
with	O
five	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
three-prong	O
forks	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
snuffer-stand	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Mackaway	O
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
five	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Burton	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
street	O
robbery	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
322	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Beckford	O
's	O
second	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
Coleby	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
443	O
,	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
513	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
July	O
11th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
514	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
and	O
cotton	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
two	O
stuff	O
petticoats	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Todrigg	I-pers
,	O
July	O
31st	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Todrigg	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
vessel	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
at	O
Cox	B-place
's	I-place
quay	I-place
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
intelligence	O
concerning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
shirts	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
bought	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
also	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
,	O
and	O
buys	O
old	O
silver	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
buckles	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
shirt	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
515	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
inkle	O
bed	O
lace	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
bed-ticks	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bolster	O
,	O
ten	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
thread	O
and	O
worsted	O
carpet	O
,	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
thread	O
and	O
worsted	O
carpet	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholder	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
journeywork	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
worked	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
counterpane	O
and	O
the	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
bed	O
lace	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
missed	O
five	O
table-cloths	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
her	O
:	O
the	O
people	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
window	O
curtains	O
and	O
a	O
bed-tick	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
in	O
search	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
near	O
her	O
lodging	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
service	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
you	O
missed	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
you	O
should	O
suspect	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
plain	O
truth	O
is	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
to	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
counterpane	O
,	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
curtains	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
counterpane	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rochford	O
's	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
curtains	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
's	O
at	O
London	O
Wall	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
corroborated	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
confession	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Floriet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Redcross-street	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
carpet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
-	O
Rochford	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
counterpane	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
David	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
at	O
London	O
Wall	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
carpet	O
,	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
carpet	O
four	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bed	O
tick	O
:	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
confession	O
was	O
drawn	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
516	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quarto	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
book	O
intitled	O
,	O
The	O
New	O
Whole	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
book	O
intitled	O
,	O
A	O
View	O
of	O
Popery	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
book	O
intitled	O
,	O
Hervey	O
's	O
Letters	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
vols	O
.	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
Anthems	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
book	O
intitled	O
,	O
Select	O
Fables	O
of	O
AEsop	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
book	O
intitled	O
,	O
A	O
New	O
Manual	O
of	O
Devotion	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
paper	O
book	O
ruled	O
and	O
bound	O
in	O
vellum	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rivington	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Rivington	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
bookseller	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
church-yard	I-place
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
February	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
he	O
then	O
lived	O
with	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
accordingly	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
for	O
robbing	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
hesitation	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
books	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
books	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confirmed	O
Mr.	O
Rivington	O
's	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
searching	O
his	O
boxes	O
,	O
they	O
observed	O
some	O
new	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rivington	O
,	O
they	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
suspicion	O
they	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
confession	O
was	O
obtained	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
promising	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
517	O
,	O
518	O
,	O
519	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Josephs	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
Reynold-court	O
,	O
Butler's-alley	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
;	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
immediately	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
ma'am	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
step	O
a	O
little	O
lower	O
with	O
me	O
down	O
this	O
passage	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
this	O
street	O
or	O
passage	O
where	O
she	O
stopped	O
me	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
down	O
the	O
passage	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
lower	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
feel	O
about	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
want	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
spoke	O
them	O
words	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
my	O
collar	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
clapped	O
something	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
pistols	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Both	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
for	O
my	O
liberty	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
me	O
farther	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
feel	O
all	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
that	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
clapped	O
something	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
spare	O
my	O
life	O
and	O
take	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
they	O
stript	O
off	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Run	O
for	O
your	O
life	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
and	O
knocked	O
myself	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
ran	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
somebody	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
:	O
window	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
She	O
stood	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
describe	O
them	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
That	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
foot	O
and	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
inches	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
nose	O
and	O
black	O
curled	O
hair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
dress	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
blue	O
jackets	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stout	O
,	O
bold	O
,	O
large	O
featured	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
manly	O
look	O
.	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
answered	O
this	O
description	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
man	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
nothing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
push	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
driving	O
me	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
taken	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
taking	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
prison	O
at	O
White-Chapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
taken	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
following	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
at	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Josephs	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
King	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
Simpson	O
was	O
taken	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Justices	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
a	O
club-feast	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Vine	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
to	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
pretty	O
freely	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
very	O
trifling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
you	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
dancing	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
acquaintances	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
at	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
Rosemary-lane	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
she	O
leaned	O
upon	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sensible	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
lamps	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
sufficient	O
light	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
chat	O
or	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
intercourse	O
with	O
this	O
Ann	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
a	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Consider	O
here	O
are	O
three	O
people	O
's	O
lives	O
at	O
stake	O
upon	O
your	O
single	O
testimony	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
-	O
a	O
late	O
hour	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
-	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
.	O
-	O
Now	O
are	O
you	O
able	O
to	O
recollect	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
certainty	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
challenge	O
them	O
immediately	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
doubt	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
not	O
disguised	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
care	O
never	O
to	O
disguise	O
myself	O
with	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
leaned	O
upon	O
your	O
arm	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
she	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
going	O
any	O
where	O
with	O
that	O
woman	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
greatly	O
surprized	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Greatly	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
would	O
not	O
that	O
surprize	O
take	O
away	O
your	O
recollection	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
surprized	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lay	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
my	O
surprize	O
was	O
more	O
over	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
no	O
house	O
after	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
club	O
but	O
the	O
place	O
you	O
danced	O
at	O
,	O
with	O
no	O
woman	O
nor	O
man	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
apprehension	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Simpson	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
much	O
disordered	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
lamps	O
on	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Haggets	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
house	O
on	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
.	O
She	O
works	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
help	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
forward	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
say	O
,	O
Is	O
the	O
pistol	O
charged	O
?	O
shoot	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
lamp	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
voice	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
shoved	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
lamp	O
from	O
your	O
window	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Joseph	B-pers
Josephs	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
had	O
got	O
somebody	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Simpson	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
say	O
,	O
Spare	O
my	O
life	O
and	O
take	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
blows	O
given	O
very	O
desperate	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Get	O
up	O
and	O
run	O
you	O
bougre	O
,	O
run	O
for	O
your	O
life	O
;	O
his	O
cloaths	O
were	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
window	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
where	O
Joseph	B-pers
Josephs	I-pers
lives	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
something	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Going	O
into	O
sixteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
men	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
altogether	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
to-morrow	O
and	O
hanged	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
mind	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
head	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
draw	O
back	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sadly	O
frightened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
speak	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paget	O
came	O
down	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
acquainted	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Ryan	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
justices	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
your	O
lordship	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
told	O
your	O
story	O
,	O
or	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
after	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
justices	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
ill	O
used	O
and	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
have	O
you	O
talked	O
with	O
about	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Nobody	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Paget	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
quarrel	O
between	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
mother	O
and	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
Simpson	O
lived	O
in	O
your	O
neighbourhood	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
Ryan	O
live	O
any	O
where	O
thereabouts	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
upon	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Josephs	O
live	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
upon	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
sometimes	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
that	O
night	O
again	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
had	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
hard	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
your	O
mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
house	O
on	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
lets	O
cut	O
two-penny	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Paget	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
thief-taker	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Paget	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
mother	O
here	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
lame	O
with	O
a	O
mortification	O
in	O
her	O
leg	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
known	O
Paget	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
your	O
reason	O
for	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
from	O
Simpson	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
sister	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
ill	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
come	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Haggets	O
.	O
She	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
.	O
Paget	O
came	O
down	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Haggets	I-pers
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Mordo	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
nick-name	O
Simpson	O
went	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Josephs	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Near	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
we	O
met	O
Simpson	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
near	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Whitechaple	O
Bail	O
Dock	O
;	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
whilst	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Josephs	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
near	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
tavern	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
justices	O
called	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
waited	O
there	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
justices	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
without	O
.	O
When	O
called	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
in	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
directly	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Ann	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
thought	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
question	O
whether	O
these	O
blackguards	O
would	O
not	O
serve	O
her	O
worse	O
than	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
served	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Pointer	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
the	O
justices	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
,	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
apprehending	O
offenders	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
mentioned	O
in	O
your	O
evidence	O
,	O
being	O
carried	O
down	O
this	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
throwing	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
stripping	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
you	O
any	O
personal	O
injury	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
They	O
beat	O
and	O
bruised	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
my	O
face	O
was	O
swell	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
they	O
kick	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
my	O
sides	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
walk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Haggets	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
mother	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
little	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
taking	O
thieves	O
on	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
search	O
their	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
up	O
in	O
their	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
promiscuously	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
several	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
or	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
Haggets	O
give	O
you	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
saw	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
beat	O
and	O
abuse	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Joseph	B-pers
Josephs	I-pers
carried	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Joseph	B-pers
Josephs	I-pers
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
first	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Haggets	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mordo	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Simpson	O
's	O
nick-name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
cast	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Hagget	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
why	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
something	O
wrong	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
secretes	O
herself	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
Wright	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
beat	O
very	O
badly	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
almost	O
blinded	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
industrious	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
Paget	O
keeps	O
a	O
disorderly	O
house	O
for	O
girls	O
.	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
un-born	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
bread	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Josephs	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
court	O
in	O
Welch-street	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Emanuel	I-pers
,	O
porter	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Simpson	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
thirteen	O
years	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Eleanor	I-pers
,	O
four	O
.	O
Josephs	O
called	O
Catherine	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eve	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Abraham	B-pers
Solomons	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
child-hood	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Solomons	I-pers
two	O
years	O
.	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Mordecai	I-pers
,	O
eighteen	O
months	O
.	O
Judea	O
Jacobs	O
,	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
And	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Emanuel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
youth	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
520	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brine	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brind	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
gally	O
tiles	O
,	O
vale	O
25	O
s.	O
forty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
iron	O
casements	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Totterel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Kent	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
miller	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Poplar	B-place
parish	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
had	O
three	O
mills	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
house	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
these	O
tiles	O
fall	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
chimney	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Totterel	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kent	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some-body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
walk	O
a-cross	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
returned	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
resist	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
surrendered	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
sixteen	O
chimney	O
tiles	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
broken	O
knife	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
excuse	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
for	O
being	O
there	O
?	O
Sayer	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
leather	O
aprons	O
on	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
overcome	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
there	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
two	O
brother	O
labourers	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
wind-mill	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
lie	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
rest	O
myself	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
waked	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
pleased	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
521	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
shag	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17th	O
.	O
*	O
Daniel	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
at	O
harvest	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
master	O
,	O
in	O
Hindon	O
parish	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
room	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
522	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilfully	O
and	O
maliciously	O
shooting	O
off	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
gun-powder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
bullet	O
,	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Creighton	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
August	O
11th	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Creighton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
him	O
talking	O
how	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
warrants	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
property	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Creighton	O
.	O
I	O
meant	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
watch	O
till	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
my	O
property	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
property	O
?	O
Creighton	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
attempt	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
here	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brain	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
flew	O
open	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
knocker	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
steps	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
stept	O
up	O
the	O
first	O
step	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
clapt	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
snap	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
jumpt	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
the	O
pistol	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
snap	O
'd	O
the	O
pistol	O
at	O
my	O
forehead	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
blood	O
ran	O
down	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
if	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
there	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
his	O
lanthorn	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
bed-stead	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
sometime	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
discharged	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
home	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
snap	O
'd	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
cock	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
snap	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
missed	O
fire	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
passage	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
yards	O
wide	O
;	O
his	O
house	O
is	O
opposite	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
within	O
about	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
directed	O
it	O
at	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
whistling	O
of	O
the	O
ball	O
or	O
slug	O
go	O
by	O
my	O
ear	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
when	O
a	O
ball	O
passes	O
you	O
?	O
Creighton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
among	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Penman	I-pers
with	O
a	O
load	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
alive	O
still	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
powder	O
and	O
ball	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
pistol	O
had	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
blown	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
good	O
slugs	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
turn	O
your	O
wife	O
's	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Creighton	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
turn	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
two	O
watchmen	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
released	O
from	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Penman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stand	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
pointed	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
pistol	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
jealous	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
because	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
wife	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
a	O
grudge	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
threatened	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
help	O
him	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
523	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Dolland	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bowling-Green	O
house	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hurst	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
between	O
the	O
Boot	O
and	O
the	O
Foundling	B-place
hospital	I-place
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
three-pence	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
behind	O
the	O
Museum	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
confirmed	O
his	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dolland	I-pers
,	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
Austin	O
Hall	O
,	O
his	O
father-in-law	O
,	O
Mary	O
Hall	O
,	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Dolland	I-pers
,	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
524	O
,	O
525	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ralph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty-seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
callico	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
twenty-nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Hunter	O
sloop	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
on	O
a	O
navigable	O
river	O
,	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
captain	O
of	O
the	O
Hunter	B-place
sloop	I-place
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
off	O
Execution-dock	O
ready	O
for	O
sailing	O
,	O
having	O
received	O
her	O
loding	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ashore	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
board	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
bales	O
cut	O
open	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
526	O
,	O
527	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Isaac	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Law	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
528	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
edged	O
with	O
yellow	O
tinsel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Nevil	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Waller	O
Agutar	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
silk-weavers	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
goods	O
(	O
producing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milliner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
different	O
sorts	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
modes	O
,	O
persians	O
,	O
sarsenets	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
In	O
May	O
he	O
brought	O
several	O
things	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
out	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
gauze	O
and	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
of	O
this	O
ribbon	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
ribbon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
ribbon	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Rothwell	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
ribbon	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
made	O
by	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
gauze	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
robbed	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
fifteen	O
hundred	O
or	O
two	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
on	O
their	O
account	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
ample	O
confession	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
us	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
favourable	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
touch	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
transport	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
us	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
seventy	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
dealing	O
with	O
this	O
lady	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
517	O
.	O
529	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
530	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
,	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
531	O
,	O
532	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dangerfield	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tattum	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
wine	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
glass	O
tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
glass	O
cruet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
four	O
earthen	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
earthen	O
sugar	O
dish	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
earthen	O
sugar	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
earthen	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
earthen	O
oval	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
earthen	O
mugs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
four	O
earthen	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
earthen	O
baking	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
earthen	O
butter	O
boats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
earthen	O
mustard	O
pot	O
,	O
twenty	O
four	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
four	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
eleven	O
half	O
pint	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Dangerfield	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
months	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
he	O
detected	O
him	O
stealing	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
warehouse	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
Tattum	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
hostler	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
received	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
searched	O
Tattum	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
that	O
Tattum	O
confessed	O
be	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Baldwin	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bacchus	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
corroborated	O
this	O
account	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
confession	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
was	O
voluntary	O
.	O
Dangerfield	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
promised	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
evidence	O
of	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
sold	O
Tattum	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
-	O
Beard	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Caxton	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
lived	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Tattum	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
eighteen	O
months	O
;	O
Crispin	B-pers
Caldwell	I-pers
,	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Dangerford	O
guilty	O
T	O
.	O
Tattum	O
T.	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
532	O
,	O
533	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
soup	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
seven	O
silver	O
German	O
sweet-meat	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
seven	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
five	O
other	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
lamp	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Swainston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dweling-house	O
.	O
~	O
William	B-pers
Swainston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-square	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Taylor	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
only	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
square	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
from	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
myself	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
only	O
catched	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
several	O
men	O
as	O
witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
signs	O
of	O
any	O
person	O
having	O
got	O
in	O
over	O
the	O
garden-wall	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
fresh	O
cleaned	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
a	O
foot	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
two-chairs	O
that	O
had	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
room	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
trap-door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
boxes	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
trap-door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
signs	O
of	O
any	O
person	O
's	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
accused	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
along	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
into	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
535	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Morgan	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
September	O
3	O
.	O
~	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
place	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Savoy	O
barracks	O
.	O
I	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
forced	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ring	O
and	O
buttons	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
whilst	O
on	O
guard	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
park	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
child	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
never	O
give	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
she	O
waited	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
at	O
the	O
barracks	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
and	O
beer	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
received	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
keep	O
till	O
we	O
are	O
married	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
buttons	O
and	O
ring	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
her	O
sake	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chiswick	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
soldier	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
barracks	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
publick-house	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
the	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
smile	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
six-pence	O
a	O
smile	O
.	O
She	O
smiled	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
536	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
butter	O
boats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
eleven	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Susannah	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick-house	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
place	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
adjoining	O
to	O
that	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
537	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Windon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
days	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
girl	O
by	O
the	O
Foundling	O
hospital	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
gowns	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
brother	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
brother	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Worthy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
-	O
Lawrence	B-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
;	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
capuchin	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
deposed	O
were	O
pawned	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
538	O
,	O
539	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Page	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hartwell	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
at	O
Charing-cross	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Hartwell	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
clear	O
lawn	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
they	O
bought	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
sight	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
stolen	O
something	O
;	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Justice	O
Keeling	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
lawn	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Carroll	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
between	O
Carroll	O
's	O
legs	O
.	O
Page	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Carroll	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
cap	O
.	O
Carroll	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Page	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
that	O
piece	O
.	O
Page	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Carroll	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
540	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horsenayle	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10th	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horsenayle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Marquis	B-place
of	I-place
Granby	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Mile-end	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Rumford	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
of	O
Oldford	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
Larkham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horsenayle	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
horse	O
ready	O
for	O
him	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
him	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
bay	O
horse	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
Woodford-bridge	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Chigwell	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
at	O
Chigwell	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
laid	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
drinking	O
milk	O
punch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
bay	O
horse	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
trotted	O
him	O
about	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
him	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
four	O
guineas	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
bid	O
nothing	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Horsenayle	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
this	O
horse	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
horse	O
this	O
witness	O
sent	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
you	O
had	O
lett	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Horsenayle	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
?	O
Horsenayle	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
hire	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
hired	O
a	O
postchaise	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
at	O
Wanstead	O
.	O
He	O
chose	O
I	O
should	O
side	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
rode	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
blinds	O
up	O
.	O
Larkham	O
had	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
stole	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
pursue	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
between	O
Mile-end	O
Turnpike	O
and	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horsenayle	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
541	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pounds	O
of	O
moist	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
7th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
542	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
August	O
21st	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Grocer	O
and	O
Oil-man	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
lived	O
in	O
Bowling-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
be	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
50	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
130	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
their	O
servant	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
master	O
sent	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
oil	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
back	O
yard	O
into	O
a	O
ware-house	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
bottle	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
that	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
leads	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
herself	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
unlocked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
money	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
searched	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
in	O
the	O
soil	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
searched	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
something	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
they	O
sold	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Redford	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
-	O
Lloyd	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
tried	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
opened	O
the	O
close	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
easily	O
pick	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
or	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Robert	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
and	O
-	O
Ford	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
two	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
The	O
notes	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
some	O
tea-chest	O
as	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
upon	O
the	O
last	O
trial	O
,	O
no	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
seven	O
bushels	O
of	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
salt	O
on	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
account	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
in	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
543	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
banjan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bulmer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
August	O
15th	O
.	O
~	O
Mr.	O
Bulmer	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Prescot-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman	I-place
's	I-place
fields	I-place
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
waked	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
supposing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
arose	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
Robinson	O
called	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Snegg	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bulmer	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
hung	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
bed-chamber	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
offered	O
her	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
again	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Bulmer	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
chamber	O
window	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
her	O
husband	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
chamber	O
window	O
fastened	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Bulmer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
Paget	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
begged	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Robinson	O
's	O
account	O
was	O
different	O
now	O
to	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Slan	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bulmer	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Catherine	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
had	O
a	O
great	O
difficulty	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
to	O
determine	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
did	O
not	O
mention	O
a	O
word	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
confessed	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
be	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
John	O
Bernard	O
,	O
Elizabeth	O
Barwick	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
544	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
,	O
August	O
27th	O
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
545	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
August	O
7th	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
546	O
,	O
547	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hogan	I-pers
,	O
August	O
9th	O
.	O
~	O
William	B-pers
Hogan	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
driver	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
his	O
partner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Ball	I-place
Cross	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
sitting	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
joined	O
their	O
company	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
offered	O
to	O
treat	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
accordingly	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
treating	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
be	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
to	O
treat	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
the	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
one	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Meadows	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
his	O
guinea	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
548	O
,	O
549	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Langford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-one	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
August	O
8th	O
.	O
~	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
who	O
drives	O
cattle	O
from	O
Wales	O
to	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
that	O
two	O
women	O
picked	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
his	O
country-man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Wales	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
country-man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Langford	O
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
;	O
that	O
Langford	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
nine	O
guineas	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
shillings	O
when	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
be	O
awaked	O
he	O
found	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
he	O
accordingly	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
searching	O
Langford	O
found	O
a	O
thirty	O
six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
described	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
two	O
dents	O
under	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Robert	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Langford	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
nothing	O
being	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Langford	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
two	O
women	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
me	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
he	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
by	O
the	O
wife	O
's	O
order	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Dun	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
defence	O
.	O
Langford	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Dun	O
acquitted	O
.	O
550	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
O'Dearsley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty-one	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
eleven	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
six	O
check	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
check	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gimp	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
O'Dearsley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
551	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
hatt	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spittle	B-place
fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
all	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
the	O
windows	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Delany	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
window	O
shutters	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Simpson	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
last	O
tried	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
more	O
money	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Simpson	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
.	O
(	O
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
whilst	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
whilst	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
frighted	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
