TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	O
BICKFORD	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Perrott	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
James	O
Eyre	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Place	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
James	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
George	B-pers
Ribright	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
William	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ely	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Jewson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Deliverance	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Eastham	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Claridge	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
James	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Franklin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Grinstead	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Eayers	I-pers
.	O
337	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
1	O
b.	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
338	O
,	O
339	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
M'Donald	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
yards	O
of	O
poplin	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
womens	O
silk	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
264	O
half-pence	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Wil	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
High-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
bolted	O
my	O
back	O
door	O
with	O
two	O
bolts	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
fast	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
window	O
throwed	O
up	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
violence	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
pallisadoes	O
on	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
over	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
and	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
go	O
out	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
burean	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
laying	O
about	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dobrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
cloaks	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
named	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Madison	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
7	O
s.	O
on	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Madison	I-pers
?	O
Dobrey	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
but	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
named	O
Cooley	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
corraborate	O
what	O
he	O
might	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
340	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
Couldter	I-pers
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
Couldter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Parliament-street	B-place
,	I-place
next	I-place
door	I-place
to	I-place
the	I-place
Sun	I-place
Tavern	I-place
.	O
Our	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
the	O
17th	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
All	O
was	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
forced	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
300	O
l.	O
worth	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
discover	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
that	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
by	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
chissel	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
strong	O
iron	O
chissel	O
.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Mathewson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
money	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
new	O
ones	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
these	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
exchange	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
straps	O
being	O
too	O
long	O
at	O
the	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
sewed	O
the	O
holes	O
up	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
buckles	O
back	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
buckle	O
tighter	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
with	O
Mathewson	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
change	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
this	O
pair	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
Mathewson	O
took	O
up	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
almost	O
beyond	O
a	O
doubt	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
your	O
new	O
breeches	O
on	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Mathewson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
breeches	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
tight	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
to	O
change	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
chose	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
them	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Banbury-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
one	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
chissel	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
much	O
like	O
this	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
iron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
return	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
he	O
of	O
?	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
is	O
ago	O
?	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
gaol	O
about	O
sixteen	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
you	O
delivered	O
the	O
chissel	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Fanning	I-pers
.	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
somebody	O
else	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
stones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
book	O
printer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
in	O
this	O
?	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
upon	O
another	O
robbery	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
these	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
James	O
Fanning	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
evidence	O
's	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
breeches	O
were	O
too	O
tight	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
exchange	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
341	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Christopher	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Chomley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
large	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
caster	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
salt-sellers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
small	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
soup-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
twelve	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Catherine	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Chomley	O
,	O
in	O
Buckingham-street	B-place
,	I-place
York-buildings	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
five	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
door	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
about	O
70	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
plate	O
.	O
(	O
Naming	O
them	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Kenney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Fanning	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Freebody	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
Fanning	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
pitched	O
upon	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
streets	O
of	O
Hungerford-Market	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
that	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
area	O
gate	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
disturbed	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Fanning	O
that	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
through	O
a	O
court	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
returning	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
was	O
transacted	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
hardly	O
find	O
our	O
way	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Fanning	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Bird	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
towards	O
Redfordbury	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
all	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
beyond	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
away	O
all	O
one	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
but	O
Fanning	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
Fanning	O
gave	O
me	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
or	O
18	O
d.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
share	O
had	O
the	O
prisoners	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Graham	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
plate	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
or	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
Fanning	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Fanning	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
chiefly	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
were	O
you	O
at	O
when	O
Graham	O
bought	O
the	O
plate	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
Fanning	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
Bird	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
Graham	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
Bird	O
's	O
lodging	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
An	O
old	O
woman	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
;	O
Fanning	O
went	O
in	O
directly	O
;	O
Bird	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
first	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
window	O
broke	O
before	O
you	O
ran	O
away	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
.	O
Note	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
contradicted	O
almost	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Galaway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Kenney	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
concerning	O
Major	O
Yorke	B-pers
's	O
plate	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
Richards	O
and	O
Bird	O
with	O
breaking	O
Mrs.	O
Chomley	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
and	O
selling	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Kenney	B-pers
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Dunn	O
,	O
Miller	O
,	O
Crookhall	O
,	O
and	O
Graham	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
221	O
,	O
222	O
,	O
223	O
,	O
224	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Session	O
Paper	O
.	O
342	O
,	O
343	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wragg	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
inkle	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen-sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
four	O
cheque	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wragg	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Mrs.	O
Wragg	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wragg	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Playhouse-yard	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
very	O
near	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
farther	O
from	O
home	O
than	O
cross	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
All	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
left	O
a	O
candle	O
alight	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Wil	O
.	O
Little	O
.	O
Keeling	O
has	O
pledged	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
pledged	O
this	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Wragg	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Girdler	O
to	O
search	O
Little	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
there	O
in	O
Keeling	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
Keeling	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
impeach	O
fourteen	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
punish	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
chandler's-shop	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wragg	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
small	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
stand	O
betwixt	O
that	O
door	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wragg	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
Keeling	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Sutton	O
.	O
As	O
night	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Keeling	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
sight	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
bought	O
a	O
candle	O
of	O
me	O
that	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wragg	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
Mrs.	O
Wragg	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wragg	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
ten	O
minutes	O
since	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
burnt	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
down	O
.	O
Keeling	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
a	O
master	O
builder	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
;	O
coming	O
from	O
there	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
lives	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
I	O
known	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
Fountain	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
keeps	O
a	O
horse	O
in	O
Playhouse-yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
.	O
Keeling	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Fountain	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
344	O
,	O
345.	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Andrews	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
vessel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Savil	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
maid-servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
evidence	O
,	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
attend	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
346	O
,	O
347	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
and	O
Wil	B-pers
.	I-pers
Jackson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Wil	O
.	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
near	B-place
Shackle-well	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Castle	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
saw	O
Gregory	O
upon	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
taking	O
some	O
lead	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
house	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
helping	O
it	O
upon	O
Jackson	O
's	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
these	O
men	O
have	O
been	O
robbing	O
that	O
house	O
of	O
lead	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Bradshaw	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
among	O
some	O
shavings	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
348	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Bisset	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pannel	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pannel	O
saw	O
from	O
a	O
building	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
of	O
my	O
seeing	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
saw	O
advertised	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
saw	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cordey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
saw	O
.	O
My	O
apprentice	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
carpenter	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
can	O
it	O
be	O
your	O
saw	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
named	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
apprentice	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Ross	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
three	O
years	O
in	O
Panton-street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
349	O
,	O
350	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
thickset	O
frocks	O
,	O
five	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Michael	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Michael	B-pers
Glyn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
parish	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
padlock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
just	O
at	O
nine	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
wrenched	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
lock	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Mentioning	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
coats	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
Ann	B-pers
Chamber	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
gully	O
hole	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Ann	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
?	O
Glyn	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Glyn	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
and	O
my	O
husband	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Creamer	O
the	O
prisoner	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
M	O
Creamer	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
against	O
your	O
husband	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
351	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
sauce-boat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
but	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cook	O
talking	O
to	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
telling	O
him	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
but	O
two	O
boats	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
brought	O
three	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
cook	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
stop	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
cook	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
sauce-boat	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
the	O
cook	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
credit	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
352	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Craft	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
settling	O
an	O
account	O
with	O
a	O
merchant	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Mosely	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
had	O
your	O
pocket	O
picked	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
turning	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
take	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Oswald	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
behind	O
this	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
turning	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
fling	O
cut	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
Tower-ditch	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
held	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bristow	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
353	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stocking	O
knit	O
breeches	O
,	O
lined	O
with	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
and	I-pers
William	I-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Wil	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
Samuel	O
are	O
partners	O
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
slop	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Lower	B-place
Thames-street	I-place
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
them	O
for	O
us	O
of	O
our	O
materials	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
last	O
Friday	O
sevenight	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
not	O
observing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Perry	O
sent	O
for	O
us	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
.	O
One	O
Catherine	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
brought	O
these	O
breeches	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
other	O
things	O
brought	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
sent	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
near	O
at	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
these	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
not	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
Do	O
you	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
-	O
Are	O
they	O
not	O
his	O
goods	O
?	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
his	O
goods	O
to	O
sale	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
them	O
both	O
he	O
would	O
transport	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
for	O
making	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
354	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Cha	O
.	O
Eyre	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
my	O
servant	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
one	O
wanted	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
shewed	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
crest	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
the	O
bowl	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
fresh	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
miss	O
a	O
spoon	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
washed	O
them	O
up	O
but	O
just	O
now	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
produced	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
crests	O
agree	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
takes	O
the	O
ashes	O
away	O
from	O
gentlemens	O
chambers	O
for	O
the	O
cinders	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
sometimes	O
to	O
assist	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
besides	O
her	O
victuals	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
washed	O
up	O
this	O
spoon	O
,	O
with	O
seven	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
up	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
water	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
She	O
first	O
sent	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
:	O
upon	O
my	O
examining	O
her	O
pretty	O
closely	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
among	O
some	O
cinders	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
fresh	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
pull	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
stood	O
to	O
it	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
where	O
she	O
did	O
business	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
and	O
enquire	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
committed	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Wil	O
.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
proposed	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
.	O
She	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
among	O
the	O
ashes	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
bent	O
twice	O
double	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
opening	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
ashes	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
broke	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
ashes	O
are	O
always	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
she	O
removed	O
none	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
M'Daniel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
containing	O
eight	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hastenny	I-pers
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hastenny	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
Birmingham	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
inn	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
in	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
to	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
awake	O
?	O
Hastenny	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
about	O
five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
three	O
?	O
Hastenny	O
.	O
The	O
hostler	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
awaked	O
I	O
missed	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
counted	O
my	O
money	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
a	O
grocer	O
eight	O
guineas	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
purse	O
out	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
another	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
purse	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
knowing	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
hostler	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
nor	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
three	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
we	O
found	O
anew	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
for	O
farther	O
examination	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
brought	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
purse	O
or	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Coventry	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
double	O
purse	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
parts	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cow-Cross	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
others	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
soon	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
one	O
guinea	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lay	O
down	O
four	O
guineas	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
her	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
removing	O
a	O
table	O
,	O
a	O
drawer	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
sell	O
out	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
this	O
yellow	O
bag	O
.	O
Rich	O
.	O
Maylin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
This	O
bag	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
ever	O
seeing	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
acknowledge	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
bag	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
up-stairs	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
.	O
We	O
lay	O
all	O
night	O
together	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bag	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
357	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Green	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Venmore	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Venmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
1	I-place
,	I-place
Upper	I-place
Thames	I-place
street	I-place
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
Easter-eve	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
that	O
afternoon	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
neither	O
I	O
nor	O
my	O
wife	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
she	O
absconded	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
found	O
her	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
358	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Wil	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty	O
bushels	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
principal	O
evidence	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
His	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
five	O
and	O
three-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
168	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Bowers	O
,	O
Newman	O
,	O
and	O
Kellyborn	O
were	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
fact	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
See	O
their	O
trial	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
300	O
,	O
301	O
,	O
302	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Session	O
Paper	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Rogan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Peter	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dowles	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
100	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
each	O
piece	O
containing	O
36	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
Wil	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Oakley-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bethnal	I-place
Green	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
on	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Looms	O
!	O
Looms	O
!	O
Looms	O
!	O
Broad	O
Looms	O
!	O
Blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
get	O
your	O
pistols	O
ready	O
!	O
Get	O
your	O
pistols	O
ready	O
!	O
They	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
right-hand	O
door	O
and	O
a	O
left-hand	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
the	O
right-hand	O
door	O
leads	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
breaking	O
that	O
door	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Blast	O
you	O
,	O
Cox	O
says	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
left-hand	O
door	O
.	O
Cox	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
open	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
turned	O
evidence	O
against	O
Perrin	O
.	O
They	O
began	O
blasting	O
their	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
Open	O
the	O
door	O
!	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
they	O
burst	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
the	O
chairs	O
and	O
table	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
immediately	O
on	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
cutlass	O
.	O
He	O
with	O
the	O
cutlass	O
was	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glimmer	O
of	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
arise	O
.	O
He	O
with	O
the	O
cutlass	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
blows	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
below	O
my	O
elbow	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
shoulder	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
elbow	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
as	O
I	O
raised	O
myself	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
kept	O
with	O
his	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
They	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
them	O
,	O
blow	O
their	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
they	O
stir	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
four	O
10	O
l.	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
20	O
l.	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
in	O
half-pence	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
seventy	O
guineas	O
worth	O
of	O
ribbon	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
an	O
hundred	O
pieces	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Perrin	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
to	O
Dublin	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
stands	O
indicted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Since	O
that	O
I	O
advertised	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Coventry	O
.	O
I	O
particularly	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
voice	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
formerly	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
odd	O
voice	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
know	O
it	O
from	O
an	O
hundred	O
people	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
by	O
three	O
names	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
covered	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
pillow	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
voice	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
cried	O
,	O
Looms	O
,	O
blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
!	O
My	O
wife	O
is	O
ill	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
;	O
Cox	O
is	O
at	O
Coventry	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
life-time	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Coventry	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Mahony	I-pers
,	O
as	O
a	O
cutter	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
,	O
Bailey	O
,	O
goes	O
by	O
two	O
names	O
.	O
He	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
formerly	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
foot	O
guards	O
,	O
and	O
deserted	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
changed	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
name	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
whipped	O
round	O
Spitalfields-market	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
whipped	O
myself	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
by	O
false	O
evidence	O
being	O
given	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Perrin	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
403	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
No	O
.	O
587	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dufore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Rich	B-pers
.	I-pers
Book	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
362	O
,	O
363	O
,	O
364	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Delaforce	I-pers
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
gun	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
inn	I-place
in	I-place
Pierpool-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
my	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
then	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
my	O
little	O
dog	O
made	O
a	O
prodigious	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
listened	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
my	O
dog	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
shut	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
disturbed	O
the	O
dog	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
dog	O
made	O
more	O
noise	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
bureau	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
several	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
unbolted	O
and	O
left	O
open	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
three	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
had	O
been	O
my	O
post-chaise-boy	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
way	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Merlin	O
's	O
Cave	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Spaw	O
Fields	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
water-works	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
and	O
peeped	O
over	O
the	O
banmisters	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gun	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
surprized	O
almost	O
every	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
two	O
double	O
doors	O
were	O
both	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
whispering	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
was	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
lay	O
above	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
The	O
thieves	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
bank	O
by	O
the	O
water-works	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
down	O
towards	O
Bagnigge	O
Wells	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
two	O
went	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
There	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
whip	O
your	O
clothes	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
pursue	O
them	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dress	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
gun	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
behind	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Bunhill-Row	O
.	O
Just	O
by	O
the	O
French	O
pest-house	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
carpenter	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
friend	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
four	O
men	O
robbing	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Bunhill-Row	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
the	O
carpenter	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Finsbury	O
watch-house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Delaforce	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
examined	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
bundle	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
meaning	O
his	O
brother	O
.	O
His	O
brother	O
answered	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
your	O
worship	O
will	O
look	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
mark	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
advertise	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
Tom	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
's	O
,	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
Freeman	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
ready	O
to	O
break	O
his	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
his	O
son	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
was	O
asked	O
about	O
a	O
gun	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
you	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
keepers	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
hand-cuffs	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Foundling	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
by	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
water-pipes	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
's	O
(	O
The	O
counterpane	O
,	O
table-cloths	O
and	O
gun	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
has	O
my	O
name	O
printed	O
at	O
length	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
chap	O
with	O
this	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
two	O
watchman	O
,	O
Wilson	O
and	O
Welch	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
asunder	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
;	O
Delasorce	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
brothers	O
cross	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
two	O
fellows	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
people	O
;	O
it	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
stronger	O
suspicion	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Featherstone-street	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
biggest	O
brother	O
.	O
-	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
two	O
brother	O
and	O
Freeman	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clayton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
given	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
twenty	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoner	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Delaforce	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
and	O
his	O
brother	O
about	O
ten	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
Delaforce	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
got	O
over	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
an	O
alley	O
.	O
They	O
threw	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
things	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
gun	O
under	O
a	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
in	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
followed	O
us	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
boy	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
till	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
fellow	O
and	O
me	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Grays-Inn-lane	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
bundles	O
and	O
the	O
fowling-piece	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
together	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
drinking	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
Delaforce	O
knowing	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
fowling-piece	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
pipe	O
;	O
that	O
gentleman	O
followed	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
gun	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Bunhill-row	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
Monday	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
drinking	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
evidence	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
this	O
bundle	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
followed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
house	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
his	O
house	O
is	O
.	O
Delaforce	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
evidence	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
drinking	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
down	O
Grays-Inn-lane	O
together	O
.	O
Freeman	O
wanted	O
more	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
say	O
that	O
Delaforce	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
that	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bunyan	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Harp-alley	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
;	O
Delaforce	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
served	O
four	O
years	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Bunyan	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Bunyan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Delaforce	O
eleven	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
in-law	O
Mr.	O
Bunyan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Delaforce	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
liking	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
lad	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
with	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
365	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-court	B-place
,	I-place
facing	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
,	O
the	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
tea-kettle	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rotchford	O
's	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ratchford	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
full	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sawyer	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
of	O
the	O
smallpox	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
and	O
owned	O
a	O
quarter	O
's	O
rent	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
366	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Tapp	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
wine	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
wooden	O
ink-stands	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Caffe	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
367	O
,	O
368	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayre	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
leather	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayre	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Black-Bull	B-place
,	I-place
Gray's-Inn-Lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
awaked	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
somebody	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
horses	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
coming	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
screw	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
sash	O
down	O
was	O
forced	O
up	O
and	O
bent	O
:	O
my	O
bar	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
halfpence	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
six	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
leather	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
table	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
but	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
trunk	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
crow	O
about	O
fourteen	O
inches	O
long	O
.	O
The	O
trunk	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
and	O
Harry	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
agreed	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
founder	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
or	O
Tudor	O
were	O
bred	O
to	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
all	O
round	O
Paddington	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
disturbed	O
us	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Underwood	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shutter	O
with	O
this	O
crow	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
lifted	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
the	O
crows	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
They	O
belonged	O
to	O
us	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
joined	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
lifted	O
Wharton	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shut	O
the	O
shutter	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
break	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Tudor	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
generally	O
leave	O
one	O
without	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
shilling	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
silver	O
;	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
child-bed	O
linen	O
;	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
work	O
basket	O
;	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
leather	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
that	O
to	O
Underwood	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
new	O
cloth	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
trunk	O
within	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
also	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
Underwood	O
had	O
the	O
child-bed	O
linen	O
:	O
some	O
she	O
gave	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
The	O
spoons	O
Underwood	O
sold	O
to	O
Lyons	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
us	O
a	O
shilling	O
each	O
;	O
the	O
halfpence	O
we	O
shared	O
among	O
us	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
had	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
before	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
Mills	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
her	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
,	O
No	O
522	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
520	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
tried	O
Nos	O
.	O
316	O
,	O
504	O
,	O
and	O
129	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
)	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
such	O
a	O
crow	O
as	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
looking	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Underwood	O
never	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
.	O
Underwood	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
buying	O
stolen	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
owed	O
for	O
about	O
seven	O
pints	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
Newgate	O
lodge	O
and	O
for	O
my	O
lodging	O
:	O
who	O
should	O
be	O
there	O
but	O
Pagget	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
not	O
drink	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
love	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
any	O
blood-sucking	O
men	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
by	O
next	O
sessions	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
:	O
who	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
but	O
this	O
Pagget	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
?	O
you	O
are	O
wanted	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
wants	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
:	O
then	O
in	O
came	O
three	O
more	O
:	O
said	O
Pagget	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
Justice	O
Camper	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliff-hig	O
hway	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
myself	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
hearing	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
compter	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
by	O
this	O
Pagget	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
had	O
up	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
villainous	O
rascal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Pearce	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
perjuring	O
yourself	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
by	O
a	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Pearce	O
in	O
getting	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Wharton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
has	O
got	O
himself	O
into	O
some	O
hobble	O
,	O
and	O
wants	O
to	O
swear	O
our	O
lives	O
away	O
.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Underwood	O
used	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
hobbled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
clear	O
myself	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mollison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
cap	O
made	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
81.	O
a	O
coral	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Mollison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
mathematical	O
instrument	O
maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
my	O
window	O
shutters	O
were	O
wrenched	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
put	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
beaufet	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
parlour	O
fronting	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
we	O
lay	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
asleep	O
.	O
She	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
.	O
He	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
her	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
into	O
that	O
parlour	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
bureau	O
and	O
book-case	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
shut	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
capped	O
,	O
and	O
jewel	O
,	O
a	O
coral	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee-buckles	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chissel	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Mary	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
so	O
slight	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
Underwood	O
,	O
Wharton	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lister	I-pers
+	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
round	O
Black-Fryars	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Underwood	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
his	O
window	O
shutters	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
lifted	O
me	O
in	O
over	O
the	O
iron	O
rails	O
.	O
+	O
See	O
Lister	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
489	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
117	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
rails	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
We	O
reached	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
with	O
our	O
iron	O
crows	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
Underwood	O
handed	O
Wharton	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
Underwood	O
put	O
the	O
shutters	O
to	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
hung	O
over	O
the	O
chimney-piece	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
in	O
a	O
metal	O
box	O
;	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
coral	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee-buckles	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
beaufet	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
our	O
escape	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
,	O
a	O
chissel	O
and	O
pistol	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
ran	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
Underwood	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opening	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
first	O
;	O
Wharton	O
said	O
something	O
about	O
d	O
-	O
ning	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
said	O
hey	O
hey	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
dropped	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mollison	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mollison	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
burnt	O
paper	O
lying	O
.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Underwood	O
brought	O
us	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
coral	O
,	O
and	O
knee-buckles	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pagget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
only	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoners	O
up	O
upon	O
Pearce	O
's	O
information	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
See	O
Underwood	O
tried	O
twice	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
234	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
New-Road	B-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
till	O
pretty	O
near	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
(	O
as	O
my	O
business	O
runs	O
pretty	O
late	O
on	O
Saturday	O
nights	O
)	O
then	O
I	O
bolted	O
and	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
my	O
window	O
shutters	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
:	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
window	O
light	O
breaking	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
glass	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
judged	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
attacked	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
If	O
my	O
house	O
is	O
attacked	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
better	O
wait	O
till	O
they	O
enter	O
,	O
for	O
may	O
be	O
they	O
may	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
attack	O
us	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
so	O
properly	O
prepared	O
.	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
stand	O
it	O
till	O
they	O
entered	O
:	O
we	O
retired	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
picking	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
frame	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
falling	O
down	O
piece	O
after	O
piece	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
my	O
musket	O
and	O
sword	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
my	O
piece	O
loaded	O
sometime	O
;	O
as	O
several	O
houses	O
near	O
me	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
lately	O
,	O
I	O
judged	O
they	O
would	O
soon	O
attack	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
little	O
fresh	O
powder	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
rubbed	O
the	O
hammer	O
.	O
After	O
watching	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
pieces	O
of	O
glass	O
still	O
falling	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
brushing	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
judged	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
entering	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
watching	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
parlour	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
inward	O
door	O
to	O
prevent	O
people	O
from	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
double	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
hear	O
him	O
move	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
passage	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
presented	O
my	O
piece	O
low	O
to	O
hit	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
snapped	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
finding	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
pricked	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
sword	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
fan	O
light	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
informed	O
me	O
afterwards	O
they	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
feet	O
foremost	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
had	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
finding	O
my	O
sword	O
had	O
pricked	O
him	O
,	O
surrendered	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
he	O
knew	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
and	O
called	O
murder	O
,	O
thieves	O
!	O
and	O
some	O
neighbours	O
came	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Gosset	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
another	O
neighbour	O
:	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
a	O
light	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
tinder	O
in	O
it	O
)	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
gang	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
or	O
upwards	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
they	O
resorted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
upon	O
Salt-petre-bank	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
many	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
gang	O
that	O
attacked	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
four	O
besides	O
himself	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Gosset	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stockbridge	O
were	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
these	O
questions	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
answers	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
given	O
him	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
might	O
have	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
too	O
powerful	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gosset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
murder	O
and	O
thieves	O
cried	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
some	O
neighbour	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
with	O
my	O
hanger	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
asked	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gosset	O
:	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stockbridge	O
,	O
another	O
neighbour	O
,	O
came	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
musket	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stockbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Andrews	O
call	O
thieves	O
and	O
murder	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
musket	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gosset	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
hold	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
information	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
upon	O
oath	O
.	O
(	O
Holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
read	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
standing	O
at	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
get	O
over	O
this	O
door	O
and	O
open	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
They	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
against	O
my	O
inclination	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
information	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
lifted	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
named	O
Jones	O
and	O
Moody	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
stranger	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
named	O
James	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
a	O
gardener	O
.	O
369	O
,	O
370	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pint	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
dollars	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Archibald	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
Archibald	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
(	O
Which	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
)	O
I	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
warehouseman	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
supposing	O
something	O
wrong	O
had	O
happened	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
street-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
feet	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suppose	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Cook	O
,	O
with	O
somebody	O
else	O
,	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
desk	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
judged	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
large	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
scissars	O
which	O
lay	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
screws	O
were	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
still	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
desk	O
and	O
papers	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
every	O
drawer	O
of	O
papers	O
had	O
been	O
tumbled	O
over	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
bank	O
notes	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
notes	O
of	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
guineas	O
and	O
half	O
guineas	O
.	O
I-missed	O
forty	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
two	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
dollars	O
,	O
a	O
remarkable	O
medal	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
from	O
the	O
kitcken	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
tea-spoons	O
.	O
Cook	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
apprentice	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
)	O
:	O
then	O
my	O
two	O
apprentices	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
eleven	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
when	O
Cook	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
a	O
person	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
person	O
went	O
by	O
different	O
names	O
:	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
took	O
the	O
gold	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
half-guineas	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
eleven	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
boy	O
Lee	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Brown-Bear	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
the	O
lining	O
and	O
crown	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
medal	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
medal	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
fresh	O
as	O
when	O
struck	O
.	O
Heley	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
cuss	O
of	O
his	O
sleeve	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
half-crown	O
piece	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
ascertain	O
the	O
dollar	O
,	O
Heley	O
.	O
Lee	O
had	O
pleaded	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
against	O
Cook	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
,	O
provided	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
admitted	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
mentioned	O
:	O
Sir	O
John	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Cook	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
.	O
Cook	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
hid	O
some	O
things	O
at	O
Somerset	O
stairs	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
Lee	O
at	O
the	O
Kings	O
and	O
Key	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
along	O
with	O
Cook	O
.	O
Andrew	O
Hill	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
Lee	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
facing	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
concealing	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sitting	O
facing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
moved	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
eighteen	O
half-crowns	O
and	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Lee	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
suspected	O
you	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Lee	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
put	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Lee	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
business	O
falling	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
aunt	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
up	O
and	O
bequeathed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
her	O
sake	O
.	O
They	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saved	O
up	O
them	O
half-crowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
relations	O
and	O
friends	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
Cook	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Cook	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
his	O
parents	O
in	O
a	O
pretty	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
good	O
education	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
this	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
371	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hiles	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
Minories	O
along	O
the	B-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
shade	O
of	O
the	O
lamps	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
somebody	O
running	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
dodging	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
tug	O
at	O
my	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
running	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
A	O
watchman	O
hearing	O
me	O
,	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
let	O
fall	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
:	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rian	I-pers
.	O
Rian	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
His	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
372	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pfluyer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
five	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
thirteen-and-six-penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
six-and-nine-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
four-and-six-pence	O
,	O
a	O
Prussian	O
six-dollar	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
crown	O
,	O
two	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
six	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
so	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little-carter-lane	B-place
.	O
My	O
servant	O
,	O
named	O
John	B-pers
Oberhimer	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
desk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
street	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
fast	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chain	O
up	O
cross	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
my	O
compting-house	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
a	O
French	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
a	O
Prussian	O
six-dollar	O
,	O
two	O
English	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
seven	O
pounds	O
in	O
loose	O
silver	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
half	O
moidores	O
,	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
five-and-three-pences	O
,	O
two	O
four-and-six-pences	O
;	O
here	O
were	O
some	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
three	O
shilling	O
papers	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
large	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
with	O
a	O
crest-upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
letter	O
W	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
bowls	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
not	O
marked	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
pair	O
of	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
dog-skin	O
shoes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
late	O
fellow-servants	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
dispatched	O
my	O
servants	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
pairs	O
of	O
shoes	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
metal	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
my	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
tongs	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
a	O
girl	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
in	O
Wentworth-street	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
between	O
Whitechapel	O
and	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
suspected	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
or	O
the	O
purse	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
we	O
found	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
French	O
crown	O
that	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
having	O
a	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
two	O
English	O
crowns	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
a	O
Prussian	O
six-dollar	O
,	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
six	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
,	O
a	O
four	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
three	O
thirteen	O
and	O
six-pences	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
concealed	O
under	O
his	O
ham	O
,	O
and	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
loose	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
people	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
desk	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
desk	O
open	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
sugar-chopper	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
such	O
an	O
instrument	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
farther	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
desk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
he	O
speak	O
English	O
?	O
(	O
He	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
understand	O
English	O
.	O
)	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
English	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
servant	O
where	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
that	O
night	O
this	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
properly	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
fasten	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
place	O
is	O
just	O
opposite	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
breeches	O
on	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
much	O
of	O
his	O
size	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
the	O
Rotation	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
