TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Barlow	O
Trecothick	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1770	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BARLOW	O
TRECOTHICK	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BATHURST	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeants	O
~	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
||	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
||	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Haller	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hiller	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Burnley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Copland	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bushell	I-pers
Jasper	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
Jabez	B-pers
Read	I-pers
George	B-pers
Beardsell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
Edmond	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
*	O
William	B-pers
Fillingham	I-pers
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
Coverdale	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Langser	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
*	O
James	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Buttery	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fillingham	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
.	O
627	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Abraham	B-pers
Maltah	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
opium	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
cassia	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Labrow	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
~	O
John	B-pers
Labrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
druggist	O
and	O
chemist	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
1769	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
cassia	O
and	O
some	O
opium	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
credit	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
agreed	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
made	O
out	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
for	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
his	O
customer	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
bill	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
man	O
aside	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
bill	O
or	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Howson	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Labrow	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
1769	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
customer	O
for	O
some	O
cassia	O
and	O
opium	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
send	O
the	O
goods	O
without	O
his	O
man	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
words	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Fore-street	O
or	O
Moorfields	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
goods	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
carry	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
porter	O
that	O
should	O
take	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Still-yard	O
or	O
Still-alley	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
goods	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
several	O
public	O
houses	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
wait	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
him	O
upon	O
credit	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
628	O
,	O
629	O
,	O
630	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clinch	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
M'Daniel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Viguers	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	O
Viguers	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel	B-place
Court	I-place
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
M'Daniel	O
and	O
Clinch	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
lawns	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
several	O
pieces	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
less	O
than	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
time	O
Brown	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
not	O
they	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
She	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
genting	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lawn	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
near	O
York-street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Clinch	O
and	O
M'Daniel	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
lawn	O
.	O
They	O
bought	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
very	O
narrowly	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
joined	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
together	O
towards	O
Russel-court	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Viguers	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
M'Daniel	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
M'Daniel	O
and	O
Clinch	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
but	O
Brown	O
was	O
very	O
abusive	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
me	O
for	O
detaining	O
her	O
.	O
M'Daniel	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Viguers	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lawn	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Clinch	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
genting	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
disputed	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
18	O
d.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
17	O
d.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
cut	O
off	O
when	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
M'Daniel	O
called	O
Jane	B-pers
Finney	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Carrell	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Clinch	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
Alice	B-pers
Medway	I-pers
ten	O
months	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Money	I-pers
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Clinch	O
and	O
M'Daniel	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Brown	O
acquitted	O
.	O
631	O
,	O
632	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Conroy	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
one	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
laced	O
with	O
silver	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
eleven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
hanger	O
with	O
an	O
ivory	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
mahogany	O
watch	O
stand	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pinch	O
beck	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Hemmings	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Air-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
apartments	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
back	O
rooms	O
that	O
look	O
into	O
Air-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
till	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
rooms	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gun	B-pers
Tavern	I-pers
,	O
where	O
I	O
supped	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
My	O
landlord	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
into	O
the	O
lock	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
turn	O
;	O
upon	O
trying	O
the	O
latch	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
unlocked	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
inside	O
shutters	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
opened	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
this	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
trod	O
upon	O
some	O
cloaths	O
;	O
this	O
frightened	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hemmings	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
my	O
trunk	O
open	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
stolen	O
four	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
mazarine	O
blue	O
,	O
trimmed	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
the	O
lace	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
drawer	O
open	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
eleven	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
chimney-piece	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
stand	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
stood	O
;	O
from	O
my	O
bed-room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
inner	O
room	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
gold	O
watches	O
that	O
hung	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hanger	O
that	O
hung	O
near	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
Henley	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
me	O
open	O
my	O
trunk	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
Conroy	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
had	O
hand-bills	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
advertized	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
till	O
about	O
eight	O
days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Henley	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
spur	O
leathers	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
Henley	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
still	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
Garridge	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Henley	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
upon	O
my	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
Conroy	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
information	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
the	O
evening	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
these	O
watches	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Garridge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
Solomans	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
They	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Henley	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Mitre	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
accordingly	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Boar	O
,	O
in	O
Camomile-street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Henley	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
plain	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
7	O
l.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
six	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
because	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
)	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
then	O
Conroy	O
pulled	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
six	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
asked	O
them	O
such	O
a	O
question	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
laced	O
cloaths	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
watches	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Pagett	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
Pagett	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
watches	O
again	O
;	O
Henly	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
Paget	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
Conroy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pagett	I-pers
.	O
Garridge	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
in	O
Camomile-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
Garridge	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
your	O
prisoners	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
they	O
started	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
chairs	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Henly	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
plain	O
gold	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
without	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
;	O
Garridge	O
had	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Garridge	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
said	O
Pagett	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
Henly	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Garridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
complete	O
with	O
both	O
the	O
cases	O
?	O
Garridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Paget	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
Garridge	O
says	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
Henly	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
mistaken	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
stand	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
watch	O
in	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
Conroy	O
said	O
if	O
Sir	O
John	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Conroy	O
said	O
Henly	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
any	O
theft	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
watches	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
Henley	O
some	O
money	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bruin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
mazarine	O
blue	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
of	O
Conroy	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
very	O
broken	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
two	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
supposed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
foreigner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
difficulty	O
to	O
understand	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
34	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
something	O
like	O
Dyane	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
somewhere	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
you	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
Bruin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
green	O
and	O
the	O
black	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
somebody	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Conroy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
goods	O
of	O
one	O
Rossinberg	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
large	O
parcel	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
boots	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
cheap	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
cash	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
31	O
l.	O
my	O
bill	O
came	O
to	O
25	O
l.	O
Henly	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Conroy	O
owed	O
me	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
lock	O
to	O
the	O
garret	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
watch	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Rosenberg	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Conroy	O
called	O
George	B-pers
Plan	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
Charles	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
about	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
Humphry	O
Bright	O
eighteen	O
months	O
;	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
five	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Henly	O
called	O
Samuel	B-pers
Beecroft	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
months	O
;	O
and	O
-	O
Morgan	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
633	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
moist	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Sept	O
,	O
28	O
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
634	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
moist	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
635	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Grace	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
636	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brookfield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
637	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Child	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Ricks	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
638	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
August	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
639	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
stuff	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
August	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
640	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Albemarle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
cutting-room	O
,	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
men	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
several	O
people	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
searched	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
sash	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
brought	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
my	O
brother	O
Guest	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
great	O
coat	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother-in-law	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
within	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Guest	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
opposite	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
haste	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bring	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linen	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
rather	O
to	O
tumble	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
fell	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
scattering	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
linen	O
bundled	O
up	O
?	O
Esther	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
villain	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
your	O
husband	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
window	O
?	O
Esther	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
brought	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
your	O
linen	O
at	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
?	O
Esther	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
there	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
window	O
was	O
shut	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
away	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
us	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Guest	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Guest	O
tell	O
her	O
husband	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alston	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Alston	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
playing	O
a	O
game	O
of	O
skittles	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Bowl	O
and	O
Pin	O
in	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Albemarle-street	O
,	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
men	O
were	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
rushed	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
jump	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
good	O
many	O
people	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
that	O
villain	O
to	O
gaol	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
gaol	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
me	O
?	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
house	O
;	O
how	O
then	O
could	O
she	O
have	O
her	O
eyes	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
my	O
trial	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
322	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turners	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
burglaries	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Beckford	O
's	O
second	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
508	O
,	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
641	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
red	O
harrateen	O
curtains	O
,	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
boiler	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
Deed	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
642	O
,	O
643	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Gustavus	I-pers
White	I-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Drummond	O
deposed	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
Hungerford	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Cockspur-street	B-place
he	O
saw	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
soldiers	O
;	O
that	O
Houghton	O
ran	O
up	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
was	O
near	O
pushing	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
asking	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Houghton	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
scuffle	O
ensued	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
fray	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
hat	O
sell	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
some	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
undoubtedly	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
assault	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
amount	O
to	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
644	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Nuttall	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hebborn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
645	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Royston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
~	O
Charles	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Cow	B-place
Cross	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
1769	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
pewter-pot	O
at	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
mug	O
's	O
being	O
empty	O
,	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
men	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Sharp	O
's	O
Alley	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Franklin	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pint	O
mug	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Oct	O
,	O
14th	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
eleven	O
pennyweights	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pint	O
mug	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
rubbish	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
at	O
Paul	O
's	O
Wharf	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
bottom	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
marks	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
fire	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
mug	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Franklin	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Franklin	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
the	O
mug	O
?	O
Franklin	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1769	O
.	O
Foreman	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
That	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
mug	O
laid	O
is	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
646	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Flowers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
~	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
when	O
the	O
press	O
broke	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
ship	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
drank	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Harwich	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
nine	O
days	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
vessel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
sailor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Smith	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
hours	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
keep	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
647	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Langrish	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langrish	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
staff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
September	O
28	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
648	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pillowcases	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
camblet	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
white	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
October	O
2	O
.	O
~	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Stepney	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
:	O
about	O
six	O
she	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
by	O
Maria	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Eccles	O
stopped	O
her	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
shop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
Eccles	I-pers
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
drying	O
upon	O
a	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
649	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
cable-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
lace	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodridge	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
17	O
.	O
~	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodridge	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Half	O
Moon	O
in	O
Purpool-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
at	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Half	O
Moon	O
in	O
Purpool-lane	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
cardinal	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
her	O
shoes	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
extremely	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
-	O
Sandwich	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
B	O
.	O
650	O
,	O
651	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
yellow	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
jug	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
11	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
September	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	O
Campasses	O
.	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Wild-street	I-place
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
after	O
my	O
wife	O
(	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
when	O
a	O
messenger	O
came	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
which	O
continued	O
ten	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
yellow	O
purse	O
,	O
containing	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
jug	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea-tong	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-strainer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
coral	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
yellow	O
purse	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
certain	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
mark	O
of	O
violence	O
upon	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
received	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
their	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Preston	B-pers
I	O
found	O
some	O
silver	O
and	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
I	O
and	O
pretty	O
certain	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
In	O
Preston	O
's	O
pocket	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
trial	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
locks	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
lost	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Preston	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
upon	O
himself	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
acquit	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tawney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
housekeeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Reynolds	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
soon	O
;	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
at	O
one	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
and	O
some	O
shrub	O
then	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
quickly	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
entered	O
into	O
conversation	O
about	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
that	O
passage	O
leads	O
to	O
Wild	O
Court	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
into	O
this	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
farther	O
is	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
connection	O
another	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
kitchen	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
lodgers	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
some	O
robbery	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
greatly	O
frightened	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
that	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
ruined	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
and	O
purses	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
talked	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
persuade	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
alarmed	O
,	O
for	O
probably	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
soon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Tumbler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
,	O
stood	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
do	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
seven	O
minutes	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
something	O
bulged	O
out	O
in	O
Preston	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
his	O
hands	O
over	O
both	O
his	O
pockets	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Preston	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Preston	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Tumbler	O
was	O
confirmed	O
in	O
this	O
account	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goddin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
who	O
added	O
that	O
they	O
ran	O
through	O
a	O
gateway	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
Duke	O
street	O
.	O
Henry	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blundell	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
wine-vault	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Preston	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Blundell	O
's	O
vaults	O
in	O
an	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
Preston	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
confused	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
two	O
sixpences	O
instead	O
of	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
above	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
both	O
their	O
pockets	O
stuck	O
out	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Preston	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Wild	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
through	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
house	O
into	O
Wild	O
Court	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
through	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
passage-again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blundell	O
's	O
wine-vaults	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
we	O
parted	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Reynold	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Tawney	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
eat	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
dined	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Clare	O
Market	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
back	O
Mrs.	O
Tawney	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
down	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
to	O
dinner	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
bed	O
chamber	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
sat	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
a	O
lodger	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Tawney	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
's	O
chamber	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
beer	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tawney	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
chair-woman	O
cleaning	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
Tawney	O
.	O
I	O
cleaned	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
only	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
nobody	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
652	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Frances	B-pers
Duffing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
ask	O
a	O
silversmith	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
sister	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
(	O
producing	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
spoon	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
arms	O
was	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
without	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
mistook	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
wrong	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
advertise	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
was	O
informed	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
matter	O
in	O
hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
silver	O
scullery	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
this	O
spoon	O
in	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
Lady	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
;	O
I	O
was	O
her	O
laundry	O
maid	O
.	O
I	O
married	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
ladyship	O
's	O
service	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
This	O
bit	O
of	O
spoon	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
by	O
one	O
Harris	O
,	O
a	O
dustman	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
lived	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ironing	O
brought	O
in	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
found	O
among	O
the	O
dust	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
e	O
a	O
to-knot	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
a	O
shelf	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
lay	O
till	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
653	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
pinchbeck	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
their	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Maynard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
christened	O
?	O
*	O
*	O
Barnet	O
is	O
a	O
black	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
christened	O
in	O
1766	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
Dock	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Holborn	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Two	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Squire	O
's	O
son	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
High	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
Holborn	B-place
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Blue	O
Posts	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
'Squire	O
's	O
son	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
'Squire	O
's	O
son	O
proposed	O
to	O
toss	O
up	O
for	O
some	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
toss	O
up	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
toss	O
up	O
for	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
tossing	O
up	O
for	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
'Squire	O
's	O
son	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
watch	O
for	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
'Squire	O
's	O
son	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
you	O
seven	O
guineas	O
for	O
your	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
'Squire	O
's	O
son	O
tossed	O
up	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
Almost	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
crossed	O
the	O
pavement	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
safe	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
'Squire	O
's	O
son	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
buckles	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
buckles	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
find	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
pewter	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
halves	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
tossed	O
up	O
and	O
them	O
?	O
Barnet	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
concern	O
with	O
the	O
tossing	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
staked	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
against	O
the	O
'Squire	O
's	O
son	O
;	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
contented	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
Henry	O
Street	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
one	O
year	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Yeoman	I-pers
three	O
years	O
;	O
Charles	B-pers
Powley	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
five	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
654	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Margaret	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
robe	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
and	O
woollen	O
check	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lovekin	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
655	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
four	O
and	O
sixpenny	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
September	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
at	O
two	O
houses	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
third	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
got	O
admittance	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
another	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Edges	I-pers
.	O
Bet	O
Green	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
court	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
houses	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
admitted	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
got	O
admitted	O
at	O
Catherine	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
's	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
liked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
best	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
*	O
Catherine	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Green	O
wanted	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lay	O
asleep	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
First	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
then	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
piece	O
.	O
We	O
divided	O
them	O
money	O
among	O
us	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Catherine	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
tried	O
No	O
.	O
586.	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
656	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
657	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Connolly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
658.	O
(	O
L	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Swinsfords	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
659	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
660	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
a	O
worsted	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8th	O
.	O
~	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
She	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
proposed	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
lodgings	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
a	O
watchman	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
alarmed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
clothes	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Salter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
hair-dresser	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
tester	O
of	O
her	O
bed	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
so	O
rich	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
He	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
661	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Grayhurst	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Mary	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grayhurst	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
striped	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Theard	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
662	O
,	O
663	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Landakin	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
and	O
cotton	O
counter	O
pane	O
,	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
sleeve	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
skirt	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
nightgown	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
and	O
worsted	O
chair	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
joins	O
to	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
a	O
passage	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
water-side	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
padlock	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
left	O
hanging	O
upon	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
with	O
a	O
padlock	O
.	O
I	O
get	O
up	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
hung	O
loose	O
upon	O
the	O
staple	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
White-Conduit-House	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bingly	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
White-Conduit-House	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
women	O
coming	O
towards	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
supposed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
they	O
passed	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
farther	O
and	O
of	O
White-Conduit-Fields	O
they	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
under	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sack	O
.	O
We	O
called	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
secured	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
account	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
bundle	O
containing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
his	O
the	O
indictments	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
stones	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Chapman	O
called	O
George	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dodfied	I-pers
,	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
-	O
Creed	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
,	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Spleen	I-pers
,	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Landakin	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Walding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purdue	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
664	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
lined	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
October	O
21st	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
.	O
My	O
trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
stolen	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
my	O
trunk	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
I	O
misled	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
at	O
Beconsfield	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
all	O
out	O
but	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
She	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
hat	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
's	O
.	O
-	O
Meredith	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
be	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
150	O
miles	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nobody	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
665	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Carry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
inside	O
watch	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
five	O
gold	O
outside	O
chased	O
watch	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
two	O
plain	O
gold	O
outside	O
watch	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
twelve	O
silver	O
inside	O
watch	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
twelve	O
silver	O
outside	O
watch	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
stone	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Burr	I-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Burr	I-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
apprentice	O
and	O
the	O
maidservant	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
trap-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
windows	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
where	O
my	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
work	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
the	O
drawer	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
maid-servant	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
proper	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wellden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
Church	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
,	O
on	O
dress	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
bundle	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Maid-stone	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
gaol	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Donnelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burr	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
When	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
for	O
an	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
plumbs	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
for	O
an	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
apples	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
children	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
parlour-door	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
applies	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
damned	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
rest	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
a	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
gone	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
tea-things	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
tea-spoons	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
by	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
led	O
to	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
?	O
Donnelly	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
errand-boy	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hooke	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
New-street	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
watch-case	O
,	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
coin	O
;	O
the	O
ring	O
had	O
a	O
stone	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
that	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
?	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Welldon	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
this	O
to	O
a	O
fellow-servant	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
that	O
now	O
lives	O
with	O
a	O
surgeon	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Burr	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
she	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
later	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
George	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
;	O
we	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Maid-stone	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
gone	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
666	O
,	O
667	O
,	O
668	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
M'Ginnis	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
six	O
and	O
nine-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
forty-eight	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
~	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
669	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenner	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
670	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Caroll	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ellstol	I-pers
,	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
~	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
671	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1st	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Abington	B-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
village	O
near	O
Northampton	O
.	O
I	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gelding	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
traced	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
Wellingborough	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
ride	O
by	O
upon	O
my	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
horse	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Langhorne	O
's	O
Repository	O
,	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
gelding	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
switch	O
tail	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
his	O
tail	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
horse	O
you	O
saw	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Langhorne	O
's	O
was	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
him	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
the	O
Boar	O
and	O
Castle	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
hostler	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
had	O
sweated	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
sweat	O
seemed	O
rather	O
dried	O
on	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
only	O
from	O
Barnet	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
walked	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Highgate	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
horse	O
a	O
food	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
farrier	O
's	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
shod	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
tail	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
switch	O
tail	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cut	O
it	O
shorter	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
my	O
advice	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
grass	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
hurt	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
borrowed	O
a	O
halter	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Repository	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
tail	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
mean	O
he	O
trimmed	O
it	O
?	O
Thorne	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
cut	O
off	O
about	O
two	O
inches	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farrier	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
horse	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
at	O
the	O
Boar	O
and	O
Castle	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
feet	O
were	O
ragged	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
ugly	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
right	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
grass	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
sell	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
shoe	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
so	O
busy	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langhorne	O
's	O
Repository	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
chop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
so	O
cheap	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
something	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
himself	O
proposed	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
grass	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
His	O
feet	O
were	O
ragged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
his	O
eyes	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
something	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
under	O
price	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Ibbetson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langhorne	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
third	O
instant	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
our	O
yard	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
signed	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
price	O
fixed	O
upon	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dow	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Wood	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
owned	O
Mr.	O
Langhorne	O
he	O
believed	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
send	O
another	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
horses	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
stand	O
at	O
a	O
stable	O
in	O
Bartholemew	O
Close	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deal	O
in	O
horses	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
horses	O
that	O
were	O
sick	O
or	O
lame	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
about	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
lost	O
money	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Ibbetson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
yard	O
pretty	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
affidavit	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
appear	O
as	O
little	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
detect	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
sale	O
,	O
Dow	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
after	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Whilst	O
we	O
were	O
asking	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
observed	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
as	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
desired	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
constable	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
Dow	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
delivered	O
him	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Ibbetson	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Dow	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
delivered	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Dow	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
down	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
talked	O
very	O
sensibly	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Langhorne	O
's	O
clerk	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
Dow	O
;	O
Dow	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
house	O
near	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
out	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
ledge	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
name	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
very	O
readily	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
Dow	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
What	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Dow	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
lie	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
write	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
faint	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
bench	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sick	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
rap	O
for	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
for	O
six	O
guineas	O
or	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
inn	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
went	O
very	O
willingly	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
pointing	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
by	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Charter-house	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
rough	O
cart	O
gelding	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
him	O
myself	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
get	O
a	O
guinea	O
or	O
two	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
horse	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
bad	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
weak	O
eyes	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
eight	O
guineas	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
for	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
my	O
watch	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
men	O
here	O
that	O
saw	O
me	O
buy	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
proof	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
misrepresented	O
what	O
passed	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
Dow	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
delivered	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
hostler	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
horse	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
horse	O
of	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Dartford	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Wood	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
creditable	O
countryman	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
;	O
when	O
his	O
feet	O
were	O
shod	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
good	O
feet	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Dow	O
's	O
advice	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
grass	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
expensive	O
feeding	O
him	O
to	O
grass	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
half	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
above	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
out	O
a	O
note	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Wood	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
many	O
horses	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
stable	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wood	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
horse	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Dow	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Apron	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
who	O
deals	O
in	O
horses	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
rider	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
twelve-months	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
a	O
horse	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
lusty	O
country	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
cart	O
gelding	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
six	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
of	O
making	O
the	O
bargain	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Barton	O
and	O
the	O
farmer	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
dealt	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Barton	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
eight	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
six	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
his	O
watch	O
for	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
man	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
from	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
from	O
Dartford	O
in	O
Kent	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Highgate	O
for	O
some	O
cash	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
disappointed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
sell	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dunball	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
at	O
Enfield	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
recollect	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
?	O
Dunball	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
remembered	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
first	O
applied	O
to	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
?	O
Dunball	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
particularly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
?	O
Dunball	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
come	O
frequently	O
and	O
lie	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
Dunball	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
acquainted	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
married	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
rheumatism	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farrier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Close	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
buying	O
horses	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
horses	O
in	O
out	O
yard	O
at	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Tide	I-pers
;	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
and	O
bought	O
another	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little-Britain	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
3d	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
or	O
afternoon	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
by	O
the	O
rank	O
it	O
stands	O
in	O
in	O
your	O
book	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
;	O
we	O
book	O
them	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
Close	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
dealing	O
in	O
horses	O
?	O
Adams	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
left	O
two	O
horses	O
in	O
my	O
stable	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
boar	O
ded	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
and	O
sold	O
horses	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
fifteen	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
from	O
his	O
masters	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thorpe	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
?	O
Thorpe	O
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
Thorpe	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dow	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
for	O
selling	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Dow	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
expences	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
the	O
jury	O
had	O
given	O
their	O
verdict	O
,	O
Solomon	O
Wood	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
informed	O
the	O
court	O
that	O
Aaron	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
had	O
confessed	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
fore-sworn	O
himself	O
:	O
Brown	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
totally	O
false	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
court	O
commanded	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
67	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
reduced	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
devil	O
,	O
not	O
regarding	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
nature	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
certain	O
beast	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
she	O
ass	O
,	O
did	O
lay	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
she	O
ass	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Bartholomew	O
did	O
carnally	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
she	O
ass	O
that	O
detestable	O
and	O
abominable	O
crime	O
,	O
(	O
among	O
Christians	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
)	O
called	O
buggery	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wickedly	O
,	O
and	O
diabolically	O
against	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
nature	O
,	O
did	O
perpetrate	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Healey	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
22d	O
October	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
came	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Healey	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
man	O
buggering	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
asses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
at	O
the	O
White-horse	O
ale-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White-horse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Piggot	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
beastly	O
action	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
acquainted	O
Mrs.	O
Lovell	O
,	O
whom	O
the	O
ass	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
opinion	O
,	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Lovell	O
is	O
very	O
ancient	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
manage	O
her	O
business	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Lovell	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
must	O
suffer	O
the	O
law	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
accordingly	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
pails	O
by	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Healey	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Pigott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Pigott	I-pers
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Scott	B-pers
the	O
brick-maker	O
near	O
Knight's-bridge	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
Knight's-bridge	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
lane	O
that	O
is	O
called	O
Yeoman	B-place
's	I-place
Row	I-place
;	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Row	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
tubs	O
standing	O
with	O
yeast	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
yoke	O
lay	O
across	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
ten	O
to	O
one	O
but	O
the	O
baker	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
brick	O
kiln	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
get	O
girls	O
there	O
sometimes	O
:	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
brick	O
kiln	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
pastime	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
brick	O
kiln	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
instrument	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
ass	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
;	O
he	O
drew	O
out	O
his	O
-	O
and	O
wiped	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
a	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pushed	O
off	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
pails	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
creeping	O
under	O
the	O
hedge	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
coming	O
for	O
his	O
pails	O
;	O
I	O
hollowed	O
out	O
,	O
here	O
he	O
comes	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
people	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
ass	O
?	O
Pigott	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
shed	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
give	O
the	O
asses	O
hay	O
;	O
the	O
shed	O
is	O
tiled	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
the	O
front	O
part	O
is	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
is	O
pailed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
off	O
was	O
the	O
brick	O
kiln	O
that	O
you	O
stood	O
upon	O
?	O
Pigott	O
.	O
Forty	O
,	O
or	O
fifty	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
;	O
the	O
brick	O
kiln	O
fronts	O
the	O
shed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
ass	O
stand	O
?	O
Pigott	O
.	O
Her	O
head	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
manager	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
foal	O
by	O
her	O
side	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
farther	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
shed	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
sideways	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
you	O
positive	O
that	O
you	O
really	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
her	O
?	O
Pigott	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
shoving	O
at	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
woman	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
till	O
he	O
withdrew	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
pails	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Pigott	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
then	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
his	O
pails	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Cow	O
and	O
Calves	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
home	O
and	O
changed	O
his	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
