TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Barlow	O
Trecothick	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1770	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BARLOW	B-pers
TRECOTHICK	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Anstead	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Bevis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
Lewis	B-pers
M'Cullock	O
John	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hardman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Schreiber	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Bedder	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
John	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Deaton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
James	B-pers
Wilce	I-pers
Solomon	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hundley	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
417	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Probit	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
cocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
21st	O
.	O
++	O
Lucy	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Addle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
casks	O
turned	O
upside	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cocks	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
maid	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
lighted	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cocks	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
barrels	O
then	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
cocks	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
cocks	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
cocks	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
many	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
thirteen	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Liquorpond-street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dickens	I-pers
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
shop	O
in	O
Berwick-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Carnaby-market	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
butter	O
and	O
a	O
groats-worth	O
of	O
eggs	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
if	O
the	O
butter	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
mine	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
send	O
the	O
girl	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
and	O
get	O
change	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Dickens	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
their	O
house	O
waited	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
.	O
She	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
girl	O
the	O
butter	O
and	O
eggs	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
girl	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
butter	O
and	O
eggs	O
came	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
girl	O
came	O
back	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dickens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Fifteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
butter	O
and	O
a	O
groats-worth	O
of	O
eggs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
to	O
send	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
the	O
butter	O
and	O
eggs	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
back	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
for	O
the	O
butter	O
and	O
eggs	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chapel-street	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
a	O
gateway	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
such	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
promise	O
to	O
send	O
back	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
Lee	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
witnesses	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
these	O
people	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
419	O
,	O
420	O
,	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Slight	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Holtham	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
carving-knife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Walter	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Walter	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
+	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Milliam	O
Holtham	O
,	O
alias	O
Slight	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
seven	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
in	O
a	O
steel	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
green	O
parchment	O
covered	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
sugar	O
cannister	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
seventeen	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isabella	O
.	O
+	O
Isabella	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
understand	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
alarmed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
broke	O
six	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
small	O
looking-glass	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
there	O
were	O
seventeen	O
guineas	O
.	O
My	O
bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
sundry	O
papers	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
books	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
memorandum	O
book	O
of	O
my	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
another	O
book	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
cover	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
stock-book	O
,	O
seven	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
marked	O
I	O
.	O
B.	O
my	O
maiden	O
name	O
,	O
the	O
odd	O
spoon	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
D	O
;	O
the	O
tea-tongs	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
P.	O
J.	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
court	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
has	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
The	O
parlour	O
window	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
us	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
I	O
took	O
Price	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
Slight	O
and	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pinnock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Mutton-lane	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Slight	O
and	O
Jones	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
from	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
tea-chest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
A	O
brother	O
officer	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
this	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
accomplice	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
was	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
tea-chest	O
is	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
thirty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
also	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
spectacles	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
-	O
Blower	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
on	O
Clerkenwell	O
Green	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
Jones	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
was	O
Slight	O
,	O
alias	O
Holtham	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
was	O
Price	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
walking	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
talking	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Holtham	O
,	O
alias	O
Slight	O
,	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Jones	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
Price	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
Opposite	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
Almost	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Slight	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
wrong	O
sort	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
loaded	O
with	O
goods	O
under	O
their	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Price	O
with	O
this	O
looking-glass	O
.	O
I	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
steel	O
spectacle-case	O
,	O
with	O
spectacles	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
pins	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
search	O
Slight	O
's	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Pinnock	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
another	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
might	O
you	O
pursue	O
them	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
passed	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
just	O
got	O
a-breast	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
when	O
I	O
attacked	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
Jones	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
on	O
when	O
my	O
brother	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
dressed	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
when	O
you	O
pursued	O
him	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
hat	O
and	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
and	O
make	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Slight	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
Jones	O
was	O
another	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Cohen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
her	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
over-night	O
;	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
window	O
fastened	O
?	O
Cohen	O
.	O
The	O
window-shutter	O
was	O
bolted	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
shut	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
within	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
bolt	O
pulled	O
back	O
,	O
or	O
wrenched	O
off	O
?	O
Cohen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
entirely	O
wrenched	O
off	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pinnock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mutton-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Slight	O
and	O
Jones	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
not	O
lodge	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Nobody	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
seeing	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
your	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
June	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
that	O
tea-chest	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Two	O
young	O
men	O
and	O
William	O
Price	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
are	O
they	O
,	O
or	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
Field-Lane	O
,	O
a	O
drinking	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
within	O
twenty-four	O
hours	O
before	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
not	O
a	O
liberty	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
when	O
they	O
pleased	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Many	O
people	O
resorted	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Field-Lane	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
more	O
than	O
with	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Hockley-in-the-hole	O
;	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
Price	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
or	O
day	O
were	O
they	O
brought	O
into	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
impossible	O
:	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
recollect	O
its	O
being	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
Price	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
day	O
or	O
night	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
they	O
waked	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
ago	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
quarter	O
or	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
long	O
ago	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
very	O
likely	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
say	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Price	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
more	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
we	O
three	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Slight	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
rob	O
;	O
we	O
attempted	O
several	O
houses	O
in	O
Islington	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
disturbed	O
at	O
one	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
none	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
By	O
forcing	O
open	O
the	O
shutter	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
a	O
chissel	O
to	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
crow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
inform	O
the	O
court	O
what	O
method	O
you	O
take	O
to	O
force	O
open	O
a	O
window	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
place	O
we	O
can	O
get	O
a	O
chissel	O
in	O
at	O
,	O
we	O
make	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
crow	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
such	O
power	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
force	O
any	O
window	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
open	O
this	O
window	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Jones	O
and	O
Slight	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
without	O
side	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
notice	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
this	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cannister	O
full	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
in	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
coloured	O
aprons	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
brandy	O
or	O
rum	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spectacles	O
;	O
this	O
book	O
was	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
bank	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
book	O
;	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
book	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directed	O
you	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Price	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
down	O
a	O
narrow	O
path	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
across	O
Clerkenwell-Green	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
brandy	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tyed	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
things	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
one	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
Jones	O
dressed	O
in	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
A	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
coat	O
on	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
coat	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
sleeves	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Blower	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
;	O
a	O
dark	O
coat	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Price	O
.	O
Had	O
Jones	B-pers
a	O
coat	O
on	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Pinnock	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
kept	O
by	O
Slight	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jones	O
frequently	O
lie	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
yourself	O
ever	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
them	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
take	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Pinnock	O
's	O
that	O
night	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
up	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Slight	O
generally	O
lodge	O
there	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
kept	O
her	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Blower	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Jones	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
then	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
a	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
round	O
short	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
passed	O
you	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
struck	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
from	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
then	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
dress	O
struck	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Blower	O
.	O
A	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Lee	O
.	O
What	O
constable	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
took	O
Slight	O
and	O
Jones	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
They	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brother	O
constable	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bishop	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Jones	O
to	O
Price	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
break	O
open	O
any	O
house	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
,	O
at	O
Ball	O
's	O
pond	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
also	O
helped	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Slight	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
break	O
open	O
any	O
house	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
's	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
with	O
them	O
seventeen	O
days	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rooper	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Slight	O
and	O
Jones	O
were	O
gone	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
our	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
pursue	O
them	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
joined	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
overtook	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
running	O
?	O
Bishop	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
every	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Holtham	O
,	O
alias	O
Slight	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Slight	O
.	O
That	O
knife	O
I	O
cut	O
my	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Slight	O
was	O
taken	O
first	O
;	O
Jones	O
jumped	O
over	O
a	O
ditch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rooper	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
searched	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
prison	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
Slight	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
claimed	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
Mott	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
Burry	O
Payne	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
that	O
robbery	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
(	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
has	O
a	O
gown	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
Slight	O
,	O
alias	O
Holtham	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Pinnock	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
with	O
butter	O
,	O
had	O
fetched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
are	O
speaking	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
work	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
by	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Jarvis	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
crnet	O
handles	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
there	O
at	O
nine	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
here	O
that	O
can	O
swear	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
this	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
For	O
Jones	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Great	O
Earl-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jones	B-pers
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
He	O
chiefly	O
lived	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
you	O
did	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Not	O
for	O
a	O
constancy	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
next	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
On	O
and	O
off	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
my	O
room	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
garret	O
floor	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
either	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
or	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
when	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
this	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
not	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
punctually	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
room	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
brick-maker	O
.	O
Slight	O
,	O
alias	O
Holtham	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Jones	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Slight	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Holtham	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Burry	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
china	O
tea-cups	O
and	O
six	O
china	O
tea-saucers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
ten	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	B-place
Green	I-place
Man	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Newington	I-place
Green	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
fastened	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bolt	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
any	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
without	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
in	O
afresh	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
windy	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
large	O
trees	O
before	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
wind	O
among	O
the	O
trees	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
the	O
bolt	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
staple	O
wrenched	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
some	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
six	O
locks	O
to	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
closet	O
at	O
the	O
upper-end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
lock	O
open	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
pannel	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
wine	O
from	O
that	O
closet	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
besides	O
those	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Price	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Pinnock	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
says	O
it	O
is	O
hers	O
.	O
Slight	O
and	O
Jones	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
This	O
looking-glass	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Pinnock	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
glass	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
evidence	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
if	O
his	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
glass	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
glass	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
wanting	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
glass	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Blower	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
Price	O
,	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Pinnock	I-pers
's	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
this	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
Price	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
three	O
persons	O
together	O
.	O
Blower	O
.	O
Only	O
three	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
Burry	O
Payne	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
looking-glass	O
at	O
Pinnock	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
Bishop	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
upon	O
Slight	O
.	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Bishop	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
Slight	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ballas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
morning	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
clock	O
had	O
struck	O
twelve	O
,	O
my	O
dogs	O
alarmed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
up	O
my	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fourth	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
breach	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
pallisadoes	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
faces	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
on	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
positively	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
Mrs.	O
Parker	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
into	O
a	O
long	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
seemed	O
no	O
other	O
room	O
but	O
that	O
;	O
it	O
seemingly	O
joined	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
from	O
thence	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
and	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
they	O
get	O
in	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
By	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
outside	O
shutter	O
.	O
Slight	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
asleep	O
under	O
a	O
tree	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Burry	O
Payne	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Slight	O
,	O
alias	O
Holtham	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Payne	O
and	O
Jones	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
423	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Beverley	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Dalman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty-nine	O
rabbit	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
425	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
ten	O
ounces	O
of	O
musk	O
,	O
value	O
44	O
l.	O
three	O
lb	O
.	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
castor	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
22	O
s.	O
twenty-two	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
rhubarb	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
five	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
cake	O
saffron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
26	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
eleven	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
hay	O
saffron	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
lb	O
.	O
six	O
ounces	O
of	O
oil	O
of	O
mace	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
five	O
canvas	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
paper	O
bags	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kenton	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vazey	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Kenton	O
and	O
Vazey	O
,	O
June	O
5th	O
.	O
++	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Vazey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wholesale	O
druggist	O
in	O
Laurence-lane	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Kenton	O
.	O
We	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
value	O
may	O
the	O
things	O
be	O
altogether	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
?	O
Vazey	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
130	O
l.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
five	O
months	O
this	O
last	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
two	O
years	O
together	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
discharged	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Winch	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Winch	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
sample	O
of	O
saffron	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
ours	O
.	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
sample	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
and	O
compared	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
as	O
much	O
alike	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Winch	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
musk	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
offered	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
musk	O
I	O
trimmed	O
up	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
Vazey	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
paper	O
bags	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Winch	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
were	O
ours	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
offered	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
very	O
few	O
words	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
have	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
duty	O
was	O
paid	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
as	O
short	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
entry	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
cake	O
saffron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
manufactured	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
imported	O
in	O
that	O
state	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
that	O
in	O
time	O
too	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
stop	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Davis	B-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Smith	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Davis	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
?	O
Vazey	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
pale	O
,	O
and	O
trembled	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
Smith	O
was	O
too	O
knowing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
smuggler	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
write	O
?	O
Vazey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
handwriting	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
castor	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rhubarb	O
and	O
the	O
musk	O
were	O
behind	O
the	O
compting-house	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
letter	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vazey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
letter	O
read	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Kenton	O
and	O
Company	O
.	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
July	O
4th	O
.	O
``	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
``	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
``	O
this	O
man	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
``	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
them	O
,	O
``	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
``	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
``	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Johnson	O
.	O
He	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
put	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
letter	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
mention	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
letter	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
wrote	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
direction	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
letter	O
read	O
.	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
July	O
4th	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
send	O
me	O
that	O
letter	O
``	O
directly	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
something	O
``	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
which	O
I	O
forgot	O
``	O
before	O
.	O
In	O
so	O
doing	O
you	O
will	O
oblige	O
``	O
Your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
carry	O
it	O
by	O
word	O
of	O
mouth	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vazey	O
's	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
and	O
his	O
uncle	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Smith	O
told	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
take	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
Mess	O
.	O
Kenton	O
's	O
and	O
Vazey	O
's	O
warehouse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
persuaded	O
him	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Smith	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Smith	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mess	O
.	O
Kenton	O
's	O
and	O
Vazey	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
sell	O
the	O
goods	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
will	O
serve	O
us	O
both	O
for	O
pocket-money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
received	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
Smith	O
sold	O
the	O
goods	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
became	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
formerly	O
a	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
druggist	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
.	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
samples	O
of	O
saffron	O
,	O
castor	O
,	O
rhubarb	O
,	O
and	O
musk	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
he	O
only	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
samples	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
goods	O
Mr.	O
Vazey	O
found	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
Smith	O
?	O
Winch	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
confess	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Shropshire	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
426	O
.	O
427	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cawdell	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
June	O
9th	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pyrke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Cawdell	I-pers
,	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
clear	O
lawns	O
of	O
about	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
first	O
pieces	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
I	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
compter	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
piece	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
these	O
three	O
pieces	O
I	O
opened	O
six	O
other	O
pieces	O
;	O
they	O
fixed	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
pieces	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
per	O
yard	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
only	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Their	O
asking	O
for	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
quantity	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
had	O
a	O
long	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
afterwards	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
her	O
hands	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Immediately	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
them	O
near	O
Newgate	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
both	O
back	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
immediately	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
's	O
foot	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
folded	O
up	O
at	O
length	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
doubled	O
up	O
short	O
.	O
I	O
imagine	O
from	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
stood	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
dropped	O
by	O
Salmon	O
.	O
Hughes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
girls	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cawdell	O
challenged	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
;	O
immediately	O
it	O
was	O
dropped	O
upon	O
my	O
shoe	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
shoe	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
very	O
light	O
weight	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
it	O
.	O
Salmon	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
we	O
met	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
lawn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
go	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
.	O
Harris	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
we	O
met	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
428	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
one	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
mittins	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
,	I-place
Shoe-lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
key	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
opened	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
sixteen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
keys	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
nineteen	O
drawers	O
,	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
trunks	O
opened	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
my	O
things	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
429	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Raines	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shackley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
15th	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
431	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
marrying	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Heckford	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
still	O
living	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
the	O
Martyr	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
register-book	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
)	O
(	O
reads	O
)	O
``	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
batchelor	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
this	O
``	O
parish	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
in	O
this	O
church	O
by	O
banns	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
of	O
our	O
``	O
Lord	O
1758	O
,	O
by	O
me	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
curate	O
;	O
``	O
signed	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
This	O
``	O
marriage	O
was	O
solemnized	O
between	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
presence	O
of	O
us	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
''	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
before	O
this	O
marriage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
captain	O
Bootle	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
his	O
marriage	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
subscribing	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
cohabiting	O
together	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
captain	O
Bootle	O
's	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
a	O
courtship	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
a-bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
acknowledged	O
their	O
marriage	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
god-mother	O
to	O
their	O
first	O
child	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
first	O
wife	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
first	O
cousin	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
last	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Rev	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
de	I-pers
Guillion	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
curate	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
the	O
Martyr	O
.	O
This	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
paper	O
)	O
is	O
an	O
exact	O
copy	O
from	O
the	O
register	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
143.	O
``	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
Jane	B-pers
Heckford	I-pers
of	O
this	O
parish	O
,	O
were	O
married	O
``	O
in	O
this	O
church	O
by	O
licence	O
,	O
April	O
8th	O
,	O
1770	O
,	O
``	O
be	O
me	O
Stephen	B-pers
de	I-pers
Guillion	I-pers
,	O
curate	O
.	O
This	O
``	O
marriage	O
was	O
solemnized	O
between	O
us	O
James	O
``	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Heckford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
``	O
Charles	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Mary	B-pers
Alfred	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
Jane	B-pers
Heckford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
subscribed	O
the	O
register	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
here	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
single	O
person	O
have	O
I	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
confuted	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
B	O
.	O
&	O
Im	O
.	O
432	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Coley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
June	O
23d	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
copper	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow-bier	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milliner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Round	I-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
my	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
any	O
force	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
lock	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
bolts	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
the	O
bolt	O
might	O
be	O
lifted	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bird-in-hand	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
.	O
I	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Tuesday	O
's	O
paper	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
advertised	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
433	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coxan	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
434	O
,	O
435	O
,	O
436	O
,	O
437	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
M'Donald	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
M'Kue	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Memory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
M'Kensie	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
French	O
plate	O
soup-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
M'Kensie	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
M'Kensie	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
.	O
At	O
two	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
June	O
10th	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
going	O
his	O
rounds	O
,	O
alarmed	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lower	O
bolt	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
parlour	O
window	O
shutter	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
upper	O
bolt	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
strong	O
one	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
shutter	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
outside	O
shutter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
was	O
fastened	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
closet	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
locked	O
,	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
chained	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Galloway	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
a	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
M'Kue	O
and	O
M'Donald	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
*	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
himself	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Thacker	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
plate	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
M'Donald	O
,	O
Memory	O
,	O
and	O
M'Kue	O
,	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
the	O
preceding	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
where	O
M'Donald	O
and	O
M'Kue	O
were	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Lambeth	O
Reading	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
Lambeth	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
pond	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
White-Conduit-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Thacker	O
and	O
Memory	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
M'Kue	O
and	O
M'Donald	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
against	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
proper	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
them	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Underwood	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
for	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
234	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
367	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Beckford	O
's	O
second	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
taking	O
Memory	O
and	O
Thacker	O
at	O
Underwood	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
tale	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Galloway	O
.	O
Lambeth	O
Reading	O
deposed	O
that	O
M'Donald	O
and	O
M'Kue	O
were	O
committed	O
as	O
being	O
disorderly	O
people	O
,	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
tile	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
concealed	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
begged	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
Underwood	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
they	O
,	O
has	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pond	O
near	O
White-conduit-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
concealed	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
.	O
M'Donald	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
M'Kue	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
called	O
upon	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
Memory	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
Underwood	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
victuals	O
;	O
that	O
Underwood	O
took	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
brick-makers	O
.	O
Thacker	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pity	O
the	O
court	O
should	O
take	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
word	O
as	O
Underwood	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Alice	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
All	O
four	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
Memory	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
100	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
438	O
,	O
439	O
,	O
440	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Worm	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fullingwood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
live	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
live	O
hen	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
copper-stew-pans	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
frying-pan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Markland	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	B-place
;	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
fowls	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
13th	O
and	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
wash-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
carrying	O
something	O
under	O
their	O
coats	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
Worm	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
ran	O
different	O
ways	O
;	O
that	O
Speed	O
threw	O
the	O
hen	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
Worm	O
had	O
the	O
cock	O
in	O
a	O
coloured	O
apron	O
;	O
that	O
Fullingwood	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
secured	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
Worm	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
fowls	O
from	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
cock	O
to	O
Waltham	O
Green	O
,	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Hopkins	O
.	O
The	O
defence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
fowls	O
of	O
a	O
traveller	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
Fullingwood	O
called	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
,	O
Speed	O
called	O
Henry	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Brecknock	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Worm	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
Speed	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T.	O
Fullingwood	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
441	O
,	O
442	O
,	O
443	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Coleby	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
till	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
hundred	O
halfpence	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Chick-lane	B-place
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
my	O
bar	O
is	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
partition	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
gardens	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
chissel	O
upon	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
large	O
chissel	O
.	O
)	O
Pinnock	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
Price	O
brought	O
this	O
chissel	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Pinnock	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
sworn	O
this	O
thing	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
revenge	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
information	O
she	O
says	O
that	O
I	O
stole	O
six	O
spoons	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
trial	O
yesterday	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
whereas	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
lost	O
no	O
spoons	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pinnock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
there	O
of	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mutton-lane	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
yesterday	O
that	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
Mutton-lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
people	O
;	O
Price	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
a	O
house	O
breaking	O
.	O
Murray	O
and	O
Coleby	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
beginning	O
or	O
end	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Murray	O
and	O
Coleby	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
agreeable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
said	O
you	O
?	O
Pinnock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
agreeable	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
scheme	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
to	O
revenge	O
themselves	O
of	O
this	O
Price	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
,	O
has	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
444	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Iveson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shagreen	O
spoon-case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Aberdeen	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Aberdeen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
corner-cupboard	O
in	O
his	O
parlour	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
ticket	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
for	O
abusing	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
some	O
suspicious	O
circumstances	O
arising	O
,	O
he	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
duplicate	O
was	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
445	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
July	O
8th	O
.	O
*	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
moving	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
seized	O
by	O
her	O
landlord	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
be	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Her	O
account	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
John	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Beedle	I-pers
,	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blanket	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
30	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
denied	O
by	O
all	O
the	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
446	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Staines	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Jodderell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
washing	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
leg	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pike	O
fish	O
,	O
seven	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
clasp	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Jodderell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
round	O
a	O
garden	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
Ormond-street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
garden-wall	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
feet	O
high	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
garden-wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
rang	O
my	O
rattle	O
and	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
garden	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jodderell	O
's	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
this	O
pewter	O
plate	O
doubled	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turnpenny	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
watchmen	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
this	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jodderell	O
's	O
maid	O
came	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
his	O
account	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
house-maid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jodderell	O
;	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
wash-house	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
copper	O
was	O
fastened	O
in	O
brick	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
pulled	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
wash-house	O
door	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
be	O
locked	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jodderell	O
's	O
butlers	O
,	O
swore	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
grass	O
wet	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
447	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Keith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
June	O
8th	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
,	O
B	O
.	O
448	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
callimanco	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
,	O
B	O
.	O
449	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
her	O
brother	O
and	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
faintly	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Burlaid	I-pers
,	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murden	I-pers
,	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
450	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Valentine	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
,	O
W	O
.	O
451	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Will	I-pers
.	I-pers
the	I-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
five	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
with	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
with	O
fringed	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Hugh	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
;	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
rule	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
properly	O
secured	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
parlour	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
window-sash	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
violence	O
with	O
which	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
,	O
the	O
screw	O
that	O
fastens	O
both	O
the	O
sashes	O
together	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hinge	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
folding	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hinges	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
hinges	O
it	O
was	O
which	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
little	O
paper	O
boxes	O
;	O
the	O
papers	O
were	O
all	O
scattered	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
was	O
a	O
bureau	O
desk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
papers	O
it	O
contained	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
scattered	O
about	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
adjoining	O
room	O
(	O
a	O
parlour	O
.	O
)	O
Upon	O
the	O
marble	O
flab	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
blade	O
of	O
a	O
sword	O
and	O
the	O
scabbard	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
hilt	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
and	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
nothing	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
closet	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
china	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
plate	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
particular	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
forwards	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
bed-chamber	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
clothes-press	O
,	O
the	O
folding-doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
suits	O
,	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
plain	O
suits	O
scattered	O
about	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
bed	O
chamber	O
)	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
plain	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
,	O
sea	O
green	O
,	O
quite	O
new	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
green	O
baize	O
door	O
stand	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
double	O
doors	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
extraordinary	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
stand	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
spring	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
chissel	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
large	O
flat	O
chissel	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
chissel	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
scarlet	O
clothes	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
clothes-press	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
absolutely	O
know	O
what	O
clothes	O
were	O
lost	O
till	O
the	O
butler	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
things	O
I	O
could	O
recollect	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
though	O
an	O
imperfect	O
one	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
butler	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
more	O
perfect	O
account	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
Saturday	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
things	O
ready	O
for	O
dressing	O
against	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
the	O
coachman	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
plate	O
behind	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
from	O
town	O
?	O
Woodham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
pantry	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
pantry	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
seldom	O
locked	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
other	O
servants	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pea-green	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
with	O
silver	O
lace	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
my	O
master	O
laid	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
drawer	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
clothes-press	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
scarlet	O
and	O
gold	O
full	O
trimmed	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
sea-green	O
with	O
gold	O
buttons	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
dressing-parlour	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
gold	O
stock-buckle	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
dressing-glass	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
into	O
my	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
five	O
large	O
silver	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
which	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
marble	O
slab	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
dressing	O
parlour	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
hat	O
which	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
wore	O
,	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
pinon	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
shirts	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
master	O
's	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
point	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
other	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
fringed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blade	O
of	O
the	O
sword	O
,	O
the	O
hilt	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
sword	O
left	O
there	O
?	O
Woodham	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
that	O
parlour	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
every	O
thing	O
but	O
the	O
scarlet	O
clothes	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
's	O
head	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
examination	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
recollection	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
discovered	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
my	O
master	O
in	O
town	O
early	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
gate	O
bell	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
coachman	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
up	O
before	O
you	O
?	O
Hale	O
.	O
The	O
cellar-man	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
wine-vaults	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shutter	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
thrown	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hale	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
ward	O
of	O
Aldersgate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
Alderman	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
chissel	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
chissel	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
2	O
chissel	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
step	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Tom	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
went	O
a	O
thieving	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Jack	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
and	O
Will	O
the	O
carpenter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Bet	O
or	O
Nan	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Alderman	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
for	O
Brush	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
things	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
's	O
;	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Lumley	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
strict	O
search	O
,	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
gold	O
buttons	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Hewetson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lace-man	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
King	O
street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
lace	O
of	O
this	O
pattern	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1768	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
my	O
manufactory	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
well	O
convinced	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
nature	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
quantity	O
of	O
lace	O
you	O
have	O
sold	O
of	O
that	O
pattern	O
?	O
Hewetson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
perhaps	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Newinburg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
button-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
This	O
(	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
buttons	O
)	O
is	O
our	O
pattern	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
buttons	O
were	O
made	O
by	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
about	O
town	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
button	O
is	O
made	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
whom	O
you	O
sold	O
these	O
identical	O
buttons	O
?	O
Newinburg	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sell	O
any	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
?	O
Newinburg	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
as	O
this	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
's	O
taylor	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
dress	O
suit	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
sold	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
?	O
Newinburg	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
chissel	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Will	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
's	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
one	O
more	O
than	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
use	O
to	O
go	O
together	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
council	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
carpenter	O
's	O
chissel	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Donaldson	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
in	O
that	O
chissel	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
cut	O
underneath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
not	O
all	O
made	O
so	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
council	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
just	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Since	O
Christmas	O
;	O
Henry	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
I	O
knew	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
their	O
having	O
been	O
together	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
did	O
they	O
use	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
The	O
Py	O
'd	O
Bull	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
from	O
?	O
Are	O
you	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
now	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
you	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
A	O
sheriffs	O
officer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tagg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
seven	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
dressing-room	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
rooms	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Lee	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
rather	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
connections	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
Donaldson	O
and	O
Lee	O
,	O
or	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
constant	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
months	O
past	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
breaking	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
together	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
Peter-street	O
,	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
,	O
Bet	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
for	O
something	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
two	O
pistols	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
two	O
chissels	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crow	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Long-Lane	O
;	O
we	O
tried	O
to	O
open	O
a	O
yard	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
called	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Bartholomew-close	O
,	O
in	O
Little	O
Britain	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
disturbed	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
remainder	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
besides	O
one	O
chissel	O
and	O
one	O
crow	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
pistols	O
we	O
had	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
hid	O
under	O
some	O
dung	O
,	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
a	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chissel	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
a	O
bullock	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Smithfield	O
down	O
Little-Britain	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bullock	O
turning	O
short	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
there	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
way	O
.	O
Donaldson	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
here	O
yet	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
get	O
something	O
may	O
be	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
paved	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
iron	O
rails	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
steps	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
over	O
them	O
iron	O
rails	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
's	O
yard	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
wooden	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
tried	O
at	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
sashes	O
would	O
shove	O
up	O
of	O
themselves	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
screwed	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
forced	O
up	O
the	O
farther	O
sash	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
and	O
a	O
crow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
that	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
helped	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
forced	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
inside	O
shutter	O
open	O
by	O
getting	O
off	O
the	O
hinge	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
that	O
were	O
upon	O
a	O
settle	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
pantry	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
we	O
first	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
pantry	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Two	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
plate	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
rightly	O
what	O
besides	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
light	O
green	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
scarlet	O
,	O
trimmed	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
hung	O
up	O
over	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Harley	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
away	O
and	O
leave	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
house	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
after	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
a	O
hat-box	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
wrote	O
upon	O
the	O
cover	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
The	O
Right	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
;	O
we	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
silver	O
hilt	O
of	O
a	O
sword	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
that	O
parlour	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
dressing-glass	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
drawer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
gold	O
stock-buckle	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Bet	B-pers
Brush	I-pers
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
they	O
weighed	O
the	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
One	O
hundred	O
and	O
six	O
ounces	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
lace	O
that	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
lace	O
off	O
the	O
scarlet	O
clothes	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
all	O
burnt	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
All	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
there	O
being	O
any	O
left	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
burnt	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
weighed	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
directly	O
:	O
we	O
sold	O
her	O
the	O
light	O
clothes	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
twenty-three	O
guineas	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
for	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
positive	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
us	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
stay	O
till	O
Isaac	O
gets	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
upon	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
time	O
Donaldson	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
eleven	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
Donaldson	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
paid	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
;	O
who	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
hat	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harley	O
's	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
hook	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
chissel	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
chissel	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
sticking	O
in	O
a	O
door	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
clock	O
had	O
struck	O
five	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
chissel	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
that	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
off	O
myself	O
.	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
chissel	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shoulder	O
of	O
it	O
near	O
the	O
handle	O
broke	O
off	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
they	O
make	O
the	O
chissels	O
often	O
so	O
?	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
judge	O
