TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
and	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coppin	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Moose	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Adam	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hancox	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Carrier	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cousway	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wilshin	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Veal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Meades	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hett	I-pers
.	O
64	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Pyne	I-pers
,	O
book-seller	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
printed	O
books	O
in	O
octavo	O
,	O
called	O
Swift	O
's	O
Works	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
printed	O
books	O
in	O
twelves	O
,	O
called	O
Deism	O
Revealed	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
book	O
,	O
called	O
Burnet	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Times	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
25	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
65	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hillman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Knibbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hillman	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Craven-street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
seven	O
at-night	O
)	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
if	O
this	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hillman	O
's	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
basket	O
directed	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
while	O
called	O
for	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bell	O
inn	O
,	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
book-keeper	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
master	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
direction	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
came	O
another	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
doctor	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
globe	O
tavern	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
hear	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
near	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
back	O
towards	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
direction	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
send	O
any	O
servant	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
candle	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
in	O
Church-court	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
instantly	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
candlestick	O
;	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
and	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
abroad	O
,	O
he	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
candlestick	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
extinguisher	O
was	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
we	O
never	O
found	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
conquered	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
we	O
took	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
(	O
The	O
candlestick	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
across	O
Church-court	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
candlestick	O
from	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
fetched	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
a	O
knock	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
assistance	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
secured	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
up	O
Church-court	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
candlestick	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
possible	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
knock	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
belt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Francis	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
silk	O
belt	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
that	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
swan	O
and	O
two	O
necks	O
,	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
box	O
was	O
there	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
That	O
direction	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
maid	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
left	O
that	O
direction	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
tall	O
,	O
thin	O
man	O
.	O
Such	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
looking	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
sword	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
sword	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sword	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
sword	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
wore	O
it	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
what	O
time	O
I	O
expected	O
him	O
in	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
uncertain	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
book-keeper	O
at	O
the	O
swan	O
and	O
two	O
necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
left	O
there	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
,	O
fearing	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
something	O
of	O
consequence	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
direction	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
front	O
parlour	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
sword	O
hung	O
in	O
that	O
parlour	O
.	O
J.	O
Jones	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
writing	O
the	O
direction	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
answer	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
asked	O
if	O
a	O
captain	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
here	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
lodger	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
direct	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
captain	O
,	O
naming	O
a	O
name	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
getting	O
his	O
friend	O
into	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
forget	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
J.	O
Jones	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
odd	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
so	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
sword	O
and	O
belt	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
master	O
returned	O
he	O
soon	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
wrote	O
the	O
direction	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
great-coat	O
on	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
his	O
voice	O
;	O
and	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
pledged	O
this	O
sword	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
25	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bland	O
,	O
a	O
single	O
gentleman	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Col.	O
Sands	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
eleven	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
horse-guards	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
army	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
66	O
,	O
67	O
,	O
68	O
,	O
69	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Corby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
And	O
Margaret	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	O
Ware	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
were	O
in	O
Brumpton-road	B-place
,	O
near	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
four	O
men	O
crossed	O
over	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Lady	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
no	O
pockets	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
pockets	O
on	O
;	O
you	O
may	O
feel	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
untied	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
white	O
sattin	O
.	O
At	O
their	O
first	O
coming	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Shoot	O
her	O
!	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
hurt	O
her	O
!	O
At	O
their	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
fright	O
,	O
pray	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
cloak	O
again	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
Blow	O
her	O
brains	O
out	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
pistol	O
snap	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
,	O
all	O
four	O
,	O
pistols	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
young	O
fellows	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
in	O
their	O
faces	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
their	O
own	O
hair	O
.	O
(	O
Such	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
,	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
M.	O
Ware	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
quite	O
moon-light	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
shortest	O
that	O
untied	O
my	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
advertised	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
within	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
cloak	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
prisoners	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Miss	O
Ware	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
four	O
young	O
men	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
not	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
our	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
town	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
pockets	O
on	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
short	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Shoot	O
her	O
!	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
her	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
my	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
their	O
faces	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Corby	O
and	O
Busby	O
;	O
Busby	O
is	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
money	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Corby	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Busby	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
se'nnight	O
after	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
mistress	O
live	O
?	O
S.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
Brumpton-road	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
S.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Walker's-court	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
lady	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
25	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
fetched	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
some	O
where	O
else	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
for	O
27	O
s.	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
cloak	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wheatly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
crown	O
ale-house	O
,	O
in	O
Brumpton-road	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
young	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
till	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Corby	O
and	O
Busby	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
Butler	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
about	O
140	O
or	O
150	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Busby	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
W.	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
near	O
18	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
Corby	O
and	O
Busby	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Brumpton-road	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
the	O
lady	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
:	O
then	O
Corby	O
took	O
her	O
cloak	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Corby	O
had	O
a	O
broken	O
pistol	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
fire	O
;	O
Busby	O
had	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
pistol	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
else	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
being	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
so	O
were	O
they	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
pockets	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
her	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
lady	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
them	O
squeak	O
when	O
we	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
said	O
,	O
Blow	O
her	O
brains	O
out	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
hole-in-the-wall	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
besides	O
myself	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
then	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
some	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
examined	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
now	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
James	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
grand-father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
Brumpton-road	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
hole-in-the-wall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
that	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
that	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Busby	O
and	O
Corby	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
she	O
pawned	O
it	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Cole	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Corby	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Butler	O
)	O
he	O
is	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Busby	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
out	O
town	O
,	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
ought	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
(	O
meaning	O
Mr.	O
Wheatly	O
)	O
We	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
robbery	O
.	O
Busby	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
post-boy	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
Church-court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Corby	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
cow	O
and	O
calf	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
named	O
Salmadine	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bull	O
,	O
at	O
Kingston	O
.	O
Warden	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
(	O
meaning	O
Butler	O
)	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Corby	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
.	O
To	O
Cole	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sawyer	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Martin-street	O
,	O
by	O
Carnaby-market	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Cole	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
To	O
Warden	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
This	O
Warden	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
behaved	O
sober	O
and	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Corby	O
and	O
Busby	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Cole	O
and	O
Warden	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Corby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
No	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
on	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
70	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
a	O
second	O
time	O
were	O
indicted	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
And	O
Warden	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Jane	B-pers
Finley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
Lucy	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
's	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
our	O
servant	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
from	O
Crown-court	B-place
,	I-place
Princes-street	I-place
,	O
some	O
men	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
arms	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
kiss	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
off	O
my	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
second	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
,	O
Butler	O
,	O
looks	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
under	O
my	O
left	O
ear	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
12	O
s.	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
pawned	O
this	O
cloak	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
J.	O
Finley	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
cloak	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
.	O
W.	O
Butler	O
.	O
Cole	O
,	O
Bromley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
.	O
Going	O
down	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
round	O
her	O
neck	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
kiss	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
cloak	O
off	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
catch	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hit	O
her	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
some	O
people	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
then	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
cloak	O
to	O
Westminster	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
hid	O
the	O
cloak	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Peg	O
Warden	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
myself	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
71	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
double-barrel	O
pistol	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
David	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
auctioneer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
named	O
William	O
More	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
and	O
lodged	O
some	O
in	O
one	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
queen's-head	B-place
tavern	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Great	I-place
Queen-street	I-place
,	I-place
Lincoln's-inn-fields	I-place
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
double-barrel	O
pistol	O
among	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
sold	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
bid	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
usual	O
to	O
keep	O
persons	O
there	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
that	O
goods	O
are	O
not	O
sold	O
at	O
an	O
underprice	O
.	O
Court	O
:	O
They	O
are	O
usually	O
called	O
puffers	O
,	O
are	O
they	O
not	O
?	O
Nilson	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
goods	O
till	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
sale	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
porters	O
,	O
and	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
bill	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
tavern	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
shewed	O
to	O
his	O
servants	O
,	O
what	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
separated	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
pistol	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
missing	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
before	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
made	O
to	O
turn	O
round	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
fire	O
both	O
barrels	O
,	O
one	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
double-barrel	O
pistol	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
put	O
this	O
double-barrel	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
gun-smith	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
repair	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
both	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
:	O
and	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
last	O
sessions	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Death	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
queen's-head	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
pistol	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Barrow	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
.	O
(	O
On	O
which	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New-prison	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
was	O
Jones	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
red-cow	O
,	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
There	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
asked	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
How	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
pistol	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sing	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
red-cow	O
,	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Langley	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
or	O
not	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
in	O
taking	O
other	O
things	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
answer	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
pistol	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
understand	O
will	O
be	O
advertised	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
auctioneer	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
Mr.	O
Langley	O
says	O
,	O
is	O
quite	O
false	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
pistol	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
at	O
the	O
half-moon	O
tavern	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
72	O
,	O
73	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Cheapside	B-place
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
Burch	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
elbow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Burch	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
a	O
motion	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
delivering	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
close	O
to	O
Thompson	O
's	O
feet	O
lay	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Burch	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
jobb	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
confederate	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Penroy	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
for	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
74	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Grace-church-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
instantly	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
fall	O
from	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
red-and-white	O
linen	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
conscience	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
other	O
lads	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
confederates	O
,	O
jostled	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
instant	O
that	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
attack	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
impertinent	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
which	O
rather	O
determined	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
indeed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-compter	O
(	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
compter	O
)	O
I	O
thinking	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
hear	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
used	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
common	O
.	O
And	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
London-bridge	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
so	O
can	O
not	O
produce	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
produced	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
grand	O
jury	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
75	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
pieces	O
of	O
stained	O
paper	O
,	O
conmining	O
200	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
paper-stainer	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
paper-hangers	O
came	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
paper	O
of	O
my	O
make	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Scully	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
30	O
pieces	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
38	O
pieces	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Scully	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
six	O
pieces	O
he	O
sold	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
were	O
worth	O
18	O
s.	O
I	O
found	O
30	O
pieces	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
piece	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scully	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
carry	O
business	O
on	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
76	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hebb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11000	O
brass	O
wire	O
pins	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sainsbury	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Sainsbury	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
brought	O
me	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
pins	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
?	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
11000	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pin-maker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
papers	O
of	O
pins	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
fell	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sibley	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
marked	O
such	O
pins	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
letters	O
which	O
are	O
here	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
produced	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pins	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Joshua	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sibley	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
these	O
papers	O
of	O
pins	O
myself	O
.	O
These	O
letters	O
tell	O
us	O
the	O
price	O
they	O
cost	O
.	O
We	O
sell	O
them	O
by	O
these	O
marks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
pins	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Parvel	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
77	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wooley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
halfpence	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garrat	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Heathfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garrat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Moor-street	O
,	O
by	O
London-wall	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Heathfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Higgens	I-pers
.	O
My	O
servant	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
is	O
the	O
chief	O
witness	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
trusted	O
with	O
papers	O
of	O
halfpence	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
carmen	O
.	O
He	O
will	O
give	O
the	O
court	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Messr	O
.	O
Garrat	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
ten	O
papers	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
three	O
shillings	O
worth	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
carmen	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
bring	O
20	O
hogsheads	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
upon	O
some	O
buts	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
turn	O
my	O
back	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
carmen	O
)	O
brought	O
his	O
cart	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
cart	O
was	O
unloaded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
telling	O
my	O
papers	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
carts	O
came	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
hay	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hay-basket	O
,	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
Another	O
of	O
the	O
carmen	O
bad	O
him	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
scandalizing	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
paper	O
of	O
halfpence	O
in	O
his	O
cart	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
hogshead	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
litter	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
for	O
his	O
fare	O
.	O
The	O
fare	O
was	O
3	O
s.	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
first	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
carman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
servant	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
fuddled	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
How	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
77	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Primrose	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec	O
,	O
29	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Primrose	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
my	O
late	O
master	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
Indies	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Vigo-Lane	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
an	O
entertainment	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
at	O
a	O
tavern	O
in	O
Sackville-Street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
gold	O
watch	O
to	O
lock	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
soon	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
returned	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
eleven	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
dressed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
company	O
were	O
all	O
come	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
four	O
:	O
dinner	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
table	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
waiters	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
dinner	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
together	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
engaged	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
see	O
him	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Dingwell	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
78	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
chain	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
hook	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
at	O
master	O
's	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
hook	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
before	O
?	O
Chambers	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
ring	O
which	O
opened	O
the	O
drawer	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
right	O
key	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Notley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kates	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Chandos-Street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
much	O
she	O
wanted	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
hesitated	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
lend	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
seemed	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
or	O
metal	O
one	O
;	O
first	O
she	O
asked	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
then	O
ten	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
sent	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
necessary	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
parlour	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
he	O
would	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
hood	O
and	O
ring	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
key	O
that	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
hook	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
lock	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
if	O
made	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
false	O
key	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
78	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Sarsfield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
seven	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
in	O
Russel-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
Naming	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
garret	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
and	O
lie	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
evening	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
once	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
absent	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
goods	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
rents	O
a	O
garret	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
garret	O
.	O
We	O
work	O
together	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
he	O
does	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
my	O
landlord	O
(	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
evening	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
just	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
He	O
wished	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
chair	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
old	O
shoes	O
to	O
mend	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
from	O
his	O
chair	O
and	O
began	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
frightened	O
me	O
to	O
death	O
to	O
hear-them	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
man	O
walked	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
leaned	O
over	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
by	O
Jesus	O
!	O
''	O
He	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
got	O
down	O
stairs	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
stir	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
opinion	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
stir	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Light	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
lighted	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
frightened	O
that	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
garret	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
room	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
watch	O
went	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
landlord	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
feet	O
seven	O
inches	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
small-pox	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dignam	I-pers
came	O
and	O
offered	O
five	O
guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twenty-six	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
tobacco	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
now	O
was	O
he	O
at	O
large	O
.	O
Felix	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Blakeney	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
comes	O
occasionally	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drinking	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
)	O
till	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
after	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
waiter	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
50	O
l.	O
bills	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
opportunities	O
to	O
take	O
great	O
advantages	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trotman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
tobacco	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Vere-Street	O
,	O
Clare-Market	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
hurt	O
on	O
one	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
undertake	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
long	O
affair	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
several	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
79	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Shepherd	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
from	O
Ratcliff-High-Way	B-place
through	O
the	O
turnpike	O
;	O
the	O
road	O
leads	O
from	O
Ratcliff-High-Way	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
go	O
very	O
safe	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
them	O
nor	O
they	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Brewer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
cross	O
road	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Half-way-house	O
:	O
the	O
road	O
goes	O
to	O
Stepney	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
walking	O
single	O
one	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stepped	O
four	O
steps	O
before	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
shoulder	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
need	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
take	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
)	O
:	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
some	O
half-pence	O
and	O
farthings	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
then	O
all	O
three	O
abreast	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
all	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
broom	O
stick	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
;	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
use	O
the	O
gentleman	O
ill	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
took	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
weapon	O
the	O
others	O
two	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
thick	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
flapped	O
hat	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
:	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
or	O
the	O
middle	O
one	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
not	O
he	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
was	O
neither	O
flapped	O
,	O
nor	O
cocked	O
,	O
so	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Brewer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Brewer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
advertised	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
served	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Brewer	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
people	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
light	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
their	O
clothes	O
:	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
another	O
a	O
white	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
brown	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
:	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
going	O
down	O
Lemond-Street	O
.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
till	O
I	O
get	O
nearer	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
Mill-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Noah	O
's	O
Ark	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
:	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
their	O
liquor	O
,	O
Robinson	O
stepped	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
whispered	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
venture	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
then	O
,	O
thinking	O
we	O
might	O
see	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
taller	O
than	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
stick	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
bad	O
houses	O
where	O
I	O
knew	O
bad	O
people	O
used	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
before	O
deposed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Robinson	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
lately	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
Northampton	O
to	O
an	O
uncle	O
and	O
aunt	O
in	O
Leather-Lane	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Well-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Landlord	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
company	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
to	O
night	O
?	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
dial	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
seven	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
will	O
come	O
soon	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
before	O
they	O
drank	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
comrade	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
stayed	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Welch	O
rabbits	O
for	O
supper	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
drawed	O
them	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
two	O
penny	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
quitted	O
the	O
club	O
room	O
till	O
the	O
company	O
broke	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Welch	O
rabbits	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
right	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
borrowed	O
a	O
penny	O
of	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prison	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
one	O
confined	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
mentioned	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
young	O
fellow	O
would	O
turn	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
people	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
the	O
club	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
seven	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
pretty	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sensible	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Well-Street	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
eating	O
a	O
Welch	O
rabbit	O
:	O
he	O
staid	O
in	O
company	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
is	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
Ratcliff-High	O
Way	O
?	O
Pen	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Man	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
wanted	O
one	O
minute	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
once	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
eating	O
a	O
Welch	O
rabbit	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
488	O
and	O
580	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
80	O
,	O
81	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Terrance	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Sarsfeild	I-pers
,	O
December	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
Terrance	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
out	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
get	O
home	O
to	O
Gutter-Lane	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
night	O
house	O
)	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
friends	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
an	O
alley	O
where	O
Michael	B-pers
Sarsfeild	I-pers
lives	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
for	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
box	O
:	O
he	O
saw	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Smith	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
fasten	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
called	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
82	O
,	O
83	O
,	O
84	O
,	O
85	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
salvatory	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
pencil-case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
lancet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
December	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
and	O
apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-End	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
coming	O
on	O
foot	O
along	O
the	O
New-road	B-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
stand	O
behind	O
a	O
watch-box	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
his	O
design	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
off	O
a	O
run	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
whistle	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
had	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
They	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
!	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
left	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
searched	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
pockets	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
my	O
salvatory	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
pencil	O
case	O
,	O
a	O
lances	O
,	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
pity	O
on	O
the	O
poor	O
weavers	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
high-constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
rotation	O
when	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
.	O
Conway	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brebrook	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Conway	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
greater	O
discovery	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
this	O
lancet	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Brebrook	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
lancet	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
silver	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
lancet	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
's	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
;	O
but	O
lancets	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
alike	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Conway	O
,	O
mention	O
this	O
without	O
being	O
assured	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
attend	O
the	O
rotation	O
at	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
Upon	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
these	O
prisoners	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
gunpowder	O
and	O
shot	O
upon	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
flints	O
upon	O
Paterson	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
rotation-office	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
examining	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
his	O
watch	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
man	O
here	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Conway	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
living	O
at	O
sea	O
.	O
That	O
lancet	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Flannagan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Conway	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
seafaring	O
way	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
character	O
that	O
Flannagan	O
gives	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
four	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
pocket	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Dec.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
Ratcliff	O
work-house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
from	O
Ratcliffe-cross	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Whitehorse-street	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
dark	O
lauthorn	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
people	O
coming	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Paterson	O
's	O
face	O
as	O
clear	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
their	O
foot-steps	O
.	O
One	O
came	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
shoulder	O
;	O
another	O
wrenched	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
's	O
faces	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
shorter	O
men	O
than	O
Paterson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
about	O
five	O
shillings	O
i	O
n	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eighteen-pence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
They	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
first	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys-out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
fire-arms	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
I	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Paterson	O
before	O
?	O
Chambers	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
Saturday	O
week	O
after	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
magistrate	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
tall	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
in	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
Paterson	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
sea	O
cap	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
his	O
sea	O
cap	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
say	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
concerning	O
some	O
robbery	O
.	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
took	O
his	O
information	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
always	O
used	O
Mackmullings	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Star	O
,	O
in	O
Star-street	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
there	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Conway	O
before	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
gunpowder	O
and	O
shot	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Mackmullings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pistol	O
found	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
In	O
Paterson	O
's	O
pocket	O
were	O
three	O
flints	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
these	O
men	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
skirmish	O
,	O
Paterson	O
dropped	O
the	O
pistol	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
Chapman	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Paterson	O
's	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
pistol	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
their	O
hands	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat-sheaf	O
.	O
In	O
Chapman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
powder	O
and	O
some	O
large	O
swan-shot	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Paterson	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
three	O
flints	O
.	O
The	O
knife	O
will	O
answer	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
screw-driver	O
.	O
Conway	O
was	O
one	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Chapman	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
On	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
Paterson	O
,	O
Conway	O
,	O
and	O
Milbank	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
together	O
.	O
Going	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
we	O
crossed	O
at	O
Tom	B-pers
Turdman	I-pers
's	O
Hole	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
asked	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
ten	O
.	O
Chapman	O
stopped	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
farthings	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Chapman	O
put	O
his	O
hat	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Milbank	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
Mile-End	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
a	O
man	O
upon	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
farthings	O
.	O
Chapman	O
or	O
Paterson	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
penny	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
stopped	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
three-half-pence	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
the	O
World's-End	O
,	O
by	O
Stepney	O
Church	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
met	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Chapman	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
his	O
lanthorn	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
Chapman	O
and	O
Paterson	O
rummaged	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
into	O
Conway	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
and	O
a	O
pocket-piece	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
.	O
Coming	O
to	O
Mackmullings	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Conway	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
but	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
brandy	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
but	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
He	O
trusted	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
had	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
your	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Chapman	O
buy	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
iron	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pocket-piece	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
an	O
eagle	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Conway	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
with	O
that	O
evidence	O
,	O
nor	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Lincolnshire	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
here	O
.	O
Paterson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
men	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
leave	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Indies	O
.	O
He	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
This	O
last	O
evidence	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
eyes	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
Pointer	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
together	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Mackmullings	O
's	O
.	O
For	O
Paterson	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
Paterson	O
's	O
brother	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Paterson	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Conway	O
and	O
Chapman	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
John	B-pers
China	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
China	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
White	O
chapel	O
road	O
up	O
the	O
New-road	B-place
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
met	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
They	O
passed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
.	O
Chapman	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
across	O
my	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Paterson	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
away	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
stripped	O
with	O
red	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
night	O
?	O
China	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
light	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
links	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
were	O
the	O
links	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
China	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
They	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
tremble	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
China	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Then	O
Paterson	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
only	O
plated	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
Chapman	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
ran	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
an	O
evidence	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Chapman	O
stuttered	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
flurry	O
and	O
frighted	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
an	O
impediment	O
in	O
his	O
speech	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
attend	O
the	O
rotation	O
at	O
times	O
.	O
Martin	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
admit	O
me	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
all	O
the	O
parties	O
are	O
that	O
have	O
done	O
all	O
these	O
robberies	O
on	O
the	O
New-road	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Star	O
in	O
Star-street	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Levi	O
,	O
Robinson	O
,	O
Pointon	O
and	O
Smith	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
these	O
men	O
were	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Levi	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
Do	O
you	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
know	O
you	O
.	O
Conway	O
said	O
,	O
Levi	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
public-house	O
.	O
Paterson	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
pursued	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
there	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
together	O
.	O
Milbank	O
that	O
is	O
cleared	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
hat	O
.	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
off	O
Chapman	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
take	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
hand-cuffed	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
along	O
the	O
back-lane	O
.	O
Chapman	O
takes	O
this	O
hat	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
right-hand	O
,	O
being	O
hand-cuffed	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
's	O
right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
heave	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
heave	O
it	O
away	O
for	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
heave	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
paper	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
crown	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
You	O
shall	O
have	O
this	O
hat	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
perhaps	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
an	O
owner	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
turnpike-man	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
footpads	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
applyed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
China	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
China	O
attended	O
the	O
Rotation	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
produced	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
hatter	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
,	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
New-church	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Chapman	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
shooting	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
only	O
to	O
scratch	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fore	O
head	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
these	O
men	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat-sheaf	O
,	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
their	O
pockets	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
powder	O
and	O
shot	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Chapman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
gun-flints	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
that	O
will	O
screw	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Paterson	O
's	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
bringing	O
them	O
along	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Chapman	O
wanted	O
to	O
sling	O
his	O
hat	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Paget	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Man-in-the-moon	O
,	O
by	O
Whitechapel	O
church	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Man-in-the-moon	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
their	O
shirts	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
ruffled	O
ones	O
.	O
Chapman	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
loath	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
any	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mackmulling	O
's	O
all	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Paterson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shire-lane	O
,	O
Temple	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
printer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	B-place
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
buying	O
some	O
china	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
behind	O
a	O
green-stall	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
standing	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
buy	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
;	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
see	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
a	O
poulterer	O
,	O
in	O
Old	O
Fish-street	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
shagreen-case-maker	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
.	O
Austin	B-pers
Strickson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
on	O
Labour-in-vain	O
Hill	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wonspear	I-pers
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
87	O
,	O
88	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
robe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
clouts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
89	O
,	O
90	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bowell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
.	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grosvenor-square	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Guild-hall	B-place
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
with	O
my	O
back	O
towards	O
these	O
lads	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Bowell	O
take	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
He	O
accused	O
Bowell	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
himself	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
drawing	O
the	O
lottery	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
boys	O
very	O
busy	O
at	O
several	O
gentlemens	O
pockets	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
leaned	O
over	O
the	O
rail	O
;	O
Jones	O
was	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Bowell	O
wheeled	O
round	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
accused	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
himself	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
this	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
Guild-hall	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
.	O
He	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
into	O
ten	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Bowell	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
Coleman-street	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
Guild-hall	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
laid	O
hole	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case-maker	O
.	O
Bowell	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Jones	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Bowell	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Bowen	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
42	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
.	O
91	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
neckcloath	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Guildhall	B-place
.	O
Just	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
drawing	O
the	O
tickets	O
,	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
,	O
concerning	O
what	O
tickets	O
had	O
been	O
drawn	O
.	O
Presently	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
came	O
and	O
tapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
your	O
pocket	O
picked	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
neckcloath	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Pain	O
ran	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
took	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
neckcloath	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
myself	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
work	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Steel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Greston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
drawer	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
cards	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
customers	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
off	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
glancing	O
my	O
eye	O
towards	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
motion	O
with	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
drew	O
my	O
attention	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
stool	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
,	O
some	O
lace	O
under	O
her	O
left-hand	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
cards	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
by	O
her	O
motion	O
,	O
she	O
shoved	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
right-hand	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
stood	O
behind	O
a	O
lady	O
that	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
some	O
double	O
blonds	O
;	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
The	O
lady	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
pay	O
another	O
time	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
any	O
lace	O
here	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
that	O
is	O
gone	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
more	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
midway	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
compting-house	O
door	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
possibly	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
further	O
conversation	O
.	O
I	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
her	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Can	O
you	O
send	O
for	O
any	O
person	O
of	O
character	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
rather	O
impertinent	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
an	O
alderman	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lace	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
ever	O
seeing	O
her	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
before	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
hard	O
of	O
hearing	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
throwed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
near	O
Smithfield-bars	O
;	O
Margaret	B-pers
Freak	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Cow-lane	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Quakers-buildings	O
;	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
George-yard	O
,	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
industrious	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
five	O
small	O
children	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
without	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
decent	O
manner	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
mother	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Shelmadine	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
94	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darke	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
