TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1770	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Tenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
Bladon	O
,	O
at	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
1st	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter-Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bullock	I-pers
William	B-pers
Kersill	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bowley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Houham	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Jerom	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Farey	I-pers
Anderton	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
George	B-pers
Pym	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
.	O
1st	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Vardey	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Shewell	I-pers
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
William	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
James	B-pers
Box	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edmundson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Elkins	I-pers
.	O
2	O
d	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Green	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brooksbank	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Cheeswright	I-pers
George	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
John	B-pers
Leasey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Faiton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Garrett	I-pers
.	O
2	O
d	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Thornwait	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Watson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
216	O
,	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roderick	B-pers
M'Cannon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Roderick	B-pers
M'Cannon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
an	O
apothecary	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
at	O
Hyde-park-corner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fool	O
enough	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
into	O
a	O
dirty	O
alley	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
coat-pocket	O
for	O
safety	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dark	O
alley	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
breeches	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
high	O
nor	O
low	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
candle	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
directed	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
,	O
if	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
as	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
reward	O
I	O
had	O
offered	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
made	O
me	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Jos	O
.	O
Jenkinson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murthwate	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Great	O
Poultney-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pledged	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
like	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Elisha	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Mason	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
my	O
eyes	O
.	O
Duck	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Knightsbridge	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
this	O
alley	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
pledged	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
detained	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
woman	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
my	O
eyes	O
before	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Ribe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
scarificator	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
catheter	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scales	O
,	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
cock-spurs	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
ditto	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Exeter-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
barber	O
surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
surgeon	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
medicines	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
near	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
cupping-instrument	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
catheter	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
cock-spurs	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
ones	O
and	O
eight	O
of	O
silver	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
after	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
daubed	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
countrymen	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
could	O
do	O
.	O
them	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
to	O
clean	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
;	O
that	O
friend	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
to	O
Amsterdam	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
friend	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
myself	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
cupping	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
these	O
instruments	O
with	O
his	O
patients	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cock-spurs	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
pricked	O
my	O
finger	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
cock-spurs	O
.	O
Master	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
two	O
doors	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
such	O
things	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
seven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
At	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
rented	O
a	O
garret	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Sarsfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dignam	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
a	O
person	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
coalheaver	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
lock	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
Sarsfield	O
and	O
Dignam	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
each	O
.	O
Said	O
Sarsfield	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
victuals	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
mutton	O
chops	O
at	O
the	O
Blakeney	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
They	O
whispered	O
together	O
.	O
Sarsfield	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
whispered	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
rented	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
garret	O
;	O
we	O
worked	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Sarsfield	I-pers
that	O
took	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Sarsfield	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
78	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
sent	O
his	O
men	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
for	O
debt	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
talk	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
about	O
making	O
this	O
matter	O
up	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
They	O
offered	O
me	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
way	O
of	O
business	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
apply	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
money	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
your	O
master	O
about	O
borrowing	O
money	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
money	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
borrow	O
while	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
.	O
I	O
rented	O
a	O
garret	O
of	O
James	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
and	O
unlocked	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
Christmas	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
locked	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Sarsfield	O
came	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
at	O
work	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Where	O
is	O
my	O
landlord	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
o'clock	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
just	O
eight	O
.	O
That	O
time	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Sarsfield	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
.	O
Sarsfield	O
sat	O
down	O
facing	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
club	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
round	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
James	O
Hall	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
Sarsfield	O
said	O
directly	O
,	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
by	O
Jesus	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Sarsfield	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
was	O
standing	O
over	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
or	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
talking	O
to	O
Sarsfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
plainly	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
examined	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Sarsfield	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
alarm	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
stir	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Sarsfield	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
my	O
landlord	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
My	O
room	O
is	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
from	O
their	O
going	O
away	O
till	O
my	O
landlord	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
being	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
mention	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
Lee	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Sarsfield	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
Sarsfield	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
landlord	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Sarsfield	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
and	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
countrymen	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
mine	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
Monday	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
seven	O
guineas	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Welshman	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
coach	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
where	O
this	O
Hall	O
lives	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
last	O
evidence	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
any	O
body	O
power	O
to	O
offer	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
shoe-maker	O
.	O
Hall	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Christmas	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
Christmas	O
week	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
shoes	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
marshal's-court	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Russell-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
money	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
paid	O
it	O
again	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
M'Man	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eighteen	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
done	O
business	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Lynam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
220	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
of	O
insane	O
mind	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
.	O
221	O
,	O
222	O
,	O
223	O
,	O
224	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crookhall	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
eleven	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
seven	O
copper	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
box	O
and	O
metal	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty-one	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Brewer's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
:	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
and	O
goods	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
proved	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
who	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Colby	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Crookhall	O
only	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
:	O
th	O
at	O
Ford	O
and	O
Miller	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
behind	O
Montague	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
Peter	O
Graham	O
's	O
house-keeper	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
then	O
on	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Crookhall	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
themselves	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
to	O
corroborate	O
his	O
testimony	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
1st	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
three	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
soup	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
soup	O
spoon	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Conduit-street	B-place
;	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
proved	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Colby	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
belived	O
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
drove	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
Graham	O
's	O
,	O
not	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
evidence	O
not	O
being	O
supported	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
2d	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
three	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Yorke	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
ten	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
soup	O
spoon	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
sauce	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-strainer	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
salt	O
sellers	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
half-pint	O
mugs	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
ditto	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
fish	O
trewel	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
stove	O
dish	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
five	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
butter	O
boats	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
bread	O
basket	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
strainer	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
sugar	O
basons	O
and	O
covers	O
,	O
two	O
small	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
filligree	O
essence	O
boxes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Martin	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
laid	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
147	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
++	O
Martin	B-pers
Yorke	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
400	O
l.	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
carefully	O
inspected	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
plate	O
as	O
mentioned	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
stair-case	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
chest	O
made	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
contain	O
plate	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
great	O
confusion	O
;	O
the	O
shutter	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
chissel	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
through	O
,	O
or	O
broke	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
parted	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
that	O
shuts	O
the	O
kitchen	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
pannels	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
a	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
cabinet	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
.	O
The	O
cupboard	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
kept	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
scattered	O
about	O
.	O
A	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
had	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
had	O
seen	O
Miller	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
their	O
examination	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
thing	O
material	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Major	O
Yorke	O
in	O
Grosvenor-square	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Upper-Brooke-street	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
all	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
area	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
then	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
only	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
house-maid	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
disturbance	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
house-maid	O
went	O
down	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
almost	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pannel	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
that	O
window	O
shoved	O
up	O
:	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
shutters	O
shut	O
to	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
bolt	O
within	O
.	O
The	O
area	O
gate	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
butler	O
's	O
drawer	O
was	O
broke	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
chissel	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
places	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
chissels	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
tinder-box	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
and	O
some	O
matches	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
tinder	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
light	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
house-keeper	O
's	O
room	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
locks	O
broke	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
writings	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
a	O
breast-buckle	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Gobey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
pantry	O
up	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
plate	O
chest	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
pantry	O
door	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
chest	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
filligree	O
boxes	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Colby	I-pers
.	O
Ford	O
,	O
Crookall	O
,	O
and	O
Miller	O
,	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Hyde-park	O
,	O
coming	O
back	O
by	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
Crookall	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
plate	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
fixed	O
upon	O
that	O
house	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
At	O
night	O
we	O
met	O
all	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Boot	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
there	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Grosvenor-square	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
plate	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
iron	O
gate	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
chissel	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
mine	O
and	O
wrenched	O
the	O
gate	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
farther	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
the	O
chissel	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
gave	O
way	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
fingers	O
under	O
it	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
hoisted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parrot	O
cage	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
light	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
grate	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
tinder	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
strike	O
on	O
the	O
brimstone	O
matches	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
fire	O
.	O
Crookall	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
under	O
the	O
shutters	O
and	O
the	O
draught	O
of	O
air	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
cut	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
bringing	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
and	O
nobody	O
brought	O
a	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
lighted	O
it	O
myself	O
at	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
;	O
Crookhall	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
a	O
little	O
door	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
:	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
of	O
any	O
value	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
from	O
the	O
dresser	O
and	O
cut	O
a	O
pannel	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bar	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
shot	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
spring	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
move	O
.	O
I	O
shoved	O
the	O
spring	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
Crookhall	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
some	O
china	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
bureau	O
desk	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
breast-buckle	O
and	O
a	O
ring	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
pantry	O
like	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
Crookhall	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
open	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
what	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
where	O
were	O
books	O
:	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
place	O
with	O
empty	O
drawers	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
ivory	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
Coming	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
window	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
Crookhall	O
looked	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
shine	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shoved	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
waiter	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
plate	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
chest	O
stood	O
upon	O
another	O
chest	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
we	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
plate	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
very	O
large	O
plate	O
,	O
butter-boats	O
,	O
sauce-boats	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
waiter	O
,	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
punch	O
ladle	O
;	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
closet	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
:	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
cupboard	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
we	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
green	O
cloth	O
which	O
Crookhall	O
brought	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
parcel	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
would	O
not	O
hold	O
it	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
gown	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
peg	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
into	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
plate	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Piccadiily	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
fearing	O
the	O
waggons	O
should	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
things	O
we	O
had	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Graham	O
's	O
at	O
Salt-peter-bank	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
Crookhall	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
plate	O
was	O
carried	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
staid	O
below	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scales	O
brought	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
weighed	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
three	O
hundred	O
and	O
thirty-three	O
ounces	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
us	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
60	O
l.	O
he	O
paid	O
54	O
l.	O
and	O
left	O
6	O
l.	O
remaining	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
on	O
a	O
bed	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
awaked	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
money	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
15	O
l.	O
each	O
:	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
received	O
the	O
other	O
6	O
l.	O
yet	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washer	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
wash	O
at	O
Lord	O
Shastesbury	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
fourth	O
door	O
cross	O
from	O
Major	O
Yorke	B-pers
's	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Miller	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
two	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
candle	O
;	O
the	O
snuff	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
very	O
low	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
woman	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
?	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
in	O
lighting	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
more	O
time	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Lane	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
knew	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
hat	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
cloth	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
a	O
long	O
way	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
difficulty	O
to	O
carry	O
your	O
candle	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
of	O
Major	O
Yorke	B-pers
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
off	O
the	O
steps	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
parted	O
we	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
young	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
two	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
towards	O
Lord	O
Shaftesbury	O
's	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
along	O
:	O
that	O
was	O
Ford	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Dunn	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
asked	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Ford	O
had	O
been	O
making	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	O
Shaftesbury	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
before	O
the	O
butler	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
Dunn	O
came	O
to	O
Lord	O
Shaftesbury	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
twice	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
towards	O
Major	O
Yorke	B-pers
's	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
singing	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
chissels	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
produce	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
at	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
far	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
keep	O
it	O
alight	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
doing	O
his	O
breeches	O
up	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Lord	O
Shaftesbury	O
's	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Miller	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Major	O
Yorke	B-pers
's	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
my	O
partner	O
to	O
light	O
his	O
candle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kenney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Miller	O
,	O
Crookhall	O
,	O
Dunn	O
,	O
and	O
Graham	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Colby	B-pers
the	O
evidence	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
on	O
Saltpeter-bank	O
.	O
Six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Colby	O
and	O
Crookhall	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
then	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bundle	O
on	O
Graham	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
peck	O
measure	O
.	O
Colby	O
and	O
Crookhall	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Graham	O
's	O
wife	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
a	O
basket	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
some	O
where	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fish-basket	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
fish	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
was	O
tyed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
coarse	O
cloth	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
saw	O
Miller	O
;	O
in	O
carrying	O
it	O
my	O
head	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
bear	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
jingling	O
in	O
it	O
like	O
plate	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
somebody	O
called	O
,	O
Morea	O
!	O
(	O
I	O
served	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
gone	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
imagine	O
that	O
was	O
Graham	O
that	O
called	O
me	O
.	O
Ford	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
spend	O
four-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
.	O
Colby	O
and	O
Crookhall	O
met	O
me	O
.	O
Miller	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
Grosvenor-square	O
.	O
He	O
stopped	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
and	O
talked	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Colby	O
and	O
Crookhall	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Miller	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
;	O
these	O
washer-women	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
seeing	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
golden	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
back	O
Colby	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
that	O
one	O
guinea	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
washer-women	O
should	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
liberty	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
evidence	O
next	O
sessions	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
back	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
bind	O
these	O
people	O
to	O
prosecute	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Crookhall	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
evidence	O
against	O
this	O
Colby	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
up	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
One	O
morning	O
since	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Colby	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
any	O
longer	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
,	O
opposite	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
Round	B-pers
-house	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Colby	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
Miller	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
foreman	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
Graham	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
Colby	O
will	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
sold	O
me	O
the	O
plate	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
To	O
Ford	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
Ford	O
is	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
He	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
then	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Adley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
He	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lemant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
good	O
servant	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
trouble	O
before	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Caswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
harmless	O
man	O
.	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
For	O
Miller	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Haxon	I-pers
.	O
Miller	O
was	O
a	O
turn-over	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carver	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Miller	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
his	O
first	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Crookhall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
here	O
.	O
Graham	O
.	O
Mine	O
are	O
all	O
gone	O
home	O
.	O
Ford	O
,	O
Miller	O
,	O
and	O
Crookhall	O
;	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Graham	O
,	O
Guilty	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
See	O
Crookhall	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Murphy	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
119	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
Colbeck	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
evidence	O
Colby	O
.	O
See	O
Graham	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
143	O
,	O
578	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Bagnall	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
467	O
.	O
And	O
see	O
them	O
both	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
477	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
:	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
jug	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
tea	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Lion-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury-market	I-place
.	O
He	O
proved	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
window-shutter	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
not	O
quite	O
shut	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
jumped	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
One	O
he	O
thought	O
like	O
Graham	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Burton	O
,	O
did	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Graham	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
though	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
in	O
his	O
information	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Burton	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
only	O
Underwood	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
while	O
Burton	O
and	O
he	O
watched	O
the	O
two	O
ends	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
)	O
His	O
account	O
being	O
unsupported	O
by	O
any	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Graham	O
and	O
Burton	O
tried	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Bagnall	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
226	O
,	O
227	O
,	O
228	O
,	O
229	O
,	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ogilvie	I-pers
,	O
Shepherd	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Nares	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
serjeants	O
at	O
law	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
diamond	O
ear-rings	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
one	O
amethyst	O
ring	O
set	O
round	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
ink-stand	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
plain	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
mourning	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
two	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
five	O
and	O
three-penny	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
three-pences	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
two-pences	O
,	O
two	O
purses	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Nares	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Maguines	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
plate	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stancliff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Mr.	O
serjeant	O
Nares	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
are	O
fast	O
before	O
we	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
at	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
forward	O
,	O
the	O
ground	O
room	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
main	O
force	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
some	O
very	O
strong	O
instrument	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
?	O
Stancliff	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
daylight	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Nares	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
as	O
early	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
rather	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
setts	O
of	O
window-shutters	O
,	O
the	O
outward	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
inward	O
.	O
The	O
outward	O
were	O
to	O
pull	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
bolt	O
withinside	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
within	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bolt	O
comes	O
down	O
to	O
fasten	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
outward	O
bolt	O
was	O
wrenched	O
by	O
an	O
instrument	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
dressing-room	O
.	O
The	O
outward	O
bolt	O
was	O
wrenched	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
bent	O
;	O
the	O
screws	O
were	O
drawn	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
bend	O
it	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
shutter	O
come	O
open	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
came	O
directly	O
down	O
cross	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
bar	O
;	O
had	O
it	O
fell	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
alarmed	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
curtain	O
had	O
catched	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
marks	O
of	O
mens	O
feet	O
on	O
the	O
pallisades	O
where	O
they	O
stood	O
to	O
wrench	O
the	O
shutter	O
.	O
My	O
bureau	O
was	O
all	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
study	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
)	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
ink-stand	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
night	O
put	O
an	O
amethyst	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
hollow	O
of	O
the	O
ink-stand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
taken	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
glasses	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
stand	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
searched	O
all	O
the	O
papers	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
dressing-room	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
childrens	O
perquisites	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
emptied	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
one	O
purse	O
there	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
in	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
dressing-room	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
surprised	O
by	O
something	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
left	O
their	O
instrument	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
a	O
strong	O
iron	O
chissel	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
purses	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
king	O
James	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
well-preserved	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
likewise	O
a	O
queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
wife	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
day-light	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Nares	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
perfect	O
day-light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
are	O
more	O
two	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
as	O
well	O
preserved	O
as	O
that	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Nares	O
.	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nares	O
.	O
The	O
purses	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
about	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
two	O
two	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
both	O
very	O
fresh	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
a	O
queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
guineas	O
besides	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
of	O
king	O
William	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
out	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
freshness	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
another	O
circumstance	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
She	O
takes	O
up	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
)	O
As	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
guinea	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Nares	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
this	O
guinea	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
upon	O
the	O
cheek	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Now	O
it	O
is	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
mark	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
remarkable	O
a	O
spot	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nares	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
diamond	O
ear-ring	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Miss	O
Nares	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
guinea	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
particular	O
spot	O
of	O
dirt	O
upon	O
the	O
cheek	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
mine	O
;	O
here	O
now	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
guineas	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Young	O
Mr.	O
Nares	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
which	O
is	O
here	O
produced	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
court	O
and	O
jury	O
inspect	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Wood	O
,	O
Ogilvie	O
,	O
Shepherd	O
Strutton	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
skittles	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
pretty	O
freely	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
pretty	O
late	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
George-alley	O
,	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
to	O
supper	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fowl	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
down	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
serjeant	O
Nares	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Wood	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
try	O
if	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
get	O
this	O
house	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
near	O
Chancery-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
then	O
about	O
breaking	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
either	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
bolts	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Ogilvie	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
By-and-by	O
Wood	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
Ogilvie	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Wood	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Ogilvie	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Wood	O
stopped	O
at	O
serjeant	O
Nare	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Strutton	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Wood	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
together	O
when	O
we	O
stopped	O
at	O
serjeant	O
Nares	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Strutton	O
and	O
Wood	O
together	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Maguines	I-pers
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
Maguines	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
Ogilvie	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
.	O
Wood	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Maguines	O
for	O
22	O
l.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
diamonds	O
.	O
Maguines	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
Hockley-in-the-hole	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
turner	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
share	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
divided	O
it	O
in	O
Maguines	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Maguines	O
's	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
's	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
wife	O
told	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
Wood	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Wood	O
took	O
Ogilvie	O
's	O
share	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
ready	O
money	O
divided	O
,	O
that	O
amounted	O
to	O
about	O
two	O
guineas	O
each	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
divided	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Wood	O
or	O
Strutton	O
say	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Lumley	O
's	O
from	O
Maguines	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
money	O
consist	O
in	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Ogilvie	O
have	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
mother	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
mentioned	O
this	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
at	O
Lumley	O
's	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Maguines	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
people	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
feast	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
Maguines	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
yet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Wood	O
that	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
understand	O
you	O
:	O
Had	O
Wood	O
sold	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Wood	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
seven	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
wife	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Wood	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
silver	O
stand-dish	O
,	O
nor	O
ear-rings	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
ready	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
Carey-street	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
homes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
Maguines	O
's	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
notion	O
of	O
meeting	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
often	O
called	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
nothing	O
particular	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
was	O
divided	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
each	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
each	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
guineas	O
each	O
was	O
divided	O
first	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nares	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
twenty-two	O
guineas	O
were	O
divided	O
not	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
Maguines	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
went	O
and	O
hid	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
ruins	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
thing	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
indict	O
me	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
chissel	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
now	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
when	O
they	O
stopt	O
at	O
Mr.	O
serjeant	O
Nares	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
tools	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Wood	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
Lumley	O
's	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
Maguines	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
Maguines	O
?	O
Tell	O
the	O
very	O
words	O
.	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Wood	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
yet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
any	O
appointment	O
with	O
Maguines	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
often	O
out	O
with	O
Maguines	O
at	O
skittles	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
walking	O
on	O
Sundays	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Haliburton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Ogilvie	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Ogilvie	O
's	O
pocket	O
either	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
twenty-seven	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
five	O
and	O
threepenny	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
produced	O
that	O
money	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
together	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nares	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
picked	O
out	O
at	O
once	O
the	O
queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Ogilvie	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Haliburton	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
mother	O
had	O
money	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
particular	O
direction	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
in	O
Hare-court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Freeland	O
,	O
a	O
stationer	O
,	O
in	O
Carey-street	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
serjeant	O
Nares	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
over-against	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
three	O
young	O
fellows	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
some	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
dress	O
.	O
He	O
lifted	O
himself	O
up	O
upon	O
his	O
toes	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
on	O
tiptoe	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Nares	O
's	O
parlour	O
.	O
They	O
rather	O
cast	O
their	O
eyes	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
looking	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bolts	O
and	O
shutters	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Bagnall	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Barron	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Watkins	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
walked	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
and	O
bolts	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
,	O
Bagnall	O
the	O
evidence	O
stood	O
upon	O
his	O
toes	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Hall	O
.	O
Bagnall	O
lived	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoners	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
beds	O
had	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
S.	O
Hall	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
one	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
one	O
room	O
,	O
an	O
upper	O
room	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
George-alley	O
,	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
a	O
night	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
on	O
an	O
evening	O
?	O
S.	O
Hall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
Ogilvie	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
S.	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tavern	O
in	O
Goodman's-fields	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Strutton	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
in	O
our	O
house	O
together	O
.	O
Once	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
Strutton	O
,	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
Bagnall	O
had	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
once	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Maguines	O
with	O
Bagnall	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Raven	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
evidence	O
Bagnall	O
?	O
Lumley	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
besides	O
Maguines	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
feast	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
Lumley	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
Maguines	O
was	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
Maguines	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
feast	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
some	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Bagnall	O
?	O
J.	O
Lumley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
nor	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
besides	O
Maguines	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Maguines	O
?	O
J.	O
Lumley	O
.	O
I	O
neither	O
saw	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
ill	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
Ogilvie	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Strutton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Wood	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
intirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
Maguines	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Bagnall	O
is	O
got	O
into	O
some	O
hobble	O
or	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
life	O
away	O
to	O
get	O
himself	O
clear	O
.	O
To	O
Wood	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Haggard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
engine	O
winder	O
for	O
the	O
weavers	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
Wood	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
sober	O
a	O
lad	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Banfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Wood	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
lad	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
now	O
?	O
E.	O
Banfield	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
the	O
Turk's-head	O
,	O
by	O
Westminster-bridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
when	O
you	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Banfield	O
.	O
In	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Banfield	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
?	O
E.	O
Banfield	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
things	O
reported	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
heard	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
several	O
times	O
lately	O
?	O
E.	O
Banfield	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Ogilvie	O
,	O
Strutton	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
,	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Maguines	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
230	O
,	O
231	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Shepherd	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Ogilivie	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-street	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
the	O
18th	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
my	O
desk	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
drawers	O
all	O
thrown	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tobacco-box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Guest	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
cut	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dorton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
house	O
shut	O
up	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
but	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Wood	O
,	O
Bagnall	O
,	O
and	O
Strutton	O
tried	O
together	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
486	O
,	O
487	O
,	O
488	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Turner	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Peter	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
tried	O
for	O
another	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
577	O
,	O
578	O
,	O
579	O
,	O
580	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
Bagnall	O
tried	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
579	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Harley	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Graham	O
,	O
Underwood	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
See	O
Strutton	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
79	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
232	O
,	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
2	O
d.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gew	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Leonard	B-pers
Tresillian	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
a	O
six-and-nine-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Leonard	B-pers
Tresillian	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
in	O
my	O
chariot	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
I	O
hardly	O
saw	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
gin	O
.	O
They	O
commanded	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
stop	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
that	O
side	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
,	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
six-and-nine-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
going	O
off	O
he	O
fired	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
whether	O
he	O
aimed	O
at	O
the	O
coachman	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
threatened	O
to	O
shoot	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
horses	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
smallish	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
round	O
cut	O
hat	O
on	O
;	O
a	O
lightish	O
bay	O
horse	O
(	O
a	O
poor	O
horse	O
)	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
swish	O
tail	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
and	O
an	O
inch	O
high	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Tresillian	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
moon-light	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
crape	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
(	O
upon	O
seeing	O
the	O
advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
)	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
Gew	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Fulham	B-place
.	O
A	O
highwayman	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chariot	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
plain	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
mask	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
on	O
;	O
his	O
coat	O
was	O
buttoned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cape	O
pulled	O
up	O
round	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
his	O
horse	O
was	O
a	O
lightish	O
bay	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
hands	O
high	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
moon-light	O
.	O
He	O
threatened	O
to	O
blow	O
the	O
coachman	O
's	O
brains	O
out	O
:	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
fired	O
at	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
just	O
looked	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
went	O
off	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
ball	O
whiz	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
scarfe	O
before	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Britannia	O
they	O
were	O
calling	O
there	O
for	O
gin	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
second	O
man	O
come	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
Britannia	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
a	O
brown	O
horse	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gandall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
Gew	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
pistol	O
and	O
this	O
crape	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
horn	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
powder	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
sword	O
,	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
tester	O
of	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
accomplice	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
one	O
Marshall	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
his	O
clothes	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
.	O
(	O
That	O
pistol	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
with	O
much	O
such	O
a	O
pistol	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
when	O
Gew	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
his	O
girl	O
was	O
brought	O
also	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
Marshall	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
clothes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
blow	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
brains	O
out	O
that	O
should	O
offer	O
to	O
attack	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
court	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Gandall	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
was	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
step	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
answering	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
Marshall	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Marshall	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
some	O
other	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
pardon	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
your	O
waistcoat	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
described	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
striped	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
under	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
under	O
that	O
)	O
He	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
slap	O
of	O
his	O
upper	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
name	O
is	O
Marshall	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Search	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
not	O
loaded	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
balls	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
crape	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White-horse	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
Long-acre	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
hired	O
two	O
horses	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Rumford	O
together	O
;	O
Marshall	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
spoke	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
by	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
their	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
returned	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
they	O
hired	O
two	O
more	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
mare	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
ride	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hired	O
one	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
They	O
ordered	O
two	O
other	O
horses	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
coming	O
in	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
horses	O
did	O
they	O
ride	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
?	O
Downing	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
two	O
dark	O
brown	O
horses	O
with	O
swish	O
tails	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
ride	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
Downing	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
little	O
chestnut	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
a	O
sorrel	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
swish	O
tail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
condition	O
was	O
the	O
sorrel	O
horse	O
?	O
Downing	O
.	O
In	O
good	O
condition	O
.	O
They	O
mounted	O
first	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
's	O
yard	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Marshall	O
a	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
them	O
together	O
before	O
?	O
Downing	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
mounted	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
horse	O
did	O
Gew	O
ride	O
?	O
Downing	O
.	O
He	O
mounted	O
the	O
light-coloured	O
horse	O
.	O
Gew	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
into	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
fired	O
these	O
pistols	O
off	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
upon	O
the	O
coach-box	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
from	O
Suffolk	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
black	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Marshall	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
cutlass	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
pistols	O
I	O
bought	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sudbury	O
we	O
fired	O
them	O
off	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
that	O
caul	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
hair	O
dressed	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
at	O
Rumford	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
we	O
dined	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Dulwich	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
fortune	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
trifle	O
a	O
year	O
for	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Marshall	O
called	O
two	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
but	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
234	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
repeating	O
table	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
twenty	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
strainers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt-seller	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt-shovel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nightengall	I-pers
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Feb	O
.	O
Sessions	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
159	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
paper	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nightengall	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
on	O
that	O
trial	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Colby	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
,	O
on	O
that	O
trial	O
,	O
Crookhall	O
calls	O
Colebeck	O
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
Crookhall	O
aid	O
on	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Crookhall	O
and	O
Murphy	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Underwood	O
for	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
evidence	O
not	O
being	O
confirmed	O
by	O
any	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Underwood	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
235	O
,	O
236	O
,	O
237	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gahagan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
poker	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
fire-shovel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
.	O
++	O
This	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
outrage	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
felonious	O
intent	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
238	O
,	O
239	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hodge	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
velvet	O
pall	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
April	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
burying	O
Mr.	O
Nicholson	O
's	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Southwark	I-place
.	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
came	O
forwards	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
corpse	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
velvet	O
pall	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
coffin	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
send	O
and	O
borrow	O
another	O
to	O
perform	O
the	O
burying	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
came	O
Paget	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
informed	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
by	O
Farrell	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
coffin	O
,	O
and	O
Martin	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
into	O
seventeen	O
pieces	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
by	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Martin	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
chief	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
discover	O
other	O
robberies	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
240	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Felix-alley	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
.	O
I	O
lett	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready-furnished	O
lodging	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lett	O
her	O
a	O
lodging	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
behaved	O
well	O
then	O
:	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
weeks	O
;	O
at	O
about	O
the	O
nineth	O
week	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
clean	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
her	O
foul	O
ones	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
.	O
Robert	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
looking-glass	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
sheets	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
I	O
owned	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
wrong	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
242	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
Prince's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
an	O
evidence	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
found	O
him	O
putting	O
my	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
my	O
coat	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
.	O
He	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
coat	O
stands	O
out	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
under	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
turn	O
midwife	O
:	O
I	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
saw	O
mine	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pockets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
(	O
243	O
.	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Osmer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Osmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
bed-side	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
lay	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
William	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
hang	O
your	O
watch	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
fasten	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
under	O
mine	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
let	O
himself	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
brought	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
five	O
guineas	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Osmer	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
writer	O
for	O
an	O
attorney	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ground-floor	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
one	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
unlock	O
it	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
company	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
cards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
and	O
regulate	O
it	O
by	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
six	O
guineas	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
lie	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
he	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
then	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
watch	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
fellow	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
gave	O
but	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
dial-plate	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
made	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Dalrymple	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Urquhart	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
honestly	O
before	O
this	O
offence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
244	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-one	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Tomison	B-pers
Dearsley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
245	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
.	O
1st	O
.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Batchelor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Delaforce	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Delaforce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Nortonfalgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
with	O
an	O
