TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
19th	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BRASS	O
CROSBY	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
EVANS	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
54	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BRASS	B-pers
CROSBY	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
*	O
and	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
~	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
1st	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charleton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Reybout	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hander	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Barnet	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skilbeck	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Delafont	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Doddington	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
served	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
instead	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Simpson	I-pers
;	O
John	B-pers
Beckley	I-pers
,	O
instead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
.	O
1st	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dearlove	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thresher	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fosbrook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
2d	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lamborne	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wheeble	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cussell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Worster	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Maiding	I-pers
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
served	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
instead	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wheeble	I-pers
.	O
534	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
postern	O
at	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
twitch	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
my	O
pardon	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
535	O
,	O
536	O
,	O
537	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hayne	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Sarah	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
but	O
the	O
accomplice	O
's	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
538	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pistol	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
pistol	O
mounted	O
with	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wm	O
.	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
insane	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
539	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Dutchess	I-pers
Dowager	I-pers
of	I-pers
Newcastle	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1st	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
Duchess	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
farm	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
park	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
bed	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
farm-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bed	O
home	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
up	O
into	O
bolsters	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
furnish	O
a	O
cradle	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
from	O
whom	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
bed	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
540	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Bedwell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brown	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5.	O
two	O
pair	O
mens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
mens	O
ribb	O
'd	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
mens	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
white	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Price	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
some	O
goods	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
can	O
give	O
the	O
particulars	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
3d	O
July	O
we	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
the	B-place
Star	I-place
livery	I-place
stables	I-place
,	I-place
Carey-street	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
live	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
four	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
sold	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Price	O
there	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
coat	O
and	O
shoes	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Bedwell	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
-	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Bedwell	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pledge	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
scrupled	O
their	O
being	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
her	O
sister	O
to	O
satisfy	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
Price	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
friends	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
my	O
trial	O
would	O
come	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
free	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
Bedwell	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
here	O
.	O
Price	O
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Bedwell	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
541	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Deborah	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
gauze	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pap	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
and	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
,	O
August	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
over	O
night	O
I	O
saw	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
appearances	O
there	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
somebody	O
that	O
had	O
secreted	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gold	O
stock	O
buckle	O
.	O
The	O
bundle	O
was	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
fresh	O
earth	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
Mary	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gowen	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
garden	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
apartments	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
as	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
apartments	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
she	O
secreted	O
herself	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
continued	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
candle	O
burning	O
on	O
a	O
hogshead	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
cruel	O
to	O
burn	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
beds	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
.	O
``	O
-	O
Stugess	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
confessed	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
girl	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
when	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Catherine	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
to	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
six	O
last	O
years	O
.	O
''	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
542	O
,	O
543	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Godbolt	I-pers
and	O
Harden	B-pers
Handland	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Frederick	B-pers
Huhff	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
certain	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Frederick	O
,	O
July	O
1st	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Godbolt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Harden	B-pers
Handland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Henry	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
21	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
July	O
1st	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Hill-street	O
,	O
Oxford-market	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Kilborn	B-place
,	O
home	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Yorkshire	B-place
Stingo	I-place
two	O
men	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
tall	O
the	O
other	O
short	O
;	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
easy	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Whilst	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
they	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
pistol	O
and	O
wrenched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
stept	O
after	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
too	O
fast	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
at	O
him	O
or	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
pretty	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
fire	O
the	O
pistol	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
flashed	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
run	O
no	O
further	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
made	O
off	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
Portland	O
Square	O
.	O
One	O
thing	O
I	O
observed	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
round	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
he	O
hopp	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
darkish	O
,	O
not	O
very	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Godbolt	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Godbolt	O
lame	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
lame	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
called	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
servants	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
run	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
very	O
fast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
The	O
tall	O
one	O
had	O
light	O
coloured	O
clothes	O
,	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
dark	O
brown	O
or	O
black	O
,	O
brown	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
hair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
great	O
coats	O
or	O
common	O
coats	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
furtout	O
coats	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
sure	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
them	O
speak	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
only	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
speak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
recollection	O
of	O
his	O
voice	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
belief	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
or	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
The	O
tall	O
one	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pistol	O
about	O
a	O
foot	O
long	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
charged	O
half	O
up	O
with	O
short	O
pieces	O
of	O
tobacco-pipe	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
coat	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
At	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
several	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
coat	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
described	O
.	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
robbery	O
;	O
only	O
I	O
heard	O
Godbolt	O
say	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
or	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bad	O
luck	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
bad	O
luck	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
stopt	O
a	O
gentleman	O
and	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
in	O
the	O
trigger	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pulled	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
gentleman	O
being	O
rather	O
stronger	O
,	O
got	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
hearing	O
somebody	O
coming	O
up	O
on	O
horseback	O
or	O
a	O
foot	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
this	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
The	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Sunday	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Thursday	O
or	O
Friday	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
Godbolt	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
told	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
after	O
the	O
robbing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hhuff	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
we	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Hhuff	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
or	O
Thursday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
pistol	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
Ours	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
hook	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
hook	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
It	O
has	O
a	O
hook	O
5	O
inches	O
long	O
to	O
hang	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
you	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Hhuff	O
with	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Godbolt	O
;	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
pistol	O
;	O
we	O
always	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Godbolt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
ammunition	O
did	O
you	O
load	O
it	O
with	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
;	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
primed	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
happened	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
somewhere	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
separate	O
places	O
near	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
was	O
Godbolt	O
dressed	O
in	O
that	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
his	O
ill	O
luck	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
coat	O
on	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
that	O
coat	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
after	O
that	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Godbolt	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
drank	O
gin	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Sheredine	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Godbolt	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Godbolt	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Handland	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
544	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
metal	O
covered	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
inside	O
case	O
metal	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
metal	O
covered	O
with	O
fish-skin	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
July	O
17th	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
:	O
we	O
are	O
watch-makers	O
,	O
in	O
Change-alley	B-place
;	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
shop	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
four	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watches	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
not	O
quite	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
errands	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
attend	O
the	O
rotation	O
office	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Buckle-street	O
,	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
had	O
picked	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
thought	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
person	O
whose	O
wife	O
wore	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
master	O
of	O
four	O
watches	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
at	O
Inglestone	O
,	O
another	O
at	O
Eastham	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
travelling	O
Jew	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
watch	O
and	O
the	O
trinkets	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
Moody	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Inglestone	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
keeps	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
valued	O
before	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
?	O
Moody	O
.	O
Much	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Winck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Eastham	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
pinchbeck	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Martha	B-pers
Winck	I-pers
.	O
Pinchbeeck	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
when	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
I	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Pewter	O
Platter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
545	O
,	O
546	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Summerayse	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
gold	O
breast	O
buckle	O
set	O
with	O
garnets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
chocolate	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
3-4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
roasted	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
3-4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
lump	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
3-4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
brown	O
sugar-candy	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
20.	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
green	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
24	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
tea	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
linen	O
cloths	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
for	O
receiving	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
excepting	O
the	O
breast	O
buckle	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Lime-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
10	O
months	O
.	O
By	O
an	O
information	O
I	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Mrs.	O
Summerayse	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
breast	O
buckle	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
said	O
the	O
chocolate	O
was	O
smuggled	O
chocolate	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
a	O
stamp	O
and	O
our-own	O
private	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
marked	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
sell	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
hundred	O
lbs	O
.	O
of	O
these	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
ca	O
n't	O
sware	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
chocolate	O
sold	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
sware	O
that	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
search	O
of	O
Summerhayse	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
cannisters	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
in	O
some	O
drawers	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
sware	O
to	O
the	O
cannisters	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
quantity	O
more	O
than	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
most	O
families	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
box	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
searched	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
breast	O
buckle	O
,	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
sware	O
to	O
the	O
aprons	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
there	O
remarkable	O
in	O
the	O
cannisters	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
thrown	O
by	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
wrote	O
on	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
make	O
and	O
fashion	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Summerayse	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
connection	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
husband	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
in	O
prison	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Summerayse	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Paved	O
court	O
,	O
Leadenhall-market	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
there	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
on	O
Michaelmas	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
often	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
he	O
husband	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Summerayse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
there	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Esther	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
frequently	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
family	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
bring	O
nutmegs	O
and	O
figs	O
.	O
One	O
night	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
loaf	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
lap	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
vexed	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
apartments	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
crank	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Summerayse	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
boy	O
wanted	O
him	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
blood	O
only	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
of	O
chocolate	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
this	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
the	O
loaves	O
of	O
sugar	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
After	O
White	O
came	O
away	O
that	O
afternoon	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
loaf	O
of	O
sugar	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
his	O
master	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
service	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Esther	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
lodge	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
apartment	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
in	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
lived	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
some	O
quarrel	O
lately	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
night	O
before	O
White	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
bad	O
names	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
little	O
right	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
encouraged	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
quarrel	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nothing	O
else	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Summerayse	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
apply	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
never	O
been	O
under	O
any	O
difficulty	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
send	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
not	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Never	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
some	O
short	O
time	O
before	O
this	O
matter	O
happened	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
refuse	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
bad	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
worse	O
,	O
to	O
encourage	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
follow	O
any	O
way	O
of	O
business	O
?	O
E.	O
Neale	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
13	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
lap	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
Mrs.	O
Summerayse	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
through	O
his	O
apron	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Summerayse	O
's	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
Mrs.	O
Neale	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Summerhayse	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Neale	O
said	O
White	O
had	O
stolen	O
goods	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
them	O
there	O
to	O
Summerayse	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
this	O
before	O
White	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
loaves	O
of	O
sugar	O
there	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
White	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
false	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
story	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
cannisters	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
-	O
Rothwell	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
cannisters	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
corded	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Prostine	O
Snow	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
a	O
twelve-mouth	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
when	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
did	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
asleep	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
one	O
day	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bag	O
full	O
of	O
tea	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
bohea	O
tea	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
looked	O
for	O
the	O
bohea	O
tea	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
tea	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
about	O
two	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
besides	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
about	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
White	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
carried	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
parcels	O
or	O
so	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
wronged	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
breast	O
buckle	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
,	O
time	O
after	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
The	O
breast	O
buckle	O
was	O
lost	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
we	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
stones	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
to	O
be	O
tender	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
children	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Summerayse	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
a	O
penny	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
justly	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
my	O
nephews	O
that	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
have	O
brought	O
things	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
and	O
coffee	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
cannisters	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
July	O
was	O
twelve-month	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
nephew	O
Robert	B-pers
Summerayse	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
chocolate	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
had	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
White	O
,	O
guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
Summerayse	O
,	O
guilty	O
,	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
547	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
silver	O
coral	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
linen	O
skirts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
callimanco	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
guinea	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
548	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ailsworth	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
linen	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Ailsworth	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
549	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
and	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Okely	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Feb	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
flowered	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
1	O
gauze	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
flowered	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
check	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Okeley	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
excepting	O
that	O
of	O
-	O
Sadler	O
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
1	O
brocaded	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
chintz	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
16th	O
.	O
+	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
550	O
,	O
551	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
O'Neale	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
brown	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
37	O
th	O
Hugh	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mariner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
tun	O
weight	O
of	O
brown	O
sugar	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
Hampshire	O
,	O
from	O
Union	B-place
stairs	I-place
.	O
The	O
thieves	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
bags	O
and	O
sacks	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cask	O
.	O
The	O
bags	O
and	O
sugar	O
were	O
found	O
a	O
landing	O
at	O
Paul	O
's	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
They	O
worked	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
John	O
Hill	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
boat	O
loads	O
one	O
night	O
and	O
two	O
another	O
.	O
Conway	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boats	O
the	O
second	O
night	O
.	O
After	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
Neal	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Conway	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
concern	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
got	O
his	O
passage	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vessel	O
.	O
Neal	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
sugar	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
that	O
bag	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
200	O
lb	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
bags	O
Q.	O
from	O
Neals	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
sugar	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
casks	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
casks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
sugar	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
casks	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
ship	O
.	O
Two	O
boats	O
were	O
loaded	O
with	O
sugar	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
both	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
helping	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
gs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
might	O
they	O
take	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
About	O
200	O
lb	O
weight	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
Monday	O
night	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
or	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
sugar	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
Hill	O
and	O
Clark	O
met	O
me	O
by	O
Paul	O
's	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
?	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Union	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
John	O
Hill	O
in	O
these	O
boats	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boats	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
3	O
s.	O
by	O
Clark	O
.	O
One	O
Fraizer	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
ship	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
take	O
the	O
sugar	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
board	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Hill	O
and	O
Clark	B-pers
the	O
employers	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
?	O
Henley	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
make	O
any	O
agreement	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walkerest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
these	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
consulting	O
about	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
sugar	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
they	O
talked	O
about	O
taking	O
a	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
sugar	O
on	O
shore	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
concerned	O
together	O
;	O
Clark	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hugh	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
objection	O
made	O
to	O
his	O
working	O
with	O
these	O
men	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
are	O
lumpers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
headborough	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
wait	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
a-shore	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
a-shore	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
boats	O
;	O
John	O
Hill	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
boat	O
.	O
Conway	O
came	O
along	O
the	O
causeway	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
bags	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
demand	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
bags	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
somebody	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
?	O
Walkerest	O
.	O
I	O
judge	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
voice	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scuffle	O
ensued	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
Conway	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
boat	O
when	O
the	O
boat	O
came	O
a-shore	O
.	O
Walkerest	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
voice	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
boat	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
o'clock	O
John	O
Hill	O
came	O
a-shore	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
second	O
boat	O
landed	O
,	O
he	O
claimed	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Neale	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
?	O
H.	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
carpenter	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Neale	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
demand	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walkerst	I-pers
said	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
property	O
too	O
.	O
Christ	O
.	O
Harne	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
parish	O
beadle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
parish	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
Hugh	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
with	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
sand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
one	O
bag	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
bags	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Neale	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wrangle	O
.	O
Neale	O
said	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
answer	O
for	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
Hill	O
and	O
Clarke	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
matter	O
up	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
One	O
bag	O
did	O
not	O
weigh	O
a	O
100	O
wt	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
bag	O
above	O
100	O
wt	O
.	O
Neale	O
claimed	O
the	O
lesser	O
bag	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Neale	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
that	O
I	O
claim	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
carpenter	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reymot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
carpenter	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
St.	O
Kite	O
's	O
.	O
Two	O
casks	O
of	O
sugar	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
duty	O
for	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Neale	O
to	O
make	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
duty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
working	O
on	O
boarp	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
on	O
shore	O
when	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
this	O
sugar	O
is	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Reymot	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
five	O
guineas	O
of	O
one	O
Chamber	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
sugar	O
Neale	O
sold	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
it	O
?	O
Reymot	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
these	O
people	O
were	O
apprehended	O
?	O
Reymot	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
guess	O
how	O
much	O
sugar	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
these	O
3	O
barrels	O
?	O
Reymot	O
.	O
About	O
600	O
lb	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
money	O
for	O
about	O
400	O
lb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
came	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
after	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
sold	O
?	O
Reymont	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
90	O
lb	O
.	O
left	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
money	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
besides	O
Chambers	O
?	O
Reymot	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
rest	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
Chambers	O
receive	O
the	O
sugar	O
of	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
on	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
carry	O
this	O
sugar	O
to	O
Chambers	O
?	O
Reymot	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Walkrest	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
expressions	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
consulting	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
sugar	O
a-shore	O
?	O
Walkerest	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Clark	O
ask	O
what	O
man	O
they	O
should	O
take	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
Conway	O
said	O
,	O
Henley	O
,	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
.	O
For	O
Neale	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Neale	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
works	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Makette	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Conway	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
laid	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Neale	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
sixteen	O
years	O
.	O
Neale	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Conway	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
551	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Leppenwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
a	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
1	O
scrubbing	O
brush	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Market	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
from	O
about	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
bread	O
fell	O
short	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
too	O
little	O
made	O
;	O
we	O
afterwards	O
missed	O
more	O
bread	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rattle	O
twice	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
four	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
;	O
he	O
set	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
shutter	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
turned	O
back	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
the	O
four	O
loaves	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
naked	O
and	O
catched	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
four	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
were	O
the	O
woman	O
lived	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
saucers	O
,	O
3	O
towel	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
flour	O
.	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Before	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pay	O
when	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
steps	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
three	O
steps	O
down	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
.	O
My	O
father	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
throw	O
the	O
bread	O
into	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
first	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
four	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
paying	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
his	O
bread	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
the	O
brush	O
and	O
saucers	O
I	O
bought	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
children	O
were	O
playing	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
loaves	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
552	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phiillps	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bellas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
July	O
23d	O
.	O
++	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bellas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Old	I-place
'Change	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
close	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
touch	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
which	O
was	O
farthest	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
tapped	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
Bellas	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
yards	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Bellas	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
a	O
croud	O
of	O
people	O
came	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
somewhere	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
?	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
553	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
1	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
Aug	O
19th	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Hart	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
garret	O
of	O
me	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
per	O
week	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
rent	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
presently	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
blankets	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
parade	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
at	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
serjeant	O
should	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
serjeant	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baylis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
here	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
that	O
were	O
pledged	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
?	O
Baylis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Baylis	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
pledged	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
week	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
but	O
the	O
tea	O
kettle	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
on	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
pawned	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
room	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
one	O
evening	O
and	O
again	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
much	O
less	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
serjeant	O
was	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
trial	O
was	O
so	O
long	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
let	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
554	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tustin	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
17th	O
,	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Tustin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
George-street	O
,	O
Grosvenor	O
square	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
On	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
by	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Dykes	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Tustin	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Tustin	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
but	O
herself	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
Leg-court	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
When	O
I	O
awaked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
robbed	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
her	O
lodging	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
?	O
Tustin	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
nobody	O
that	O
night	O
but	O
her	O
?	O
Tustin	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
there	O
?	O
Tustin	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Tustin	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
robbed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
charged	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
with	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
they	O
both	O
owned	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Tustin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Arms	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
from	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Tustin	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
always	O
particular	O
respecting	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dally	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
girls	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dykes	I-pers
owned	O
.	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
say	O
?	O
Dally	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
examined	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
sold	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
Stewart	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
even	O
my	O
own	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
own	O
things	O
.	O
Dykes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Chairing	O
Cross	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
lock	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Stewart	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Dykes	O
,	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
554	O
,	O
555	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dupere	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burnthwaite	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
Aug.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burnthwaite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Surry-street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
Dupere	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
rapper	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
several	O
pieces	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
pitched	O
on	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
four	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
pretty	O
closely	O
;	O
Ann	O
Duper	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
following	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
stept	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
stoped	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
red	O
cloak	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
wear	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
cloak	O
so	O
hot	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
lifting	O
up	O
her	O
cloak	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
rapper	O
,	O
it	O
measured	O
seven	O
yards	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
my	O
worst	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
saucy	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
Ann	O
Dupere	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
take	O
the	O
lawn	O
?	O
Burnthwaite	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
busy	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
lawn	O
.	O
Burnthwaite	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
examining	O
my	O
rapper	O
I	O
missed	O
that	O
very	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
Millet	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
never	O
was	O
under	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Dupere	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
the	O
lawn	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
;	O
we	O
deal	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
556	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Bail	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
five	O
neckclothes	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
buckle	O
gil	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Harrord-street	O
,	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
livery	O
stables	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Broughton	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
livery	O
coat	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
besides	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
five	O
neckclothes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
;	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
my	O
razors	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gilt	O
metal	O
buckle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Lacy	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Lacy	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
July	O
21	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stable	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
three	O
tiles	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
roof	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
boxes	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
four	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
repeated	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
week	O
afterwards	O
,	O
August	O
13	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
against	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
shoes	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
promise	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Lacy	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
week	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
?	O
Lacy	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
whose	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
directed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
linen	O
was	O
in	O
boxes	O
,	O
the	O
boxes	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
robbery	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
these	O
two	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicates	O
to	O
me	O
while	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
so	O
we	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
neckcloths	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Henshaw	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
this	O
neckcloth	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
,	O
)	O
was	O
pawned	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
duplicate	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
(	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
threw	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
557	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hornaby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
mens	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
taylor	O
's	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
hats	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
taylor	O
's	O
iron	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
two	O
nights	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
hats	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hats	O
and	O
this	O
iron	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
hat	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
owe	O
me	O
nine	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
you	O
a	O
six	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
in	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
and	O
three-pence	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Glain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
hat	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
man	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
not	O
purchase	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
my	O
son	O
gave	O
him	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Broadwich	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
left	O
this	O
hat	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
four	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
distressed	O
for	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nine-pence	O
for	O
it	O
(	O
the	O
hats	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
sold	O
that	O
hat	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
allowed	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
pledged	O
the	O
new	O
hat	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
false	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
585	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Werton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stone	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reneals	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Reneals	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
August	O
6	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
buttons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
handed	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mecho	O
stone	O
buttons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
ring	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
buttons	O
;	O
rns	O
himself	O
round	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
the	O
taking	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Reneals	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
closet	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
denied	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
which	O
apartment	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
examining	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
opened	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
stuck	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
ring	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
brought	O
him	O
here	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
can	O
contradict	O
him	O
?	O
Reneals	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
Sir	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
his	O
property	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
no	O
witness	O
that	O
will	O
speak	O
in	O
my	O
behalf	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
constable	O
could	O
contradict	O
him	O
;	O
therefore	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
brought	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Stealing	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
559	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Milsworth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
September	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
-	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Craven	B-place
Hill	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
fetched	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
two	O
fellows	O
I	O
imagine	O
are	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Milsworth	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
go	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
and	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
on	O
their	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
he	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Milsworth	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
overtook	O
him	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
copper	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
Bush	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
make	O
this	O
in	O
your	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
mile	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
bringing	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shenn	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Holborn	O
Hill	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Milsworth	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Craven	O
Hill	O
,	O
by	O
Baise	O
Water	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
excuse	O
till	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
copper	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
legs	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
any	O
seen	O
design	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
copper	O
away	O
;	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Stain	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Milsworth	O
's	O
round	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
anothers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Menn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
copper	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
copper	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mayner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
upon	O
this	O
occ	O
asion	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
copper	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
Mayner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
bodies	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
Chancery	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
had	O
the	O
copper	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sheen	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Holborn	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sayer	O
who	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Charter	O
house	O
.	O
560	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Buckcudge	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
561	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rachel	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Donald	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maclane	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1st	O
.	O
++	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maclane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pensioner	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
college	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
college	O
yard	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
my	O
money	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
drinking	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
my	O
comrade	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
me	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
sitting	O
close	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
modest	O
like	O
woman	O
by	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
thigh	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
her	O
left	O
thigh	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
her	O
thigh	O
slip	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
thigh	O
went	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
;	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
seeing	O
her	O
so	O
free	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
foot	O
back	O
and	O
sat	O
beside	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
beer	O
and	O
drank	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
person	O
very	O
lovely	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
drink	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
time	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
directly	O
;	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
round	O
my	O
waist	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
seat	O
I	O
challenged	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
your	O
comrade	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
hand	O
was	O
under	O
your	O
pettycoats	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
unstrip	O
;	O
O	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
you	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
is	O
safe	O
enough	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
better	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
than	O
yourself	O
;	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Woman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
rose	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
reckoning	O
with	O
the	O
loose	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Woman	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Hock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Hock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
carry	O
you	O
to	O
?	O
Maclane	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
place	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
known	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
satisfied	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
humoured	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Night	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
for	O
flinging	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
men	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
by	O
without	O
drinking	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
call	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
drank	O
first	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
pay	O
for	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
penny	O
then	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
this	O
man	O
is	O
blaming	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
follow	O
you	O
any	O
longer	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
in	O
another	O
company	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
your	O
pardon	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
I	O
throwed	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
costs	O
me	O
a	O
dollar	O
to	O
morrow	O
morning	O
I	O
will	O
find	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
kick	O
with	O
my	O
right	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
find	O
you	O
to-morrow	O
morning	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
safe	O
enough	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
lied	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
below	O
Jews	O
row	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
some	O
cloaths	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
day	O
light	O
came	O
I	O
put	O
no	O
cloaths	O
on	O
but	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
rose	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
waked	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Maclane	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
getting	O
up	O
?	O
your	O
money	O
is	O
safe	O
enough	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
rise	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
rose	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
partner	O
,	O
take	O
her	O
clothes	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
true	O
as	O
I	O
'm	O
the	O
devil	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
such	O
an	O
oath	O
before	O
from	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
find	O
you	O
before	O
night	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
comrade	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
English	O
woman	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
minded	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
served	O
so	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
countrywoman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
or	O
drunk	O
?	O
Maclane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
sign	O
where	O
you	O
picked	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Maclane	O
.	O
The	O
Mermaid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
loose	O
?	O
Maclane	O
.	O
Two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
it	O
three	O
hours	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Addey	I-pers
.	O
He	O
received	O
his	O
money	O
at	O
our	O
college	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Mermaid	O
yard	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
next	O
paper	O
to	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
next	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
moved	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
sitting	O
very	O
lovingly	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
presently	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
that	O
woman	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
bad	O
hand	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
company	O
but	O
her	O
and	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Mermaid	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Jews	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
his	O
money	O
was	O
safe	O
enough	O
:	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
want	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
to	O
him	O
than	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
man	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
enough	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
farthing	O
till	O
she	O
thought	O
proper	O
herself	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
man	O
never	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
Addey	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
destitute	O
woman	O
;	O
my	O
friends	O
live	O
in	O
Scotland	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
advantage	O
of	O
of	O
this	O
;	O
what	O
one	O
says	O
the	O
other	O
will	O
swear	O
.	O
As	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
judge	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
spin	O
at	O
the	O
wheel	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
any	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
562	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hand	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
frame	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
1	O
tennant	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
augers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kinsey	I-pers
;	O
and	O
1	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
,	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wheeler	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
Road	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
tools	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
frock	O
cut	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
frock	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
stealing	O
my	O
frock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
three	O
years	O
(	O
the	O
frock	O
produced	O
and	O
swere	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
frock	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
friend	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
worn	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
563	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hipsey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hair	O
pin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
curls	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
ditto	O
hair	O
pin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Doddington	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Grace	B-pers
Doddington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
my	O
aunt	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
on	O
August	O
19	O
my	O
aunt	O
lost	O
eight	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
we	O
accused	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
new	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
new	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
564	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Colvill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
.	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long	B-place
Acre	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
cloak	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
staymaker	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicate	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
gowns	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
draw	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
by	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
Guilty	O
B	O
.	O
565	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berridge	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Berridge	O
and	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tavern	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
said	O
pepper	O
box	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Berridge	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
lamb	O
's	O
chop	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
pen	O
,	O
ink	O
and	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
porter	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
in	O
the	O
pepper	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
turn	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
his	O
reckoning	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pepper	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
pepper	O
box	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
cast	O
or	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
-	O
Maurice	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chant	I-pers
,	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
12	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
''	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
566	O
,	O
567	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
and	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Boothman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
bushels	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Burnett	I-pers
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
568	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
copper	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Garrot	B-pers
Kavenor	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
569	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
silk	O
cloak	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
570	O
,	O
571	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
pieces	O
of	O
worked	O
muslin	O
,	O
containing	O
52	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
August	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Christopher	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Foot	O
,	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
,	O
after	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
nothing	O
would	O
suit	O
them	O
;	O
our	O
apprentice	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
.	O
Jones	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
her	O
move	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
remnants	O
of	O
worked	O
muslin	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
ready	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
rapper	O
(	O
the	O
muslin	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
low	O
price	O
linen	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Styles	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
she	O
liked	O
,	O
Jones	O
's	O
child	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Presten	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pieces	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pieces	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
shops	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
into	O
Mr	O
.	O
Foot	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
these	O
muslins	O
from	O
under	O
their	O
cloaks	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
unfortunate	O
accident	O
or	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
something	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
three	O
waited	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
these	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
shops	O
did	O
you	O
watch	O
them	O
into	O
?	O
Ham	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
at	O
least	O
fifteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
what	O
hour	O
?	O
Ham	O
.	O
From	O
three	O
o'clock	O
till	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
same	O
two	O
people	O
go	O
into	O
every	O
shop	O
?	O
Ham	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
two	O
always	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
stood	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
muslin	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
maintain	O
my	O
two	O
children	O
since	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
pressed	O
.	O
Styles	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
one	O
house	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
jam	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
only	O
went	O
into	O
three	O
shops	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Angel	O
Alley	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
when	O
they	O
accused	O
her	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Styles	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
572	O
,	O
573	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
1	O
brass	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
worked	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
linen	O
pillow	O
bier	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
woollen	O
wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
paper	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
*	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
-	O
Morley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
