TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BRASS	O
CROSBY	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
EVANS	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
54	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
IN	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BRASS	O
CROSBY	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
;	O
++	O
JOHN	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
~	O
JOHN	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
||	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
~	O
||	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bigger	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Siddall	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ponsonby	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashwell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
1st	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Maddock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bayne	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Longbotham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Mallard	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
Hans	B-pers
Tennis	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
Gravely	O
Seaborn	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Carmock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Jecks	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Frome	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
680	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
May	O
23d	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
his	O
recognizance	O
war	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
681	O
,	O
682	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
6th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
683	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
sauce-pans	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
.	O
March	O
3d	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
684	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
M'Kirk	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Sept.	O
12th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
685	O
,	O
686	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jedear	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
eight	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
coverlid	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jedear	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
October	O
8th	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jedear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
houses	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Pancrass	I-place
;	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Symmonds	I-pers
,	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
houses	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
things	O
at	O
his	O
office	O
.	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Symmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jedear	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
she	O
resided	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
house	O
open	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Jordan	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Jedear	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
lies	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
preceding	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
this	O
glass	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Westcot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
our	O
parroles	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
Mitchel	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
removing	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
apartments	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Palace	O
,	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
road	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
writ	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Carter	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
assisting	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
upon	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
believed	O
what	O
Mitchel	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
goods	O
till	O
the	O
landlord	O
was	O
satisfied	O
and	O
so	O
Mitchel	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
upon	O
,	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
his	O
landlord	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
appeared	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
confused	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
and	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
Mitchel	O
came	O
back	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
apartments	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
palace	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
fields	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
promised	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
detain	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
brother	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
assisted	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
Carter	B-pers
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
came	O
through	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
I	O
heard	O
Carter	O
say	O
to	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
/	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
hurt	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
garden	O
wall	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
all	O
very	O
right	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
Ormond	O
street	O
,	O
Queen	O
square	O
;	O
Carter	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
Mitchel	O
had	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
offered	O
me	O
some	O
beer	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
Murray	O
.	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
patroles	O
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence.	O
``	O
Martha	O
inurst	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
room	O
stript	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
William	B-pers
Halliday	I-pers
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
fixed	O
on	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forced	O
off	O
with	O
violence	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
in	O
Islington	O
road	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
glass	O
tied	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
expecting	O
his	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
seized	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
removing	O
them	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
the	O
patrole	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Carter	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
brother	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
goods	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
seized	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
``	O
Carter	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
his	O
serjeant	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
''	O
Mitchel	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Carter	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
687	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Currier	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rachel	B-pers
Minors	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
October	O
14th	O
.	O
++	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Currier	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
petticoat	O
and	O
gown	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
garret	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
Jackson	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
knew	O
the	O
petticoat	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
to	O
be	O
Rachel	B-pers
Minors	I-pers
's	O
.	O
-	O
Jackson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
worked	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
gown	O
hang	O
up	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Currier	O
's	O
garret	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
dress	O
was	O
too	O
bulky	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
inside	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
this	O
petticoat	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Currier	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
gutter	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
688	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Lyon	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lype	I-pers
Saunders	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
counterpanes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
corded	O
silk	O
embroidered	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sconces	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Jess	I-pers
Alvarar	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Isaac	B-pers
Jess	I-pers
Alvarar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Axe	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
family	O
at	O
my	O
country-house	O
at	O
Hackney	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
every	O
lock	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
afterwards	O
some	O
silk	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
own	O
embroidering	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
then	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
or	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
two	O
chintz	O
counterpanes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
fine	O
and	O
handsome	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
they	O
were	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
had	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
produced	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
cloaths	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
at	O
Canterbury	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
brought	O
me	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
after	O
hawking	O
them	O
about	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
six	O
shillings	O
a-piece	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
check	O
silk	O
sack	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
a	O
grey	O
silk	O
gown	O
full	O
of	O
spots	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
damask	O
curtain	O
for	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
for	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
public	O
sales	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
from	O
Monday	O
till	O
Friday	O
in	O
selling	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
or	O
delivered	O
any	O
things	O
to	O
Levi	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
travelled	O
that	O
country	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
produced	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
near	O
Canterbury	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
for	O
three	O
pounds	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
present	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Saunders	O
Aaron	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
bought	O
several	O
hundreds	O
of	O
snuff	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
very	O
honestly	O
for	O
his	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Goldsborough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-spring	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
in	O
Union-court	O
,	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
snuff	O
and	O
rhubarb	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Brett	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
about	O
two	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
Bank	O
notes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lady	O
Mayo	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
684	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Trecothick	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
689	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
George	O
and	O
Vulture	O
tavern	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
table-spoons	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
then	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
or	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Axford	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
away	O
some	O
sugar-candy	O
to	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
two	O
spoons	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Barton	O
my	O
predecessor	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
B	O
in	O
the	O
bowl	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
fellow-servant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
and	O
Vulture	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
marked	O
as	O
these	O
are	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dust	O
or	O
dust-hole	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
silver	O
;	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
690	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
James	O
Barnard	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Guildhall	B-place
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
attending	O
my	O
duty	O
as	O
a	O
constable	O
during	O
the	O
poll	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
the	O
hall	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
and	O
watched	O
him	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
drop	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
seized	O
my	O
hand	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
691	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gorsford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ayton	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15th	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Ayton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
horse	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
at	O
Southgate	B-place
,	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
15th	O
and	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
livery	O
stable	O
,	O
in	O
Hart	O
street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
carried	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stable	O
keeper	O
,	O
at	O
Moorgate	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Ayton	O
's	O
horses	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
horse	O
stood	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
about	O
fifteen	O
hands	O
high	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ayton	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Southgate	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
.	I-pers
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
last	O
week	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
stable	O
keeper	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
sign	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Ayton	O
's	O
horse	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
inn	O
,	O
in	O
Bermondsey	O
street	O
,	O
Southwark	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Ayton	O
owns	O
,	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
stables	O
,	O
near	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
stables	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
or	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
maid	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
while	O
it	O
stood	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
ride	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
sometimes	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
once	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
saddle	O
and	O
bridle	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ayton	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
loose	O
a	O
saddle	O
and	O
bridle	O
?	O
Ayton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Russel	O
.	O
The	O
saddle	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
new	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Gorsford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ayton	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
close	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
out	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
horses	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
again	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
livery	O
stables	O
,	O
in	O
Hart	O
street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brahan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
highwayman	O
upon	O
this	O
horse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Fidlers	O
,	O
at	O
Houghton	O
,	O
near	O
Dartford	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
highwayman	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Fiddlers	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
very	O
agreeable	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
horse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
horse	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Judd	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sow	O
gelder	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
when	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Enfield	O
Chase	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
owned	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
me	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
miles	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
nobody	O
here	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
horse	O
of	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
692	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cobham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hockey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
seven	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
September	O
21st	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hockey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Devonshire	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
suddenly	O
broke	O
,	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
lay	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
:	O
upon	O
examination	O
I	O
missed	O
seven	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
five	O
lay	O
about	O
twenty	O
inches	O
from	O
the	O
showboard	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
stood	O
opposite	O
the	O
shop	O
said	O
the	O
thief	O
ran	O
through	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
passage	O
,	O
into	O
Gloucester	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Gloucester	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
halloo	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
them	O
cry	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
he	O
comes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Blotcham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Blotcham	O
had	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
hands	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
committed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
Hockey	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lighted	O
candies	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
day	O
light	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
?	O
Hockey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dusk	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
without	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
drew	O
up	O
the	O
indictment	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
;	O
he	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
seven	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
seven	O
till	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
break	O
his	O
windows	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
?	O
Hockey	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blotcham	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
King'sgate	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
opposite	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
butcher	O
throw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
him	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
it	O
ran	O
down	O
in	O
drops	O
.	O
(	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
forgiven	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
,	O
at	O
down-lying	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
roving	O
about	O
almost	O
mad	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
head	O
fell	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
I	O
find	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
man	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
recover	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
butcher	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
King'sgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
door	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
by	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
catch	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
,	O
run	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
something	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
motion	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Blotcham	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
almost	O
mad	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
head	O
fell	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
fell	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Crane-court	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
this	O
accident	O
happened	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
jobb	O
;	O
on	O
coming	O
along	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
halloo	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
ran	O
down	O
that	O
dark	O
passage	O
?	O
Hockey	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
one	O
minute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
as	O
you	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Hockey	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
693	O
,	O
694	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Guitano	B-pers
Menini	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
wooden	O
cane	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
amethyst	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Guitano	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
*	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
Guitano	O
Menini	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mount	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
on	O
Friday	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
near	B-place
Lord	I-place
Hertford	I-place
's	I-place
house	I-place
;	O
a	O
fellow	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
eye	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
stop	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
he	O
frightened	O
;	O
then	O
three	O
fellows	O
more	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
stopt	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
one	O
penny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
breeches	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
another	O
put	O
my	O
finger	O
into	O
this	O
mouth	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
of	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
an	O
amothyst	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
face	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flesh	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mount	O
's	O
coffee	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
faces	O
?	O
Menini	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
voice	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
held	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
be	O
Murray	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
voice	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
produced	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
produced	O
by	O
Hawthorn	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
gold	O
of	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
from	O
the	O
particular	O
make	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Fotterel	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Eagle	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
,	O
Red	O
Lyon-square	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
Murray	O
and	O
Freel	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Fotterel	O
met	O
us	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
near	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
committed	O
two	O
robberies	O
before	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
Frenchman	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
towards	O
Marybone	O
,	O
we	O
committed	O
a	O
robbery	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Hanover-square	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
square	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
along	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
we	O
resolved	O
to	O
attack	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
pistol	O
,	O
Freel	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
we	O
were	O
behind	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
made	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
tussle	O
,	O
and	O
Murray	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
behind	O
and	O
pinioned	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
whist	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
hold	O
his	O
tongue	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
cleverly	O
,	O
and	O
Fotterel	O
cut	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
Freel	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
little	O
finger	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
the	O
ring	O
off	O
his	O
finger	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
Freel	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
took	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
got	O
any	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
any	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
breast	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
our	O
lodging	O
in	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carver	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
lodging-house	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Freel	O
kept	O
the	O
watch	O
till	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
following	O
and	O
the	O
ring	O
;	O
Freel	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
one	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Saunders	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
eight	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
both	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
divided	O
it	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
a-piece	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
ring	O
because	O
they	O
esteemed	O
me	O
the	O
genteelest	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
Freel	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
a	O
stone	O
with	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
a	O
head	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
stone	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
socket	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
it	O
into	O
another	O
piece	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
silversmith	O
here	O
?	O
Delaney	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Eagle	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
.	O
-	O
Hawthorn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Delaney	B-pers
the	O
accomplice	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
Delaney	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
(	O
producing	O
several	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
a	O
ring	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Gallaway	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
ng	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Delaney	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Eagle	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
Freel	O
had	O
two	O
pistols	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
charged	O
,	O
and	O
Murray	O
had	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
Delaney	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
false	O
keys	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
pockets	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
whose	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lyons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Eagle	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
confirms	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Pomroy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
Murray	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Freel	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
loaded	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
picklock	O
keys	O
?	O
Pomroy	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
two	O
pistols	O
out	O
of	O
Freel	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
one	O
was	O
loaded	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
picklocks	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
whose	O
pocket	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
.	O
Murray	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
swares	O
that	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
swares	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Delaney	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk-weaver	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
business	O
.	O
Freel	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Delaney	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
picklocks	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
to	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
business	O
is	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
running	O
about	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
695	O
,	O
696	O
,	O
697	O
,	O
698	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
,	O
Mary	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
,	O
Rose	B-pers
Keefe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
wooden	O
drawers	O
,	O
four	O
hundred	O
and	O
eighty	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
hat-buckle	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
set	O
with	O
chrystal	O
stones	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
nine-shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
six	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ferquharson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Ferquharson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
yard	O
near	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
two	O
fiddles	O
;	O
Murray	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
drunk	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
fiddle	O
playing	O
down	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
They	O
danced	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
rapped	O
all	O
their	O
hands	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
liquor	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
serve	O
them	O
.	O
Rose	O
Keefe	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
the	O
music	O
began	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
loud	O
cough	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
except	O
one	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
behind	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
their	O
design	O
.	O
Murray	O
seemed	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
door	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
bureau	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
upwards	O
of	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
drawers	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
my	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
good	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
bad	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
changed	O
the	O
six	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
Keefe	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
as	O
my	O
room	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
Keefe	O
went	O
about	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
people	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
led	O
us	O
wrong	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
again	O
but	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
mother-in-law	O
to	O
Delaney	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
drunk	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
sober	O
?	O
Ferquharson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
sober	O
by	O
drinking	O
more	O
liquor	O
?	O
Ferquharson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
only	O
shammed	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
soon	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
drawers	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
bad	O
halfpence	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
drawers	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	O
Delaney	O
.	O
Freel	O
's	O
wife	O
and	O
Keefe	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
secret	O
to	O
impart	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
Ferquharson	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
making	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Keefe	O
lived	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
opposite	O
Ferquharson	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
disappointed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
fixed	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
Freel	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
fiddle	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
dancing	O
below	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
might	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
above	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
her	O
husband	O
lodged	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Fotterel	I-pers
there	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
secret	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Freel	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
Fotterel	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Keefe	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
was	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
fidles	O
,	O
Keefe	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
hired	O
Murray	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
d	O
below	O
;	O
Freel	O
,	O
Murray	O
d	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
began	O
dancing	O
Freel	O
,	O
the	O
husband	O
.	O
h	O
ad	O
a	O
which	O
he	O
broke	O
upon	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Fotterel	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
smith	O
had	O
chissels	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
cut	O
away	O
the	O
wood	O
from	O
the	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
one	O
drawer	O
of	O
had	O
and	O
one	O
drawer	O
of	O
good	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
and	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
guineas	O
only	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
Freel	O
supprested	O
them	O
.	O
Rose	O
Keefe	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
once	O
to	O
dance	O
with	O
the	O
people	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
Earl-street	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
Murray	O
and	O
Freel	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
had	O
halfpence	O
in	O
Long	O
,	O
by	O
M.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
Freel	O
had	O
the	O
silver	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
about	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
at	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Murray	O
,	O
Freel	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
Fotterel	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Boot	O
near	O
the	O
Foundling	O
Hospital	O
.	O
where	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
Murray	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
Freel	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
Freel	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
the	O
buckle	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
Freel	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
among	O
more	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
told	O
me	O
Mrs.	O
Freel	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Ferquharson	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
music	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
Keefe	O
was	O
there	O
only	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Freel	O
came	O
down	O
at	O
last	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
doing	O
above	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
Freel	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Fotterel	O
;	O
they	O
shuffled	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
wrong	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
husband	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
for	O
with	O
his	O
Irish	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
us	O
all	O
hanged	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
upon	O
that	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Murray	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
all	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
walked	O
about	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Murray	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
lie	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
Jackson-alley	O
?	O
Delaney	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
halfpence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
any	O
questions	O
,	O
be-	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
Pomroy	O
.	O
This	O
guinea	O
and	O
halfpenny	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
guinea	O
and	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
from	O
particular	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
Keefe	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
us	O
Delaney	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
Delaney	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
son-in-law	O
Delaney	O
;	O
that	O
guinea	O
and	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
just	O
now	O
produced	O
,	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Murray	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
notion	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
was	O
forward	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Ireland	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
weaver	O
,	O
the	O
business	O
is	O
dead	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
to	O
seek	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
Freel	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Ferquharson	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
Ferquharson	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
Freel	O
promised	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
being	O
shut	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Delaney	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
lodging	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
somewhere	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
bed	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Keefe	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
or	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
when	O
the	O
merriment	O
began	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Delaney	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
.	O
John	O
Freel	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
five	O
weeks	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
my	O
mother-in	O
law	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Murray	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Delaney	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Delaney	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Freel	I-pers
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Murray	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Keefe	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
699	O
,	O
700	O
,	O
701	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Ardle	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Spur	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Spur	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
+	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
702	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
an	O
inland	O
bill	O
or	O
exchange	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
upon	O
Edward	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Count	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
forging	O
an	O
acceptance	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
bill	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
3d	O
Count	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
said	O
bill	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forged	O
.	O
June	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
++	O
-	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
,	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
difference	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
accepted	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
difference	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
my	O
banker	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
clerk	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
's	O
partner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
and	O
hi-partner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forged	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Donaldson	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
at	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Hospital	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
enquiry	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
dismissed	O
some	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
some	O
weeks	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
Mr.	O
Russel	B-pers
the	O
8	O
l.	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
last	O
indorser	O
on	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
dispute	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
refer	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Boulton	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cruttenden	O
:	O
they	O
determined	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Russell	B-pers
the	O
8	O
l.	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
settled	O
point	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
will	O
make	O
no	O
difference	O
,	O
let	O
this	O
cause	O
turn	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
settled	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
my	O
rent	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
bill	O
or	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
clerk	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
paid	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
,	O
and	O
settled	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
no	O
condition	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
is	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
21	O
June	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
``	O
Sir	O
,	O
``	O
Twenty	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
``	O
Rogers	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
eight	O
``	O
pounds	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Roger	O
``	O
Mohleat	O
,	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
''	O
To	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
This	O
bill	O
(	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
is	O
counterfeited	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
acceptance	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
wrote	O
my	O
name	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
my	O
writing	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
there	O
never	O
been	O
any	O
transaction	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
remembered	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
till	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
supposed	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
a	O
mere	O
fiction	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
paid	O
by	O
your	O
partner	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
,	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
desk	O
;	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
clerk	O
brought	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
mine	O
is	O
all	O
home	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
drawn	O
upon	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
live	O
near	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
Hospital	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
foot	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
governor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
seen	O
me	O
write	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
resemble	O
your	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
The	O
flourish	O
is	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
write	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
circumstances	O
in	O
his	O
favour	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
know	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
forged	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
letters	O
sent	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
his	O
handwriting	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
(	O
Four	O
letters	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
.	O
All	O
these	O
letters	O
are	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
four	O
letters	O
are	O
read	O
;	O
in	O
all	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledges	O
his	O
guilt	O
,	O
professes	O
penitence	O
,	O
and	O
begs	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilkins	O
:	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
note	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Culer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
writing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Astley	O
ride	O
at	O
his	O
school	O
at	O
Westminster-bridge	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
riding	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
New-Inn	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
a	O
gentleman	O
was	O
drinking	O
punch	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
six	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
punch	O
:	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
a	O
third	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
something	O
:	O
we	O
entered	O
into	O
conversation	O
together	O
:	O
he	O
understood	O
that	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Yorkshire	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
discount	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
suited	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
wanted	O
but	O
a	O
fortnight	O
of	O
being	O
due	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
address	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
being	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
sum	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
readily	O
gave	O
him	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
receiving	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
discount	O
:	O
he	O
indorsed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
under	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
two	O
indorsements	O
which	O
were	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
the	O
bill	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
shoes	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
away	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
difference	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
indorsed	O
my	O
name	O
under	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
for	O
a	O
debt	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
charged	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
forged	O
this	O
draft	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
produce	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
gave	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
witness	O
or	O
two	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
transaction	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Antigallican	O
coffee-house	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Inn	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
Westminster-bridge	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
there	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
till	O
about	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
gentlemen	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
riding	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
any	O
thing	O
pass	O
about	O
a	O
note	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Donaldson	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
blue	O
and	O
gold	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Donaldson	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
that	O
gentleman	O
cash	O
for	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Berresford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
working	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Donaldson	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Astley	O
's	O
riding	O
school	O
:	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
money	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
a	O
note	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
how	O
come	O
you	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
eight	O
guineas	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
there	O
in	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
blue	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
Berresford	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
something	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
a	O
note	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Williams	O
there	O
?	O
Berresford	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Williams	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
man	O
there	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
This	O
subpoena	O
was	O
served	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
or	O
late	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
703	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Askham	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30th	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Askham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Guildhall	B-place
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
feel	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
follow	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
Payne	O
had	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
concealed	O
between	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
and	O
watched	O
him	O
narrowly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
somebody	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
away	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
tucking	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
throwed	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
tucked	O
into	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
704	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Akerman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
eleven	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whelan	I-pers
September	O
22d	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Whelan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford	O
road	O
;	O
after	O
drinking	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
houses	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
landlady	O
the	O
candle	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
waked	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman.	O
``	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chissey	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
''	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
705	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Barnsley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Sept.	O
26th	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
but	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
706	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
707	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Aspinall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Sept.	O
22d	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
708	O
,	O
709	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
15th	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
710	O
,	O
711	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
eight	O
iron	O
bolts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
forty-eight	O
iron	O
nutts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
eighteen	O
bolts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
eighteen	O
nuts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
October	O
4th	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
712	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
17	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
two	O
china	O
sawcers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
scrubbing	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Leppenwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29th	O
.	O
++	O
(	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Leppenwell	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
See	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions.	O
``	O
Robert	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
that	O
Leppenwell	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
missed	O
bread	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
accordingly	O
watched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
Thursday	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
as	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Leppenwell	O
set	O
four	O
loaves	O
on	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
four	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pushed	O
her	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
naked	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
loaves	O
in	O
apron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Leppenwell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
loaves	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
loaves	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
My	O
first	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
John	O
Hall	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
died	O
I	O
married	O
Leppenwell	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
owe	O
this	O
Leppenwell	O
two	O
weeks	O
wages	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
paid	O
every	O
Saturday	O
.	O
He	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
bread	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
preceding	O
Saturday	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Leppenwell	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T.	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
713	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
,	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
pinchbeck	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Garner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
May	O
17th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
714	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barrat	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smeeton	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22d	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smeeton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smeeton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
glass	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
admire	O
himself	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
your	O
tea-kettle	O
boils	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
pray	O
let	O
it	O
stand	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
no	O
harm	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
kettle	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
beaufet	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
beaufet	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
the	O
spoon	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
wiped	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
beaufet	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
serve	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
the	O
spoon	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
till	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
715	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
dimity	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
broad	O
cloath	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2d	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Wylde-street	I-place
,	I-place
Lincoln	I-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
fields	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
dimity	O
waistcoats	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
three	O
eighths	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
made	O
fresh	O
enquiry	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
myself	O
in	O
Brook	O
's	O
Mews	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoats	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
lane	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
's	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn	O
broker	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
-	O
Bradley	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
white	O
waistcoats	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
716	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Tireman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
:	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
3d	O
.	O
Jefferry	O
Jenread	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
led	O
me	O
across	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Foundling	O
Hospital	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bagnigge	O
Wells	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
there	O
,	O
playing	O
at	O
nine	O
pins	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
biscuits	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
hold	O
the	O
bundle	O
the	O
while	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
biscuits	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
snatched	O
at	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
fast	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
me	O
till	O
almost	O
dark	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
towards	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
near	O
some	O
water	O
works	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seemed	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
gloves	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
parcel	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
out-ran	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
Justice	O
Lane	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
bargained	O
for	O
seven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
by	O
my	O
boy	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
soon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
liked	O
them	O
so	O
well	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
six	O
more	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
wrapped	O
up	O
thirteen	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
lad	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
back	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
,	O
a	O
g	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
a	O
fraud	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
understood	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
w	O
Justice	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
loan	O
debts	O
he	O
owed	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
alternately	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
urged	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
grow	O
late	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
accordingly	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
run	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
some	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Hassell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Tireman	O
his	O
uncle	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
''	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
717	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Grace	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
*	O
Grace	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
relief	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
patient	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
hospital	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Down	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
Elizabeth	O
Tilley	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
cloaths	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
gown	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Master	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Murthwaite	O
's	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
goods.	O
``	O
Henry	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Masters	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Viper	I-pers
.	O
``	O
-	O
Jenkinson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
Murthwaite	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
goods	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
B	O
.	O
718	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lunn	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
green	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
of	O
feathers	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Susannah	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
719	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brace	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
++	O
Mrs.	O
Davidson	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
,	O
is	O
a	O
hosier	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
cheapened	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
quite	O
away	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
I	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
searched	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
buttons	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
living	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pick	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
720	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elijah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
cutting	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
forty	O
pounds	O
of	O
lead	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
affixed	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bodicoat	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Bodicoat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Brompton	B-place
as	O
assignee	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
instant	O
Morris	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
man	O
with	O
some	O
lead	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
appear	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loaded	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
lead	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
Brompton	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
matched	O
the	O
place	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
knew	O
nothing	O
dishonest	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
721	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Vale	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Vale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Guildhall	B-place
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
Guildhall	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hall	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
723	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
vintner	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
about	O
ten	O
nights	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
sheet	O
from	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
an	O
overtook	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
sheet	O
wrapped	O
round	O
his	O
body	O
,	O
(	O
The	O
sheet	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
sheet	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
723	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk-gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
this	O
gown	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
-	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davidson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
gown	O
in	O
to	O
pledge	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
gown	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
nobody	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Read	O
's	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
this	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
gown	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
countrywoman	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
gown	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Samuel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
lately	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
724	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
hogshead	O
bound	O
with	O
eight	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Kenton	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kenton	O
's	O
to	O
bring	O
home	O
an	O
iron-bound	O
hogshead	O
and	O
an	O
iron-bound	O
barrel	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cart	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
horses	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rolling	O
the	O
hogshead	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
roll	O
the	O
hogshead	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
some	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
case	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
till	O
the	O
owner	O
might	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
roll	O
it	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
friends	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
725	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Stantan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
deal	O
board	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
726	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
canvas	O
bags	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty-seven	O
pounds	O
of	O
white	O
ginger	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
William	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lighter	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
navigable	I-place
river	I-place
the	I-place
River	I-place
Thames	I-place
,	O
August	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
727	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
ounces	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
.	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
wooden	O
bobbins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Enoch	B-pers
Woodhand	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
728	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Beane	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Ackman	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
729	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Warcup	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
cotton	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Warcup	I-pers
,	O
+	O
Christopher	B-pers
Warcup	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
a	O
coal	O
merchant	O
in	O
Milford-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
house	O
allotted	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
ground	O
floor	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
warehouses	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Warcup	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
apartment	O
,	O
we	O
dress	O
our	O
victuals	O
and	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
nobody	O
has	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
apartment	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
double-locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
padlocked	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
a-jar	O
,	O
the	O
staple	O
that	O
served	O
for	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
wrench	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
staple	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
spring-lock	O
was	O
forced	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
's	O
:	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
upon	O
examining	O
my	O
room	O
I	O
missed	O
she	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
Joe	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
upon	O
the	O
wharf	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
go	O
by	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
with	O
a	O
bundles	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Feather	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
