TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERROT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
*	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
*	O
David	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
George	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Buxton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
James	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
Frederick	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
William	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Churchman	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
James	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
+	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
+	O
Dormer	B-pers
Hefford	I-pers
+	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Dormer	B-pers
Hefford	I-pers
;	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Churchman	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Puller	I-pers
William	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hocker	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OGILBY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
with	O
silver	O
bows	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Susanna	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
King-square-court	B-place
,	I-place
Dean-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
parlour	O
windows	O
were	O
shut	O
up	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
said	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
over-head	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
feet	O
over-head	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
screamed	O
out	O
immediately	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
run	O
along	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
feet	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
pull	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
themselves	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
kept	O
,	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
closet	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
.	O
A	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
scissars	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cases	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
cases	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
This	O
pepper	O
castor	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
mark	O
'd	O
?	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
foot	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chartier	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
scream	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
single-lock	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
off	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Life	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
against	O
King-square-court	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
people	O
running	O
very	O
fast	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
immediately	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
just	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
a	O
green-woman	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
three	O
men	O
run	O
by	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
down	O
Queen-street	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
three	O
man	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
standing	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
cluster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
three	O
men	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
under	O
a	O
lamp	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Life	O
seiz	O
'd	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
struggled	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
drop	O
from	O
Coleman	O
.	O
Life	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
has	O
he	O
dropt	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Life	O
stoop	O
'd	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
cream-jug	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Coleman	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Life	O
felt	O
down	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
Ogilby	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
Ogilby	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
faint	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
watch-house	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
pepper-box	O
was	O
found	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cream-jug	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Ogilby	O
is	O
the	O
lad	O
that	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
Life	O
?	O
Crompton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
clear	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Life	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Dean-street	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
bell	O
ring	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Highlander	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
run	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
justices	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
the	O
three	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Crompton	O
,	O
they	O
three	O
have	O
been	O
doing	O
no	O
good	O
;	O
the	O
words	O
were	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
crying	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Crompton	O
,	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
run	O
so	O
fast	O
as	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
follow	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
may	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
injury	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
green	O
woman	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
three	O
men	O
run	O
by	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Glazier	O
,	O
in	O
Greek-street	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
standing	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
but	O
immediately	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
other	O
fast	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Coleman	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
stood	O
so	O
close	O
together	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
that	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
was	O
Ogilby	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
got	O
clear	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Ogilby	O
.	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crompton	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
stopt	O
Ogilby	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
behind	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Coleman	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
wrist	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
dropt	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
stoopt	O
directly	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
cream	O
pot	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
declared	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
strangers	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
well	O
;	O
Ogilby	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
stop	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
saint	O
;	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Covent-garden	O
play-house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
place	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Greek-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
running	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
Ogilby	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
step	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
tumbled	O
his	O
cloaths	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
sit	O
still	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
pulled	O
and	O
hawled	O
his	O
clothes	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
right	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
found	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
shewed	O
me	O
next	O
day	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
just	O
behind	O
the	O
stone	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
Pearce	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
has	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Coleman	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
passed	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
another	O
man	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
;	O
something	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
loose	O
while	O
he	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
cream	O
pot	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
fell	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Ogilby	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
distiller	O
,	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Oxford-market	O
for	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
mutton	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
rather	O
above	O
my	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
haste	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
disturbance	O
in	O
Soho	O
.	O
square	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
then	O
that	O
man	O
seized	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
searched	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
distiller	O
lives	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
.	O
Ogilby	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Berry-street	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
never	O
a	O
distiller	O
in	O
that	O
street	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
on	O
7th	O
Nov.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
John	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Tottenham-court-road	I-place
.	O
As	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
jump	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
child	O
into	O
the	O
cradle	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
immediately	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
closet	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
plate	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rustle	O
against	O
the	O
wainscot	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rushed	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
speak	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
tussel	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
lived	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
window-sash	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
pushed	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
gown	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
at	O
full	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
rolled	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
boy	O
threw	O
his	O
hat	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
cousin	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Coote	I-pers
,	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
sash	O
down	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
when	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
dark	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coote	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
sash	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
when	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
came	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
16	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
on	O
Nov.	O
7	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
cloaks	O
,	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
white	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
circumstances	O
of	O
this	O
burglary	O
were	O
similar	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
charge	O
.	O
A	O
fore	O
parlour	O
window	O
was	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
on	O
the	O
foregoing	O
charge	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
the	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Phillips	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
his	O
sister	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
apron	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
to	O
be	O
altered	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
his	O
sister	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
White	B-place
cross-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
or	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
redeem	O
a	O
pledge	O
:	O
while	O
my	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
my	O
neckcloths	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
them	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
to	O
release	O
a	O
pledge	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
discharged	O
another	O
customer	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
be	O
down	O
up	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
watched	O
her	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
lean	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
again	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Masey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
she	O
washed	O
for	O
me	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
money	O
.	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
service	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
For	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goldin	I-pers
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pistereen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
leather	O
glove	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
farthing	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Iredle	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Iredle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Goldin	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
White	B-place
house-inn	I-place
,	I-place
Mile-end	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
he	O
sad	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
glove	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glove	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
stocking	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
heat	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
pull	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
nor	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
give	O
change	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
chest	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
have	O
taken	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Iredle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
nobody	O
could	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
ther	O
offence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Several	O
young	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
waked	O
me	O
by	O
throwing	O
the	O
clothes	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ARDELL	B-pers
HENLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2.	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
six	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
two	O
doors	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
scattered	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stuff	O
green	O
petticoat	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buttons	O
,	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
neighbours	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
catched	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
afterwards	O
catched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
buttons	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Tottlefields	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
searched	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
buttons	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Gee	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
began	O
spanking	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
buttons	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
swears	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
:	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
[	O
See	O
him	O
No	O
.	O
700	O
,	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
]	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
check	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
jam	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
SCATONAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
nankeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
a	O
half-penny	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Aldin	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Aldin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
three	B-place
butchers	I-place
in	I-place
Hungerford-market	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
(	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
things	O
of	O
mine	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ibbet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Aldin	O
's	O
waistcoat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
robbed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
noise	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Kynaston	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shirt	O
and	O
gold-ring	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
assist	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
justices	O
that	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
that	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DULEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
at	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wellis	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
LEWIS	B-pers
HUMPHRYS	I-pers
and	O
DUNCAN	B-pers
HARDY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
earthen	O
jarrs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
wooden	O
barrels	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
800	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
almonds	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Corbin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
ship	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Betsey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
navigable	O
river	O
of	O
Thames	O
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Corbin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
ship	B-place
Betsey	I-place
;	O
she	O
lay	O
off	O
Cox	O
's	O
key	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cargo	O
we	O
found	O
20	O
jarrs	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
three	O
barrels	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
almonds	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
cargo	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
shipped	O
by	O
the	O
mate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Betsey	O
.	O
On	O
delivering	O
the	O
cargo	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
received	O
from	O
Hunt	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
on	O
board	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
cargo	O
delivered	O
;	O
Hardy	O
owned	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
raisins	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Hull	O
.	O
Humphreys	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
witness	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belonged	O
to	O
this	O
ship	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
bringing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
almonds	O
,	O
raisins	O
,	O
and	O
lemons	O
in	O
bags	O
;	O
the	O
bags	O
were	O
pretty	O
large	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
different	O
sizes	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
on	O
shore	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Welch	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
's	O
watchman	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
on	O
shore	O
several	O
nights	O
with	O
bags	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
hold	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
one	O
night	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bags	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
pass	O
.	O
Another	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
on	O
shore	O
with	O
a	O
jarr	O
of	O
raisins	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
had	O
better	O
not	O
carry	O
them	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
officers	O
were	O
further	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
lose	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
jars	O
down	O
till	O
the	O
officer	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
suffered	O
this	O
man	O
very	O
quietly	O
to	O
bring	O
those	O
goods	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
smuggled	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
's	O
watchman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
merchants	O
will	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
your	O
conduct	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
may	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
trusty	O
servant	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Humphrys	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
carried	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
shore	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
quantity	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hold	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
casks	O
in	O
the	O
hold	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
pound	O
weight	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
Hardy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
fruit	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Hewstall	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
allowed	O
no	O
private	O
trade	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
FORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
steel	O
watch-chains	O
,	O
value	O
8l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
BENNET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
sixteen	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-one	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
is	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
arose	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
made	O
under	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BALDWIN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
cloth	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
six-and	O
nine-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FLENDELL/	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gun-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Artillery	I-place
ground	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fastened	O
only	O
with	O
a	O
hasp	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
slight	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
fall	O
down	O
of	O
itself	O
sometimes	O
by	O
shaking	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
opens	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
wall	O
which	O
a	O
person	O
might	O
get	O
over	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
pantiles	O
that	O
lie	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
that	O
usually	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
rush-light	O
was	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
:	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
taken	O
out	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
iron	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
the	O
flap	O
was	O
let	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
tool	O
that	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
spoons	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
beauset	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
window-frame	O
appeared	O
dirty	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
trod	O
upon	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
that	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
not	O
the	O
hasp	O
fall	O
down	O
by	O
shaking	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sturley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
it	O
might	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
from	O
some	O
circumstances	O
,	O
the	O
tool	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Friday	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
rotation	O
at	O
White-chapel	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
four	O
spoons	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
recovered	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
again	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
pawnbronot	O
here	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
my	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
was	O
up	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Care	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
this	O
robbery	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
committed	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
rotation	O
office	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
four	O
spoons	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
knees	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
shown	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
shall	O
recover	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
officer	O
returned	O
afterwards	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
iron	O
box	O
with	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
late	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
worked	O
at	O
his	O
business	O
lately	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
lived	O
upon	O
his	O
friends	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
DEATH	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
CASEY	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
SAMPSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
Herring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATERS	I-pers
and	O
AARON	B-pers
SPENCER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
butter	O
boats	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gaper	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
PETER	B-pers
FARRELL	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NICHOLLAY	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
NICHOLAS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellinger	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
seven	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
soup	O
spoon	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
120	O
copper	O
half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bellinger	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Belinge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
safe	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
knocked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Mince	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
forgot	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Higbet	I-pers
that	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
drawer	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
shut	O
in	O
between	O
two	O
cup-boards	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
easily	O
discovered	O
but	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
house	O
is	O
robbed	O
,	O
my	O
bat	O
is	O
broken	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
lodgers	O
a-bed	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
thieves	O
could	O
have	O
broke	O
in	O
.	O
Mince	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watchmen	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
someby	O
must	O
have	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
finding	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
a-jar	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
lodgers	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
all	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
tool	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
line	O
pin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
Belinger	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
pull	O
back	O
the	O
spring	O
lock	O
,	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
was	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
-	O
Mince	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lodged	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
eleven	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bar	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
alarmed	O
Mrs.	O
Bellinger	O
.	O
The	O
top	O
shutter	O
was	O
put	O
down	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
till	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O
-	O
Wetherby	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
twelve	O
having	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
,	O
whistled	O
between	O
his	O
fingers	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
opened	O
a	O
sash	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
shoulders	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
where	O
are	O
they	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
He	O
replied	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
four	O
.	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
see	O
no	O
person	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
it	O
be	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
?	O
Wetherby	O
.	O
More	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
The	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
is	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
within	O
sight	O
of	O
my	O
stand	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
all	O
was	O
fast	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Wetherby	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
at	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
then	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
calling	O
the	O
half	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
,	O
Sam	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
sirname	O
?	O
Wetherby	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
then	O
:	O
He	O
threw	O
something	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
path	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
before	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
stories	O
high	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
throw	O
any	O
thing	O
up	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sash	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
wagged	O
his	O
fingers	O
,	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
beckoning	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
Sam	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
pulled	O
the	O
sash	O
down	O
again	O
:	O
Then	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
candle	O
was	O
almost	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
spare	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
challenged	O
some	O
draymen	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
standing	O
a	O
little	O
a	O
jar	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
stirring	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
:	O
I	O
struck	O
the	O
door	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
my	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
young	O
fellows	O
jumped	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
there	O
:	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
their	O
work	O
.	O
Then	O
presently	O
another	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
a	O
candle	O
a	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Mince	O
came	O
down	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
careless	O
lodgers	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
thieves	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
taken	O
.	O
Sam	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
that	O
Sam	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
first	O
?	O
Wetherby	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Wetherby	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ellidge	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Wetherby	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
pockets	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shephard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Sam	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Movon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Peter	B-pers
Farrell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
four	O
more	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Bellenger	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Sam	O
the	O
waiter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bowman	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
discharged	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Sam	O
said	O
Moxon	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
lend	O
me	O
six-pence	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lay	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bellenger	O
's	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lend	O
Sam	O
six-pence	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
Farrell	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
out	O
a	O
glove	O
and	O
comb	O
.	O
Sam	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
your	O
head	O
off	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
comb	O
and	O
glove	O
again	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Moody	O
attempted	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
Farrell	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
about	O
4	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Edridge	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
him	O
get	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Moxon	O
.	O
No	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
:	O
Somebody	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
whistle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
that	O
is	O
Shepherd	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
a	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Edridge	O
jumped	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
is	O
it	O
Shepherd	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
nobody	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pushed	O
me	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
Shepherd	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
Edridge	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
Shepherd	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Moxon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
this	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
Edridge	O
was	O
detained	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
in	O
Sam	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
men	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
po	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Nicholay	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
have	O
escaped	O
.	O
Farrel	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TURVEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Keven	I-pers
,	O
January	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Alexander	B-pers
Keven	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
sawyer	O
at	O
Durham	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
in	O
Durham-yard	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Chelsea	O
Pensioner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
pension	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
some	O
money	O
I	O
owed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Kevan	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
money	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
sober	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
have	O
only	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
waked	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
bed-side	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
another	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
to	O
Durham-yard	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
off	O
for	O
paying	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
His	O
mother	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
IVES	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BALLARD	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
NIMMEY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
cane	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
November	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COX	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Scypher	I-pers
:	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Schutz	I-pers
.	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
,	O
sugar-refiner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
This	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
on	O
Bennett	B-place
's	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
at	O
Bennett	O
's	O
Hill	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
maid	O
talk	O
of	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
coming	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
The	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
Sykes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
I	O
saw	O
Sykes	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
prove	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
men	O
go	O
into	O
their	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Scypher	I-pers
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
another	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
:	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Schutz	I-pers
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
man	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
had	O
no	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
shook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sykes	O
,	O
that	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
He	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
buckles	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
eat	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
examined	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
two-pence	O
halfpenny	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
In	O
shaking	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
thimble	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Schutz	I-pers
's	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
searched	O
him	O
further	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Bennett	O
's	O
Hill	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
cook	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
men	O
's	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
about	O
the	O
third	O
step	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
head	O
clerk	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sykes	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
counting-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
money	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
lining	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
the	O
way	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Sykes	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rider	O
at	O
Bennett	O
's	O
Hill	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
Ludgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
first	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
a	O
lining	O
under	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
pence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Scypher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
buckles	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
in	O
the	O
bed-room	O
.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Schutz	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
more	O
?	O
Schutz	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
That	O
thimble	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
plead	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
the	O
thimble	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Esther	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bulford	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
ear-ring	O
case	O
,	O
one	O
gold-ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bristol	O
stone	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
stone	O
breast	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
eighteen-pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Bulford	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Esther	B-pers
Bulford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bride	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Finchley	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
post-chaises	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
were	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
daughter	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
over	O
Finchley-common	B-place
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
haley	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
light	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
round	O
and	O
put	O
their	O
heads	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
what	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
a	O
paper	O
ear-ring	O
case	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
wires	O
in	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
ears	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
pen-knife	O
,	O
a	O
breast	O
buckle	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen-pence	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
dark	O
coloured	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
the	O
colour	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
-	O
Bulford	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bulford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
men	O
they	O
were	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
fat	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
about	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
frightened	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
could	O
you	O
make	O
such	O
particular	O
observation	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
Just	O
light	O
enough	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
b	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
he	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
A	O
darkish	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
looked	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bulford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Finchley	O
on	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
before	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
chaise	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
and	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
chaise	O
was	O
stopped	O
before	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
behind	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
hindermost	O
chaise	O
first	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
man	O
on	O
Finchley-common	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
your	O
wife	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Bulford	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
It	O
was	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
uncle	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
Norwich	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
house	O
home	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
proof	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
appeared	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
DEATH	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
POSSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
;	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
made	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Benjey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Benjey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clergyman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
Gore	I-place
.	O
My	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
boarding-school	O
for	O
young	O
ladies	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
our	O
knowledge	O
:	O
and	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
ladies	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hickes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
teacher	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Benjey	O
's	O
school	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
on	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
?	O
Hickes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
perfectly	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
missed	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
?	O
Hickes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
these	O
stays	O
were	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
was	O
missed	O
of	O
Miss	O
Sutton	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
linen	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
aprons	O
a	O
book	O
muslin	O
and	O
a	O
stript	O
one	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
and	O
a	O
long-lawn	O
apron	O
;	O
a	O
gown	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
's	O
;	O
(	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
here	O
,	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
misled	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
a	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
-	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
one	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
one	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
duplicate	O
:	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
place	O
she	O
mentioned	O
:	O
He	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
questioned	O
her	O
further	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
satisfy	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
Round-house	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
contained	O
in	O
this	O
foul-cloaths	O
bag	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
for	O
examination	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
Mr.	O
Benjeys	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
consult	O
Sir	O
John	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Benjey	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
should	O
take	O
a	O
servant	O
without	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
A	O
servant	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
recommended	O
this	O
young	O
girl	O
:	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
on	O
her	O
character	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
35	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LUMDAY	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
tea-spoons	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
J	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
B.	O
the	O
other	O
A.	O
M.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sort	O
;	O
Levi	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fire-ball-court	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
ladies	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
spoons	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
together	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
at	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Funendos	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
knowing	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
two	O
spoons	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Lumley	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
He	O
drew	O
out	O
one	O
tablespoon	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
He	O
then	O
drew	O
out	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
both	O
.	O
Mills	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
fetch	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
bring	O
handcuffs	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
Loveday	O
said	O
his	O
mother	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
small	O
tea-spoons	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
flannel	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
searched	O
to	O
shuffle	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
uncle	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
one	O
Betmaker	O
,	O
a	O
master	O
cow-keeper	O
.	O
Next	O
day	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Betmaker	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
spoons	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
over	O
her	O
plate	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
after	O
looking	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
none	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
spoons	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
letters	O
as	O
these	O
last	O
two	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
same	O
make	O
.	O
Loveday	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
in	O
Betmaker	O
's	O
.	O
Mills	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
passage	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WYLDE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
,	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Hannah	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shipley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
9.	I-place
in	I-place
Marybone-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
That	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
apartments	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
Part	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
a	O
buckle	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
shut	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
the	O
wash-house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen-door	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fastened	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
then	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
body	O
hear	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lived	O
there	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
stockings	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
painter	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
middle-aged	O
woman	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
apartment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Great	O
Russ	O
ell-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
Standing	O
at	O
that	O
street	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
cross	O
Russell-street	O
;	O
each	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
what	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
good	O
fellow	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
looked	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
their	O
having	O
bundles	O
;	O
on	O
this	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
his	O
bundle	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
rattle	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
for	O
more	O
assistance	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
made	O
off	O
:	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
now	O
produced	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
man	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
with	O
orders	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
likely	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
money	O
was	O
?	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
six-pences	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
and	O
Flag	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bundle	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
38	O
,	O
39	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
QUIN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
76	O
pair	O
of	O
pattens	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
King's-street	B-place
.	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
pattens	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
warehouse	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
1500	O
dozen	O
perhaps	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
about	O
six	O
dozen	O
pattens	O
from	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
directly	O
opposite	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
locked	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
myself	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
opened	O
by	O
force	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
box-lock	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
opened	O
;	O
about	O
Tuesday	O
se'nnight	O
following	O
I	O
heard	O
these	O
pattens	O
were	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pattens	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
manufactory	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
deal	O
largely	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
sold	O
great	O
numbers	O
of	O
these	O
pattens	O
?	O
Hayter	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
wholesale	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
great	O
numbers	O
;	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
sold	O
a	O
100	O
dozen	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
fifty	O
dozen	O
to	O
one	O
person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ellingham	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Horn	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
then	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
pattens	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
many	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
five	O
dozen	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
then	O
where	O
I	O
should	O
meet	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
they	O
fixed	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
meantime	O
,	O
being	O
suspicious	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
appointed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
cloak	O
on	O
purpose	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
pattens	O
were	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
pattens	O
then	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
next	O
night	O
,	O
only	O
six	O
pair	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
in	O
Rose-street	O
;	O
accordingly	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
having	O
spoke	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
to	O
watch	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
some	O
court	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
showed	O
me	O
two	O
bags	O
filled	O
with	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
dozen	O
of	O
pattens	O
.	O
Stevens	O
was	O
gone	O
on	O
a	O
message	O
for	O
Quin	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Quin	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Stevens	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Clarke	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Quin	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
these	O
pattens	O
from	O
an	O
oil-shop	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
they	O
had	O
advertised	O
these	O
pattens	O
?	O
Eillingham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
court	O
was	O
a	O
thorough-fare	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
pattens	O
;	O
the	O
six	O
pair	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
bags	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
;	O
these	O
pattens	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Steven	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
we	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
St.	O
George's-fields	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
pillar	O
and	O
the	O
King's-bench	O
prison	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
pick	O
up	O
some	O
pattens	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
challenged	O
by	O
Quin	O
when	O
in	O
Tottlefield	O
's	O
prison	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
visit	O
at	O
the	O
prison	O
to	O
some	O
friend	O
about	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
assaulted	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
challenged	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
pattens	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
pick	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
prize	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
swore	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
pattens	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
dark	O
and	O
light	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
these	O
pattens	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
four	O
feet	O
from	O
the	O
foot-path	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
off	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
pattens	O
were	O
lying	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
nearer	O
them	O
by	O
ten	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
trade	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
George-yard	O
,	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
when	O
a	O
ship	O
returns	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
to	O
Quin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
;	O
Quin	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
faithful	O
trusty	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
better	O
then	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
having	O
found	O
some	O
pattens	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
offence	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
bond	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
thing	O
could	O
be	O
softened	O
,	O
provided	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
and	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
his	O
friends	O
would	O
make	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
his	O
recognizance	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
40	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
robbing	O
a	O
mail	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
bag	O
of	O
letters	O
called	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight-bag	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
2	O
d	O
count	O
or	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
mail	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
sent	O
and	O
conveyed	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
a	O
letter	O
before	O
sent	O
by	O
Job	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Buswell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
linen-drapers	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
3d	O
count	O
for	O
stealing	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
mail	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
letters	O
were	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
letter	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Job	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Messrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
Buswell	O
,	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
containing	O
therein	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs	B-pers
.	I-pers
Eade	I-pers
and	I-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
at	O
ten	O
days	O
sight	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
4th	O
count	O
for	O
stealing	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
letter	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
Job	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
directed	O
by	O
Messrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
Buswell	O
,	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
bag	O
of	O
letters	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight-bag	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
5th	O
count	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
bag	O
of	O
letters	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight-bag	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
one	O
letter	O
before	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Job	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
wight	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
Buswell	O
,	O
and	O
containing	O
a	O
certain	O
paper	O
writing	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
words	O
and	O
figures	O
following	O
.	O
Portsmouth	O
Com	O
.	O
``	O
16	O
Oct.	O
61	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
at	O
ten	O
days	O
sight	O
pray	O
pay	O
unto	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
or	O
order	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
without	O
further	O
advice	O
,	O
from	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Crafts	I-pers
.	O
To	O
Messrs.	O
Eade	O
and	O
Wilton	O
,	O
at	O
King	O
Edward	O
Stairs	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
''	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
6th	O
count	O
charges	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
fourth	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
letter	O
sent	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	B-pers
T.	I-pers
Webb	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
No	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Grace-church-street	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
7th	O
count	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
letter	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
certain	O
paper-writing	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
William	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
and	O
Son	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Macaulay	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
8th	O
count	O
for	O
a	O
letter	O
sent	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Grosmith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pidgeons	I-pers
distiller	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
9th	O
count	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
letter	O
containing	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
subscribed	O
William	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
and	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Macauley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
King	I-pers
or	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
in	O
account	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
The	O
10th	O
count	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
packet	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
bag	O
of	O
letters	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight-bag	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
10th	O
count	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
packet	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
bag	O
of	O
letters	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight-bag	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
11th	O
count	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
bag	O
one	O
packet	O
,	O
sent	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Jemmet	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
The	O
12th	O
count	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
packet	O
containing	O
two	O
paper	O
writings	O
,	O
putporting	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
bills	O
of	O
exchange	O
subscribed	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
twenty-two	O
pounds	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
in	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
Graff	B-pers
Huber	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
eighteen	O
pounds	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
;	O
for	O
value	O
in	O
account	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
+	O
Job	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
rider	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
Roswell	O
,	O
in	O
Corbet-court	O
,	O
Grace-church-street	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
;	O
I	O
dispatched	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
there	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Brown	O
and	O
Co.	O
the	O
contents	O
was	O
a	O
ten-pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
and	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
this	O
memorandum	O
book	O
an	O
entry	O
of	O
the	O
particulars	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
on	O
Eade	O
and	O
Wilton	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
or	O
order	O
(	O
a	O
draft	O
shewn	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
White	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
at	O
ten	O
days	O
sight	O
,	O
pray	O
pay	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
without	O
further	O
advice	O
from	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Craff	I-pers
.	O
To	O
Messrs.	O
Eades	O
and	O
Wilton	O
at	O
King	O
Edward	O
Stairs	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
endorsement	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
upon	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
acceptance	O
has	O
been	O
written	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
this	O
letter	O
myself	O
into	O
the	O
post-office	O
at	O
Newport	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Newport	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
.	O
I	O
inclosed	O
four	O
Bills	O
in	O
letter	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Jemmet	I-pers
,	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Borough	O
,	O
London	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
22	O
l.	O
one	O
of	O
18	O
l.	O
one	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
74	O
l.	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
post	O
myself	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
bills	O
of	O
22	O
l.	O
and	O
18	O
l.	O
drawn	O
upon	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Upon	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Graff	O
Huber	O
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
of	O
Exeter	O
payable	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bills	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Exon	O
,	O
21	O
Sept	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
22	O
l.	O
30	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
pay	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	O
Coade	O
,	O
or	O
order	O
22	O
l.	O
for	O
value	O
in	O
account	O
as	O
per	O
advice	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
Graff	O
Huber	O
and	O
Co.	O
merchants	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Exon	O
,	O
the	O
28	O
Seqt	O
.	O
1771	O
.	O
30	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
pay	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
,	O
on	O
order	O
18	O
l	O
,	O
value	O
in	O
account	O
,	O
per	O
advice	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Coade	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
To	O
Messrs.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Craff	O
Huber	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
merchants	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Newport	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
post-office	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
T.	O
Webb	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
Grace-church-street	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
closed	O
a	O
bill	O
drawn	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
letter	O
was	O
wrote	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
was	O
drawn	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Macaulay	I-pers
for	O
30	O
l.	O
31	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
or	O
order	O
.	O
A	O
bill	O
shewn	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
Richard	O
Brown	O
endorsed	O
upon	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
.	O
Newport	O
,	O
Oct.	O
5	O
,	O
1771	O
,	O
30	O
l.	O
30	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
or	O
order	O
30	O
l.	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
as	O
advised	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
and	O
Son	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Macaulay	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Abels	I-pers
,	O
London	O
.	O
Endorsed	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tesdale	O
Webb	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cows	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pigeon	I-pers
,	O
distiller	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
that	O
letter	O
contain	O
?	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
A	O
bill	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
drawn	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
and	O
Son	O
.	O
A	O
draft	O
shewn	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
the	O
letter	O
was	O
wrote	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
paper	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
.	O
Newport	O
,	O
October	O
16	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
30	O
l.	O
30	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
King	I-pers
or	O
order	O
,	O
30	O
l.	O
value	O
in	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
at	O
advised	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
and	O
Son	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Macaulay	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Abels	I-pers
,	O
London	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
this	O
letter	O
to	O
David	B-pers
Dore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
post-office	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Dore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
at	O
Cows	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
giving	O
you	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
?	O
Dore	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
post-office	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
?	O
Dore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
any	O
partner	O
?	O
Dore	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Grossmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
any	O
other	O
partner	O
?	O
Dore	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
letter	O
into	O
the	O
post-office	O
?	O
Dore	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
21st	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
charge	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
particular	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
carried	O
the	O
letter	O
?	O
Dore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
post-office	O
at	O
Newport	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
all	O
the	O
letters	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
then	O
I	O
sealed	O
the	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
forwarded	O
it	O
as	O
usual	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
usual	O
time	O
of	O
its	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Lawrence	O
of	O
Cows	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
bag	O
was	O
it	O
put	O
in	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
A	O
leather	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
tie	O
it	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
seal	O
the	O
string	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
that	O
the	O
bag	O
goes	O
to	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
To	O
Cows	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
post-office	O
at	O
Cows	O
.	O
The	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
bag	O
came	O
safe	O
sealed	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
all	O
the	O
Newport	O
letters	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
my	O
own	O
letters	O
out	O
and	O
stamp	O
and	O
mark	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
bag	O
goes	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
letters	O
did	O
you	O
forward	O
to	O
Southampton	O
?	O
Todd	O
.	O
About	O
fifty-four	O
