TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Eleventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BRASS	O
CROSBY	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
COOKE	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
BRASS	O
CROSBY	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
1st	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Flexmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trimby	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
served	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
1st	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Capell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Choyce	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Stancy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Aberdeen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Lassel	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pinner	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Morling	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Boch	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Shatten	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Gelly	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hopwood	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harward	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
and	O
Christopher	O
Knight	O
served	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lassell	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Camden	I-pers
,	O
instead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Choyce	I-pers
.	O
232	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
Abraham	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
plain	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Franco	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
hats	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
my	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
lemons	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
two	O
hats	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
a	O
plain	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
near	O
Cree-Church	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
hats	O
were	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
frightened	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chair	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
lemons	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
hats	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Franco	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Factor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
.	O
He	O
porters	O
and	O
sells	O
lemons	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
worthy	O
,	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
233	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Ruth	B-pers
Frostick	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Francis	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petty	B-place
France	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
gown	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
It	O
hung	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
hook	O
,	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
:	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
gown	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
untie	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
out	O
(	O
the	O
gown	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
tore	O
it	O
in	O
pulling	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
hook	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
bed	O
gown	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
meat	O
for	O
my	O
four	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
wanted	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
service	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
children	O
has	O
she	O
got	O
?	O
Sunderland	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
since	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
worked	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
about	O
the	O
Commons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
she	O
any	O
children	O
?	O
George	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
last	O
woman	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
George	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
she	O
has	O
any	O
children	O
?	O
George	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
very	O
sure	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
absent	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
ill.	O
She	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
family	O
she	O
has	O
?	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
talk	O
of	O
her	O
children	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
234	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Orme	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Marybone-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
linen	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
bundles	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeats	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
three	O
bundles	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
some	O
upon	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
some	O
upon	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
upon	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
One	O
parcel	O
was	O
pinned	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
upon	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
that	O
contained	O
seven	O
shirts	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
ironed	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Macaulay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
two	O
rooms	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Spicer	O
desired	O
my	O
boy	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
eye	O
to	O
her	O
door	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
lift	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
latched	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
passage	O
leads	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
candle	O
from	O
her	O
:	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Spicer	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
slipped	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
.	O
They	O
slipped	O
down	O
stairs	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
bundles	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Spicer	O
's	O
son	O
.	O
Whilst	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
by	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Two	O
women	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Barns	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
unlatched	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Orme	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Spicers	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
light	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
fire	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
candle	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
blowed	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
light	O
some	O
paper	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
my	O
candle	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
light	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
locked	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
shutting-to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
open	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Macaulays	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
candle	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Barns	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Not	O
then	O
.	O
Whilst	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
pass	O
by	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
One	O
Mrs.	O
Barnes	O
ran	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
?	O
Spicer	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
and	O
detained	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
235	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
bowl	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
seven	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
pewter	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Upper	B-place
Grosvenor-street	I-place
:	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
servants	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
He	O
advertised	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
reward	O
.	O
The	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
went	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
robbery	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
John	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
cook	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
crying	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
sash	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
bar	O
that	O
went	O
from	O
side	O
to	O
side	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
damaged	O
,	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
splintered	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
iron	O
gate	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
that	O
gate	O
was	O
left	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
myself	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Llewellyn	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
a-robbing	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
rather	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
together	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
rob	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
particular	O
place	O
mentioned	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
one	O
attempt	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
declined	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
area	O
gate	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
;	O
Llewellyn	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
Murphy	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
window	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
Llewellyn	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
force	O
open	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
with	O
our	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
:	O
Llewellyn	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
first	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
bowl	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
then	O
seven	O
tea	O
spoons	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cupboard	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
doors	O
off	O
.	O
Llewellyn	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
brought	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Murray	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
that	O
Murray	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
evidence	O
against	O
,	O
and	O
hanged	O
so	O
many	O
men	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
accused	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
236	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
ten	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
six	O
printed-linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
eight	O
linen	O
pillow	O
biers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Red-lion	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Charter-lane	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
afterwards	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
's	O
clothes	O
!	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
stop	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bannistock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
one	O
had	O
one	O
handle	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
handle	O
;	O
the	O
basket	O
had	O
wet	O
linen	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
's	O
doors	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
clothes	O
?	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
collared	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
stroke	O
at	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
dropped	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
dragged	O
me	O
two	O
yards	O
:	O
I	O
hollowed	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
The	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stripped	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Winder	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
his	O
blue	O
jacket	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
near	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
lay	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bevistock	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Bevistock	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
'	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
237	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-third	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
she	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
bad	O
fame	O
in	O
Church-lane	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
laid	O
together	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
stole	O
my	O
watch	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Foreman	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
laid	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
those	O
were	O
not	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
stamp	O
yours	O
were	O
of	O
?	O
Foreman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
miss	O
your	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
?	O
Foreman	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
day	O
light	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
whole	O
fact	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
acknowledgment	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
her	O
any	O
favour	O
?	O
Foreman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
depends	O
upon	O
her	O
confession	O
,	O
made	O
under	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
allowed	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Connicombe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
spade	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilbraham	I-pers
Bootle	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
the	O
22	O
d	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
239	O
.	O
240	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
muslin	O
slips	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Coward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-six	O
half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Peter	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hatter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
quarter	O
,	O
by	O
filing	O
the	O
edges	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
other	O
servants	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
dinner	O
and	O
leave	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
another	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
from	O
dinner	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
sixteen-pence	O
deficient	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
were	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
pull	O
their	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
pockets	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
shook	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
half-pence	O
in	O
your	O
coat	O
pocket	O
:	O
my	O
brother	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
marked	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
half-pence	O
:	O
they	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
exactly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
marked	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
missed	O
about	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
over	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
searched	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
or	O
none	O
:	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
indeed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
:	O
my	O
brother	O
touched	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
rattled	O
:	O
my	O
brother	O
put	O
his	O
hands	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
eight	O
pennyworth	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
penny-worth	O
were	O
marked	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
satisfied	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
was	O
what	O
you	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
paid	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
marked	O
money	O
away	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
servants	O
orders	O
not	O
to	O
add	O
or	O
diminish	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
paid	O
sometimes	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
pockets	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
file	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
all	O
alike	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
change	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
242	O
,	O
243	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Southwark	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
shillings	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee-buckles	O
:	O
the	O
till	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
is	O
here	O
with	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bruin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Dawson	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-third	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
eight	O
shillings	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
enough	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
buying	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
two	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
his	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Davis	O
.	O
Dawson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
buckles	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Magpie	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
Davis	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
February	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
244	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Clement	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clement	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
.	O
Yesterday	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
woman	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
pass	O
:	O
afterwards	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
something	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
cloak	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
cotton	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
pattern	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
pattern	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
pile	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
nobody	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
answer	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
245	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
fish-skin	O
smelling	O
bottle	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
make	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
cases	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
six-penny	O
penknife	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
one	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
half	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
This	O
case	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
them	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pedlar	O
's	O
licence	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
in	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
case	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
moment	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Upford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pedlar	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
tin	O
case	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
my	O
master	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
licence	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
this	O
case	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
draw	O
'd	O
himself	O
away	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
246	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
Cricket	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cricket	O
,	O
a	O
proctor	O
in	O
Doctors-Commons	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
with	O
a	O
napkin	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
napkin	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
immediately	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
deposed	O
to	O
his	O
confessing	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
first	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
247	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
M'Feast	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hasher	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hasher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
cheapside	B-place
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
nuts	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
girls	O
stood	O
round	O
me	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
round	O
about	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
248	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Ferrall	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
249	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
window	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Knowler	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
peticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Knowler	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
250	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Amelia	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
251	O
,	O
252	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Mannon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliffe-high-way	B-place
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
drinking	O
tea	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Knight	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
opposite	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
sold	O
a	O
glass	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
saw	O
two	O
women	O
take	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
stall	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
talking	O
together	O
in	O
Princes-square	O
.	O
They	O
denied	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Mannon	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
cloak	O
on	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
glass	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Mannon	O
said	O
Murphy	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
just	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
glass	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
stall	O
,	O
that	O
Murphy	O
went	O
rather	O
before	O
Mannon	O
whilst	O
Mannon	O
took	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
Mannon	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Princes-square	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
glass	O
whilst	O
she	O
made	O
water	O
;	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
come	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
with	O
it	O
openly	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Colsgrove	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Mannon	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
childhood	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mannon	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Murphy	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
253	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Day	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harnan	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harnan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
spoon	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
when	O
my	O
neighbour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bootle	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
for	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
my	O
spoon	O
.	O
-	O
Bootle	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
spoon	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
this	O
spoon	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
twenty-five	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
twenty-three	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
master	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brother	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
none	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
spoon	O
:	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
cut	O
down	O
his	O
breeches	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
next	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harnan	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
day	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
spoon	O
amongst	O
some	O
turnep	O
pairings	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
254	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dolman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Harnan	B-pers
Paogus	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Harnan	O
Paogus	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford	B-place
Road	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
;	O
on	O
February	O
25th	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walk	O
softly	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
three	O
blankets	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
table	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
walk	O
softly	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
past	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
blankets	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
some	O
people	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Paogus	O
pursuing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
with	O
the	O
blankets	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
errand	O
boy	O
to	O
a	O
copper	O
plate	O
printer	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
necessary	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
needs	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
button	O
up	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
blankets	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
255	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Rumbles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harling	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
256	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
stewpan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
fender	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Catharine	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
257	O
,	O
258	O
,	O
259	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hogshaw	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
blue	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
blue	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
cloath	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
new	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
crimson	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
stone	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hogshaw	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
in	O
Goswell-street	B-place
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Islington	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Sibber	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
will	O
in	O
my	O
favour	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Sibber	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
became	O
my	O
house	O
upon	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
will	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
six	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
windows	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
outside	O
shutters	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
wrenched	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
sash	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
lifted	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parlour	O
door	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
locks	O
of	O
a	O
beauset	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Sibber	O
kept	O
all	O
his	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
papers	O
were	O
thrown	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
(	O
repeats	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Hogshaw	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Burrel	O
's	O
the	O
butcher	O
.	O
The	O
cloaths	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
beds	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
's	O
apparel	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
left	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sibber	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Lowe	O
,	O
Who	O
lives	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
now	O
?	O
Hogshaw	O
.	O
An	O
officer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sibber	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
at	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Moody	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
us	O
lurking	O
about	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Hogshaw	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
before	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
my	O
hour	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
walked	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
stand	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
coming	O
with	O
three	O
large	O
bundles	O
;	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
's	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
knowing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
coming	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
sheered	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
that	O
bundle	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
man	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
stuck	O
between	O
the	O
posts	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
man	O
dropped	O
his	O
bundle	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
stand	O
to	O
mine	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
third	O
man	O
as	O
close	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
across	O
Moorfields	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
dropped	O
out	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
to	O
them	O
but	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Finsbury	O
watchmen	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
time	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
things	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
advertised	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hogshaw	O
claimed	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Compasses	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
them	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lumb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
Samuel	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
's	O
house	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
then	O
in	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
Court	O
,	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
circumstance	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
prisoners	O
but	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
260	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
261	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
cutting	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
temple	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
with	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Roger	O
.	O
+	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
charges	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
count	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Glynn	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
and	O
Tomkins	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
A	O
fourth	O
count	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
steward	O
to	O
the	O
proprietors	O
of	O
Ranelagh	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
adjoining	O
.	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Glynn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dew	O
are	O
trustees	O
;	O
the	O
freehold	O
was	O
bought	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
some	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
placed	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hearnshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
piedement	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
building	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
temple	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
be	O
locked	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
discovered	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
caused	O
a	O
ladder	O
they	O
left	O
behind	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
down	O
to	O
Mill-bank	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
advertisement	O
inserted	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
with	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
end	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
going	O
down	O
Millbank	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Beach	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
belonged	O
to	O
Blackfriars	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
discovered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Bear-lane	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
his	O
landlady	O
denied	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
whilst	O
he	O
dressed	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
his	O
innocence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
innocence	O
would	O
greatly	O
depend	O
upon	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
for	O
seven	O
weeks	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
warrant	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
for	O
Michael	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Callo	I-pers
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
they	O
declared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Fox	O
hounds	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
denied	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
for	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
lame	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hearnshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
Ranelagh	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
set	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
March	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
gardens	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
set	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
temple	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
building	O
?	O
Hearnshaw	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
foot	O
high	O
;	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
college	O
clock	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
a-top	O
of	O
the	O
building	O
by	O
a	O
ladder	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
came	O
a-top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
passed	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
concealed	O
,	O
to	O
listen	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
watching	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
began	O
working	O
,	O
cutting	O
,	O
and	O
ripping	O
the	O
lead	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
blunderbuss	O
a-top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
out	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
advanced	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
taking	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
fired	O
at	O
his	O
legs	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
disable	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
wall	O
about	O
two	O
foot	O
above	O
the	O
leads	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
head	O
foremost	O
over	O
there	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
eighteen	O
foot	O
high	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
throwed	O
themselves	O
over	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
this	O
Boyce	O
;	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
cloudy	O
?	O
Hearnshaw	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
obstruct	O
my	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
people	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
the	O
man	O
lived	O
near	O
Black-friars	O
Bridge	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Sunday	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
direction	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
gave	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
denied	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
we	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
about	O
being	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
seven	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Hearnshaw	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
also	O
watched	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Richard	O
Beach	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
spoke	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
being	O
wounded	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
too	O
positive	O
;	O
Hernshaw	O
spoke	O
positively	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
Holmes	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
positive	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
so	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
were	O
mistaken	O
;	O
therefore	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
so	O
positive	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
men	O
and	O
one	O
woman	O
,	O
they	O
only	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
a-piece	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
opinion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
positively	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
your	O
belief	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Shaw	O
.	O
Positively	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Callo	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Hounds	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
Swan	O
Walk	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
almost	O
nine	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
flood	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
far	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
To	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
odd	O
thing	O
to	O
come	O
against	O
the	O
tide	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
tide	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
come	O
against	O
tide	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
back	O
against	O
tide	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
cold	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
walk	O
.	O
One	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Masters	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
without	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
carry	O
you	O
for	O
nothing	O
than	O
go	O
without	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
seven	O
weeks	O
,	O
till	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
case	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
for	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Bear-lane	O
.	O
Boyce	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Boyce	O
's	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
twentieth	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
very	O
early	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
limp	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
sigh	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
carried	O
these	O
people	O
up	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
purl	O
and	O
some	O
hot	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
rum	O
.	O
I	O
landed	O
them	O
at	O
Westminster	O
bridge	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
smoaking	O
a	O
pipe	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
I	O
was	O
lame	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
needle	O
in	O
my	O
leg	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
worked	O
out	O
now	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
charged	O
with	O
ripping	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
knows	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
key	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
chamber	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
unlocked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
this	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
night	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hard-working	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
wounded	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
mark	O
of	O
powder	O
or	O
shot	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hit	O
his	O
knee	O
against	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
him	O
limp	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cook	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
him	O
lame	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
sixteen	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shipmate	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
war	O
,	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
at	O
major	O
Wade	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
often	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
262	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Solomon	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Whitrow	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Routh	I-pers
,	O
two	O
hundred	O
dozen	O
of	O
silk	O
knee-garters	O
,	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
their	O
property	O
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Routh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Esther	B-pers
Whitrow	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
silk	O
knee-garter	O
makers	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
at	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
in	O
our	O
lane	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
twenty-fifth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
just	O
grew	O
dark	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
which	O
is	O
within	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
counter	O
there	O
laid	O
drawers	O
with	O
silk	O
knee-garters	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Routh	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
drawer	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
contained	O
silk	O
knee-garters	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
advertiser	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
printed	O
hand-bills	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Homan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Bunhill-row	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-fifth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
work	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
seven	O
.	O
Going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Levi	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
walking	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
walk	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
looking	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
stand	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
holding	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
on	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Stony-lane	O
.	O
About	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Levi	O
receive	O
one	O
drawer	O
covered	O
with	O
paper	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
took	O
another	O
drawer	O
.	O
Levi	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
came	O
up	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
them	O
walked	O
soberly	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Levi	O
receive	O
the	O
first	O
drawer	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
follow	O
Levi	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
:	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
gentleman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
some	O
drawers	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
master	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
gone	O
up	O
this	O
lane	O
,	O
another	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
gentleman	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
take	O
some	O
drawers	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
lock	O
to	O
mend	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
Marlborough-court	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
took	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Routh	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Brabroke	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
men	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
:	O
Levi	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
saw	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
paper	O
,	O
received	O
by	O
Levi	O
?	O
Routh	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
wore	O
an	O
apron	O
like	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
cane	O
like	O
a	O
bailiff	O
's	O
follower	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
stop	O
me	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Why	O
not	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
notice	O
?	O
Homan	O
.	O
Seeing	O
the	O
other	O
parties	O
go	O
along	O
so	O
peaceably	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
harm	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
him	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Homan	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
gang	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
gang	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
a	O
Jew	O
?	O
Homan	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
four	O
Jews	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
was	O
they	O
at	O
?	O
Homan	O
.	O
A	O
bad	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
indicted	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dishonest	O
person	O
?	O
Homan	O
.	O
He	O
slash	O
'd	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
seemed	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
a	O
living	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
load	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
strained	O
my	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Marks	O
got	O
something	O
for	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
get	O
his	O
living	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Portering	O
.	O
He	O
lodges	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Mark	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
in	O
Marlborough-court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
garters	O
were	O
stole	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
nursed	O
Mrs.	O
Mark	O
's	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
next	O
Monday	O
come	O
fortnight	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mark	O
's	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Marks	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
his	O
back	O
by	O
carrying	O
a	O
load	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
Mrs.	O
Marks	O
's	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
fish	O
for	O
supper	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
who	O
sells	O
fish	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
brought	O
some	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Marks	O
called	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
walked	O
about	O
,	O
smoaking	O
his	O
pipe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
liquor	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Only	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Marks	O
fetched	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
boiler	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Bowman	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
lodged	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
for	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
this	O
happen	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
A	O
fortnight	O
,	O
next	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
on	O
Monday	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
last	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
fortnight	O
next	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
had	O
happened	O
on	O
Lady-day	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
known	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
Lady-day	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
received	O
this	O
shilling	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
She	O
pays	O
me	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
due	O
then	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Simons	O
.	O
In	O
Duke	O
's	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Simons	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Marks	O
?	O
Simons	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
porter	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
Haget	O
's	O
passage	O
some	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
worked	O
hard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
carry	O
loads	O
from	O
Spital-fields	O
market	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bakaruk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
family	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
portered	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Marks	O
?	O
Simons	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
has	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
263	O
,	O
264	O
,	O
265	O
,	O
266	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Magdalen	I-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
soup	O
ladle	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pearl	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pearl	O
drops	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
smelling	O
bottle	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
top	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Guinnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
:	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
South-Audley	B-place
street	I-place
:	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
hall	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
pantry	O
adjoining	O
to	O
this	O
hall	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
from	O
the	O
hall	O
into	O
the	O
pantry	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
more	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
lights	O
in	O
their	O
hand	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
one	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
first	O
,	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
dog	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
stir	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
Immediately	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
other	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
one	O
cried	O
out	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
Cock	O
your	O
pistols	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
pointed	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
pistols	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
stirr	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
rose	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Hold	O
your	O
tongue	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
every	O
thing	O
we	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
every	O
thing	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
plate	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
,	O
where	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
in	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
where	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
backwards	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
None	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
hall	O
where	O
I	O
laid	O
,	O
and	O
rummaged	O
about	O
.	O
Presently	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
take	O
my	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Isaacs	O
take	O
up	O
my	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
afterwards	O
into	O
the	O
hall	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
hat	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
my	O
hall	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
Price	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
robbers	O
,	O
asked	O
Isaacs	O
why	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
other	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
belonging	O
to	O
this	O
servant	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
thereupon	O
Isaacs	O
laid	O
my	O
hat	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
consulted	O
together	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
agreed	O
among	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
stay	O
below	O
stairs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
agreed	O
that	O
Price	O
should	O
stay	O
below	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Price	O
staid	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
walking	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
by	O
my	O
bed	O
side	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
after	O
this	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
above	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
first	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
breaking	O
open	O
something	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
presently	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
bell	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pounding	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
alarm	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
that	O
were	O
up	O
stairs	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
as	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
and	O
over	O
the	O
back	O
wall	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
brought	O
bundles	O
of	O
things	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
hall	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
directed	O
them	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
escape	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
which	O
opened	O
from	O
the	O
hall	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
that	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
unlock	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
and	O
make	O
their	O
escape	O
:	O
immediately	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
watchmen	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
find	O
some	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
observed	O
the	O
watchmen	O
were	O
pursuing	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
robbers	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Isaacs	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
that	O
Isaacs	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
Butcher	O
and	O
Haines	O
,	O
but	O
verily	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
breakfast	O
room	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
room	O
forwards	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
whether	O
shut	O
down	O
over	O
night	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
particularly	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
pepper	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hall	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Some	O
things	O
were	O
never	O
found	O
again	O
:	O
two	O
tablespoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
some	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
bottle	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
of	O
Captain	O
Sloper	B-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
others	O
in	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
maid	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
particularly	O
,	O
this	O
sash	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
being	O
shut	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
lower	O
shutters	O
were	O
shut	O
to	O
and	O
the	O
curtains	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
let	O
down	O
likewise	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
again	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
particularly	O
at	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
curtains	O
were	O
still	O
hanging	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
situation	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
garret	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
noise	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
looked	O
down	O
the	O
bannisters	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
strange	O
voices	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nobody	O
;	O
then	O
withdrew	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
drew	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
watchmen	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
watchman	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
thieves	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
three	O
more	O
watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
knock	O
and	O
ring	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
till	O
the	O
man-servant	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
he	O
assured	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
into	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
into	O
the	O
breakfast	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutters	O
put	O
back	O
which	O
were	O
shut-to	O
at	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
room	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
drawers	O
had	O
been	O
all	O
pulled	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
thrown	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
bundles	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
bed	O
room	O
below	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
standing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
candlesticks	O
and	O
a	O
soup	O
ladle	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
were	O
,	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
room	O
:	O
also	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
,	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
a	O
wash	O
stand	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
buckles	O
in	O
some	O
other	O
drawer	O
:	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
bundle	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
you	O
call	O
the	O
breakfast	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
three	O
.	O
They	O
let	O
the	O
curtains	O
down	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
light	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
eyes	O
.	O
The	O
window-curtains	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
shut	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
awaked	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
light	O
and	O
noise	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
repeated	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
answer	O
.	O
They	O
began	O
to	O
rifle	O
my	O
drawers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
mistook	O
him	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
recollect	O
him	O
perfectly	O
now	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
bed-side	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
requested	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
murder	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
No	O
,	O
immediately	O
,	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
minutes	O
after	O
we	O
both	O
ceased	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
light	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
burn	O
a	O
lamp	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
through	O
the	O
curtains	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
linen	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
light	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
curtain	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
stood	O
there	O
about	O
seven	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
acknowledged	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
sign	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Did	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidences	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Butcher	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
justice	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
admitted	O
without	O
farther	O
discoveries	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
no	O
threats	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
Butcher	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
without	O
he	O
made	O
other	O
discoveries	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
discoveries	O
were	O
made	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
and	O
what	O
answer	O
did	O
they	O
make	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Another	O
man	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
Isaacs	O
was	O
so	O
changed	O
with	O
fear	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
pale	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
Butcher	O
said	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
that	O
confessed	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
Butcher	O
said	O
that	O
Isaacs	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
bedside	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
first	O
suspected	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
the	O
dyer	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Little	O
Suffolk-street	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
green	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
is	O
here	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
the	O
dyer	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
Haines	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Butcher	O
;	O
Butcher	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Haines	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
Haines	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
You	O
said	O
some	O
bundles	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
just	O
produced	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
gowns	O
and	O
some	O
linen	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
gown	O
was	O
one	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
ptman	O
's	O
bed	O
room	O
below	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
Haines	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
bedroom	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Not	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
A	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
repeating	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
constable	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
dyer	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Butcher	O
and	O
Haines	O
were	O
first	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
this	O
dyer	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
Isaacs	O
(	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
resemblance	O
between	O
the	O
Jew	O
and	O
this	O
dyer	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Jew	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
and	O
altered	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
remember	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
dyer	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
recollect	O
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
perfectly	O
well	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
The	O
Thursday	O
following	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
there	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
had	O
accused	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
dyer	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
recollected	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
trace	O
the	O
features	O
of	O
Isaacs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
rows	O
of	O
white	O
metal	O
buttons	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
His	O
life	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
stake	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
had	O
not	O
apprized	O
you	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
fixed	O
on	O
a	O
wrong	O
man	O
,	O
should	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
certain	O
knowledge	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
corrected	O
what	O
you	O
had	O
said	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Together	O
with	O
the	O
dyer	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
row	O
of	O
white	O
buttons	O
upon	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
two	O
.	O
Q.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
mistaken	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
declare	O
that	O
the	O
dyer	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
said	O
so	O
;	O
Butcher	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
looked	O
so	O
horrid	O
that	O
he	O
frightened	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
eyes	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Sloper	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
on	O
the	O
seventeenth	O
of	O
March	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
fore	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
and	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
watchmen	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
search	O
our	O
garden	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
area	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
hollowed	O
out	O
,	O
Who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
a	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
thieves	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
watchmen	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
Isaacs	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
give	O
myself	O
prisoner	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
searched	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoon	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
doors	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
silver	O
spoons	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
bottle	O
rack	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soup	O
ladle	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
cases	O
like	O
buckle	O
cases	O
,	O
with	O
buckles	O
and	O
rings	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Isaacs	O
if	O
he	O
left	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
our	O
area	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
Butcher	O
or	O
Haines	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
under	O
a	O
bottle	O
rack	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Guinnet	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
cases	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
were	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
's	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
These	O
cases	O
were	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
These	O
cases	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wingrove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
in	O
South	O
Audley	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
sash	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
footman	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
chissel	O
lay	O
by	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
stones	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
An	O
information	O
was	O
brought	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
stables	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stables	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
were	O
his	O
accomplices	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
him	O
,	O
Haines	O
,	O
Butcher	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
his	O
confederates	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Little	O
Suffolk	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
green	O
shop	O
.	O
Isaacs	O
said	O
Haines	O
got	O
in	O
first	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
next	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
palisadoes	O
,	O
up	O
the	O
lamp	O
