TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
1772	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	O
STAFFORD	O
SMYTHE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
||	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
~	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
&	O
c.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Trantum	I-pers
Chamberlin	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hastead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harbrige	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Key	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dibbs	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sheredine	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tuffnell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Haselington	I-pers
John	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Babbs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gaff	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
192	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CROFTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
to	O
Middlerow	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
Coming	O
back	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
my	O
beer	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Leaden-hall	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
coach	O
among	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
it	O
much	O
.	O
One	O
went	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
Leaden-hall	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
up	O
Long-lane	O
and	O
into	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Duke's-head	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
wrong	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
all	O
came	O
into	O
one	O
road	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
Sun-dial	O
just	O
by	O
Swan-alley	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
they	O
sent	O
the	O
coach	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
way	O
,	O
pointing	O
down	O
the	O
Rope-walk	O
,	O
Swan-alley	B-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
Shilcock	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
held	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
down	O
Swan-alley	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
out	O
when	O
they	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
I	O
durst	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
purse	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
Fourteen	O
shillings	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
half-pence	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
counted	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Gates	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Consider	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
heavy	O
charge	O
you	O
bring	O
against	O
these	O
people	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
very	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
place	O
is	O
this	O
rope-walk	O
?	O
is	O
it	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
but	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
only	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
sober	O
enough	O
to	O
run	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hand-basket	O
upon	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
some	O
sowls	O
in	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
the	O
woman	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bad	O
company	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
countryman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
In	O
Essex	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
not	O
pretty	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
London	O
streets	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Leadenhall-market	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
much	O
acquainted	O
with	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
pulled	O
your	O
purse	O
out	O
while	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
?	O
Gates	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
reckoning	O
.	O
Jonathan	O
Shilcock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
John	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
and	O
Chequer	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
liked	O
a	O
good	O
hearty	O
fellow	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
frolick	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
spend	O
it	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cart	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
or	O
Leadenhall-market	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
best	O
go	O
through	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
walk	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
We	O
ordered	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
stop	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Sweatman	I-pers
there	O
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
and	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Gates	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
this	O
Sweatman	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
We	O
ordered	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
up	O
Goswell	O
street	O
to	O
Islington	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
head	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
)	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
paid	O
the	O
other	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
We	O
discharged	O
the	O
coach	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
rank	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
called	O
the	O
same	O
coach	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
rank	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
Pyed	O
Bull	O
coming	O
down	O
Islington	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
aniseed	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
paid	O
for	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gun	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
aniseed	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Swan-alley	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
discharged	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
sign	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
paid	O
for	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
enlisted	O
people	O
for	O
the	O
East-India	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
trepanned	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
or	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
near	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
Rope-walk	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
down	O
the	O
Rope-walk	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
reckoning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
?	O
Shilcock	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
share	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
liquor	O
at	O
other	O
houses	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
towards	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
about	O
him	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
held	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
Sweatman	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
pushed	O
down	O
?	O
Shilcock	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pushed	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
his	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
so	O
might	O
drop	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
they	O
held	O
him	O
while	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
money	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Shilcock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
his	O
purse	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Magpie	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Gates	O
pursue	O
you	O
?	O
Shilcock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
near	O
Hicks's-hall	O
;	O
I	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
among	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Magpie	O
,	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Plato	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
beat	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
John	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
had	O
committed	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
from	O
children	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
old	O
Sun-dial	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
strict	O
search	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
old	O
offenders	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
his	O
brother	O
John	O
and	O
Shilcock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
and	O
Shilcock	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
Croft	O
's	O
mother	O
lives	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
dropt	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
shew	O
me	O
a	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
picked	O
up	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sober	O
?	O
Plato	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
We	O
watched	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
shillings	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
friends	O
here	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
expected	O
my	O
trial	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Plato	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
to	O
sobriety	O
?	O
Plato	O
.	O
Not	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Plato	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Plato	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
193	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
thirty-one	O
ounces	O
of	O
mohair	O
twist	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
partner	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Craven-buildings	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
twist	O
and	O
buttons	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
goods	O
several	O
times	O
within	O
these	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
twist	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
number	O
thirty-two	O
ounces	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
samples	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
pattern	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
piece-brokers	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
offered	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
none	O
offered	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
again	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
said	O
some	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
him	O
in	O
samples	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
whole	O
quantity	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
30th	O
was	O
Thursday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Teage	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
some	O
silk	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
sent	O
to	O
stop	O
twist	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
sold	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
Bedfordbury	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
objection	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
recollect	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
twist	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
twist	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
sent	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
bid	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
whilst	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
step	O
to	O
take	O
.	O
They	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
attended	O
with	O
the	O
twist	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
it	O
corresponded	O
exactly	O
with	O
my	O
sample	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
piece-broker	O
in	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
some	O
twist	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
things	O
at	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
twist	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
compared	O
with	O
his	O
sample	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Davis	O
deposed	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
silk	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
warning	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
31	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Court	O
severely	O
reprimanded	O
Davis	O
for	O
his	O
conduct	O
in	O
purchasing	O
goods	O
at	O
half	O
their	O
value	O
.	O
-	O
Teage	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
and	O
piece-broker	O
in	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
some	O
silk	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
that	O
suspecting	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
of	O
the	O
circumstance	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
man	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
for	O
the	O
twist	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
194	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BUTLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Comer	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
195	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
ALMAN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
large	O
planes	O
,	O
four	O
moulding	O
planes	O
,	O
two	O
smoothing	O
planes	O
,	O
one	O
rabbet	O
plane	O
,	O
one	O
carpenter	O
's	O
plow	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
hammer	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
long	O
planes	O
,	O
four	O
moulding	O
planes	O
,	O
two	O
smoothing	O
planes	O
,	O
nine	O
iron	O
chissels	O
,	O
seven	O
gouges	O
,	O
one	O
oil	O
stone	O
,	O
one	O
rabbet	O
plane	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
hammer	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
at	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
tools	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Ferguson	O
and	O
Edwards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
tools	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Isaac	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
196	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
SOPHIA	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
;	O
Jan.	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILCOX	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty-nine	O
handkerchiefs	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Aldgate	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
behind	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
young	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
windows	O
are	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearcey	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
thieves	O
were	O
run	O
up	O
Church	O
Row	O
;	O
we	O
run	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Bell	O
ale-house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
ignorant	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
dropt	O
them	O
there	O
ourselves	O
:	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
square	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
lay	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
parcels	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
parcels	O
missing	O
from	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
makers	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
and	O
the	O
pattern	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearcey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carry	O
coals	O
for	O
a	O
coal	O
shed	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
standing	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Caley	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
standing	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stared	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
pane	O
crack	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
draw	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
up	O
Church	O
Row	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Caley	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Caley	O
's	O
Sister	O
take	O
one	O
parcel	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apron	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
parcels	O
lay	O
right	O
under	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
parcels	O
there	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
Nancy	B-pers
Caley	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
into	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
lap	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
his	O
apron	O
was	O
tuck	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
parcel	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchiefs	O
laid	O
quite	O
in	O
view	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
other	O
parcels	O
had	O
dropt	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lanrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sold	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
such	O
goods	O
as	O
these	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Caley	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
upon	O
this	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Caley	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
his	O
mother	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
198	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MACKEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ninety-four	O
pounds	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
sheep	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
my	O
people	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
thief	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sheep	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farms	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
the	O
sheep	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
channel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
joined	O
Mr.	O
Worth	O
's	O
servants	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
sheep	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
another	O
person	O
laid	O
the	O
sheep	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
who	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
199	O
,	O
200	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
YOUNGER	I-pers
and	O
PETER	B-pers
M'CLOUD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Holborn	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
pint	O
mugs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Holborn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
||	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
201	O
,	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BALLARD	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
HASSIN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
watch	O
key	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blinkinsop	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
23d	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
203	O
,	O
204	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
and	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
steal	O
springs	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
stay	O
brass	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dimsdale	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
204	O
,	O
205	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAVAGE	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
M'DUFF	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
stuff	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Lyon	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
White's-alley	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
pots	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Main	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
something	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cloak	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
the	O
pots	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
pots	O
home	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
RANKAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
laced	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CUSHINBOROUGH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
white	O
hand	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Gammage	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Resin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk-weaver	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gammage	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
winding	O
hand	O
silk	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
on	O
Jan.	O
8th	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
girl	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
some	O
work	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
girl	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
about	O
three	O
ounces	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
silk	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gammage	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lidden	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
silk	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
informed	O
her	O
mistress	O
of	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bosom	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
seventy	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CROFTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
bundles	O
of	O
espalier	O
rods	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kemshead	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Kemshead	I-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
basket-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Wood's-close	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
to	O
him	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
work	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
several	O
bundles	O
of	O
rods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
two	O
entire	O
bundles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
particular	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
enabled	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
restitution	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Kemshead	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
rods	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
rods	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
eight	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
210	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CROSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
three	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
gauze	O
shifttuckers	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
laced	O
hood	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Penrose	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
||	O
Sarah	B-pers
Penrose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Pen	I-pers
-rose	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Bisseter	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Miller	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Shire-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
made	O
a	O
complaint	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Westminster	O
;	O
a	O
girl	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
information	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
moving	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
robbery	O
;	O
she	O
burst	O
out	O
a	O
crying	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
box	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
clothes	O
in	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
wear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Magdalen-house	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
another	O
girl	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
gaol	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
box	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Miller	O
's	O
husband	O
was	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
a	O
sessions	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
What	O
people	O
live	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
earrings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
dimity	O
robe	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Francis	B-pers
Swingood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
wires	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
pledged	O
on	O
January	O
11	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Keates	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
three	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Renshaw	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
gold	O
wires	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
they	O
informed	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Renshaw	O
's	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Renshaw	I-pers
produced	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
gold	O
wires	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
were	O
pledged	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keates	I-pers
produced	O
three	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
were	O
pawned	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Brown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
tyed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
-	O
Dennison	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
offered	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GREEVES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Masey	I-pers
,	O
February	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Philip	B-pers
Masey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lad	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
dropt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
might	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
bound	O
with	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mess	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gosse	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
LEVI	B-pers
PHILIPS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Poyner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
back	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
shoes	O
into	O
the	O
dirt	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shoes	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
,	O
cheapening	O
some	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
shoes	O
from	O
the	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
money	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Poyner	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
true	O
?	O
Poyner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
216	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ANDREW	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Haysom	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
December	O
12	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Haysom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
king	B-place
's	I-place
road	I-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
four	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
upon	O
me	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
bank	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
they	O
caught	O
my	O
horse	O
's	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
both	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
dead	O
,	O
or	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Haysom	O
.	O
A	O
moon-light	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
at	O
my	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
Collins	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Tudor	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
or	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
felt	O
up	O
my	O
thigh	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
easily	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
myself	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
instantly	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
messenger	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
at	O
the	O
Admiralty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
Haysom	O
.	O
Collins	O
turned	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
my	O
watch	O
or	O
money	O
since	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
Collins	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
?	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
up	O
his	O
all	O
;	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
turnpike	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
prudent	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
swore	O
positive	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fieldings	I-pers
?	O
Haysom	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
swore	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
saved	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
near-sighted	O
?	O
Haysom	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
expression	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
on	O
Parker	O
's	O
tryal	O
,	O
he	O
standing	O
farther	O
off	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Urton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
smith	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
Mr.	O
Nailor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nailor	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
stood	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hope	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
twenty	O
robberies	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
drives	O
a	O
jack-ass	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
horses	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
See	O
William	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
tried	O
for	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
113	O
,	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOWERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
.	O
While	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
lay	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
back	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
me	O
any	O
damage	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
overhauled	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
about	O
9	O
l.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
moidore	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
John	B-pers
M'Carty	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
his	O
confession	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
sign	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
easy	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
all	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
separate	O
times	O
;	O
Hill	O
.	O
All	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
new	O
clothes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
and	O
pushed	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
M'Carty	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
had	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
impressed	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
India-house	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
stood	O
bonds-man	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Hill	O
's	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
these	O
clothes	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
drawer	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
LITTLE	I-pers
JOHN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
her	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
laced	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
check	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Pyne	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Pyne	I-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
any	O
notice	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
clothes	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
-	O
Lyons	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
pledged	O
with	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
master	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
denied	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
committing	O
this	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
another	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
220	O
.	O
221	O
,	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
ANN	I-pers
SARSFIELD	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
MARGARET	B-pers
REVES	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cattnack	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9th	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
222	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
NIMNEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Shephard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty-four	O
silver	O
handle	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
silver	O
handle	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
shagreen	O
knife	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
silver	O
dish	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Nimney	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
stuff	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
coat	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
224	O
.	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HART	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
he	O
missed	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
oats	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
that	O
lay	O
at	O
his	O
wharf	O
near	O
the	B-place
Savoy	I-place
.	O
-	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
at	O
Somerset-house	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stationed	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
water-side	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
the	O
sentry	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
they	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
among	O
the	O
craft	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
Hart	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
time	O
the	O
same	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
each	O
had	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
steps	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
Hart	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
Will	O
.	O
Hart	O
?	O
then	O
I	O
recollected	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
trial	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
Hart	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Field	O
stole	O
the	O
oats	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
baker	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann's-lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
respecting	O
the	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
oats	O
and	O
some	O
sacks	O
at	O
the	O
baker	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
sacks	O
had	O
no	O
marks	O
.	O
Hart	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
confessed	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Henry	B-pers
Neale	I-pers
his	O
serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
Hart	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Field	O
acquitted	O
.	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
FINCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
jam	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
January	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
226	O
,	O
227	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
WILTON	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WILTON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
barn	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Berridge	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
Charles	B-pers
Berridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
barn	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
barn	O
cloth	O
stolen	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
promised	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
secured	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
loitering	O
about	O
at	O
Harlington	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
barn	O
cloth	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
stole	O
the	O
barn	O
cloth	O
;	O
that	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
barn	O
cloth	O
made	O
into	O
two	O
sheets	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
brother	O
Francis	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jove	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
cloth	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
Samuel	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
Francis	O
acquitted	O
.	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tarling	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
February	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
229	O
,	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DIBBINS	I-pers
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
CEAR	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
fence	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
25	O
||	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
231	O
,	O
232	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
KIRK	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
West	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
shifted	O
his	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
drank	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suspected	O
West	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
perceived	O
that	O
half	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
pane	O
was	O
cracked	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
against	O
that	O
pane	O
.	O
The	O
hole	O
was	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
arm	O
in	O
at	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pair	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
for	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
West	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
them	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
shoes	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
offered	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
shoes	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
West	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
West	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
enquire	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
shoes	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
claim	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
shut	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
attention	O
was	O
fixed	O
upon	O
West	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
West	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Kirk	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
Kirk	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
When	O
Kirk	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
remarkably	O
thin	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
this	O
country	O
's	O
wear	O
.	O
West	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
shoes	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Kirk	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
with	O
a	O
shop-mate	O
for	O
these	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
committed	O
me	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
234	O
,	O
235	O
,	O
236	O
,	O
237	O
,	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
JENNINGS	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
,	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARGARET	B-pers
MICHENER	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
said	O
notes	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Maddan	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
locket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pistol	O
locket	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
garnets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Maddan	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Michener	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Nash	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
harbouring	O
and	O
maintaining	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
felony	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
with	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Maddan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
at	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
theatre	I-place
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
theatre	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
instruments	O
,	O
two	O
lottery	O
tickets	O
of	O
1770	O
,	O
20	O
l.	O
prizes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
bank	O
notes	O
.	O
-	O
Rooke	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hope	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
together	O
;	O
Jennings	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Gordon	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
.	O
Gordon	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
lads	O
were	O
saying	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
two	O
girls	O
had	O
got	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
girls	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
leaning	O
their	O
heads	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
lottery	O
tickets	O
that	O
were	O
20	O
l.	O
prizes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Gordon	O
immediately	O
went	O
and	O
thrust	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
prizes	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
L	O
,	O
a	O
figure	O
of	O
2	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
o	O
,	O
wrote	O
in	O
ink	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
having	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
stop	O
you	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Noakes	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
women	O
frequented	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
sold	O
fish	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
their	O
way	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sisters	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
score	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Nor	O
of	O
Gordon	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
boys	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
No	O
farther	O
than	O
frequenting	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
house	O
frequented	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
such	O
company	O
as	O
that	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
frequented	O
by	O
such	O
company	O
as	O
that	O
before	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Justices	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
your	O
licence	O
.	O
Rooke	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
already	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
my	O
house	O
being	O
bad	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
is	O
bad	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
it	O
that	O
is	O
bad	O
.	O
Rooke	O
.	O
The	O
boys	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
thing	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
run	O
the	O
hazard	O
of	O
their	O
lives	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
,	O
sooner	O
than	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
lay	O
an	O
information	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
the	O
boys	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
into	O
Nancy	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
's	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
50	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
if	O
possible	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
detain	O
the	O
other	O
sister	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
.	O
They	O
looked	O
over	O
some	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
they	O
mentioned	O
a	O
50	O
l.	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
boys	O
say	O
what	O
these	O
papers	O
were	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
some	O
back	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
Gordon	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
twenty-one	O
or	O
twenty-two	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
old	O
the	O
boys	O
are	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noakes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
night	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
wanted	O
at	O
the	O
Oak	O
in	O
Thieving-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
and	O
boys	O
;	O
Kenney	B-pers
the	O
evidence	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
St.	O
Anne's-lane	O
,	O
where	O
Mitchel	O
and	O
Graham	O
lived	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
was	O
burnt	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
lottery	O
ticket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
opened	O
it	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
raked	O
among	O
the	O
ashes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
bits	O
of	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
part	O
appeared	O
like	O
a	O
rivet	O
to	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
opera	O
ticket	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
that	O
Miller	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Graham	O
's	O
apartment	O
?	O
Noakes	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
Kenney	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
was	O
standing	O
by	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
under	O
the	O
piazza	O
's	O
at	O
Govent-Garden	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Smith	O
went	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
play-house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
it	O
behind	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Govent-garden	O
market	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
some	O
notes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
locket	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Noakes	O
has	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
true-lover	O
's	O
knot	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
market	O
to	O
examine	O
it	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
All	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Gordon	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
keep	O
it	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
to	O
Westminster	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Oak	O
in	O
Thieving-lane	O
.	O
Gordon	O
saw	O
Graham	O
at	O
the	O
Hope	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
silver	O
instruments	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
lottery	O
tickets	O
.	O
Upon	O
searching	O
farther	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Gordon	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
50	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
;	O
come	O
and	O
kiss	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
25	O
l.	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
.	O
She	O
searched	O
the	O
book	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
notes	O
.	O
We	O
tore	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
papers	O
;	O
Gordon	O
had	O
the	O
lottery	O
tickets	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Hope	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Graham	O
asked	O
Gordon	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
any	O
beef	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
pretence	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
Miller	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
Michener	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
She	O
only	O
fetched	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
body	O
lodge	O
with	O
Graham	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Michener	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
I	O
when	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
yards	O
behind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Birch	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
gate-way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Hope	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
pure	O
love	O
then	O
;	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
pure	O
love	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
usually	O
let	O
those	O
into	O
your	O
secrets	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
prizes	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
that	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
used	O
to	O
this	O
way	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Hope	O
this	O
day	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Catharine	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
and	O
her	O
sister	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
disturbance	O
about	O
this	O
note	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Graham	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
just	O
this	O
story	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
Graham	O
's	O
lodgings	O
when	O
the	O
boys	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
fancy	O
they	O
expected	O
you	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
first	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understood	O
from	O
Kenney	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
Graham	O
's	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
her	O
sister	O
Michener	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
evidence	O
cleared	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Hope	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
able	O
to	O
identify	O
these	O
notes	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
numbers	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
clerk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
clerk	O
here	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Jennings	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hope	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Noakes	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
nor	O
was	O
I	O
ever	O
at	O
Graham	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
.	O
Birch	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
Kenney	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
this	O
night	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Westminster	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Hope	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
Kate	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
Kenney	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Hope	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
apprentices	O
;	O
two	O
lads	O
were	O
selling	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rooke	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Graham	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
oranges	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
houses	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rooke	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
market	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Michener	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
oysters	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Hope	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
;	O
Noakes	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Jennings	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Birch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Smith	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Graham	O
guilty	O
of	O
concealing	O
and	O
harbouring	O
the	O
principals	O
.	O
239	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
LAURENCE	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
BAKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
eight	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
copper	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	B-pers
united	I-pers
company	I-pers
of	I-pers
merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
3d	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
240	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DEWELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
,	O
beating	O
and	O
kicking	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
breaking	O
his	O
right	O
leg	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
to	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
man-slaughter	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
after	O
his	O
uncle	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
crying	O
:	O
he	O
began	O
abusing	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
fire	O
and	O
burn	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hit	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
liquor	O
left	O
to	O
pay	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
husband	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
windows	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
push	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
the	O
dunghill	O
:	O
he	O
hit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
pushed	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
his	O
leg	O
caught	O
in	O
the	O
drain	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
hit	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hit	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
mortification	O
in	O
his	O
leg	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
uncle	O
's	O
ducks	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
a	O
good	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
for	O
being	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
fear	O
any	O
man	O
:	O
that	O
then	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
wrestling	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
wrestle	O
or	O
fight	O
again	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
uncle	O
were	O
shuffling	O
fellows	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stript	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
Parsons	O
and	O
James	O
were	O
not	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
by	O
Dewell	O
's	O
cloaths	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
only	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
collar	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
support	O
himself	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
journey-man	O
carpenter	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stript	O
,	O
and	O
measured	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
biggest	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
wrestle	O
or	O
fight	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dispute	O
about	O
the	O
payment	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
went	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
reckoning	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
you	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
without	O
his	O
cloaths	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
deceased	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
witness	O
prevented	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pushed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
stomach	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
violently	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
temples	O
,	O
which	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twisted	O
him	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
leg	O
hitched	O
in	O
the	O
drain	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
deceased	O
would	O
have	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
his	O
uncle	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
by	O
some	O
villains	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bruised	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
threatened	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Corson	O
the	O
surgeon	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
fracture	O
in	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
leg	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
business	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
abused	O
him	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
a	O
crying	O
cull	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
him	O
to	O
wrestle	O
for	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
wrestle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
challenged	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
bet	O
twenty-six	O
shillings	O
to	O
his	O
guinea	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
difference	O
of	O
their	O
age	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
his	O
uncle	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
fight	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
blows	O
passed	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
uncle	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
foot-path	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pints	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
mobbed	O
and	O
jawed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
then	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
them	O
all	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rogue	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
threatened	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
keep	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
warm	O
him	O
;	O
with	O
one	O
blow	O
he	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
great	O
force	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swung	O
him	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
caught	O
in	O
the	O
gutter	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
leg	O
fell	O
under	O
him	O
and	O
broke	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
John	O
James	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
represented	O
it	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
merely	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Ann	B-pers
Kimber	I-pers
,	O
the	O
nurse	O
who	O
attended	O
the	O
deceased	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
mentioned	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
that	O
Dewel	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
fault	O
was	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Winfield	B-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
uncle	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
aggrivated	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
talked	O
of	O
fighting	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
quiet	O
,	O
peaceable	O
man	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pecock	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
peaceable	O
man	O
.	O
''	O
Guilty	O
of	O
manslaughter	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
PAGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
December	O
25th	O
.	O
||	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
private	O
road	O
:	O
between	O
Bloody	B-place
Bridge	I-place
and	O
the	O
last	O
bar	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
see	O
they	O
walked	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
They	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
information	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
Lewis	B-pers
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Leigh	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Lewis	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
point	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
no	O
body	O
describe	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
point	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
Lewis	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
convicted	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
among	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
about	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
's	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pointed	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
claped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
violence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
arms	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
horse-dealer	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
Grey	O
hound	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
recommend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
violence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Lewis	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
signed	O
a	O
petition	O
for	O
Lewis	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
to	O
beg	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
prison	O
some	O
where	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
this	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
for	O
above	O
twenty	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
hospital	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
be	O
dark	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Day	O
light	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
shade	O
between	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
walked	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
242	O
.	O
243	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
REBECCA	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
spinster	O
and	O
REBECCA	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
under	O
case	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
out-side	O
fish-skin	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
once	O
before	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
ribbon	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
maid	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
hung	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
bonnet	O
.	O
Amelia	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
``	O
who	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
her	O
mistress	O
to	O
bring	O
back	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
as	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
The	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Smith	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
She	O
called	O
Sarah	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
necklace	O
maker	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
servant	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Esther	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Davis	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
servant	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Numan	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
Smith	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
sometime	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
both	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
''	O
Smith	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
Davis	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
REBECCA	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
spinster	O
and	O
REBECCA	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve-yards	O
of	O
broad	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
-	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
||	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blue	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
rose-colloured	O
pink	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
ribbon	O
that	O
they	O
bought	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
Then	O
Davis	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
black	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
the	O
drawer	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
inside	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
Smith	O
threw	O
a	O
long	O
red	O
cloak	O
over	O
a	O
drawer	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
took	O
something	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
ribbon	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Emelia	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
,	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
tell	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
ribbon	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
asked	O
for	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
call	O
another	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
after	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
Davis	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
Davis	O
got	O
up	O
she	O
left	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
she	O
had	O
sat	O
in	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Davis	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
black	O
cloak	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
ribbon	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoners	O
into	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
likely	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
ribbon	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
.	O
Howard	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
ribbon	O
was	O
found.	O
``	O
Amelia	B-pers
Cary	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
threatened	O
to	O
stone	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
ribbon	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
''	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
244	O
.	O
245	O
.	O
246	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATERS	I-pers
,	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HART	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
ANN	B-pers
BATH	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
French	O
plate	O
coffee-pot	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
French	O
plate	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
French	O
plate	O
sauce	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
one	O
French	O
plate	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
French	O
plate	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
French	O
plate	O
candlestick	O
socket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Claudius	B-pers
Adrian	I-pers
Charie	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28th	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
247	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ISAAC	B-pers
SHIEFFELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
wooden	O
boxes	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2361	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
value	O
220	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4th	O
1771	O
.	O
+	O
Leah	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Odell	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
,	O
and	O
deals	O
in	O
lace	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
300	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
lace	O
sent	O
up	O
in	O
three	O
wooden	O
boxes	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Bedford	O
waggon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
our	O
servant	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
Penny	O
's	O
Folly	O
in	O
Islington-road	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
Reservoir	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
hot	O
wine	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
quart	O
hot	O
,	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
fronting	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
for	O
breakfast	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
got	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
quarts	O
of	O
wine	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
boxes	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
One	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
horse	O
;	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
horse	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
my	O
stable	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
perhaps	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
stay	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
perhaps	O
they	O
might	O
dine	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
consulting	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
sometimes	O
one	O
,	O
sometimes	O
two	O
were	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
found	O
of	O
gold	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
gaming	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
One	O
man	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Brown-Bear	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
box	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
lace	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
box	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
wallets	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
across	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
boxes	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
wallet	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
very	O
easy	O
;	O
my	O
house	O
is	O
built	O
fifty	O
feet	O
from	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
road	O
for	O
a	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
very	O
gently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
conversation	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
four	O
men	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
talk	O
about	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
I	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
lace	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
four	O
men	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
come	O
in	O
doors	O
,	O
than	O
Hopkins	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
enquired	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Brown-Bear	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rode	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
boxes	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
might	O
bring	O
them	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
or	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
once	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
sound	O
of	O
gold	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
quiet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
person	O
there	O
might	O
