TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
DECEMBRR	O
,	O
1772	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
JOHN	B-pers
GLYNN	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
London	O
,	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heyward	I-pers
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hills	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pentland	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Laud	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Musson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Derby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Frisby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chew	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Brazier	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chew	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Vian	I-pers
John	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
George	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gutton	I-pers
George	B-pers
Curling	I-pers
George	B-pers
Minett	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Vian	I-pers
,	O
Barnard	B-pers
Brooshoost	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strike	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gatton	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
M'DANIEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mowbray	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Henry	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
these	O
shoes	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
George	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phelps	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
stick	O
she	O
had	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
several	O
pair	O
;	O
she	O
objected	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
strong	O
enough	O
;	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
reaching	O
some	O
shoes	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
I	O
had	O
shewn	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
the	O
stick	O
and	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
shoes	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
-	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
shoes	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
WARDENS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ganden	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ganden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Shadwell	B-place
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Ganden	O
.	O
Howard	O
is	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
Green	O
thirteen	O
and	O
Wardens	O
eleven	O
.	O
Johannes	B-pers
Terrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
Dock	O
:	O
Wardens	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
10	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
poor	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
lend	O
so	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
produced	O
another	O
pair	O
she	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
Wardens	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
another	O
pair	O
she	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
Wardens	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Wardens	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
Dock	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
among	O
the	O
ocum	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
.	O
Howard	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
used	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
the	O
vessel	O
.	O
Green	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Howard	O
took	O
the	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
held	O
them	O
.	O
Warden	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
boy	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
where	O
my	O
mother	O
used	O
;	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
HOWARD	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
GREEN	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
WARDENS	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
KIRKE	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
chamber	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	B-pers
majesty	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brass	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
like	O
a	O
cannon	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
Jones	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
brass	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ashmore	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
pitched	O
the	O
chamber	O
upon	O
a	O
post	O
in	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
one	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
;	O
they	O
confessed	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Store-house	O
;	O
the	O
store-keeper	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
missing	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
they	O
say	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
-	O
Ashmore	O
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
-	O
Stanfield	O
,	O
concerned	O
in	O
keeping	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
stores	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
chamber	O
produced	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
loaded	O
and	O
fired	O
it	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
returned	O
again	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
store	O
room	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
review	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
review	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
intoxicated	O
;	O
coming	O
by	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
something	O
resting	O
on	O
a	O
post	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
brass	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
iron	O
shops	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
majesty	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
-	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
their	O
serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
Smith	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Kirke	O
eight	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Passivill	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
Smith	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Kirke	O
nine	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ALLWRIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edmead	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spurs	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edmead	I-pers
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoome	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Oct.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Edmead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
at	O
Staines	B-place
:	O
my	O
mother	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
and	O
listened	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rapping	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
frock	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
men	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
gun	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
unlocked	O
and	O
unbolted	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
shut	O
to	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
kitchen	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
person	O
there	O
;	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
dark	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pick	O
ax	O
and	O
iron	O
bar	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spurs	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
cupboard	O
at	O
the	O
stair	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
boots	O
and	O
shoes	O
were	O
found	O
next	O
morning	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
out	O
houses	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
spurs	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
my	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Edmead	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
plough	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
enough	O
;	O
he	O
received	O
but	O
little	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
working	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
Colebrook	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
house	O
fastened	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Edmead	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
then	O
?	O
Edmead	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Horme	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
severally	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
of	O
theirs	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Gurney	O
and	O
Horme	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
WADE	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
jumps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Flocks	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Flocks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Brick-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Spital-fields	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
and	O
returned	O
at	O
six	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Basing-house	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
master	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Edmonton	O
stage	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
to	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
better	O
watch	O
than	O
that	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
more	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Capps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
;	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
jumps	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
master	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
,	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
JORDAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SARAH	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
SAMUEL	I-pers
BLYTH	I-pers
,	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BLYTH	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
JORDAN	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
long	O
lawn	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
sattin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
black	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Yarley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Yarley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacconist	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
unlock	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
chamber	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
standing	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
strange	O
key	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
large	O
drawers	O
almost	O
emptied	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
herself	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Yarley	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
Alex	B-pers
.	I-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
apartments	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
her	O
goods	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
JORDAN	I-pers
guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
BLYTH	O
acquitted	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
JORDAN	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mackintosh	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Rachael	B-pers
Yateman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mackintosh	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
passed	O
for	O
a	O
deaf	O
and	O
dumb	O
woman	O
,	O
served	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
chips	O
for	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
wanted	O
chips	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
signs	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
starve	O
with	O
cold	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
sit	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
near	O
a	O
table	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
spoon	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
that	O
table	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
being	O
removed	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
A	O
message	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
spoons	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
among	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
wanting	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
she	O
first	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
among	O
some	O
kitchen	O
stuff	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
glover	O
's	O
near	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
woman	O
whose	O
name	O
she	O
used	O
passed	O
for	O
deaf	O
and	O
dumb	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
spoke	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
defect	O
in	O
my	O
speech	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SWINNEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
Snow-hill	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
gateway	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
entered	O
into	O
conversation	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
gateway	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
gateway	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
six-pence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
three-pence	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
my	O
breeches	O
were	O
unbuttoned	O
;	O
I	O
buttoned	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
chain	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
snatch	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
her	O
hand	O
went	O
down	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
perfectly	O
well	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
immediately	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hopwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
accident	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
squatted	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
watch	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bamford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
,	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BEDELL	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HORNSBY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
walnut-tree	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
picture	O
in	O
a	O
gilt	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
picture	O
in	O
a	O
gilt	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BEDELL	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HORNSBY	I-pers
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
bird	O
cages	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
live	O
birds	O
called	O
red	O
poles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
small	O
picture	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BEDELL	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HORNSBY	I-pers
were	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spearing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
seven	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BEDELL	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HORNSBY	I-pers
were	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
gimblet	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
worsted	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
green	O
baize	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HORNSBY	I-pers
was	O
(	O
a	O
sixth	O
time	O
)	O
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
(	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
)	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quart	O
bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
rum	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
quart	O
bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
brandy	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
quart	O
bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
gin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ELIAS	B-pers
CHERRY	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
lined	O
with	O
ticken	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Watkin	B-pers
Lewes	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
+	O
Simon	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Lewes	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
carriage	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
tavern	O
,	O
whilst	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Young	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Cherry	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
Cherry	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
the	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
Cherry	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
has	O
got	O
a	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Smith	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
Pump-court	O
,	O
Devonshire-square	O
;	O
Smith	O
first	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
this	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
selling	O
it	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
people	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Cherry	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
;	O
that	O
Smith	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Cherry	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
.	O
Cherry	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
CRABB	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
BURNELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glass	O
polisher	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
published	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
her	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
stuff	O
gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
Margaret	O
Read	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Read	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
goods	O
which	O
were	O
pawned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
24	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
and	O
HENRY	B-pers
HOLDER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
punch	O
bowl	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
border	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
two	O
china	O
bowls	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
one	O
china	O
saucer	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
drinking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
NAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
russel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quill	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27	O
,	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
and	O
DEBORAH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greer	I-pers
,	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
take	O
46	O
l.	O
for	O
some	O
flour	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
30	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
draft	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
16	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
I	O
saw	O
somebody	O
stand	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
right-road	O
to	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
walked	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
leading	O
me	O
into	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
another	O
street	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
Red-cross-street	B-place
,	I-place
towards	I-place
Ratcliffe-highway	I-place
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
a	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shove	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
good	O
,	O
bad	O
or	O
indifferent	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
first	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
way	O
for	O
Tower-hill	O
sure	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
might	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
being	O
a	O
country	O
fellow	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
h	O
-	O
p	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
old	O
for	O
h	O
-	O
p	O
-	O
g	O
;	O
then	O
Clarke	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
shoved	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
my	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
make	O
off	O
you	O
bitch	O
!	O
She	O
catched	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
hold	O
me	O
while	O
Jones	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
her	O
up	O
by	O
main-strength	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
turn	O
down	O
.	O
they	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
Clarke	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
Clarke	O
:	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pull	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
tore	O
my	O
breeches	O
when	O
Jones	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
hollowed	O
for	O
Deb	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
round	O
me	O
presently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
The	O
clock	O
had	O
not	O
struck	O
six	O
.	O
Next	O
day	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
described	O
Jones	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
time	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
positively	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
that	O
pulled	O
you	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
drag	O
me	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
?	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
?	O
Ramsay	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
witnesses	O
will	O
prove	O
that	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Signal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
tell	O
a	O
lye	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
to	O
heaven	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Swear	O
him	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
Signal	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
past	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
Deb	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Poll	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
(	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
Deb	O
,	O
Deb	O
,	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
Deb	O
could	O
not	O
pull	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
Deb	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
stedfast	O
in	O
her	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
farmer	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
!	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
watch	O
!	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
!	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
watch	O
set	O
yet	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
house	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
One	O
Greer	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
A	O
private	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Greer	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
gaol	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
lived	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
Greer	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
kept	O
some	O
women	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
farmer	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
liquor	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
just	O
a	O
little	O
merry	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
bowls	O
of	O
punch	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
had	O
he	O
received	O
?	O
Signal	O
.	O
46	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
30	O
l.	O
note	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Knox	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
farmer	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
Red-cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
thieves	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
farmer	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Cross	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
farmer	O
holding	O
Clark	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
was	O
decent	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Percival	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
farmer	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
coat	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
clothes	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
bury	O
Charles	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Clark	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
715	O
,	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
proves	O
it	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greer	I-pers
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
in	O
gaol	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
Clarke	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
searched	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
31	O
,	O
32	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DALE	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HENLEY	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
TRUSTY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
BROOKFIELD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
live	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
live	O
drake	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Timmings	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ebbern	I-pers
,	O
and	O
three	O
live	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
live	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Letitia	B-pers
Browning	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
-	O
Ashworth	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Browning	O
,	O
the	O
fowls	O
were	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hen-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Timmings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
ducks	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
six	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
-	O
Chaplain	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
fowls	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
youngest	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
fowls	O
.	O
-	O
Cartwright	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
lads	O
by	O
the	O
Barley-mow	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
youngest	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ordered	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
while	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
found	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
ducks	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
on	O
Dale	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Weakley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibs	O
,	O
a	O
jewellers	O
;	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
;	O
Trusty	O
was	O
my	O
school-fellow	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
these	O
lads	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
show	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
walk	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
Henley	O
and	O
Dale	O
took	O
the	O
fowls	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
field	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
ducks	O
in	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
we	O
drove	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
run	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Dale	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Henley	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
ducks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
that	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
;	O
is	O
nineteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Trusty	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
Brookfield	O
,	O
and	O
Weakley	O
,	O
were	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
contribute	O
to	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
dressing	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Brookfield	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
fowls	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Barley-mow	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
his	O
club	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
used	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
imputation	O
on	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
garden	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sage	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
line	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drying	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
clothes	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
gather	O
some	O
sloes	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
lie	O
by	O
the	O
hedge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
34	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BEST	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Grimilone	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Mr.	O
Cavendish	O
's	O
coachman	O
deposed	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
his	O
``	O
great	O
coat	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
Farme	B-place
's	I-place
meuse	I-place
,	O
``	O
Berkley-square	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Guy	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
``	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
produced	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
``	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
afternoon	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
``	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
``	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
his	O
stables	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
``	O
people	O
saw	O
him	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
in	O
``	O
the	O
yard	O
behind	O
a	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
``	O
not	O
enquired	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
''	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
36	O
,	O
37	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
TUCKER	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Nutt	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
first	O
field	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
Dwarf	O
tavern	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Turner	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
-	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
!	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
two	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Simpson	O
is	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
scratched	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
while	O
Simpson	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
rings	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
penknife	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
brisket	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
basket	O
;	O
they	O
blinded	O
my	O
eyes	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Turner	O
that	O
held	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
blinded	O
my	O
eyes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
twice	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
or	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
resistance	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
call	O
out	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
one	O
passing	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Turner	O
by	O
his	O
jacket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
all	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hair	O
or	O
a	O
wig	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
hair	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
enough	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
jacket	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
His	O
jacket	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
had	O
he	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
Really	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
hats	O
now	O
there	O
are	O
so	O
many	O
sorts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
27th	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
describe	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
:	O
you	O
described	O
this	O
man	O
by	O
his	O
jacket	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
shorter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
drab	O
coloured	O
coat	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
in	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
(	O
Simpson	O
)	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
speak	O
but	O
Turner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
?	O
Nutt	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Turner	O
held	O
something	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
dagger	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
since	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
brought	O
me	O
my	O
penknife	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Nutt	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
information	O
that	O
another	O
person	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
field	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Nokes	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
Ambury	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
thieves	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
two	O
penny	O
,	O
lodging	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
Turner	O
and	O
Simpson	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
Simpson	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
penknife	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
penknife	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nokes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Heley	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
Simpson	O
and	O
Turner	O
in	O
Fisher	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
Turner	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Heley	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
companions	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
wedge	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
you	O
had	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
:	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
here	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
cart	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
work	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
work	O
I	O
go	O
with	O
carmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
give	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
victuals	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
knife	O
in	O
Bridge-street	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Charing	O
cross	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
stick	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
kennel	O
.	O
Turner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
being	O
tried	O
to	O
day	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
friends	O
here	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Oct.	O
28th	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
forty	O
minutes	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
foot	O
road	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
Davis	O
's	O
:	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
!	O
they	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
rebel	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
I	O
wrenched	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
Turner	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
advanced	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
stick	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Simpson	O
)	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
if	O
I	O
stirred	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
halfpence	O
and	O
a	O
farthing	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
my	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
constrained	O
my	O
foot	O
in	O
hopes	O
some	O
relief	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
Simpson	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
ease	O
my	O
foot	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
very	O
often	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
their	O
faces	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
sure	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
persons	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
of	O
any	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Humphreys	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
hoping	O
somebody	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
relief	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
dangerous	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Simpson	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
by	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
whitish	O
jacket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
Turner	O
,	O
Simpson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
Simpson	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
Turner	O
took	O
his	O
buckles	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
rightly	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
six-pence	O
and	O
five-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
linen	O
which	O
we	O
threw	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Because	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
vinegar	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
robbed	O
of	O
any	O
vinegar	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
We	O
threw	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
and	O
a	O
girl	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
throw	O
the	O
buckles	O
away	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Because	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
search	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
A	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
these	O
men	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
,	O
only	O
by	O
drinking	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happened	O
between	O
Graham	O
and	O
your	O
party	O
after	O
his	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Nothing	O
happened	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
skirmish	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
use	O
to	O
lye	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Ambury	O
,	O
at	O
Westminster	O
;	O
we	O
lay	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Ashley	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
together	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Heley	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
at	O
Fisher	O
's	O
?	O
Heley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Fisher	O
's	O
;	O
Ashley	O
's	O
and	O
Fisher	O
's	O
houses	O
join	O
together	O
:	O
he	O
mistakes	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Humphreys	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
some	O
times	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Turner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
a	O
barge	O
to	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
38	O
,	O
39	O
,	O
40	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PATRICK	B-pers
TRANER	I-pers
,	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
HARLING	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAYS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
6th	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	B-place
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
missed	O
16	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
shoes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
second	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shoes	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
every	O
man	O
's	O
work	O
that	O
does	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
I	O
put	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
Harling	O
brought	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
with	O
the	O
night	O
charge	O
;	O
Francis	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Aunt	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Black-horse-yard	O
,	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
met	O
Pat	O
Traner	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
aunt	O
's	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
trunk	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
conveyed	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
room	O
two	O
doors	O
below	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
Traner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Harling	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
liquor	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
other	O
shoes	O
he	O
could	O
clear	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
Harling	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Harling	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
;	O
knew	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
lamp-lighter	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Meach	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
aunt	O
to	O
Harling	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
crime	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
lamp-lighting	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Harling	O
12	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
lad	O
.	O
HARLING	O
guilty	O
.	O
TRANER	O
acquitted	O
.	O
HAYS	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BRADS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stick	O
of	O
Turkey	O
box	O
wood	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3d	O
.	O
++	O
Susanna	B-pers
Patridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Low	O
,	O
a	O
turner	O
,	O
in	O
White-cross-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
;	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
stick	O
of	O
Turkey	O
box	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
the	O
wood	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Peacock	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
turner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bud	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
wood	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Low	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
some	O
pieces	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
purchaser	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
away	O
two	O
pieces	O
and	O
left	O
that	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
before	O
the	O
grand	O
jury	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Low	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
box	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
piece	O
round	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
that	O
piece	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
wood	O
down	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
taking	O
any	O
wood	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
42	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gladstone	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	B-place
11	I-place
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Gladstone	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
King-street	B-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
two	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
quitted	O
his	O
hold	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
way	O
for	O
those	O
persons	O
to	O
go	O
between	O
the	O
houses	O
and	O
us	O
;	O
whether	O
I	O
pushed	O
again	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
pushed	O
so	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
hurt	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
elbow	O
;	O
my	O
friend	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
missing	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
a	O
chair	O
was	O
passing	O
,	O
which	O
stopt	O
,	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
lifted	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
chairmen	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
you	O
look	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
stir	O
a	O
foot	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
gentleman	O
has	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
wanting	O
;	O
then	O
some	O
people	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
and	O
left	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
directions	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
if	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
offered	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
that	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
Heather	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
2nd	O
he	O
lest	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
within	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
me	O
prisoner	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
his	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Heather	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Drury-lane-playhouse	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
across	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
opposite	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
clear	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
hit	O
my	O
foot	O
against	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
seal	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
foot	O
off	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
facing	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
down	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
my	O
friend	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
a	O
treat	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
advertized	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
up	O
two	O
guineas	O
upon	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
seeing	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
advertized	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
papers	O
to	O
see	O
.	O
When	O
Heather	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Journyman	O
hair-dresser	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
White-Lion	O
,	O
up	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Piazza	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
dressing	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
kept	O
one	O
in	O
White-horse-street	O
,	O
Piccacadily	O
;	O
we	O
crossed	O
Covent-garden	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
on	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
crossed	O
into	O
the	O
high	O
way	O
and	O
stooped	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
a	O
treat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Dun	O
was	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
detected	O
in	O
passing	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
guessed	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
watch	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
of	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
containing	O
Bank-notes	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
amount	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
DUCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
54	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
fresh	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Vinecomb	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vinecomb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
flat	O
of	O
butter	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hatton	O
's	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
unloaded	O
the	O
waggon	O
in	O
Newgate-market	B-place
;	O
I	O
gave	O
this	O
flat	O
of	O
butter	O
to	O
Roworth	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Vinecomb	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Wine	O
Office	O
Court	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Roworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
flat	O
of	O
butter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
flat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
market	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
employment	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
flat	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
44	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Hinchcliffe	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Hinchcliffe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Small-Pox-Hospital	B-place
and	O
the	O
turnpike	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
in	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
within	O
about	O
300	O
yards	O
of	O
Tottenham-court	O
turnpike	O
;	O
three	O
persons	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
their	O
persons	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Murphy	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
sessions	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
executed	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plenius	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Count	O
and	O
Steadman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
their	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
horse	O
and	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
we	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
road	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
these	O
men	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
;	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Gray's-inn-lane-road	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
rails	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
several	O
oaths	O
that	O
a	O
carriage	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
road	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
sight	O
,	O
I	O
dismounted	O
by	O
the	O
new	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
horse	O
serve	O
as	O
a	O
screen	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
Plenius	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
moon	O
light	O
;	O
it	O
grew	O
lighter	O
and	O
lighter	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
they	O
would	O
attack	O
that	O
chaise	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
said	O
that	O
?	O
Plenius	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
in	O
case	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
attacked	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
fire	O
and	O
would	O
kill	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
turned	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
Road	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
chaise	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
,	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
posts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
was	O
Murphy	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
Earle	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stopped	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
mounted	O
my	O
horse	O
by	O
the	O
turnpike	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
Pancras	O
;	O
the	O
chaise	O
came	O
toward	O
the	O
turnpike	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
further	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
attack	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
demand	O
their	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
young	O
men	O
delivered	O
their	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
words	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
Earle	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Murphy	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
Earle	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
fire	O
!	O
and	O
Lewis	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
fired	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
fire	O
arms	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
with	O
certainty	O
whether	O
Lewis	O
or	O
Murphy	O
fired	O
?	O
Plenius	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Count	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
Murphy	O
got	O
through	O
the	O
rails	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
Lewis	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
rails	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
persons	O
that	O
followed	O
us	O
on	O
foot	O
secured	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
-	O
Steadman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Count	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
attacked	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
Plenius	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
attacked	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
or	O
upwards	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
money	O
they	O
wanted	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
chopped	O
at	O
Murphy	O
with	O
my	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
(	O
Earle	O
)	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
attempted	O
to	O
fire	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
pistol	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
back	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
!	O
and	O
Lewis	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
judgement	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
firing	O
from	O
one	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plenius	O
I	O
believe	O
fired	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
report	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
then	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
distance	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
who	O
fired	O
.	O
Q.	O
Plenius	O
says	O
one	O
fired	O
first	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
pistol	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
flash	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Hinchcliffe	O
's	O
watch	O
ever	O
found	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Count	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
attacked	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
held	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
with	O
pistols	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
Steadman	O
said	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
money	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
one	O
down	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
we	O
both	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
Earle	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Earle	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
fire	O
!	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
fire	O
?	O
upon	O
that	O
a	O
pistol	O
flashed	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
pistol	O
away	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
;	O
Steadman	O
halloo	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
!	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Plenius	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
Steadman	O
and	O
Count	O
had	O
acquainted	O
you	O
that	O
Hinchcliffe	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
was	O
this	O
attack	O
made	O
?	O
Plenins	O
.	O
The	O
highest	O
time	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
attacked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
o'clock	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
fired	O
?	O
Plenius	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Earle	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
trial	O
say	O
something	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Plenius	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Murphy	O
who	O
got	O
off	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
denied	O
his	O
having	O
robbed	O
Hinchcliffe	O
,	O
and	O
attacked	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
or	O
has	O
he	O
a	O
family	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
single	O
or	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
Single	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
work	O
at	O
time	O
?	O
Perry	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Arbutbnot	I-pers
.	O
It	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
seventeen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
last	O
?	O
Arbuthnot	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Rees	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Oxford-market	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Veals	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty-two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
of	O
good	O
parents	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dennington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
worked	O
last	O
?	O
Deminngton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Steadman	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
on	O
this	O
trial	O
were	O
Steadman	O
,	O
Count	O
and	O
Plenius	O
whose	O
testimony	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
trials	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
714	O
and	O
715	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
45	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOOTH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wickstead	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Wickstead	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	B-place
hill	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
informed	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
had	O
been	O
picked	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dropt	O
my	O
shirt	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Clowes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
46	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ANSON	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
silver	O
three-penny	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
LIDDLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	O
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
49	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DEVEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
groat	O
,	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
50	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Trueball	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
51	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
O'CONNOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Granby	B-place
's	I-place
head	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Knight	I-place
's	I-place
bridge	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
this	O
day	O
sevennight	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
something	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
their	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
a	O
small	O
bundle	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
returned	O
for	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ordered	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
piece	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
informed	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
inclosed	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
looked	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
half	O
crown	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Queen-Ann	O
's	O
shilling	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
money	O
over	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
coin	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
three	O
fingers	O
and	O
his	O
thumb	O
among	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
further	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
Queen-Ann	O
's	O
shilling	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Queen-Ann	O
's	O
shilling	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
4	O
s.	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
confident	O
he	O
kept	O
back	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
another	O
dip	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
money	O
over	O
my	O
hand	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
separated	O
6	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
towards	O
the	O
tip	O
of	O
my	O
finger	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
sure	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
one	O
Queen-Ann	O
's	O
shilling	O
among	O
all	O
this	O
number	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
six	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
them	O
over	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
back	O
3	O
s.	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
hurry	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
his	O
thumb	O
I	O
found	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
lad	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
my	O
money	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
learnt	O
him	O
the	O
trick	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
52	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ALICE	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
last	O
Saturday	O
sevennight	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Bridges-court	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
me	O
count	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
with	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
shirt	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
shirt	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
totally	O
false	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
53	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ESTHER	B-pers
KELK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
park	I-place
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
will	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
grass	O
?	O
I	O
consented	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
:	O
after	O
the	O
affair	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
clandestine	O
manner	O
,	O
which	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
directly	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
shrieked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
girls	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
to	O
my	O
shame	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
what	O
Hetty	O
are	O
you	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
girl	O
that	O
has	O
robbed	O
my	O
husband	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
your	O
husband	O
,	O
but	O
since	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
that	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
also	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
beyond	O
decency	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
only	O
six	O
weeks	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
54	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COSTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
nine	O
pence	O
halfpenney	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flanders	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
,	O
October	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flanders	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Askue	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
that	O
very	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
High-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
hats	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
out	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Leadbeater	O
,	O
who	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
buckles	O
or	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
produced	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Askue	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
55	O
,	O
56	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
TREVIS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
LYONS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
she	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
watch	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
27th	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
57	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Oct.	O
30th	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Gun	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Hungerford-market	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
so	O
took	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
employed	O
her	O
as	O
house	O
maid	O
,	O
chiefly	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
only	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
this	O
room	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
made	O
my	O
wife	O
used	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
doing	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
was	O
always	O
kept	O
locked	O
;	O
sometimes	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
work	O
after	O
making	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
;	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
silver	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
bag	O
a	O
reserve	O
for	O
change	O
when	O
the	O
taylors	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
bag	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
which	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
for	O
common	O
change	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
13	O
l.	O
odd	O
shillings	O
only	O
left	O
in	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
examine	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
way	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ten	O
guineas	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
this	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
less	O
than	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
I	O
counted	O
it	O
and	O
discovered	O
my	O
loss	O
.	O
I	O
wondered	O
the	O
girl	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
for	O
her	O
wages	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
flush	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
then	O
own	O
