TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1772	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
||	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
&	O
c.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
||	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Josiah	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
Gilbert	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Dobinson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
George	B-pers
Meager	I-pers
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Zacharias	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Solomon	B-pers
Marriott	I-pers
Ely	B-pers
Dyson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Battray	I-pers
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gooch	I-pers
William	B-pers
Finn	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Kirkby	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Vardy	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
William	B-pers
Nichol	I-pers
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
John	B-pers
Elkins	I-pers
George	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
William	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Birtles	I-pers
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Lovelin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jupp	I-pers
John	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Truman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
316	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOLMES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
,	O
February	O
26th	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
plumber	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Duke's-head	B-place
in	I-place
Warwick-street	I-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
box	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
wear	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
free	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
further	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
coats	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
lodging	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Liddiard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
ten	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
up	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
chain	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
surtout	O
coats	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
surtout	O
coats	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
to	O
a	O
brother	O
soldier	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
soldier	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
loose	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
gave	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
condition	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
promise	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
?	O
Liddiard	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
purpose	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
these	O
cloaths	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
earned	O
the	O
money	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
industry	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
soldier	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
317	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
PHILIP	B-pers
CRATEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
a	O
fruiterer	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann's-court	O
,	O
King-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
I	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
night	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
message	O
to	O
Oxendon-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
overtook	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
upon	O
his	O
stand	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
chairman	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
me	O
a	O
slap	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Dean-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
still	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
slap	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
pulled	O
me	O
from	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
publick-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lift	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Plow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
this	O
Plow	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
lay	O
backwards	O
where	O
the	O
people	O
drank	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
came	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
led	O
me	O
about	O
from	O
street	O
to	O
street	O
till	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
street	O
by	O
Covent-garden	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
dragged	O
me	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
fool	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
pulled	O
me	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
when	O
you	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
what	O
time	O
might	O
it	O
be	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
into	O
this	O
alley	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
at	O
the	O
publick-house	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
country	O
are	O
you	O
of	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Devonshire	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
pulled	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
walked	O
up	O
,	O
being	O
pulled	O
by	O
her	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
strained	O
my	O
stays	O
open	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
undress	O
you	O
quite	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
Was	O
he	O
rude	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
undressed	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
offer	O
any	O
violence	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
He	O
pushed	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
my	O
breath	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
yourself	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
after	O
he	O
stopped	O
your	O
mouth	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
threaten	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
stopped	O
my	O
breath	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
after	O
he	O
stopped	O
your	O
mouth	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
had	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
account	O
you	O
gave	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
when	O
he	O
pulled	O
you	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
altered	O
that	O
position	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
enter	O
your	O
body	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
stopping	O
your	O
mouth	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
He	O
still	O
kept	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
long	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
recollect	O
whether	O
you	O
staid	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
an	O
hour	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
get	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
At	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lye	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
six	O
hours	O
together	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
for	O
five	O
hours	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lye	O
down	O
again	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
pushed	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
you	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
A	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
doing	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Both	O
sitting	O
still	O
then	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
let	O
you	O
out	O
at	O
last	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
unbolted	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
out	O
before	O
me	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
after	O
him	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
soon	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
street	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
you	O
went	O
home	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
there	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
walk	O
the	O
streets	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
this	O
story	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
of	O
it	O
on	O
Sunday	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
here	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
took	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
,	O
you	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
hit	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
slaps	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
call	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
next	O
morning	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
proper	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
strangers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
The	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
Devonshire	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
from	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Exeter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
my	O
nineteenth	O
year	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
half-brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
shoe-black	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
while	O
she	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
stay	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
burst	O
into	O
tears	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
away	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
ill	O
used	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
court	O
about	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
R.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Only	O
by	O
sight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
her	O
lye	O
out	O
before	O
?	O
R.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
but	O
about	O
ten	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
only	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
master	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
,	O
in	O
Oxendon-street	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
returned	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
R.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
who	O
had	O
abused	O
her	O
?	O
R.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
lye	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
before	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
Months	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
the	O
``	O
prosecutrix	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
the	O
way	O
``	O
to	O
Oxendon-street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
treat	O
him	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
several	O
public	O
``	O
houses	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
``	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
her	O
``	O
errand	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
``	O
get	O
her	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
``	O
in	O
Jackson	O
's	O
alley	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
``	O
maid	O
lighted	O
them	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
``	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
went	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
``	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
``	O
told	O
the	O
maid	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
``	O
without	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
herself	O
and	O
her	O
``	O
husband	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
room	O
``	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Betty	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
``	O
bed	O
to	O
you	O
now	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
if	O
``	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
undressed	O
himself	O
and	O
went	O
``	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
almost	O
``	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
``	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
several	O
public	O
houses	O
in	O
``	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
perswade	O
``	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
lap	O
``	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
sedan	O
chair	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
''	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
in	O
Jackson's-alley	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
lye	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
when	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
room	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
at	O
first	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
lye	O
there	O
without	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
for	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
her	O
spouse	O
by	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
after	O
;	O
one	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Glover	O
.	O
They	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
Glover	O
.	O
Till	O
seven	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
fasten	O
themselves	O
in	O
?	O
Glover	O
.	O
They	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
fastening	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
like	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
just	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
?	O
Glover	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
maid	O
drag	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
these	O
men	O
were	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
men	O
and	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
two	O
people	O
came	O
through	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
chairman	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
our	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
there	O
unless	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
for	O
herself	O
and	O
her	O
spouse	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
one	O
to	O
yourself	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
through	O
our	O
room	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
hardly	O
shut	O
;	O
she	O
must	O
get	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
beds	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
,	O
the	O
partition	O
was	O
very	O
thin	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
sit	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
bed	O
touched	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
will	O
go	O
there	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
disturbances	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
disturbance	O
but	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
up	O
drunk	O
and	O
plagued	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
crying	O
out	O
then	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
had	O
spoke	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
sware	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
for	O
yourself	O
and	O
your	O
spouse	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
words	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
maid	O
dragged	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
mentioned	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
one	O
house	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ate	O
nothing	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
318	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
LAREY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
cutting	O
,	O
breaking	O
,	O
stealing	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
March	O
27th	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Smith	I-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Sir	O
Rob	B-pers
.	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
some	O
lead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
from	O
the	O
garret	O
windows	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
back	O
and	O
fore	O
fronts	O
were	O
covered	O
with	O
lead	O
instead	O
of	O
tyles	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
doomers	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
matched	O
exactly	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
lead	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
uncle	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
that	O
some	O
people	O
threw	O
the	O
lead	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
on	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
319	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LUM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Sheild	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Patrick	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	B-pers
Sheild	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Patrick	B-pers
Sheild	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
1.	I-place
in	I-place
Martlet's-court	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
below	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
persons	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
maid	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
street-door	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
fastened	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
cat	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
cat	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
fronted	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
rogues	O
and	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
window	O
fastened	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Sheild	I-pers
.	O
The	O
window-blinds	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
shutters	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
bolted	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Macardel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sheild	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
some	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
passed	O
by	O
the	O
parlour-window	O
,	O
the	O
shutters	O
were	O
violently	O
thrown	O
open	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
received	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
scraped	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
moment	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Sheild	O
cry	O
out	O
there	O
are	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
up	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
Martlet's-court	O
?	O
Macardel	O
.	O
One	O
end	O
comes	O
into	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
Russel-street	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
into	O
Broad-court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
.	O
A	O
chairman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
in	O
your	O
pursuit	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
Macardel	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
turned	O
round	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Macardel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
we	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sheild	O
examined	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pier-glass	O
was	O
moved	O
a	O
little	O
off	O
the	O
skrew	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
skrew	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
suppose	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
happened	O
by	O
his	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
further	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
jumped	O
out	O
?	O
Macardel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
had	O
the	O
man	O
got	O
when	O
you	O
began	O
the	O
pursuit	O
?	O
Macardel	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
yards	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
dress	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Macardel	O
and	O
a	O
chairman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Broad-court	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
lordship	O
will	O
shew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
mercy	O
.	O
My	O
life	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Macardel	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
instruments	O
of	O
violence	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
for	O
Burglaries	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
511.	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Trecothick	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Burton	O
,	O
Flanagan	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
96.	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
]	O
320	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN-JAMES	B-pers
GILBERT	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Durne	I-pers
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
cotton	O
counter	O
panes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
four	O
small	O
looking-glasses	O
,	O
with	O
mahogany	O
frames	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Durne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Durne	I-pers
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Durne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
gravel-pits	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
towards	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
windows	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
I	O
had	O
ready-furnished	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
occupied	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
ready	O
for	O
a	O
tenant	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
a	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
farther	O
the	O
traces	O
of	O
their	O
feet	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
forced	O
the	O
bars	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
own	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Durne	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
was	O
safe	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
garden-door	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
standing	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
-	O
Causey	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
in	O
Barwick-street	O
,	O
produced	O
two	O
cotton	O
counter-panes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Eagland	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
apprentice	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eagland	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
their	O
story	O
true	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
returned	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
printed	O
hand-bills	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
distributed	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Leighton	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
Windmill-street	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
accomplice	O
turned	O
round	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seized	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
loose	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leighton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
counter-pane	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barrel	I-pers
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
-	O
Treslove	O
,	O
in	O
Chappel-court	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
produced	O
five	O
blankets	O
and	O
a	O
curtain	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
pledged	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
believing	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
-	O
Hemmings	O
,	O
-	O
Levey	O
,	O
-	O
Barron	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King's-highway	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
321	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
MIDDLETON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
feather	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
322	O
.	O
323	O
.	O
324	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
,	O
HENRY	B-pers
RINGWOOD	I-pers
,	O
and	O
HENRY	B-pers
STOCKLEY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
bushels	O
of	O
barley	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collinson	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Bainton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31st	O
.	O
++	O
2d	O
Count	O
charges	O
it	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
3d	O
Count	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
324	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
PETER	B-pers
M'CLOUD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
sash-window	O
screw	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
charges	O
him	O
with	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Poplar	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleep	O
by	O
some	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
not	O
hearing	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
concluded	O
the	O
wind	O
had	O
blown	O
some	O
rubbish	O
from	O
the	O
scaffold	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
repairing	O
.	O
The	O
nurse	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
something	O
for	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
more	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
waked	O
Mrs.	O
Hankey	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
my	O
suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
beset	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
alarmed	O
.	O
I	O
rested	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
break	O
with	O
amazing	O
force	O
,	O
enough	O
to	O
wake	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
opened	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
softly	O
down	O
stairs	O
in	O
my	O
shirt	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
weapons	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
on	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
stair-case	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
discover	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
there	O
about	O
twenty	O
seconds	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
heard	O
the	O
skrew	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
unscrew	O
and	O
draw	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
nut	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
best	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
street-door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
could	O
alarm	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
perhaps	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
secure	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
street-door	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
glass	O
to	O
my	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
or	O
little	O
more	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
jumped	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
rails	O
where	O
they	O
stood	O
immediately	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
jumped	O
from	O
the	O
rails	O
,	O
I	O
jumped	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
.	O
They	O
kept	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
asunder	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
quitted	O
my	O
hold	O
,	O
but	O
rolled	O
over	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
his	O
comrade	O
,	O
Peter	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
Peter	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
Mr.	O
Keeler	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
one	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
attempting	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
is	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
lowermost	O
middle	O
pane	O
in	O
the	O
uppermost	O
sash	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
him	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hankey	O
and	O
the	O
servants	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Wollaston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
over-night	O
,	O
pushed	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
skrewed	O
the	O
upper	O
sash	O
to	O
the	O
under	O
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
was	O
struggling	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
apprehended	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
out	O
Peter	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
blunt	O
,	O
white-handled	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
crow	O
,	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
maid	O
secure	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
screw	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
and	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
see	O
to	O
the	O
fastening	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
window	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pane	O
above	O
the	O
skrew	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
screw	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
screw	O
out	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
screw	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
gave	O
this	O
screw	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
screw	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
nut	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
screw	O
fits	O
it	O
exactly	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cole	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
About	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
Smith	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
accomplice	O
go	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
head-borough	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
hold	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
knife	O
and	O
small	O
crow	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Keeler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
chissel	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
large	O
chissel	O
)	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Hunter	O
pick	O
up	O
another	O
.	O
-	O
Hunter	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
chissel	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
large	O
iron	O
chissel	O
)	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
labour	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
bars	O
;	O
some	O
man	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
pretty	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
lad	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
roll	O
and	O
tumble	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
;	O
he	O
smiled	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
as	O
much	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
his	O
life	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Sellon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
a	O
great	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pity	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
snigasneed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
too	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
fit	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
the	O
edge	O
is	O
an	O
inch	O
thick	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
knife	O
with	O
a	O
broad	O
blade	O
and	O
white	O
handle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pity	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
snigasneed	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
age	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Rockingham	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
cousin	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
strong	O
flood	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
men	O
running	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
breaking	O
his	O
house	O
open	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
said	O
the	O
lower	O
pane	O
of	O
the	O
upper	O
sash	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Hankey	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
upper	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hankey	O
corrected	O
herself	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
jumped	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
little	O
crow	O
belongs	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
,	O
he	O
lent	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ballast	O
trimmer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
this	O
crow	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
crow	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
pewterers	O
use	O
it	O
in	O
making	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
for	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
200	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
326	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
WEBSTER	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
,	O
April	O
18th	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Spittal-fields	B-place
;	O
the	O
gown	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
I	O
had	O
pinned	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
for	O
sale	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
about	O
30	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
gown	O
as	O
it	O
hung	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Chance	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
informed	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
gown	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
327	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
LANKEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
328	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
EDMONDS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
stilliards	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
April	O
16th	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
stilliards	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
stilliards	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
them	O
constantly	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
therefore	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
barn	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
's	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
thorough-fair	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
stilliards	O
about	O
10	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
stopt	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
329	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MANNING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daw	I-pers
.	O
March	O
14th	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daw	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
victaler	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Pall	B-place
Mall	I-place
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
children	O
alarmed	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
outcry	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
run	O
down	O
from	O
my	O
chamber	O
with	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
continued	O
running	O
till	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
distribute	O
hand	O
bills	O
for	O
marking	O
letters	O
upon	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
chairmen	O
wanted	O
to	O
duck	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
just	O
gone	O
home	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
330	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tannance	O
saw	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harvey	I-pers
;	O
a	O
hand	O
saw	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Job	O
Chandler	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hand	O
saw	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
Job	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
and	O
myself	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
Blossom	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
our	O
tools	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
information	O
from	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
tools	O
since	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woods	O
;	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
the	O
brick	O
wall	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
by	O
fixing	O
two	O
gimblets	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
to	O
stand	O
upon	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
his	O
purpose	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
stool	O
and	O
fixed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
saws	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
inform	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
gimblets	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
mortar	O
in	O
the	O
screws	O
of	O
the	O
gimblets	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
stopt	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
without	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
lad	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
331	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
KILMESTER	I-pers
,	O
FRANCES	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GRIER	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
STOCKER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Brasil	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
1000	O
silk	O
cawls	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
300	O
thread	O
cawls	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
50	O
silk	O
fillets	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
50	O
thread	O
fillets	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
seven	O
thread	O
hoods	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
lappet	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brasil	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
25th	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
200	O
silk	O
cawls	O
,	O
100	O
thread	O
cawls	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grier	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
100	O
silk	O
cawls	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
24	O
silk	O
fillets	O
,	O
24	O
thread	O
fillets	O
and	O
6	O
thread	O
hoods	O
,	O
they	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
++	O
332	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
cutting	O
,	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
said	O
lead	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
summer	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elisha	B-pers
Biscoe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
13th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
333	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PROCTER	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
ROACH	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
ANN	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
PROCTER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
bed	O
curtains	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Orange-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
.	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
lodging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
the	O
lodging	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
something	O
there	O
that	O
caused	O
me	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
apartments	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
-	O
Murthwaite	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
which	O
was	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
curtain	O
she	O
pawned	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Procter	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
his	O
goods	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
Procter	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Roach	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
334	O
.	O
335	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
RANCE	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HANNAH	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
EDWARD	I-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
laced	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
neck-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
studs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
hair-pin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
stone-cross	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
tucker	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff-shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foskett	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4th	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
receiving	O
them	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Rance	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Anderson	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
336	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
japanned	O
tea-tray	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
three	O
India	O
window-blinds	O
,	O
value	O
31	O
s.	O
five	O
glass	O
cruets	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Round-court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
case-door	O
of	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
shop-window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
stolen	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bakaruk	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bakaruk	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
one	O
Laman	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
brought	O
two	O
window-blinds	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
them	O
'till	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
a	O
purchaser	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
advertised	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
mentioned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Levi	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
admitted	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Mermaid	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
other	O
places	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Mermaid	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
window-blinds	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
another	O
publick-house	O
and	O
bring	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
met	O
us	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Addington	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Maidenhead	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
are	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
attempted	O
to	O
resist	O
I	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
head	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
Addington	O
offered	O
to	O
become	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ordered	O
the	O
'coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Theobald's-row	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
tea-tray	O
;	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
tears	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
hoped	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
tea-tray	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
tray	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Weston	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
afterwards	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Turk's-head	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
there	O
from	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
till	O
seven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
glass-case	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
Bambury-street	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
caps	O
to	O
a	O
walking	O
Jew	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
for	O
16	O
d.	O
Laman	O
Abraham	O
.	O
Addington	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
window-blinds	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
two	O
window-blinds	O
to	O
Bakaruk	O
.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Addington	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Dawson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
337	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
ISAAC	B-pers
LIPTRAP	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Eliezar	B-pers
Pigot	I-pers
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
spurs	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
woollen	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
hunting	O
whip	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
powder-proof	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Eliezar	B-pers
Pigott	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Eliezar	B-pers
Pigot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Endfield	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
my	O
maid	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
three	O
panes	O
over	O
the	O
shutter	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
leaded	O
window	O
)	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
room	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
arm	O
over	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
inside	O
one	O
that	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
only	O
with	O
a	O
button	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
buttoned	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
desk	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
powder-proof	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
pap-spoon	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
dresser	O
;	O
the	O
spurs	O
,	O
boots	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
shoes	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
fast	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Pigot	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
were	O
put	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
;	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
,	O
was	O
locked	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
boots	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
and	O
my	O
spurs	O
and	O
whip	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
my	O
whip	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
by	O
Isaac	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
whip	O
and	O
my	O
spurs	O
;	O
Francis	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
;	O
Francis	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
stolen	O
my	O
whip	O
and	O
spurs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
Francis	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
my	O
powder-proof	O
piece	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
whip	O
and	O
spurs	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
powder-proof	O
piece	O
at	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
somehow	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
the	O
first	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
fully	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
Francis	O
and	O
Walby	O
with	O
being	O
both	O
concerned	O
in	O
breaking	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
magistrate	O
bid	O
him	O
be	O
upon	O
his	O
guard	O
?	O
Pigot	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
impeach	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
last	O
?	O
Pigot	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
words	O
the	O
magistrate	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Pigot	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
fully	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
turn	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
promises	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
sort	O
?	O
Pigot	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pepper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pigot	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
shutters	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
usual	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
buttoned	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
hasped	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
shutters	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
?	O
Pepper	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
things	O
my	O
master	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
desk	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutters	O
took	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
open	O
it	O
?	O
Pepper	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
one	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
about	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
whip	O
and	O
the	O
spurs	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Pigot	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
had	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
smacking	O
the	O
whip	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
another	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
purchas	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
spurs	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
a	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
whip	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
died	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
whip	O
,	O
boots	O
,	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
two	O
friends	O
to	O
Little-Heath	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
Wormly	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
to	O
dine	O
there	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
there	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
publick-house	O
examined	O
the	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pigot	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spurs	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
my	O
friends	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
person	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
Mr.	O
Pigot	O
the	O
whip	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
sell	O
you	O
the	O
whip	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horsenail	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
in	O
any	O
private	O
way	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
None	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
fully	O
committed	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
sent	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
who	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
commit	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
indulged	O
me	O
with	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
sponging-house	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
gaol	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
fully	O
committed	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
one	O
Walby	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
character	O
and	O
property	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
re-examined	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
six	O
justices	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
justices	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
case	O
related	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
bailiff	O
's	O
house	O
from	O
Saturday	O
night	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Piner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pigot	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
panes	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
-	O
Flanagan	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
spurs	O
and	O
whip	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
Hick's-hall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Justice	O
deliver	O
the	O
powder-proof	O
piece	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Flanagan	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
signify	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Pigot	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Pigot	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
sworn	O
to	O
?	O
Flanagan	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
just	O
immediately	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
things	O
enough	O
already	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
council	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Liptrap	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
questioned	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
boots	O
and	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
impeach	O
any	O
confederates	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
White-chappel	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
as	O
a	O
carter	O
and	O
plowman	O
,	O
and	O
bears	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ponder	O
's	O
end	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
impeachment	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
Ballard	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
two	O
suits	O
of	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wharfinger	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Ralph	O
's	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
338	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
COX	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
jug	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
base	O
metal	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
crape	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
flowered	O
net-apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
eight	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
pillow	O
biers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
2d	O
Count	O
charged	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
339	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HEFTERMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Obday	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11th	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Obday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
room	O
is	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
over	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
gown	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
's	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
-	O
Hill	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
was	O
pledged	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
Bet	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
;	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
spite	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
340	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GAINER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13th	O
.	O
++	O
Mark	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Red-lion	B-place
in	I-place
Nottingham-court	I-place
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
waked	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
hat	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lorimar	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
whilst	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sate	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
witness	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cobham	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
[	O
The	O
hat	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
hat	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
341	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SANDFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half-pint	O
mug	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
342	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
25th	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
soot	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
about	O
his	O
cellar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
church-yard	O
.	O
The	O
Silversmith	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
that	O
Edward	O
produced	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
pepper-box	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
343	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BRANSGROVE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
ewe-sheep	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
lambs	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Clitherow	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
26	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Clitherow	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
or	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
year	O
my	O
bailiff	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
flock	O
four	O
ewes	O
and	O
five	O
lambs	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
myself	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
;	O
apprehending	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
only	O
strayed	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
neighbouring	O
grounds	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hand-bill	O
printed	O
,	O
offering	O
five	O
shillings	O
reward	O
to	O
any	O
that	O
would	O
discover	O
the	O
offender	O
;	O
I	O
published	O
the	O
bills	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
of	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
sheep	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
might	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
my	O
bailiff	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
over	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
ewes	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
square	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
large	O
H	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
just	O
over	O
the	O
rump	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
family	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Brentford	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
when	O
an	O
enquiry	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
fled	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
by	O
that	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
accident	O
very	O
lately	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Clitherow	O
's	O
bailiff	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
after	O
his	O
sheep	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
lambs	O
and	O
four	O
ewes	O
lost	O
from	O
his	O
flock	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
fold	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
lambs	O
and	O
four	O
ewes	O
there	O
that	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Clitherow	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
ewes	O
were	O
marked	O
with	O
three	O
H	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
rump	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
riddle	O
on	O
the	O
necks	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
lambs	O
by	O
their	O
faces	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
we	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
26th	O
or	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1771	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
four	O
lambs	O
and	O
four	O
ewes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
hand-bill	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clitherow	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
further	O
;	O
his	O
bailiff	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
delivered	O
the	O
ewes	O
and	O
lambs	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
they	O
marked	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
With	O
three	O
small	O
H	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
rump	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
riddle-mark	O
on	O
the	O
neck	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Provice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
the	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
ewes	O
and	O
lambs	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
Mr	O
.	O
Burn	O
coming	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Burn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
servant	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
seven	O
lambs	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clitherow	O
's	O
fold	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
344	O
.	O
345	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
L.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROWLAND	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-six	O
ells	O
of	O
linen-cloth	O
,	O
called	O
white	O
roll	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
called	O
white	O
essene	O
,	O
containing	O
fifty-six	O
ells	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
ten	O
ells	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
called	O
paterbone	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
ninety-four	O
ells	O
of	O
and	O
eight	O
ells	O
of	O
hempen	O
Russia	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hotchkin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Feb.	O
23d	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
[	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hotchkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1771	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
quitted	O
my	O
service	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
Sydden	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
convey	O
'd	O
to	O
Sydden	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
's	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
Sydden	O
we	O
took	O
Morgan	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
in	O
Noble-street	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
several	O
things	O
from	O
me	O
while	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
;	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Bell-inn	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Birmingham	O
waggon	O
;	O
on	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Pollard	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
traced	O
it	O
to	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
till	O
called	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
many	O
goods	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
article	O
has	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
cotton	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
printed	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
white	O
essene	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
particular	O
number	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
number	O
that	O
the	O
maker	O
puts	O
on	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
sells	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
particular	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
have	O
different	O
marks	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
Morgan	O
's	O
having	O
robbed	O
me	O
broke	O
out	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
,	O
one	O
Cist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Rowland	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
's	O
coachman	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
different	O
goods	O
they	O
had	O
in	O
their	O
custody	O
;	O
Rowland	O
had	O
ten	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
printed	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
appears	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
torn	O
off	O
a	O
piece	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tuck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Bell-inn	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Morgan	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
boxes	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
coachmen	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
,	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
and	O
Morgan	O
talked	O
together	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
conversation	O
between	O
Morgan	O
and	O
Rowland	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
's	O
coachman	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
said	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
box	O
to	O
the	O
stables	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
the	O
loft	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
brought	O
them	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
Rowland	O
and	O
I	O
expressed	O
some	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
rectitude	O
of	O
this	O
transaction	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
said	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
that	O
Morgan	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
settle	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
we	O
packed	O
up	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
corded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
Morgan	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
direction	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
;	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
's	O
man	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
Morgan	O
to	O
be	O
off	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
very	O
kindly	O
helped	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
these	O
goods	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
delivered	O
that	O
message	O
?	O
Tuck	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
notion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
goods	O
?	O
Tuck	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
meant	O
by	O
being	O
off	O
?	O
Tuck	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bollard	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
when	O
Morgan	O
was	O
under	O
examination	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
several	O
times	O
taking	O
goods	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
being	O
packed	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Bell-inn	O
in	O
Smith-field	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
Baker	O
's	O
waggon	O
for	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
this	O
box	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
directed	O
for	O
one	O
Matthews	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
ware-house	O
till	O
called	O
for	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hotchkin	O
being	O
engaged	O
,	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
recover	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
mayor	O
of	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
the	O
mayor	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
waggon	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Baker	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
remembered	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
considerable	O
trouble	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
dispense	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
my	O
authority	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
unloaded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hotchkin	O
,	O
who	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Oliver	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
and	O
Savage	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Morgan	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
box	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
smuggle	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Christmas	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
as	O
much	O
linen	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
carry	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
coachman	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
asked	O
his	O
leave	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
coachman	O
myself	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
put	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
more	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
till	O
night	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
counter	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
came	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
coarse	O
sheeting	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
ticking	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
one	O
morning	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
borrowed	O
an	O
old	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cord	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
there	O
till	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
meet	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Stracey	O
's	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
the	O
Birmingham	O
waggon	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
