TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1772	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKSTONE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kidman	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Goddely	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chunn	I-pers
Marmaduke	B-pers
Storr	I-pers
John	B-pers
Darencrook	I-pers
Donald	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Redburn	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
*	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dakin	I-pers
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowan	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Orgill	I-pers
George	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cubitt	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Byrchmore	I-pers
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Erwine	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
;	O
John	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dakin	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cowan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
.	O
510	O
,	O
511	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
and	O
MARTHA	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
512	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
EUSTACE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
44	O
s.	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
of	O
narrow	O
white	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
and	O
nine	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
513	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOSELY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
paper	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
514	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
CHARLOTTE	B-pers
BALDWYN	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3d	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
nephew	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
Inn	I-place
at	I-place
Islington	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
My	O
business	O
is	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
graziers	O
with	O
their	O
cattle	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
following	O
a	O
boy	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
help	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
to	O
move	O
off	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
goods	O
lying	O
inside	O
the	O
gate	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
removed	O
till	O
day	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
somebody	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Odell	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Pitler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
which	O
adjoins	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
divides	O
a	O
skittle	O
ground	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Oldstock	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
pales	O
which	O
are	O
easily	O
got	O
over	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
quart	O
saucepan	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
matter	O
you	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
gather	O
elder	O
flowers	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
I	O
met	O
offered	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
watch	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
removing	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
landlord	O
seizing	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Catharine	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
and	O
Judith	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murdoch	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
515	O
,	O
516	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WALLIS	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6th	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sun	B-place
and	I-place
Bull	I-place
in	I-place
Oxford	I-place
Road	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
company	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
silver	O
mug	O
stood	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
moved	O
it	O
a-cross	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
laid	O
their	O
heads	O
together	O
and	O
whispered	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
my	O
wife	O
move	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
removed	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
Wallis	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
George	O
gave	O
my	O
wife	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
squabble	O
about	O
the	O
shilling	O
;	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
disputing	O
about	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
that	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
suspect	O
that	O
the	O
dispute	O
about	O
the	O
shilling	O
was	O
an	O
artifice	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
George	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
court	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Wallis	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
mug	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
Wallis	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
I	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Pye	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
they	O
were	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
after	O
Wallis	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
George	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Wallis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
mug	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
several	O
gentlemens	O
families	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
George	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
517	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
TUDOR	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SLINGSBY	I-pers
TUDOR	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Hayssom	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
.	O
Dec.	O
12th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
518	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
VENDOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1st	O
.	O
+	O
Martha	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Hine	O
,	O
of	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
in	O
Bleeding	B-place
Hart	I-place
Yard	I-place
;	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
bundle	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dunfield	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
clothes	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
linen	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
fetching	O
some	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
this	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
Dunfield	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dunfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
different	O
accounts	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
lad	O
who	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
bundle	O
for	O
him	O
into	O
Tooley	O
Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
519	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MASSEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
four	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
and	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hillson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
June	O
11th	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hillson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
at	I-place
Bow	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
thieves	O
!	O
thieves	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
chamber	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
housekeeper	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
holding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
round	O
the	O
waist	O
;	O
she	O
appeared	O
vastly	O
frightened	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
!	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
deliver	O
up	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
two	O
rings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
money	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
and	O
counted	O
it	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
rings	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
dropped	O
near	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
13	O
guineas	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
19	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
;	O
that	O
money	O
was	O
loose	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	B-pers
the	O
high	O
constable	O
was	O
in	O
town	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
Ann	O
Church	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
housekeeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hilson	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
candles	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
unlocked	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
picklock	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
right	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
d	O
-	O
g	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
;	O
he	O
drawed	O
me	O
down	O
three	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
back	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
is	O
always	O
kept	O
locked	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
high	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
Tower	O
Hamlets	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
officers	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
picklock	O
keys	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
picklocks	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
large	O
bunch	O
of	O
picklocks	O
about	O
two	O
dozen	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
these	O
and	O
they	O
open	O
every	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
knife	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
strong	O
clasp	O
knife	O
with	O
a	O
square	O
end	O
like	O
a	O
chissel	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
admit	O
me	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
No	O
.	O
321	O
and	O
645	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
520	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
CARTWRIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Browman	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
feloniously	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
June	O
9th	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Browman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	O
near	O
Burlington	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
coach	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
weapons	O
;	O
I	O
pushed	O
my	O
cane	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
and	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
men	O
who	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Browman	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Head	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
coachman	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Albemarle	O
Street	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
drive	O
him	O
down	O
Northumberland	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
harness	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
stop	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
deliver	O
,	O
twice	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
struck	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
cane	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
towards	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
use	O
any	O
violence	O
to	O
you	O
or	O
the	O
gentleman	O
?	O
Head	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
weapon	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
stopt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
for	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
ill	O
it	O
overcame	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
intoxicated	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Head	O
both	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
intoxicated	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
20	O
and	O
30	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
521	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SLINGSBY	I-pers
TUDOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
thickset	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
thickset	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
scarlet	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2d	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Whitechappel	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodging	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
by	O
another	O
key	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
high	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
Hamlets	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
this	O
scarlet	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
filing	O
this	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
picklock	O
;	O
)	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Massey	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
just	O
been	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
carried	O
together	O
before	O
justice	O
Fell	O
;	O
Massey	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Massey	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
together	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
517	O
.	O
522	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
CHAPPELERS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
jam	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
blue	O
sattin	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Frenshane	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Frenshane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
coach-maker	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
died	O
in	O
child-bed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
jam	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
groat	O
on	O
the	O
jam	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
blanket	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
blankets	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
stripe	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
the	O
children	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
every	O
night	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
formerly	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
523	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
RYER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Errington	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
in	O
court	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
clothes	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
524	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
dimity	O
robe	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
3d	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
child	O
at	O
nurse	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Armstrong	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
shifted	O
myself	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
suckle	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
shift	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
for	O
my	O
shift	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
an	O
apron	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Two	O
pawnbrokers	O
produced	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
several	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
-	O
Saltmarsh	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
formerly	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
,	O
real	O
necessity	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
committing	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
525	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
pick	O
axes	O
with	O
wooden	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
shovel	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pick-axes	O
and	O
a	O
shovel	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
5th	O
and	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Noble	O
and	O
Phillips	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
near	O
Marybone	B-place
Bason	I-place
;	O
they	O
lost	O
their	O
two	O
shovels	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
over	O
night	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
stands	O
in	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
a	O
gate	O
that	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
gate	O
open	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tools	O
mentoned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
the	O
tools	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Day	O
early	O
that	O
morning	O
with	O
some	O
tools	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
tools	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
different	O
owners	O
,	O
whose	O
marks	O
were	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
tools	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
Gravel	O
Pit	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
another	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
Barnet	O
and	O
St.	O
Albans	O
;	O
these	O
tools	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
son-in-law	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
set	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
3	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
526	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
FLOWERS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
527	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Pointer	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Pointer	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
metal	O
engraved	O
watch	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
:	O
the	O
4th	O
and	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
turned	O
over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
for	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
real	O
worth	O
;	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sometime	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
here	O
yesterday	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
pawn	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
I	O
understood	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Half	O
Moon	O
Street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fetched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Scott	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
slight	O
intimacy	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
several	O
watches	O
to	O
mend	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
all	O
back	O
again	O
but	O
one	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Kennedy	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Gardiner	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
528	O
,	O
529	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
DEMPSEY	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
DEVINE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
paper	O
machee	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
between	O
Kingsland	B-place
Turnpike	I-place
and	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
by	O
I	O
thought	O
four	O
men	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
dusk	O
;	O
one	O
thrust	O
a	O
pistol	O
through	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
opened	O
that	O
door	O
likewise	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
forced	O
themselves	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
bent	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
rifled	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
chain	O
,	O
two	O
seals	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
a	O
paper	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
who	O
the	O
persons	O
were	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
near	O
sighted	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
my	O
snuff-box	O
since	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Meyers	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
fortnight	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
Gore	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
dial	O
plate	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Lyons	I-pers
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
dial	O
plate	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
Lyons	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
watches	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Camomile	O
Street	O
.	O
Devine	O
had	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
Gore	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Lyons	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
then	O
Gore	O
produced	O
the	O
pinchbeck	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
one	O
box	O
,	O
they	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
Lyons	O
offered	O
six	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
both	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
gold	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
the	O
pinchbeck	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
watches	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
sixpence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stay	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
as	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
opposite	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Dempsey	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
shew	O
me	O
to	O
ever	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
satisfy	O
you	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
ever	O
a	O
one	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
Ever	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
can	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Devine	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
watch	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
was	O
the	O
gold	O
one	O
,	O
white	O
enamelled	O
,	O
or	O
gold	O
dial	O
plate	O
?	O
Meyers	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
plain	O
case	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
.	O
Was	O
yours	O
a	O
plain	O
watch	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
the	O
Back	O
Road	O
from	O
Islington	O
and	O
Highgate	O
;	O
we	O
stopt	O
a	O
chaise	O
behind	O
Islington	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Road	I-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
gentleman	O
again	O
?	O
Gore	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
stoop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
burst	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
you	O
all	O
armed	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
John	O
Devine	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
pistols	O
each	O
;	O
Dempsey	O
and	O
Devine	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
Devine	O
jumped	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Gore	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Devine	I-pers
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
.	O
Devine	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
gentleman	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
painted	O
snuff	O
box	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
desired	O
the	O
post	O
boy	O
to	O
drive	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
straight	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
post	O
chaise	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
?	O
Gore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
straight	O
to	O
town	O
through	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
night	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
one	O
Lyons	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
in	O
Sweet	O
Apple	O
Court	O
I	O
think	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
.	O
We	O
spoke	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
Lyons	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
street	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
words	O
pass	O
between	O
the	O
gentleman	O
and	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
robbed	O
him	O
?	O
Gore	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
paying	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
would	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
down	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Search	O
gentlemen	O
where	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
We	O
just	O
put	O
a	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
flap	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
;	O
we	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
for	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
Gore	O
.	O
Five	O
guineas	O
;	O
Lyons	O
gave	O
us	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
dial	O
plate	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Dempsey	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
speak	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Devine	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
Dempsey	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
whilst	O
Devine	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
afterwards	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Lyons	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Lyons	O
's	O
whore	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
Dempster	O
followed	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
conversation	O
that	O
passed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
confined	O
myself	O
merely	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
lead	O
the	O
accomplice	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
yet	O
mentioned	O
the	O
conversation	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
nearly	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
accomplice	O
has	O
related	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
ask	O
for	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
contained	O
nothing	O
but	O
old	O
letters	O
;	O
one	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
may	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
to-morrow	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
unnecessary	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
contained	O
nothing	O
but	O
old	O
letters	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Gore	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
?	O
Gore	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
Gore	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
robberies	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
take	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
immediately	O
;	O
accordingly	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
or	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
)	O
in	O
Bell	O
Yard	O
,	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Dempsey	O
by	O
both	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hands	O
into	O
his	O
inside	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
pistol	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
powder	O
and	O
a	O
ball	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
setting	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Dempsey	O
's	O
business	O
?	O
Heley	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
writer	O
to	O
a	O
stationer	O
;	O
the	O
evidence	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Devine	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
or	O
woman	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
,	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
paper	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Devine	O
?	O
Heley	O
.	O
A	O
shoe	O
or	O
clog	O
maker	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Devine	O
's	O
woman	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
pawned	O
a	O
paper	O
snuff	O
box	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Rochford	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Devine	O
any	O
weapon	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
Heyley	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
none	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Highland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
abroad	O
*	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
Devine	O
almost	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
and	O
Devine	O
,	O
were	O
altogether	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
ask	O
Devine	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
Dempsey	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
emptied	O
the	O
snuff	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Rochford	O
's	O
.	O
*	O
Her	O
husband	O
was	O
transported	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Highland	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
you	O
pledge	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Highland	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
I	O
pledged	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
or	O
Devine	O
's	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Devine	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
a	O
pistol	O
of	O
mine	O
?	O
Highland	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
even	O
carried	O
a	O
knife	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Devine	O
's	O
trade	O
?	O
Highland	O
.	O
A	O
shoe	O
and	O
clog	O
maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Dempsey	O
?	O
Highland	O
.	O
A	O
clerk	O
.	O
Gore	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
late	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
Devine	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
this	O
black	O
eye	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
Gore	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
Dempsey	O
come	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
snuff	O
box	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Highland	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
June	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
6	O
d.	O
(	O
The	O
snuff	O
box	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Dempsey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
Gore	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
pistol	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Devine	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
;	O
Gore	O
wants	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
lying	O
with	O
Highland	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
Dempsey	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Academy	O
Court	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
Dempsey	O
was	O
a	O
clerk	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
any	O
business	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
employ	O
him	O
constantly	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
writing	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
stationers	O
;	O
Dempsey	O
has	O
wrote	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
did	O
my	O
business	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
wrote	O
for	O
me	O
within	O
this	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Devine	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Mole	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Mole	I-pers
with	O
whom	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DEVINE	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DEVINE	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
watch	O
string	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
June	O
22d	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
``	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
near	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
about	O
``	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
``	O
one	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
``	O
gold	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
the	O
dial	O
plate	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
either	O
``	O
gold	O
or	O
metal	O
gilt	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
``	O
his	O
pocket	O
book	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
``	O
they	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Penny	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
accordingly	O
received	O
it	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
``	O
after	O
by	O
that	O
conveyance	O
.	O
''	O
Aaron	B-pers
Meyers	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
first	O
trial	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
``	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
himself	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
``	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
Lyons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
``	O
sent	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
his	O
pocket	O
book	O
by	O
the	O
``	O
Penny-Post	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
530	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
BIGGS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
96	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Alkins	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Alkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
six	O
shillings	O
worth	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
guinea	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
half	O
pence	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
drawer	O
locked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
angry	O
at	O
my	O
suspecting	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
threatened	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
send	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
drawer	O
where	O
she	O
kept	O
her	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
121	O
halfpence	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bunch	O
,	O
which	O
opened	O
the	O
look	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
halfpence	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Landaway	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
531	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
HICKS	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WHITE	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brailsford	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Brailsford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
before	O
nine	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
St.	O
Martin	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
)	O
not	O
coming	O
home	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
opened	O
her	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
missed	O
several	O
things	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
connected	O
with	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
in	O
Tothil	O
Fields-Bridewell	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
petticoat	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
and	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
shewing	O
her	O
favour	O
?	O
Brailsford	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
her	O
directly	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brailsford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
one	O
cotton	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Brailsford	O
.	O
One	O
month	O
and	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Brailsford	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
says	O
near	O
21	O
;	O
she	O
comes	O
from	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Wight	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
place	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Swingwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
two	O
gowns	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fault	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
informed	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
me	O
pardon	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friends	O
in	O
London	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
532	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BOWYER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
into	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Youins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
pickled	O
pork	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Youins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Poplar	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
first	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bolt	O
withinside	O
;	O
I	O
bolted	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
eight	O
inches	O
square	O
,	O
with	O
bars	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
light	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bars	O
was	O
loose	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
that	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
observed	O
the	O
bars	O
were	O
loose	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
four	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
after	O
three-quarters	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pork	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
some	O
workmen	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
heavy	O
loaded	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
quite	O
light	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
?	O
Youins	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
workmen	O
said	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Youins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Youins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Youins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
our	O
gate	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Crelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
attend	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pork	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
earthen	O
pan	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartments	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
pork	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
cut	O
I	O
remember	O
I	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
pork	O
just	O
like	O
this	O
produced	O
.	O
Phineas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Youins	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
three	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
to	O
warm	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
shaking	O
with	O
cold	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
about	O
seven	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
ditch	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
trowsers	O
pocket	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
heavy	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Youins	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
an	O
India	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
supposed	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
loaded	O
.	O
-	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Phineas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartments	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
pork	O
there	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
to	O
warn	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
pork	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
I	O
met	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
533	O
,	O
534	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
OWEN	B-pers
COSGROVE	I-pers
and	O
MARGARET	B-pers
CASSADAY	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
lace	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
twelve	O
plain	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
six	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
twenty-seven	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
two	O
crown	O
pieces	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Michael	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
;	O
two	O
wooden	O
boxes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
studs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
mittens	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
eleven	O
guineas	O
,	O
eleven	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
three	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Michael	O
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
535	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Francis	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
nature	O
,	O
carnally	O
did	O
know	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
did	O
commit	O
that	O
detestable	O
and	O
abominable	O
vice	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
among	O
Christians	O
,	O
called	O
buggery	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Hay	I-pers
-	O
Sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
thirteen	O
next	O
January	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
can	O
say	O
your	O
catechism	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
sworn	O
for	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
school	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
Parliament	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
buckle	O
to	O
mend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
his	O
dining	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
halfpence	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
down	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
then	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
frightened	O
at	O
this	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
He	O
set	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
elbow	O
chair	O
;	O
he	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
kissed	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
lay	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
face	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
c	O
-	O
k	O
into	O
my	O
b	O
-	O
e.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
submit	O
to	O
it	O
quietly	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
submitted	O
to	O
it	O
quietly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
he	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
minutes	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
quite	O
in	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Some	O
wet	O
stuff	O
that	O
was	O
white	O
;	O
I	O
wiped	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
describe	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
how	O
far	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
body	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
wipe	O
the	O
wet	O
off	O
with	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
My	O
shirt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
you	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
He	O
spouted	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
spout	O
some	O
into	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
He	O
set	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
elbow	O
chair	O
,	O
kissed	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
groat	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
attempt	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
ever	O
any	O
body	O
served	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
before	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
your	O
uncle	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
again	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
unbuttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
rub	O
his	O
c	O
-	O
k	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
till	O
some	O
white	O
stuff	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
-	O
into	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
stiff	O
and	O
hard	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
attempt	O
any	O
thing	O
behind	O
then	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
quietly	O
submitted	O
to	O
all	O
that	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
buckle	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
eleven	O
;	O
he	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
breeches	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
again	O
that	O
time	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
this	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
after	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
thighs	O
and	O
legs	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
show	O
glasses	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
he	O
bespoke	O
a	O
shirt	O
buckle	O
of	O
my	O
uncle	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
home	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
uncle	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
buckle	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
so	O
willingly	O
two	O
days	O
together	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
objection	O
to	O
go	O
now	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
object	O
to	O
go	O
now	O
and	O
not	O
before	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
;	O
the	O
reason	O
was	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
a	O
wrong	O
thing	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
directly	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
uncle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
captain	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
tell	O
your	O
uncle	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
uncle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
there	O
before	O
dinner	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
your	O
uncle	O
the	O
whole	O
story	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
you	O
these	O
three	O
times	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
kept	O
it	O
a	O
secret	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
of	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
a	O
wrong	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
accord	O
the	O
second	O
and	O
third	O
times	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
uncle	O
might	O
get	O
business	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
mother	O
live	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
In	O
Tavistock-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
her	O
often	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ashamed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
it	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Brast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
intimate	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
trade	O
he	O
is	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
told	O
them	O
was	O
Capt	O
,	O
Jones	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Hay	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
friends	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
captain	O
after	O
you	O
made	O
this	O
discovery	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
discovered	O
this	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brest	O
first	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
happen	O
than	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
told	O
us	O
now	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
you	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
you	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
body	O
below	O
.	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
shop	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
other	O
people	O
there	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
saw	O
you	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
see	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
nothing	O
I	O
suppose	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
had	O
no	O
marks	O
of	O
having	O
been	O
crying	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
call	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
heard	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
c	O
-	O
into	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hurt	O
you	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
against	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
or	O
in	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
washed	O
your	O
linen	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
One	O
Mrs.	O
Jerret	O
that	O
washes	O
for	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
your	O
linen	O
being	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
found	O
no	O
inconvenience	O
afterwards	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
sore	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
sore	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
straddled	O
as	O
I	O
walked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
never	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
by	O
your	O
uncle	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
ever	O
mentioned	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
yourself	O
sore	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
directly	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
wiped	O
something	O
from	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
with	O
your	O
shirt	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
white	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
the	O
captain	O
squirted	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
not	O
much	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
white	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
did	O
you	O
wipe	O
it	O
off	O
of	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
my	O
thigh	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
wet	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
while	O
in	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
?	O
You	O
must	O
remember	O
you	O
are	O
on	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
life	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
on	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
saying	O
,	O
therefore	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
strictly	O
true	O
;	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
wipe	O
the	O
wet	O
from	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
your	O
thigh	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
thigh	O
on	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
soreness	O
over	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
ill.	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
this	O
was	O
you	O
taken	O
ill	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
surgeon	O
attend	O
you	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
got	O
well	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
illness	O
was	O
pains	O
in	O
your	O
thighs	O
and	O
legs	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
your	O
relations	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
cramp	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
captain	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
A	O
week	O
after	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
told	O
here	O
now	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
whole	O
week	O
after	O
your	O
telling	O
this	O
story	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
you	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
as	O
now	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
my	O
uncle	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
uncle	O
what	O
a	O
sad	O
affair	O
had	O
happened	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
or	O
tell	O
him	O
at	O
your	O
uncle	O
's	O
shop	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
un	O
cle	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
captain	O
been	O
gone	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
ago	O
that	O
you	O
told	O
this	O
story	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
A	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
hurt	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
second	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
money	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
shame	O
nor	O
remorse	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
ashamed	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
on	O
a	O
perfect	O
knowledge	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
saying	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
hour	O
appointed	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
you	O
discovered	O
it	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
meet	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
that	O
ever	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
afterwards	O
during	O
the	O
three	O
weeks	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
this	O
lad	O
's	O
uncle	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
formerly	O
with	O
his	O
grandfather	O
opposite	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
the	O
boy	O
behaved	O
himself	O
since	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
for	O
veracity	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Very	O
good	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
lying	O
boy	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
lies	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
was	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
shew-glass	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
friend	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
evasions	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
and	O
such	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
bashfulness	O
;	O
the	O
captain	O
afterwards	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
shirt	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
bespoke	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
home	O
:	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
?	O
his	O
reply	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
perhaps	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
some	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
business	O
by	O
so	O
doing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
backwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
used	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
commit	O
buggery	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
this	O
discovery	O
was	O
made	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
captain	O
up	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
Mr.	O
Brest	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
communicate	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
sooner	O
than	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
story	O
;	O
I	O
rather	O
chose	O
the	O
boy	O
might	O
tell	O
it	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
then	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
ashamed	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
further	O
and	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bid	O
the	O
boy	O
tell	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
father	O
(	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
grandfather	O
)	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
was	O
the	O
application	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
after	O
this	O
discovery	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
justice	O
was	O
the	O
application	O
made	O
to	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Justice	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
captain	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
till	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Mercer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mercer	O
desired	O
we	O
might	O
consider	O
minutely	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
rashly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
captain	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
any	O
awkwardness	O
in	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
gate	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
walked	O
lamish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
immediately	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
general	O
pain	O
all	O
over	O
his	O
limbs	O
.	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
thighs	O
and	O
legs	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
education	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
he	O
read	O
and	O
write	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
sensible	O
boy	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
rather	O
so	O
than	O
otherwise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
told	O
this	O
story	O
pretty	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
he	O
has	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brest	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
his	O
linen	O
was	O
washed	O
before	O
this	O
discovery	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
any	O
blood	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
his	O
shirt	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
story	O
here	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
the	O
story	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
here	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
the	O
story	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
captain	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
body	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
wiped	O
some	O
wet	O
off	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
from	O
others	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
rather	O
chose	O
he	O
should	O
tell	O
the	O
story	O
to	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
never	O
observed	O
any	O
aukwardness	O
in	O
his	O
gate	O
till	O
the	O
pains	O
in	O
his	O
legs	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
these	O
days	O
to	O
the	O
captain	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
[	O
Francis	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Hay	I-pers
again	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
evidence	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
jury	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
may	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
consider	O
his	O
life	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
if	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
said	O
is	O
true	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
every	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
conceal	O
nothing	O
?	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
all	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
.	O
-	O
Rapley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
bespoke	O
a	O
shirt	O
buckle	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
believe	O
Mr.	O
Mercer	O
went	O
backwards	O
after	O
the	O
captain	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
expressed	O
a	O
wish	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
word	O
;	O
)	O
``	O
I	O
wish	O
my	O
uncle	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
carry	O
the	O
buckle	O
home	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
?	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
repeated	O
the	O
question	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
tell	O
you	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
captain	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
cry	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
head	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
still	O
persisted	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
knowing	O
how	O
he	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
otherwise	O
I	O
would	O
inform	O
his	O
uncle	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
further	O
persisting	O
in	O
knowing	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
promise	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
uncle	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
evaded	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
shifted	O
on	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
his	O
uncle	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
story	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
meeting	O
the	O
captain	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
knee	O
,	O
unbottoned	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
him	O
that	O
way	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
c	O
-	O
k	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
;	O
he	O
persisted	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
vulgar	O
name	O
of	O
a	O
-	O
e	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hurt	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
by	O
shoving	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
there	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
any	O
wet	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
question	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
mention	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
shoved	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
he	O
laid	O
him	O
down	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
laying	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
stayed	O
with	O
the	O
captain	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
captain	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
besides	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
served	O
him	O
so	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
always	O
took	O
his	O
breeches	O
down	O
,	O
likewise	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
further	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
frequent	O
in	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
company	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
by	O
seeing	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
uncle	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
veracity	O
or	O
used	O
to	O
tell	O
lies	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
any	O
other	O
then	O
to	O
tell	O
truth	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
shoved	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
And	O
hurt	O
him	O
by	O
shoving	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
penetrating	O
his	O
body	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
story	O
of	O
the	O
wet	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
but	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
first	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
After	O
having	O
informed	O
the	O
uncle	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brest	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
more	O
particularly	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
The	O
uncle	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
from	O
the	O
boy	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
related	O
,	O
prevented	O
my	O
further	O
enquiry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
his	O
account	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
you	O
told	O
the	O
uncle	O
,	O
you	O
thought	O
it	O
an	O
attempt	O
only	O
?	O
Rapley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Prater	O
,	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
boy	O
from	O
his	O
cradle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
veracity	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
any	O
little	O
fault	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
if	O
asked	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
uncle	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
respecting	O
this	O
charge	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
when	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
uncle	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
story	O
particularly	O
.	O
Brest	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
business	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
in	O
Parliament-street	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Mercer	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
terrible	O
accident	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
item	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
party	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
Punch	O
at	O
the	O
Masquerade	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
intermediate	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
again	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
by	O
ourselves	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
God	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
family	O
is	O
a	O
religious	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
church	O
every	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
afterwards	O
kept	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
read	O
his	O
catechism	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
telling	O
a	O
lie	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
call	O
God	O
to	O
witness	O
to	O
an	O
action	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
tell	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
either	O
truth	O
or	O
a	O
lie	O
;	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
terminate	O
either	O
his	O
fate	O
or	O
your	O
happiness	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
particular	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
began	O
his	O
story	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
bad	O
people	O
went	O
to	O
hell	O
,	O
and	O
good	O
people	O
to	O
heaven	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
these	O
things	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
caution	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
utter	O
nothing	O
but	O
truth	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
buckle	O
to	O
mend	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Jones	O
pulled	O
down	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
knee	O
,	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
)	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
c	O
-	O
k	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
hands	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
rubbed	O
it	O
till	O
some	O
wet	O
stuff	O
came	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
wet	O
stuff	O
coming	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
kissed	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
intermediate	O
time	O
of	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
in	O
an	O
elbow	O
chair	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
c	O
-	O
k	O
to	O
his	O
a	O
-	O
e	O
hole	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
language	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
there	O
pushed	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
wet	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wiped	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
-	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
body	O
;	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
particularly	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
hurt	O
him	O
exceedingly	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
interrogated	O
him	O
very	O
minutely	O
,	O
respecting	O
its	O
being	O
in	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
push	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
positively	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
wet	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
a	O
-	O
e	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wiped	O
it	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
whether	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
himself	O
put	O
his	O
breeches	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Brest	O
.	O
Half	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
pence	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
however	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
twice	O
more	O
;	O
that	O
each	O
time	O
he	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
white	O
stuff	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
carpet	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
boy	O
told	O
you	O
this	O
story	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pushed	O
at	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
elbow	O
chair	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
his	O
expression	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
more	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
several	O
times	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
answer	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
case	O
without	O
any	O
emotion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
answer	O
in	O
the	O
negative	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
any	O
question	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
consider	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
telling	O
this	O
story	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
public	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
first	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
that	O
the	O
captain	O
had	O
entered	O
him	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
question	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
body	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
the	O
captain	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
b	O
-	O
e	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
chief	O
matter	O
turned	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
entered	O
his	O
body	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
depended	O
upon	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
spoke	O
true	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
he	O
be	O
hanged	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
true	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
be	O
quick	O
and	O
explicit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
this	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
believe	O
him	O
.	O
Brest	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
applied	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apply	O
to	O
any	O
;	O
his	O
friends	O
I	O
believe	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
grandfather	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
cautioned	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
advice	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
particular	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
fortune	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
Captain	O
Jones	O
by	O
same	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
every	O
body	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
that	O
crime	O
,	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
justice	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
justice	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
justice	O
Mercer	O
here	O
?	O
Brest	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bishop	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bishop	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
justice	O
Mercer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
my	O
attachment	O
to	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
landlady	O
can	O
prove	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
minute	O
in	O
my	O
lodgings	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Epiphania	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
.	O
Captain	O
Jones	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
these	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
that	O
little	O
boy	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Dobson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
three	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Dobson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
coming	O
once	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
hardly	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Frank	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
buckle	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
go	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
his	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Dobson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
,	O
or	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
noise	O
of	O
feet	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
struggling	O
.	O
Dobson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
apartments	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
dining	O
room	O
and	O
a	O
bed-chamber	O
;	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
is	O
over	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bedchamber	O
over	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
noise	O
or	O
struggle	O
should	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
shop	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
A	O
china	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
a	O
carpet	O
in	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
go	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
Almost	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
go	O
under	O
the	O
chairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
captain	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
maid	O
servants	O
complained	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
that	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
were	O
people	O
of	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
chairs	O
are	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
Two	O
two-arm-chairs	O
;	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
others	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Captain	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
appeared	O
so	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
connexions	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
I	O
have	O
known	O
Captain	O
Jones	O
near	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
abroad	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
in	O
his	O
conduct	O
,	O
character	O
and	O
connections	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
thought	O
him	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
thought	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
staid	O
a	O
night	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
that	O
boy	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Dabson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Captain	O
Jones	B-pers
a	O
twelve-month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
is	O
quite	O
a	O
different	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
an	O
extreme	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
him	O
capable	O
of	O
committing	O
such	O
a	O
crime	O
as	O
is	O
a	O
ledged	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
lived	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
engraver	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Business	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
publications	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
have	O
thought	O
this	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
engraved	O
the	O
plates	O
for	O
A	O
Treatise	O
on	O
Scaiting	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
Fire-works	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
his	O
character	O
impeached	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
suspected	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
amazed	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Captain	O
above	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
on	O
terms	O
of	O
intimacy	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Hope	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
formerly	O
much	O
so	O
seventeen	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
young	O
,	O
about	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
was	O
addicted	O
to	O
women	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
once	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
clapped	O
or	O
poxed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
capable	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
alledged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Hope	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
quite	O
a	O
different	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
had	O
a	O
difference	O
with	O
her	O
