TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
JUNE	O
,	O
1772	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
Fiftth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
||	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
justices	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
||	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Maritau	I-pers
Bartholomew	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
George	B-pers
Grainge	I-pers
Patrick	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Talbott	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cobbett	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
William	B-pers
Owens	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
on	O
this	O
Jury	O
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Bongshage	I-pers
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
.	O
411	O
,	O
412	O
,	O
413	O
,	O
414	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ISAAC	B-pers
HOLMES	I-pers
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
FOX	I-pers
,	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILCOX	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
on	O
19th	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
scarlet	O
duffel	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
two	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
two	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
drudging	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
a	O
flowered	O
linen	O
child	O
's	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
child	O
's	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
three	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
one	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
four	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
pin	O
cushion	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILCOX	I-pers
for	O
procuring	O
,	O
counselling	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abeting	O
Isaac	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Burglary	O
to	O
do	O
and	O
commit	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
Francis	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
the	O
Accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
All	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
415	O
,	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SIDAY	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
three	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
buttons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
Bath	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
four	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
two	O
leather	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brown	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
case	O
of	O
instruments	O
,	O
one	O
dove	O
tail	O
saw	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
seven	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Waterson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Waterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Goswell	B-place
Street	I-place
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
green	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
stone	O
coloured	O
clothes	O
with	O
yellow	O
metal	O
buttons	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
bottom	O
drawer	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
blue	O
with	O
white	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
drab	O
coloured	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
mixed	O
metal	O
buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Bath	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
mixture	O
of	O
brick	O
dust	O
colour	O
and	O
white	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
with	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
the	O
knees	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
deal	O
box	O
with	O
seven	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
Saturday	O
)	O
three	O
shirts	O
marked	O
J.	O
W.	O
four	O
neckcloths	O
not	O
marked	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
,	O
two	O
lawn	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
coloured	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
one	O
red	O
,	O
one	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brown	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
two	O
leather	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
one	O
red	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
;	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
mathematical	O
drawing	O
instruments	O
,	O
a	O
dove	O
tail	O
saw	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fieldings	I-pers
(	O
producing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
)	O
the	O
accomplice	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
blue	O
clothes	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
one	O
Caple	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
cloaths	O
in	O
Paris	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
Grub	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
picklock	O
keys	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
clothes	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Siday	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Goswell	O
Street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
Shrove	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
throw	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shipman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
blue	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
here	O
?	O
Shipman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Paris	O
.	O
She	O
proved	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Nobody	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
lodgers	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
that	O
morning	O
to	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
pushed	O
against	O
it	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
,	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bars	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
nothing	O
there	O
;	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Waterson	O
's	O
Room	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
two	O
drawers	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
five	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
Fisher	O
your	O
son	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
or	O
unlocked	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
broke	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
picked	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
often	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Siday	O
and	O
Paris	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Sun	O
Dial	O
,	O
in	O
Goswell	O
street	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
mother	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Waterson	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Paris	O
now	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
Paris	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
;	O
Siday	O
went	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
Paris	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
this	O
box	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Paris	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
Grub	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
William	B-pers
Siday	I-pers
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
three	O
suits	O
of	O
clothes	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
Paris	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Blake	O
's	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Blake	O
's	O
for	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Paris	O
's	O
lodgings	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
suits	O
of	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
carried	O
to	O
Siday	O
's	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
Paris	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Siday	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
printer	O
s	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
trade	O
Paris	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
false	O
keys	O
got	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
From	O
Paris	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Whose	O
proposal	O
was	O
it	O
to	O
rob	O
your	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
proposal	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
lodger	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Siday	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
Paris	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ravenscrest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
William	B-pers
Paris	I-pers
thirteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
wire	O
drawer	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
our	O
business	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
watch	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Revenscroft	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridge	O
Water	O
Garden	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
joint	O
watch-case	O
maker	O
;	O
Paris	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
our	O
work	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
left	O
your	O
work	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
Eight	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
diligent	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Farnworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
copper-plate	O
printer	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
well	O
behaved	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
general	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
particularly	O
sober	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Copel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
leather	O
cutter	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
becoming	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bench	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
imputation	O
upon	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridge	O
Water	O
Square	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
watch-case-maker	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
For	O
Siday	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Siday	O
where	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
since	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
417	O
,	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
SHARPLESS	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
forest	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
stocking	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
419	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LILLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
live	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
420	O
,	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
ADSHEAD	I-pers
and	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
ALSWORTH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
gauze	O
sack	O
and	O
petticoat	O
with	O
silk	O
and	O
gold	O
flowers	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
silk	O
sacks	O
and	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
silk	O
night	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
brocaded	O
silk	O
night	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
chased	O
gold	O
outside	O
watch	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
base	O
mettal	O
etwee	O
case	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
gilt	O
base	O
mettal	O
spunge	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
ten	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
houswif	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
four	O
silk	O
sacks	O
and	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
night	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
Count	O
.	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newman	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Marybone	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
my	O
daughter	O
and	O
another	O
lady	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
left	O
in	O
it	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
great	O
holes	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
double	O
doors	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
bolted	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
door	O
had	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
holes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
holes	O
were	O
made	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
and	O
bottom	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
to	O
enable	O
them	O
to	O
undo	O
the	O
bolts	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
sacks	O
and	O
five	O
gowns	O
;	O
(	O
repeats	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
some	O
were	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
clothes	O
at	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
?	O
Bellamy	O
.	O
A	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
return	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
produced	O
the	O
cloaths	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deposed	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
now	O
as	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Miss	O
Ann	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
in	O
Newman	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
lady	O
's	O
house	O
opposite	O
my	O
mamma	O
's	O
whilst	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
clothes	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
door	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
)	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
holes	O
broke	O
large	O
enough	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
holes	O
were	O
made	O
just	O
over	O
the	O
bolts	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
a	O
bureau	O
and	O
a	O
clothes	O
press	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
front	O
room	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
are	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
negligees	O
and	O
sacks	O
and	O
a	O
night	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
bundles	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
contained	O
several	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
and	O
mine	O
;	O
th	O
e	O
other	O
bundle	O
was	O
not	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
miles	O
from	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
from	O
top	O
to	O
bottom	O
,	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
forwards	O
unlocked	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
fast	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
unlocked	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
on	O
Friday	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
area	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
parlour	O
had	O
two	O
holes	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
clothes	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnhill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
bolted	O
both	O
the	O
bolts	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
area	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
double-bolted	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
area	O
door	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
holes	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
as	O
you	O
go	O
from	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
?	O
Barnhill	O
.	O
The	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
a	O
gateway	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
must	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
shut	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
holes	O
were	O
cut	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Pancras	O
Parish	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
they	O
crossed	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
towards	O
Russel-street	O
;	O
Henry	O
Green	O
,	O
a	O
brother	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
bedding	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
a	O
coverlid	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Russel-street	O
corner	O
,	O
Emmington	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
smoaking	O
his	O
pipe	O
,	O
I	O
beckoned	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
seize	O
them	O
;	O
Emmerton	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
we	O
seized	O
Alsworth	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
;	O
Adshead	O
upon	O
that	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
bundle	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Alsworth	O
away	O
to	O
Giles	O
's	O
round-house	O
;	O
Adshead	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Leadbetter	O
searched	O
Alsworth	O
before	O
Adshead	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
secured	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
bundles	O
contained	O
all	O
these	O
cloaths	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
clothes	O
to	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
Office	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
first	O
stopt	O
them	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
Alsworth	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
we	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
stopt	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
remove	O
them	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
seized	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Alsworth	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
you	O
should	O
see	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
?	O
Bannister	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
any	O
further	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
up	O
Windmill	O
Street	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
upon	O
each	O
of	O
their	O
backs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Bannister	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
men	O
moving	O
their	O
lodgings	O
and	O
carrying	O
their	O
beds	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
will	O
see	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
going	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
;	O
then	O
Bannister	O
went	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
hailed	O
another	O
watchman	O
;	O
they	O
stopt	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
stopt	O
Alsworth	O
,	O
Adshead	O
run	O
into	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
buildings	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
down	O
Diot-street	O
.	O
Bannister	O
and	O
Emmington	O
took	O
Alsworth	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bundles	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
tied	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bundles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
being	O
stopt	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Alsworth	I-pers
confessed	O
that	O
morning	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Newman-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
gateway	O
going	O
through	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Emmington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
down	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
partner	O
John	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Duke's-head	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
doors	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
smoking	O
my	O
pipe	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Oldham	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
bedding	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
step	O
on	O
and	O
attack	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Bannister	O
made	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
signal	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
to	O
Oldham	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
made	O
that	O
sign	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
200	O
yards	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
Adshead	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
he	O
immediately	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
short	O
round	O
and	O
caught	O
Alsworth	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
fast	O
till	O
Bannister	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
examining	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
Adshead	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
Oldham	O
and	O
one	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
his	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
opened	O
at	O
the	O
Duke's-head	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Alsworth	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
you	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Emmington	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Alsworth	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
I	O
say	O
?	O
Emmington	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leadbetter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
searched	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
Alsworth	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
in	O
my	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
one	O
or	O
other	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
case	O
and	O
an	O
etwee	O
case	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
center	O
bit	O
upon	O
Alsworth	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
bore	O
holes	O
with	O
;	O
that	O
center	O
bit	O
directly	O
fits	O
the	O
hole	O
that	O
is	O
made	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
's	O
doors	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Alsworth	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
us	O
within	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
or	O
without	O
side	O
?	O
Leadbetter	O
.	O
Within	O
side	O
.	O
Alsworth	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
ask	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
that	O
question	O
.	O
Bannister	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
insisted	O
on	O
searching	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
things	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
search	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
or	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
round-house	O
?	O
Bannister	O
.	O
He	O
began	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
but	O
searched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
:	O
Emmington	O
held	O
the	O
hat	O
inside	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Leadbetter	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
hat	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Emmington	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
within	O
side	O
or	O
without	O
side	O
?	O
Bannister	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
attacked	O
him	O
outside	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
off	O
duty	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
men	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
some	O
bedding	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
step	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
(	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
Adshead	O
had	O
thrown	O
his	O
bundle	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
Diot-street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
opposite	O
the	O
Turk's-head	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Charlotte-street	O
the	O
man	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
bundle	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Oldham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
till	O
the	O
man	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
inside	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
Leadbetter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
Alsworth	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
Alsworth	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
where	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
two	O
people	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
one	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
they	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
chapel	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Adshead	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
put	O
down	O
their	O
bundles	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Adshead	O
,	O
stand	O
a	O
little	O
aside	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
have	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
whispered	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
these	O
bundles	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
bundles	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Bellamy	O
lived	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
would	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
on	O
our	O
backs	O
;	O
some	O
things	O
tumbled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
Adshead	O
put	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
some	O
in	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
that	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
bundles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
chose	O
it	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Bannister	O
watched	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
till	O
they	O
stopt	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bannister	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
pick	O
the	O
bundles	O
up	O
?	O
Bannister	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
upon	O
their	O
backs	O
.	O
Adshead	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
myself	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
burglary	O
.	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
MASCADO	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
CAR	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
DA	I-pers
SILVA	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
PERRIRA	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
April	O
18th	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
some	O
beef-steaks	O
and	O
mutton-chops	O
for	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
surprised	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
did	O
not	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
nice	O
clean	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
He	O
desired	O
very	O
particularly	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
clean	O
tankard	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
like	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
scarlet	O
and	O
gold	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
star	O
on	O
one	O
breast	O
and	O
a	O
diamond	O
cross	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
name	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Da	O
Silva	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
eat	O
plentifully	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
desired	O
several	O
times	O
they	O
did	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
he	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
his	O
reckoning	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Walpole	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fieldings	I-pers
after	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
information	O
:	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
pounds	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
beef	O
steak	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
the	O
landlord	O
had	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
beef	O
steaks	O
and	O
mutton	O
chops	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
both	O
got	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
nice	O
clean	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
particularly	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
under	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
particularly	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
I	O
was	O
eating	O
my	O
supper	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
his	O
friends	O
never	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
eat	O
all	O
himself	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
us	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
we	O
refused	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
importuning	O
my	O
friend	O
he	O
drank	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asking	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
once	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
but	O
our	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
before	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
me	O
will	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
me	O
will	O
have	O
fresh	O
and	O
fresh	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
captain	O
?	O
(	O
the	O
landlord	O
had	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
)	O
they	O
said	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
the	O
landlord	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
captain	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
office	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
we	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
about	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
that	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Walpole	O
's	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
your	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
person	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
;	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
tankard	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
weighted	O
it	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
dress	O
had	O
he	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
buttoned	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
George	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
duplicate	O
in	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
-	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
or	O
five-months	O
;	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lain	O
there	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
came	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
discharged	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
search	O
being	O
made	O
at	O
his	O
lodging	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Heley	O
take	O
several	O
papers	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Walpole	O
's	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
the	O
duplicate	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
pawn	O
the	O
tankard	O
:	O
call	O
my	O
landlady	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Savage	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
quiet	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
son	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
pretty	O
handsome	O
sometimes	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
in	O
scarlet	O
and	O
gold	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
423	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
London	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
between	O
mother	O
Redcap	O
's	O
and	O
Kentish	B-place
Town	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
and	O
Burton	O
the	O
witness	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
;	O
Burton	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
he	O
jumped	O
into	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
brandished	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
then	O
;	O
Jones	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
darkish	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
lamps	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
in	O
finding	O
the	O
person	O
or	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
witness	O
or	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
distinguished	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
chocolate	O
coloured	O
cloaths	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
some	O
difficulty	O
about	O
delivering	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
up	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
know	O
Burton	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
however	O
as	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
two	O
foot-pads	O
;	O
one	O
came	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
one	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
Rose	O
kept	O
them	O
in	O
talk	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
did	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
accurately	O
what	O
passed	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
Rose	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
know	O
Burton	O
too	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
Burton	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
Burton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
fellow-apprentice	O
s	O
to	O
an	O
arts-master	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Jones	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
collared	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
away	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
his	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
money	O
into	O
Jones	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
Jones	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
next	O
night	O
for	O
having	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
our	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
-	O
Standard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
beadle	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
cofined	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
eighteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
lad	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
four	O
years	O
of	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
proficient	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
workman	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
capable	O
of	O
getting	O
his	O
livelihood	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
his	O
conduct	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
honestly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hanley	I-pers
,	O
May	O
12th	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Hanley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
New	O
Bond	B-place
Street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
articles	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
Morgan	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
425	O
,	O
426	O
,	O
427	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BARRETT	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CHERRY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
commiting	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Ann	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
16th	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
47	O
.	O
Old	O
Bethlem	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Sherrard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
at	O
Temple	B-place
Bar	I-place
,	O
at	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
company	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
within	O
compass	O
;	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
jumped	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
very	O
furiously	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
threw	O
down	O
directly	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
pulled	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
some	O
by	O
my	O
hands	O
and	O
others	O
by	O
my	O
feet	O
.	O
I	O
soon	O
fainted	O
by	O
their	O
pulling	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
me	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
seat	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
standing	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
one	O
sitting	O
opposite	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
doing	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
my	O
husband	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
which	O
that	O
was	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
his	O
private	O
parts	O
in	O
yours	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
screamed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quiet	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
confusion	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
my	O
apron	O
string	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
any	O
thing	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
using	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
actual	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
indeed	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
the	O
men	O
kept	O
hollowing	O
and	O
hooting	O
inside	O
and	O
outside	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
a	O
brother	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
more	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
pulling	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
coachman	O
did	O
not	O
drive	O
up	O
the	O
main	O
street	O
.	O
They	O
hauled	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
as	O
they	O
chose	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
men	O
or	O
boys	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
fathers	O
or	O
mothers	O
or	O
wives	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
men	O
,	O
have	O
humanity	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
lain	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
lye	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
cursing	O
,	O
swearing	O
and	O
hallowing	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
no	O
particular	O
answer	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
lain	O
with	O
twice	O
:	O
when	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
plain	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
punctual	O
to	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
circumstances	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
entered	O
your	O
body	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopt	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
by	O
the	O
mob	O
upon	O
my	O
screaming	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
drove	O
me	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
clergyman	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
men	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
themselves	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
accordingly	O
taken	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
They	O
owned	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
they	O
owned	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
employment	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
marshall	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
before	O
her	O
marriage	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
spent	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
with	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
,	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
supped	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hargrave	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
stage	O
coaches	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
coach	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
brother	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
himself	O
getting	O
in	O
when	O
the	O
coachman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
rushed	O
in	O
immediately	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
brother	O
wanted	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sherrard	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
sister	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Mercer-street	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hargrave	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
their	O
return	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
coach	O
on	O
the	O
stand	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
helped	O
his	O
sister	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
to	O
Old	O
Bethlem	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
whereupon	O
about	O
nine	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
from	O
their	O
appearance	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
they	O
had	O
hired	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
insisted	O
on	O
being	O
drove	O
to	O
Old	O
Bethlem	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
rushed	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
seized	O
one	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
drove	O
off	O
immediately	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
furious	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
That	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
coachman	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Coleman	O
that	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Magpie	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
Cherry	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
rushed	O
into	O
the	O
coach.	O
``	O
Michael	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
by	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
from	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
!	O
that	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
going	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
stopt	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
men	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
off	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
jumped	O
out	O
,	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
knew	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Old	O
Bethlem	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
clergyman	O
came	O
by	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
573	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
direction	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
had	O
let	O
the	O
step	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Barrat	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
eyes	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
pull	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
accompany	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
drove	O
with	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
down	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
the	O
horses	O
could	O
go	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Magpie	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
husband	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
Barrat	O
and	O
Cherry	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Swetman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
cousin	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
lodged	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
nurse	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
afflicted	O
with	O
fits	O
at	O
times	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Saffory	O
the	O
surgeon	O
to	O
attend	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
produced	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
almost	O
new	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
torn	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
with	O
several	O
cuts	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
she	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
were	O
torn	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
''	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
knife	O
when	O
they	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
kill	O
her	O
nor	O
cut	O
her	O
clothes	O
.	O
Barrett	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Cherry	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
;	O
we	O
hired	O
a	O
coach	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Catharine-street	O
;	O
we	O
stopt	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
our	O
coach	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
Sherrard	O
swore	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
out	O
by	O
fair	O
means	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
drove	O
off	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
where	O
we	O
went	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
drive	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
sung	O
a	O
song	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
of	O
the	O
huntsman	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
bore	O
chorus	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
besides	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
nine	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
going	O
from	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
we	O
stopt	O
there	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
She	O
began	O
to	O
hallow	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
down	O
Houndsditch	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
did	O
her	O
any	O
injury	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Cherry	O
's	O
mother	O
in-law	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Cherry	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
Barratt	O
has	O
said	O
is	O
true	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
us	O
four	O
bloody	O
thiever	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
crap	O
us	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
then	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
alias	O
Barber	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offended	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
;	O
she	O
sung	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
agreeable	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Cherry	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
matter	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
Cherry	O
and	O
Smith	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
Barret	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Waterman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
Cherry	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Morris	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
both	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
Morris	O
also	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
Barrat	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
stopt	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Cherry	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Cherry	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
damage	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
would	O
cost	O
20	O
l.	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
raise	O
that	O
;	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
prosecute	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
rigour	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
dinner	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
Allen	O
said	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
at	O
Cherry	O
's	O
,	O
Price	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Cherry	O
's	O
mother	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
desired	O
the	O
witness	O
to	O
accompany	O
her	O
to	O
Cherry	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Cherry	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
prosecuting	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
only	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
deposed	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
conversation	O
about	O
money	O
.	O
Cherry	O
's	O
father	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
asked	O
20	O
l.	O
to	O
compromise	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
twenty	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
428	O
,	O
429	O
,	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
EDWARD	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
and	O
FRANCES	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Abigail	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
metal	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
covered	O
with	O
black	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
mode	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
love	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abigail	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
black	O
mode	O
cloak	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
16th	O
.	O
+	O
Hannah	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
walk	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Great	O
Rider-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
does	O
not	O
follow	O
any	O
business	O
.	O
Coming	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
first	O
five	O
fields	O
of	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
three	O
footpads	O
,	O
Adams	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
madam	O
!	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
out	O
your	O
brains	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
both	O
say	O
that	O
?	O
Sherman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
which	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
your	O
head	O
?	O
Sherman	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
moon-light	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
something	O
else	O
:	O
they	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
riffle	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
watch	O
;	O
a	O
third	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
untied	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
towards	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
mode	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
love	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Sherman	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cocked	O
hat	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
same	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
cloak	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Sherman	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
consider	O
one	O
man	O
may	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Sherman	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
among	O
a	O
thousand	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
Jones	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
lads	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Andrews	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
jeweller	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
advertised	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3333	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
remarkable	O
number	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fieldings	I-pers
,	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
Jones	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Senhouse	I-pers
.	O
After	O
these	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Siday	I-pers
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
chain	O
there	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
chain	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Sherman	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Siday	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
Senhouse	O
.	O
In	O
Holborn-court	O
,	O
Charlotte-street	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Siday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn-court	O
,	O
Charlotte-street	O
;	O
last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
May	O
,	O
Adams	O
,	O
Waters	O
,	O
and	O
Burton	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Waters	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
eat	O
;	O
(	O
Adams	O
and	O
Burton	O
were	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Waters	O
brought	O
some	O
clothes	O
)	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
ribs	O
of	O
lamb	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Adams	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
chain	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
concerning	O
a	O
robbery	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
Adams	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
rob	O
a	O
man	O
then	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
hard	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
snatched	O
her	O
cloak	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
cap	O
came	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Siday	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
and	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
three	O
thieves	O
and	O
treat	O
them	O
with	O
ribs	O
of	O
lamb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
chain	O
left	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Siday	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Frances	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
cloak	O
from	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
apprehended	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
that	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
Adams	O
,	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
Five	O
Fields	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
two	O
gentlewomen	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
stopped	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
their	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
pistols	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
One	O
,	O
Adams	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
cloak	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
Jones	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
Adams	O
the	O
cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Siday	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
.	O
Burton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
another	O
way	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
coming	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
two	O
pistols	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sherman	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
two	O
pistols	O
?	O
Sherman	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pistol	O
put	O
to	O
both	O
our	O
heads	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
from	O
?	O
Sherman	O
.	O
From	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
pound	O
.	O
Adam	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Burton	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
fields	O
we	O
met	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
Burton	O
drawed	O
back	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
claped	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
.	O
For	O
Adams	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
inn	O
,	O
at	O
Linster	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
waiter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
at	O
London	O
?	O
Abrahams	O
.	O
Only	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
called	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glover	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burtoff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Dobney	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
near	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carver	O
and	O
gilder	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
52	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
Adams	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
an	O
under	O
clerk	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1771	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burtoff	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
entrusted	O
to	O
receive	O
and	O
pay	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
and	O
industrious	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
leave	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Fenton	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
,	O
not	O
returning	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Clerkenwell	O
Green	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
buckle-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
above	O
a	O
twelve	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
195	O
,	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
-	O
Fenton	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
.	O
For	O
Jones	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
Hospital	O
:	O
Jones	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
about	O
last	O
Sunday	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
up	O
his	O
indentures	O
?	O
Wilby	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
absconded	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
ADAMS	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
JONES	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
PALMER	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
431	O
,	O
432	O
,	O
433	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
CAIN	I-pers
,	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SPUR	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
pillow	O
bier	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
one	O
stock	O
,	O
one	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
apron	O
with	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
three	O
odd	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
three	O
other	O
napkins	O
,	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
three	O
old	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
counterpane	O
,	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
one	O
coloured	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
napkins	O
,	O
three	O
other	O
aprons	O
,	O
three	O
towels	O
,	O
one	O
white	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spurr	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
white	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
napkin	O
,	O
one	O
pillow-bier	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
one	O
stock	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
napkin	O
,	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
apron	O
with	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
three	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
three	O
odd	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
counterpane	O
,	O
five	O
towels	O
,	O
one	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
coloured	O
apron	O
,	O
other	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
18th	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
lord	O
Beauchamp	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
now	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
militia	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
regiment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
returned	O
post	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
box	O
with	O
Humphry	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
waggon	O
or	O
coach	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
since	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Wotton	O
left	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
it	O
the	O
Saturday	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
so	O
heavy	O
loaded	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
waggoner	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
man	O
is	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Cain	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
Wotton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
packed	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
(	O
repeating	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
)	O
these	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
lost	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
t	O
he	O
Ambury	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Tothil-fields	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Everet	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Easter	O
Eve	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
and	O
several	O
women	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
cardinals	O
in	O
particular	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Spur	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
Wells	O
in	O
Ship-yard	O
,	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
Easter	O
week	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
having	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wotton	O
's	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wotton	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
field	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
loose	O
earth	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Cain	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
cloaks	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
three	O
soldiers	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
men	O
into	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spur	I-pers
's	O
room	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
these	O
men	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
burst	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
three	O
soldiers	O
are	O
?	O
Everet	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Tothill	O
Street	O
,	O
last	O
Easter	O
;	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
Cain	O
and	O
Wells	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
aprons	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
them	O
of	O
any	O
room	O
to	O
set	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Esther	B-pers
Paters	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
Wells	O
and	O
Cain	B-pers
the	O
way	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
bundles	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
for	O
them	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
money	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
apron	O
for	O
Esther	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
;	O
the	O
soldiers	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Eben	B-pers
.	I-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Wells	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Wells	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
given	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
gown	O
of	O
Spur	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
of	O
Wells	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Spooner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sixteen	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Jortan	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
gown	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Spurr	O
.	O
Well	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Cain	O
brought	O
the	O
box	O
into	O
the	O
barracks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
Jerry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
let	O
your	O
wife	O
pawn	O
something	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
Cain	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
somebody	O
that	O
will	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Cain	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Spur	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
these	O
men	O
were	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
two	O
gowns	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
sister	O
was	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
money	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
CAIN	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
SPUR	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
WELLS	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
Years	O
.	O
434	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
HUTSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Silvanus	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Silvanus	O
.	O
Silvanus	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
;	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
lower	O
apartment	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
getting	O
supper	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
ill	O
at	O
an	O
hospital	O
;	O
my	O
children	O
were	O
at	O
nurse	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
blankets	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
blankets	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
's	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
Sunday	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
accord	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
blankets	O
were	O
up	O
George	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
the	O
two	O
lower	O
rooms	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
afterwards	O
till	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Hill	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
blankets	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
my	O
wife	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
or	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
afterwards	O
why	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
her	O
blankets	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
without	O
she	O
brought	O
somebody	O
to	O
prove	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
without	O
she	O
brought	O
somebody	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
children	O
were	O
crying	O
for	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
get	O
any	O
body	O
then	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
buy	O
bread	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Hill	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
Hill	O
immediately	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
were	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle	O
Alley	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
heel-cutter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
twenty	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
misdemeanor	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
free	O
with	O
her	O
tail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
sometimes	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
children	O
there	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
her	O
father	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
work-house	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
work-house	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
buss	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Nanny	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
gate-keeper	O
of	O
the	O
work-house	O
.	O
Hill	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Kitchens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
near	O
eleven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
loose	O
with	O
her	O
tail	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
looseness	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Teel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
this	O
man	O
fetched	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
.	O
Her	O
father	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
workhouse	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
from	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Touchberry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
four	O
years	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
wild	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Hill	O
say	O
if	O
her	O
father	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
dishonest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
no	O
harm	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
natured	O
with	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BARRY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
steal-from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
earthen	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
what	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
a	O
good	O
or	O
a	O
wicked	O
thing	O
.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
A	O
wicked	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
Bow	B-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
last	O
Saturday	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
you	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
again	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
but	O
once	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
home	O
?	O
Ingram	O
.	O
My	O
parents	O
live	O
in	O
Robinhood	O
lane	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
over	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
six-pence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
grand-mother	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
his	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
grandmother	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
and	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
?	O
Ingram	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
overtook	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
run	O
along	O
my	O
girl	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
talk	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
what	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
talked	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
gone	O
he	O
run	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
little	O
plate	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
apron	O
that	O
I	O
worked	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
dish	O
?	O
Ingram	O
.	O
A	O
penny	O
earthen	O
dish	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
a	O
field	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
doing	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
grass	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
shall	O
lose	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
took	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Murphy	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
cried	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
asked	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
along	O
Bow	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
immediately	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
apron	O
and	O
dish	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
;	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Bromley	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Bromley	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
cover	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
stooping	O
to	O
buckle	O
her	O
shoe	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
shillings	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
rag	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
sewed	O
a	O
seam	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
rob	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
girl	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Coe	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
poor	O
girl	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
by	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
description	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shilling	O
drop	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
coarse	O
apron	O
,	O
dish	O
and	O
rag	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
girl	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
and	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
girl	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
God	O
Almighty	O
knows	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
-	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
callico-ground	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
six-pence	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
victuals	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
to	O
receive	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
436	O
.	O
(	O
1st	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Morocco	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
lock	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tweezers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
