TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
1772	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
+	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKSTONE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Loftus	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Bucklee	I-pers
James	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Longes	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lack	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Hancox	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Day	I-pers
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hett	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
William	B-pers
Meades	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Beales	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
William	B-pers
Almond	I-pers
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
108	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
NEWLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
December	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Hugh	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
drawing	O
out	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Another	O
boy	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
dropt	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
a	O
collier	O
,	O
at	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
ashore	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
109	O
,	O
110	O
,	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BURKS	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ANN	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Maxamillian	I-pers
MILLER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
twenty-two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
fifteen	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
castor	O
tops	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
bowl	O
of	O
a	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Collins	O
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
112	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
(	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
RIMER	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ANN	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Maxamillian	O
MILLER	O
(	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
defect	O
in	O
evidence	O
in	O
this	O
trial	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
(	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
RYMER	I-pers
(	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
)	O
and	O
ANN	B-pers
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Maxamillian	O
MILLER	O
(	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s	O
and	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
defect	O
of	O
evidence	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Maxamilian	O
Miller	O
,	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
102	O
.	O
113	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
(	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
)	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOBBS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Hasson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
watch	O
in	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Hasson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
||	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Hobbs	O
,	O
tried	O
No	O
.	O
775	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
114	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
(	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
)	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
BURN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
walnut-tree	O
cabinet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
tortoishel	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
mounted	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
snuff-box	O
of	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
,	O
mounted	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
medal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
nine	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
eight	O
silver	O
groats	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
threepences	O
and	O
16	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
China-row	B-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
;	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
bolt	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
also	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
affording	O
room	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
hand	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
sash	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
thrown	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
by	O
finding	O
the	O
cabinet	O
and	O
papers	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
seek	O
whose	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
cabinet	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
;	O
it	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
[	O
repeating	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
cabinet	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
was	O
locked	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
their	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
too	O
the	O
shutter	O
and	O
screwed	O
the	O
sash	O
about	O
dusk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
rung	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
shutters	O
were	O
put	O
too	O
;	O
the	O
bolt	O
was	O
forced	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
up	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
go	O
;	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
to	O
fetch	O
out	O
a	O
bible	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
cabinet	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bell	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
sink	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
screw	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
marks	O
of	O
feet	O
upon	O
the	O
iron	O
rails	O
that	O
are	O
before	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
-	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
four	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
cabinet	O
[	O
producing	O
it	O
]	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
papers	O
lying	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
cabinet	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
picture	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Tinsdale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
City-marshal	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hue-and-cry	O
of	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Collins	B-pers
the	O
evidence	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
lodge	O
and	O
searched	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
hue-and-cry	O
was	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
their	O
having	O
robbed	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
.	O
]	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
Parker	O
five	O
new	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
six-pence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
Burn	O
or	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
concealed	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
searched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
seat	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
crown-piece	O
,	O
[	O
producing	O
it	O
]	O
the	O
prisoners	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
new	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pences	O
in	O
the	O
cabinet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
cabinet	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Burke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Collins	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
clothes	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
sold	O
Burn	O
a	O
Bath	O
surtout	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
two	O
crown	O
pieces	O
and	O
a	O
six-pence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
new	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Parker	O
afterwards	O
bought	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
thirty-two	O
new	O
six-pences	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
Collins	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
persons	O
?	O
Burke	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Harwood	O
.	O
What	O
number	O
of	O
new	O
six	O
pences	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
exactly	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
the	O
number	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
collect	O
crowns	O
of	O
any	O
particular	O
reign	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Because	O
these	O
four	O
crowns	O
are	O
all	O
Charles	O
the	O
Second	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
particular	O
marks	O
by	O
which	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Burke	O
again	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
new	O
money	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
!	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Downs	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Downs	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
's	O
money	O
;	O
a	O
boy	O
seeing	O
this	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
this	O
alarm	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tinsdale	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hope	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
Collins	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
They	O
owed	O
me	O
a	O
trifling	O
score	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
expected	O
some	O
money	O
belonging	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
by	O
Nancy	B-pers
Everet	I-pers
;	O
she	O
always	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Miller	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Everet	O
come	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
discharge	O
their	O
scores	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
disappointed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
they	O
owe	O
you	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
They	O
owed	O
me	O
some	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
others	O
15	O
d.	O
Collins	O
owed	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
much	O
liquor	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
porter	O
,	O
some	O
half	O
in	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
they	O
frequented	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
Ever	O
since	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
Collins	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
party	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sawyer	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
his	O
way	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Burn	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
owe	O
you	O
a	O
score	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Little	O
Burke	O
,	O
Rimer	O
,	O
Parker	O
and	O
Collins	O
owed	O
me	O
a	O
score	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Hope	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to-bed	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Rooke	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
Collins	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
till	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
there	O
till	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
Collins	O
was	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Collins	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
about	O
going	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
Nothing	O
more	O
than	O
common	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Burn	O
and	O
Parker	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
places	O
about	O
Westminster	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
bolt	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
pulled	O
off	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
two	O
chissels	O
;	O
the	O
nail	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bolt	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
over	O
the	O
bell	O
to	O
prevent	O
its	O
ringing	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Burn	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
Parker	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
brass-headed	O
iron	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
.	O
Parker	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
again	O
almost	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
such	O
a	O
little	O
desk	O
as	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
cabinet	O
open	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
crown	O
pieces	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
either	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
new	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pences	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
two-guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
picture	O
inside	O
it	O
like	O
a	O
bracelet	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
stone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
medal	O
that	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Popes	O
.	O
We	O
threw	O
the	O
desk	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
papers	O
too	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
divide	O
the	O
money	O
regularly	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
crown	O
pieces	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
Parker	O
one	O
crown	O
to	O
buy	O
his	O
cloaths	O
;	O
Burn	O
had	O
two	O
crowns	O
of	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
Parker	O
had	O
the	O
sixpences	O
and	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
crowns	O
underneath	O
the	O
seat	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
drawn	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
.	O
We	O
changed	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
crowns	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
just	O
above	O
Mr.	O
Burke	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
two	O
crowns	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
eight	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Parker	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
I	O
some	O
new	O
silver	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
silver	O
you	O
paid	O
away	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Burke	O
's	O
shop	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
snuffbox	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
Burn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
crown	O
pieces	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
that	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Parker	O
's	O
Def	O
ence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
at	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Horns	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
we	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
a-piece	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
new	O
silver	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
buy	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
silver	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
at	O
Chatham	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a-board	O
a	O
ship	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
Burn	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Hope	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
Collins	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
Collins	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
buy	O
their	O
great	O
coats	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
their	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
one	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
Collins	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lend	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
then	O
two	O
crowns	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hooke	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
116	O
,	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TIREMAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
nine	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
York-buildings-water-works	B-pers
company	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
nine	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Holt	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
boots	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
Tireman	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
half-crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
O'Brien	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
O'Brien	I-pers
.	O
||	O
Andrew	B-pers
O'Brien	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Porter-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair-dresser	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
parlour	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
who	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
appeared	O
confused	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
boy	O
flung	O
his	O
hat	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
flung	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
maid	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
two	O
coats	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
bundled	O
up	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
for	O
my	O
maid	O
to	O
brush	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
your	O
maid	O
was	O
confused	O
;	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
attribute	O
that	O
to	O
?	O
O'Brien	O
.	O
Finding	O
the	O
boy	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
O'Brien	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
brushed	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
two	O
coats	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
always	O
hung	O
;	O
no	O
person	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
after	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
or	O
down	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Fowler	O
.	O
Shut	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
between	O
the	O
chairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
coats	O
and	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
they	O
had	O
hung	O
on	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
boy	O
threw	O
his	O
hat	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
body	O
hear	O
,	O
so	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
:	O
two	O
lads	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
body	O
hear	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
that	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Marine	O
Society	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
merchantman	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
things	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
errands	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
120	O
,	O
121	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROADES	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
122	O
,	O
123	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
RANDALL	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Christmas	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
across	B-place
the	I-place
Park	I-place
from	I-place
Knightsbridge	I-place
;	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
under	O
the	O
trees	O
by	O
the	O
bason	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Randall	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Ward	O
stopt	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
lamps	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
Tooth	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Tooth	O
.	O
A	O
fine	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
well	O
?	O
Tooth	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
regimentals	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
that	O
Randall	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sixteen	O
years	O
old	O
next	O
July	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Tooth	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Park-lane	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
Park-gate	O
.	O
Knowing	O
them	O
both	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
dogg	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
at	O
Hyde-park	O
corner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
aunt	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
deserters	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
regiment	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
by	O
their	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
lamps	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
lamps	O
in	O
Park-lane	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
whom	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
pretty	O
briskly	O
,	O
so	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
your	O
aunt	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
is	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
Randall	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
Ward	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Randall	O
.	O
(	O
Describing	O
them	O
wrong	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
searched	O
;	O
one	O
had	O
three	O
six-pences	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
horse-grenadier	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
Hyde-park	O
corner	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
is	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
to	O
Hyde-park	O
corner	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
About	O
fifty	O
yards	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Salmon	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
just	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
.	O
Randall	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nearer	O
the	O
Park	O
than	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
comrades	O
in	O
Brigg-street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
pretty	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
below	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Randall	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
;	O
Salmon	O
described	O
our	O
dress	O
wrong	O
.	O
Salmon	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
garters	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
by	O
the	O
appearance	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
turned	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
dark-coloured	O
stockings	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Brigg-street	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
our	O
serjeant	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lees	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
soldiers	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
witnesses	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
their	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Brigg-street	O
.	O
Lees	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
of	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
trial	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
called	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
first	O
mention	O
these	O
two	O
people	O
?	O
Lees	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Salmon	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
Brigg-street	O
is	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Be	O
cautious	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
true	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
question	O
-	O
After	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Park-lane	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Brigg-street	O
to	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Park-gate	O
towards	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
not	O
going	O
from	O
Brigg-street	O
towards	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
124	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BISHOP	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
's	O
in	O
Hoxton	B-place
fields	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
that	O
were	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
portmanteau	O
was	O
carried	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
one	O
,	O
three	O
neck-cloths	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
piece	O
of	O
nankeen	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
that	O
morning	O
before	O
day-light	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
since	O
till	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
his	O
absconding	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
,	O
near	O
Fullmore	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
born	O
a	O
threshing	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
by	O
my	O
marks	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hans	I-pers
at	O
Staines	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
coat	O
at	O
Godalmin	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Castle	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
when	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
moved	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
John	O
Castle	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
for	O
Bishop	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
Fullmore	O
,	O
and	O
Staines	O
,	O
with	O
Castle	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
at	O
Staines	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
coat	O
at	O
Godalmin	O
.	O
They	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
one	O
bed	O
John	B-pers
Hanas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
at	O
Staines	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
owned	O
it	O
because	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
125	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
china	O
punch-bowl	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
sheet	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
lives	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
We	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
about	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
sheet	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sheet	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
stopt	O
for	O
another	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
sheet	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
having	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wildman	O
's	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sheet	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Wildman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
sheet	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
the	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
released	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
126	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUNNETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Betheridge	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Betheridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
saw	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
's	O
,	O
Black-friars	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
saw	O
was	O
found	O
pawned	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Simons	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
in	O
Knightrider-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
this	O
saw	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
distressed	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
saw	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
printer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
,	O
at	O
Black-friars	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
appeared	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
HERBERT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
sewing	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
sewing-silk-dyer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
weekly	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
believe	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
my	O
dye-house	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
I	O
discovered	O
some	O
silk	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brick	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
parcel	O
we	O
had	O
in	O
hand	O
t	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dyed	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
took-off	O
;	O
the	O
gum	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
dye	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
brick	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
little	O
lad	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Hord	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
that	O
has	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
silk	O
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
Hord	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
discovered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
silk	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
produce	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
gum	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
Horton	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hord	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
came	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
detect	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
silk	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
silk	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stoop	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
silk	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Pilgrim	O
the	O
foreman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Pilgrim	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
we	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
silk	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
frivolous	O
excuses	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
indicted	O
on	O
his	O
delivering	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
silk	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
in	O
hand	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
Pilgrim	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
that	O
very	O
silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
silk	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
hand	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
Pilgrim	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
silk	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
distressed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
necessary	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
immediately	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
the	O
silk	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eyrewater	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
and	O
Aaron	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
Dec.	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
George	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
livery-stable	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
in	O
a	O
one-horse	O
chaise	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
the	B-place
King's-road	I-place
,	O
we	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
star-light	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
sixty	O
yards	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
Mathews	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
clear	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
bank	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
sixty	O
or	O
seventy	O
men	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
at	O
the	O
Brown-bear	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
pick	O
the	O
men	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
my	O
information	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
,	O
with	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Mathews	O
.	O
They	O
shewed	O
me	O
up	O
a	O
long	O
passage	O
.	O
This	O
John	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
stood	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
looks	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
such	O
a	O
coat	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hopwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
twenty-three	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
under	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
.	O
He	O
entered	O
volunteer	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
pressing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whitehouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
The	O
father	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
prisoner	O
work	O
?	O
Whitehouse	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
he	O
work	O
for	O
?	O
Whitehouse	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
wore	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
might	O
you	O
not	O
mistake	O
a	O
person	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
very	O
gently	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
their	O
voices	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
particularly	O
;	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
his	O
voice	O
now	O
;	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
clear	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
(	O
the	O
father	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
dutiful	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
last	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
certain	O
then	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
evening	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
certain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
At	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
coat	O
did	O
he	O
wear	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
wore	O
any	O
but	O
blue	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
he	O
wore	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
and	O
trowsers	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
scarlet	O
serge	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
crimson	O
serge	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Bedford	O
carrier	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
cloth	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
waggon	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	B-place
Barnet	I-place
and	I-place
Whetstone	I-place
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
truss	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
Jones	O
and	O
Co.	O
No	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Swinston	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Bedford	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
William	I-pers
Stonehouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
Jones	O
,	O
Habbard	O
and	O
Burd	O
.	O
I	O
measured	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
porter	O
to	O
be	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
of	O
nap	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
mix	O
'd	O
lightish	O
colour	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
fifteen	O
of	O
crimson	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
scarlet	O
serge	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
Paul	B-pers
the	O
porter	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
White-hart	O
,	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
nap	O
cloth	O
were	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
measure	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
cut	O
up	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
seal	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
serge	O
was	O
deficient	O
,	O
only	O
six	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
one	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
was	O
remaining	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
that	O
quantity	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
entered	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
carrier	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Jones	O
and	O
Co	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
parcel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pack	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
to	O
the	O
Bedford	O
carrier	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
book	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ambridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
Bedford	O
waggon	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
cloth	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Swinston	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
between	O
Whetstone	O
and	O
Barnet	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Barnet	O
hill	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Whetstone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
staid	O
behind	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
Ambridge	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
waggon	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
passengers	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
about	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
Ambridge	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
thereabouts	O
?	O
Ambridge	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
empty	O
flatts	O
that	O
we	O
put	O
butter	O
in	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
shake	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
beyond	O
Whetstone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
truss	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
truss	O
pretty	O
heavy	O
?	O
Ambridge	O
.	O
It	O
weighed	O
something	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Barner	O
hill	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
something	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
somebody	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
waggon	O
with	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
thought	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass-founder	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three-Pigeons	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
parcel	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
one	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
that	O
was	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
crimson	O
serge	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
fetch	O
him	O
the	O
outside	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
wanted	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
Puller	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
words	O
arose	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
breakfast	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
landlady	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
in	O
carrying	O
up	O
that	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
stopt	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
serge	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Laws	B-pers
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stocks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three-Pigeons	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Puller	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
call	O
Puller	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
crimson	O
serge	O
under	O
the	O
bolster	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
next	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
serge	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Stonehouse	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
quality	O
and	O
colour	O
as	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Laughar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stocks	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
serge	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
below	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
more	O
right	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
Wenmore	O
,	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
party	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
four	O
hours	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
Daily	O
Advertiser	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
apprehend	O
he	O
meant	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
cloth	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Laughar	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
humanity	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Prebble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White-horse	O
,	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
on	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
lodge	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
spiteful	O
person	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
measured	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
was	O
light	O
cloth	O
;	O
one	O
17	O
yards	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
16	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
serge	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pinmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Prebble	O
acquainted	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
cloth	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Stonehouse	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
number	O
on	O
this	O
cloth	O
.	O
The	O
seal	O
and	O
number	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
by	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
cloth	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
Prebble	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
cloth	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
the	O
Bedford	O
waggon	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
parcel	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Bedford	O
waggon	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
Whetstone	O
and	O
Barnet	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
was	O
very	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Causeway	O
;	O
found	O
it	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
to	O
pretend	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
hay-carts	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
bring	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
colour	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
piece	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
man	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hay-cart	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Prebble	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
advertised	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
going	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
Pigeons	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
cloth	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
waggon	O
when	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Jury	O
to	O
the	O
waggoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
in	O
the	O
situation	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
to	O
fall	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
without	O
its	O
being	O
removed	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Ambridge	I-pers
.	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
flats	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Stonehouse	O
.	O
Six	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
is	O
missing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
WOADLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-market	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
behind	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
thump	O
upon	O
the	O
board	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
mouse	O
buttock	O
of	O
beef	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
beef	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
beef	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
lame	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wigeon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
teal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apoulterer	O
in	O
Oxford-market	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
wigeon	O
and	O
a	O
teal	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Butcher	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
buttock	O
of	O
beef	O
;	O
my	O
wigeon	O
and	O
teal	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
the	O
teal	O
had	O
the	O
head	O
partly	O
tore	O
off	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
wigeon	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
hen	O
wigeon	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
home	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
stunk	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
accept	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
131	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
ANGLE	I-pers
and	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
COTTER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
book	O
,	O
bound	O
in	O
red	O
leather	O
,	O
intitled	O
``	O
The	O
Daily	O
Journal	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
year	O
1766	O
.	O
''	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
steel	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davids	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Dec.	O
15	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davids	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
writer	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
December	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
foolish	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Angle	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
liquor	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Angle	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
Angle	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
lodges	O
with	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Angle	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
sufficient	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Davids	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
liquor	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
Davids	O
.	O
A	O
two-shilling	O
bowl	O
of	O
negus	O
.	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Angle	O
put	O
the	O
change	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
Cotter	O
played	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
change	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Davids	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
your	O
breeches	O
waistband	O
unbuttoned	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Davids	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Angle	O
unbuttoned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mention	O
you	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
book	O
and	O
watch	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Davids	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
watch	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noakes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
a	O
barber	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
robbed	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
underneath	O
the	O
drawers	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
papers	O
all	O
loose	O
;	O
the	O
papers	O
had	O
all	O
been	O
examined	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Angle	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
watch	O
!	O
said	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
I	O
shall	O
search	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
hesitated	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
On	O
examining	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
I	O
found	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
this	O
man	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
a	O
letter	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pocket-book	O
and	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Angle	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
woman	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
picked	O
us	O
both	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
farthing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
but	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
half	O
pence	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
his	O
watch	O
with	O
us	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
our	O
directions	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Cottor	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
Angle	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GOLDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
fish-skin	O
spectacle-case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pensioner	O
at	O
Greenwich-college	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
High	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Green-bank	O
,	O
Wapping	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
way	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
ride	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
ride	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
he	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
spectacles	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
down	O
to	O
Holborn	O
;	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
channel	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
drunk	O
,	O
very	O
drunk	O
!	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
shocking	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
causeway	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
exposed	O
to	O
the	O
carts	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
at	O
Bartler	O
's	O
buildings	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
reared	O
up	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
take	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
walk	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
it	O
struck	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
these	O
fellows	O
have	O
in	O
view	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
snatch	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
run	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spectacles	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spectacles	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
man	O
quite	O
drunk	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Wapping	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
as	O
a	O
security	O
for	O
paying	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
flag	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Truss	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Truss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wharfinger	O
at	O
the	O
Kennet	B-place
wharf	I-place
,	I-place
Queenhithe	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
warehouses	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
raisins	O
and	O
the	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
slept	O
back	O
a	O
step	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
impudence	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
pardon	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
Malaga	O
raisins	O
,	O
about	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
five	O
we	O
had	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
from	O
Reading	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
sack	O
lay	O
empty	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
work	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
employed	O
about	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
sack	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
jobb	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
two-pence	O
or	O
three-pence	O
.	O
The	O
warehouse	O
is	O
common	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
wind	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
FRESHWATER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
base-metal	O
watch-chain	O
washed	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Drury-lane	B-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
by	B-place
the	I-place
New	I-place
Burying-ground	I-place
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
elevated	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
the	O
woman	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
nor	O
the	O
money	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
together	O
?	O
Morrison	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
familiarities	O
pass	O
?	O
Morrison	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
Then	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
several	O
protestations	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
her	O
bosom	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barrett	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
hanging	O
by	O
her	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
seal	O
was	O
tuck	O
'd	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat-string	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
taking	O
five	O
shillings	O
to	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
swear	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Morrison	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
while	O
you	O
conversed	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Morrison	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
Barrett	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
appeared	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
persuaded	O
of	O
her	O
innocence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
certainly	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shift	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
seemed	O
confused	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
eye	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
used	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
the	O
number	O
and	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
Steward's-rents	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
refusal	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
three	O
watchmen	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	B-pers
BECKET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
case-metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
136	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
TRUEMAN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
leather	O
cloak	O
bags	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
callico	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
eight	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
livery	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
flannel	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
livery	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
socks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
night	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
thread	O
net	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
breakfast-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
shagreen	O
buckle-case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
gauze	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Jeremiah	I-pers
De	I-pers
Sallis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Burrow	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drive	O
the	O
Northampton	O
coach	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Barnet	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
an	O
outside	O
passenger	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
bundle	O
into	O
the	O
boot	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Sadler's-wells	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
himself	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
bundle	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
bundle	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Knight	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
when	O
I	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
path-way	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
The	O
portmanteau	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Sallis	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
two	O
portmanteaus	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
?	O
Knight	O
.	O
One	O
portmanteau	O
with	O
a	O
case	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
?	O
Knight	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
light-coloured	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
on	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
laid	O
it	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
being	O
found	O
?	O
Knight	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Sallis	O
,	O
whose	O
portmanteau	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
at	O
Horton	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Lord	O
Hallifax	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Here	O
are	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
myself	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
some	O
trunks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boots	O
hung	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
nail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
Heley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Card	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
warning	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Northampton	O
fly	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
notice	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
in	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Brown	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Burrow	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Burrow	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
gold	O
knee-buckles	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches-knees	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
he	O
sold	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
an	O
ounce	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
standard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Very	O
genteel	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
wear	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
wore	O
them	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
l.	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
two	O
shirts	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Burrow	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
doubt	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
more	O
might	O
be	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
than	O
there	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ransom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
his	O
honesty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Ransom	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacco-pipe-maker	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hasgrave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
quiet	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Koker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
137	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
SELLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
candlestick	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
formerly	O
;	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Milk	O
street	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
My	O
servants	O
had	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
candlestick	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
candlestick	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
-	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
candlestick	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
seek	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
staid	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
his	O
apprentice	O
called	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
candlestick	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
138	O
,	O
139	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
BANKS	I-pers
and	O
PATRICK	B-pers
FENLEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Minories	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Butcher-row	B-place
,	I-place
Lower	I-place
East-Smithfield	I-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
remnants	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
running	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
into	O
a	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
main	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Fenley	O
by	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
carman	O
's	O
whip	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
mob	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
encreased	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
Fenley	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Nightingale-lane	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
enough	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
?	O
Paxton	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
collared	O
Fenley	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
us	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
Paxton	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
encounter	O
with	O
three	O
?	O
-	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
;	O
seeing	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
.	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
whip	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
the	O
tall	O
man	O
had	O
the	O
horse-whip	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Nightingale-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
men	O
you	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Banks	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
vindicate	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
swore	O
pretty	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
Fenley	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Banks	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Deptford	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
through	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
from	O
here	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
peeping	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
resistance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
lad	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
me	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Fenley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
when	O
this	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
again	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
witness	O
swear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
used	O
to	O
the	O
Sea	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Paxton	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
take	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
for	O
your	O
cloth	O
?	O
Paxton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
colour	O
his	O
face	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
remand	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
prison	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
his	O
face	O
was	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Paxton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
discharge	O
them	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
140	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
LOROSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Manders	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Manders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Aldgate	B-place
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
ringing	O
the	O
bell	O
at	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
He	O
run	O
away	O
straight	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
stript	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
was	O
week	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Shoemaker-row	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
.	O
He	O
stopt	O
a	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
lad	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
then	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
behind	O
a	O
