TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1772	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twelfth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
||	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
||	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
London	O
,	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Russell	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gammon	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
John	B-pers
Knightley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
George	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
David	B-pers
Laing	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Berkett	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fillingham	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
John	B-pers
Livie	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Heymour	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Cleghorne	I-pers
2d	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Exeter	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
John	B-pers
Peavely	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Wyburd	I-pers
694	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SEAMAN	B-pers
HICKMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Oct.	O
6th	O
.	O
+	O
Second	O
Count	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
for	O
stealing	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
6th	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
informed	O
me	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
bespoke	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
names	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
supposed	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
while	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
accordingly	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
swept	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
25	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
shoes	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
the	O
pumps	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
shoes	O
worth	O
5	O
s	O
?	O
Randal	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
nicety	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
what	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
says	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
695	O
,	O
696	O
,	O
697	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARTHA	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
HILL	I-pers
,	O
MARY	B-pers
HUSSEY	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
M'EVOY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
MURDOCK	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Notingham	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
698	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
set	O
with	O
paste	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
699	O
,	O
700	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
printed	O
book	O
,	O
entitled	O
,	O
a	O
collection	O
of	O
ridiculous	O
stories	O
and	O
jests	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Overs	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
701	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SHELDON	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
laced	O
with	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Lucy	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridges-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
day	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
some	O
street	O
in	O
Soho	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
pinned	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
ticket	O
for	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Miss	O
Draper	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
Miss	O
Cooper	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
bid-me	O
pawn	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
next	O
morning	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
my	O
washer-woman	O
in	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
men	O
came	O
after	O
her	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
disturbance	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
what	O
a	O
place	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
warning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
does	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
passing	O
about	O
her	O
calling	O
upon	O
her	O
washer-woman	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
of	O
Draper	O
's	O
name	O
before	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
702	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
five	O
dozen	O
of	O
gold	O
thread	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Mosai	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
703	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PHILIP	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hanger	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
belt	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22d	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
704	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
ROWLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
nankeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wrench	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
705	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
(	O
a	O
black	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Geofrey	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
706	O
,	O
707	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
DRAKE	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
GROVES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Hugh	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
five	O
and	O
three-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hugh	O
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
708	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
French	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Philip	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Philip	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
street	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
bottom	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
parlour	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
inhabited	O
by	O
different	O
tenants	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
only	O
a	O
cellar	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
deducts	O
me	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
year	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
wrenched	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
shutter	O
was	O
open	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
had	O
this	O
apartment	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
rent	O
do	O
you	O
pay	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
Twelve	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
gives	O
me	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chandler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
parlour	O
doors	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
the	O
keys	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
his	O
drawers	O
in	O
his	O
parlour	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
;	O
one	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
was	O
shoved	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shutter	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
se'ennight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
money	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
piece	O
since	O
at	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
it	O
by	O
any	O
name	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
foreign	O
piece	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
French	O
crown	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Hart	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
West-Harding-street	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
Three	O
women	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
change	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
among	O
the	O
five	O
?	O
Thorn	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
clear	O
.	O
-	O
Roman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
Chandler	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
condition	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Pool	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
opposite	O
Chandler	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
effects	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
place	O
fastened	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lodgings	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
.	O
After	O
I	O
left	O
work	O
that	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
,	O
in	O
Newport	O
Market	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	O
Flanagan	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Rogers	O
was	O
in	O
Chandler	O
's	O
apartment	O
;	O
she	O
over	O
persuaded	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Rogers	O
there	O
;	O
Flanagan	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
their	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
salts	O
,	O
three	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
piece	O
?	O
Poole	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
like	O
this	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Betty	O
Main	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
Thorn	O
's	O
?	O
Poole	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
pots	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Poole	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
Main	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Flanagan	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Rogers	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
Sunday	O
se'ennight	O
;	O
Betty	B-pers
Main	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Betty	B-pers
Main	I-pers
in	O
Chandler	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Poole	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
Betty	B-pers
Main	I-pers
?	O
Poole	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Thorn	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
piece	O
shewn	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
different	O
places	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
crown	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
several	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
died	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
some	O
crowns	O
and	O
some	O
dollars	O
;	O
this	O
dollar	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
livery	O
lace	O
weaver	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
apprentice	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
lad	O
when	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
hears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
young	O
lad	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
709	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
AARON	B-pers
SILVA	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
David	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
.	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Moorgate	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
Hutchinson	O
)	O
touched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Hutchinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Coleman-street	B-place
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
a-cross	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
saw	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
710	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
PETER	B-pers
MAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
and	O
shopman	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
Yard	I-place
;	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
over	O
my	O
private	O
cash	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
swept	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
clasps	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
they	O
offered	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
change	O
not	O
having	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
silver	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
for	O
another	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
cash	O
drawer	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
objected	O
to	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
round	O
enough	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
pardon	O
,	O
you	O
put	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
perhaps	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
one	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
looked	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
pardon	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
overlooked	O
a	O
queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
your	O
cash	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
it	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
suffered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
among	O
my	O
cash	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
never	O
a	O
queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
begged	O
pardon	O
for	O
giving	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
a	O
guinea	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
way	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
conceal	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
found	O
it	O
appeared	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
dropt	O
only	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
more	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
removed	O
into	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
upon	O
my	O
seizing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pushed	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
about	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
four	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
cash	O
account	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
just	O
four	O
guineas	O
.	O
-	O
Shagg	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nicoll	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
stop	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Watson	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
pocket	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
took	O
four	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
to	O
overtake	O
her	O
when	O
they	O
stopt	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
709	O
,	O
710	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ISAAC	B-pers
ASHER	I-pers
and	O
LAZARUS	B-pers
BOCHERO	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
840	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
84	O
l.	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
446	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
77	O
l.	O
and	O
96	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Buswell	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
warehouse	O
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Buswell	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
linen	O
draper	O
s	O
;	O
our	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Corbet-court	O
,	O
our	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Corbet-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
.	O
The	O
warehouse	O
was	O
robbed	O
between	O
the	O
22d	O
and	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tippler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Phillips	O
and	O
Buswell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
some	O
pieces	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
latch	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
spring	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
picked	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
about	O
fifty	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
and	O
cottons	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
dozen	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
out	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cottons	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
patterns	O
that	O
we	O
lost	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Abrahams	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
yards	O
were	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Barak	O
Fleming	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
these	O
three	O
remnants	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
my	O
asking	O
her	O
some	O
questions	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
Tippler	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
remnants	O
has	O
our	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
number	O
is	O
altered	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
originally	O
5308	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
ones	O
put	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
with	O
a	O
different	O
ink	O
and	O
is	O
very	O
visible	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
our	O
mark	O
:	O
we	O
mark	O
the	O
pieces	O
progressively	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
These	O
three	O
remnants	O
my	O
shop-mate	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Abrahams	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
being	O
disappointed	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
Eve	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sold	O
three	O
remnants	O
of	O
cotton	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
;	O
they	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
different	O
people	O
in	O
remnants	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
this	O
piece	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
put	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Eve	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
raise	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
bill	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
to	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Isaac	B-pers
Asher	I-pers
eight	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Northumberland-alley	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dealer	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
17	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
sale	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
eight	O
weeks	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
brown	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
flapped	O
hats	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
little	O
brown	O
bags	O
on	O
their	O
backs	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
others	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Asher	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
tied	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
Bochero	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
two	O
people	O
came	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
Bochero	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
they	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
three	O
more	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
in	O
brown	O
cloaths	O
and	O
flapped	O
hats	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bags	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
was	O
Isaac	B-pers
Asher	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
Keys	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
remnants	O
of	O
cotton	O
at	O
Eve	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Tippler	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
marks	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
(	O
Jews	O
)	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Hart	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
sink	O
his	O
evidence	O
for	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
unfortunately	O
contradicted	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
ASHER	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
BOCHERO	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Bochero	O
tried	O
No	O
.	O
636	O
,	O
in	O
Alderman	O
Crosby	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
711	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEALE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
Oct	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
in	O
Red-lion-square	O
;	O
going	O
home	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Queen	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
opposite	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
cloak	O
off	O
my	O
shoulders	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
minute	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Parker's-lane	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
cloak	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
walked	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
having	O
stolen	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
knocked	O
down	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
retook	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
home	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
run	O
by	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
712	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
MURPHY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Sadler	B-place
's	I-place
Wells	I-place
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Battle-bridge	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
(	O
George	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
who	O
has	O
been	O
executed	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
Lovell	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
money	O
!	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
pull	O
my	O
gloves	O
off	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
fumbled	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
gloves	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
Lovell	O
,	O
tript	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
grappled	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
holding	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
when	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
kicked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Murphy	O
had	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
her	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
Lovell	O
till	O
an	O
old	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
direction	O
there	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
desirous	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
now	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Collier	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
remarked	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
minutes	O
or	O
two	O
minutes	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
that	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
while	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
gloves	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
Collier	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
growing	O
dark	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discover	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
that	O
his	O
knees	O
were	O
not	O
straight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
examined	O
his	O
knees	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
knees	O
are	O
so	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
came	O
up	O
together	O
;	O
Murphy	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
Lovell	O
presented	O
another	O
pistol	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
Murphy	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
excepting	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
Collier	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
life	O
or	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Bridges	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
fellow	O
servants	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
now	O
that	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
of	O
.	O
Collier	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Murphy	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Collier	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Collier	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
jobs	O
for	O
Mr	O
.	O
Steward	O
,	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
besides	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
give	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
tell	O
any	O
person	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
you	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
of	O
.	O
Collier	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
you	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Collier	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
713	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cloth	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
laced	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Goff	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Duke	B-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
July	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Goff	O
for	O
safety	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
August	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
information	O
Mrs.	O
Goff	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Carnaby	O
Market	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
apron	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
's	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
produced	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
-	O
Hill	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
deposed	O
were	O
pledged	O
with	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
cloaths	O
in	O
an	O
unlocked	O
drawer	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
some	O
business	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Goff	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Goff	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
false	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
714	O
,	O
715	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MURPHY	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
EARLE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Hinchcliffe	I-pers
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
Earle	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hinchcliffe	I-pers
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
between	O
the	O
Small	B-place
Pox-Hospital	I-place
and	O
the	O
Tottenham-court	B-place
turnpike	I-place
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
to	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
at	O
Epping	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
three	O
persons	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
shorter	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
*	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
or	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
one	O
held	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
came	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
*	O
Earle	O
is	O
but	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
held	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
all	O
ones	O
;	O
I	O
fancy	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Then	O
Murphy	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Murphy	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
clear	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
watch	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
Murphy	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
might	O
that	O
be	O
my	O
destruction	O
if	O
I	O
prosecuted	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Earle	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
men	O
were	O
drinking	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
be	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Steadman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Count	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Plenius	I-pers
,	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
brought	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Earle	O
;	O
Murphy	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
your	O
watch	O
back	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
these	O
two	O
were	O
examined	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
Murphy	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
was	O
secured	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
gone	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
that	O
was	O
here	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
about	O
Murphy	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
asked	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
right	O
to	O
speak	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
then	O
to	O
turn	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
in	O
fact	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Hinchcliffe	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Plenius	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Grafton	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Tottenham-court	O
Road	O
;	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
Count	O
and	O
Steadman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
Count	O
told	O
me	O
their	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
bring	O
my	O
horse	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
them	O
through	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
by	O
Battle-bridge	O
,	O
near	O
Grays-Inn-lane-road	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
peeping	O
through	O
the	O
rails	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
past	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
supposed	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
sight	O
,	O
I	O
dismounted	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
screen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Murphy	O
,	O
Earle	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
talk	O
how	O
they	O
would	O
attack	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
as	O
near	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
they	O
see	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
Plenius	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
stray	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
accompanied	O
them	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
roods	O
;	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
off	O
towards	O
Paddington	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
swore	O
a	O
bitter	O
oath	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
carriage	O
comming	O
,	O
mind	O
how	O
you	O
come	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
resists	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
foot	O
;	O
they	O
panted	O
;	O
Lewis	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
Earle	O
went	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
rails	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
,	O
and	O
Murphy	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Turnpike	O
facing	O
Grays-Inn-lane-road	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
mounted	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
twice	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
distant	O
;	O
then	O
Lewis	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bridle	O
;	O
Murphy	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
Earle	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
their	O
money	O
or	O
their	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Steadman	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
give	O
Murphy	O
a	O
cut	O
;	O
Earle	O
received	O
a	O
cut	O
from	O
Count	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
fire	O
?	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
Lewis	O
fired	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
fired	O
at	O
Lewis	O
immediately	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
we	O
had	O
fire	O
arms	O
,	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
Steadman	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
Earle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
pursue	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
Murphy	O
got	O
under	O
the	O
rails	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
followed	O
Lewis	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
there	O
till	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Lewis	O
fired	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Earle	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
powder	O
upon	O
Earle	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Earle	O
about	O
the	O
robbery	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
Earle	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Murphy	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
their	O
examination	O
;	O
Hinchcliffe	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Murphy	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
attack	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cut	O
upon	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
bid	O
him	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
loth	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cut	O
through	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
in	O
his	O
flesh	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Earle	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
about	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
Plenius	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Bartholomew-fair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
powder	O
was	O
to	O
blow	O
the	O
sausage	O
womens	O
pans	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Steadman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hinchcliffe	O
;	O
young	O
Mr.	O
Hinchcliffe	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
near	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Count	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Plenius	O
in	O
Tottenham-court	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
apprehended	O
Earle	O
and	O
Lewis	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plenius	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
by	O
Earle	O
or	O
Lewis	O
about	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
Earle	O
was	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Hospital	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
his	O
head	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
young	O
dog	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
he	O
bled	O
pretty	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sore	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
dying	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Murphy	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
attacked	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
mark	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
I	O
cut	O
the	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
Count	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
Earle	O
spoke	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Count	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
Earle	O
and	O
Lewis	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plenius	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
Earle	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
our	O
young	O
master	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
off	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
Earle	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
by	O
himself	O
at	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Hospital	O
.	O
Earle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sense	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Steadman	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
attacked	O
you	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
Murphy	O
came	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
Earle	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
when	O
Murphy	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
cut	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
his	O
cloaths	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cut	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cut	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
which	O
was	O
sewed	O
up	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
this	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
be	O
.	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
other	O
affairs	O
then	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
ours	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
account	O
of	O
our	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
second	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
charged	O
with	O
your	O
affair	O
then	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
us	O
any	O
question	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Steadman	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
they	O
had	O
intended	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
spoke	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
our	O
affair	O
.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
they	O
should	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
one	O
man	O
from	O
another	O
.	O
Earle	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
in	O
Bowling-green	O
lane	O
,	O
Marybone	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
thief	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
tied	O
my	O
hands	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
a	O
chaise	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
good	O
,	O
bad	O
,	O
nor	O
indifferent	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
For	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
office	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hinchcliffe	O
said	O
the	O
prisoners	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
.	O
Murphy	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
darker	O
then	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
Murphy	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Plenius	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
is	O
Lewis	O
's	O
own	O
brother	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Vials	I-pers
,	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Hinchcliffe	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Earle	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Murphy	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
Lewis	O
is	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
son	O
;	O
Murphy	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
accord	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
large	O
then	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Murphy	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
green	O
shop	O
and	O
coal	O
shed	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
sickly	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
business	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Murphy	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
opposite	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
bed-ridden	O
;	O
he	O
supported	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
lad	O
;	O
I	O
admired	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
industrious	O
and	O
dutiful	O
to	O
his	O
parents	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
one	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Conelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
dutiful	O
children	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
husband	O
and	O
son	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
in	O
general	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Connelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
obedient	O
child	O
to	O
his	O
parents	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
diligent	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Malloy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
the	O
lad	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Malloy	O
.	O
If	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
that	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
Lewis	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
his	O
trial	O
.	O
See	O
Earle	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
320	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
373	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Alderman	O
Crosby	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
716	O
,	O
717	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLLINGS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HASLET	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Isaac	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mess	O
.	O
Few	O
and	O
Scruden	O
,	O
wharfingers	O
and	O
coal	O
dealers	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Essex-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
the	O
wharf	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
some	O
sacks	O
on	O
their	O
backs	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dogged	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Collings	O
go	O
with	O
one	O
sack	O
of	O
coals	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
milk	O
cellar	O
in	O
Essex-street	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
stepped	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Haslet	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
sack	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
challenge	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
sack	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
milk	O
cellar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
their	O
cellar	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
down	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Collings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
coals	O
tied	O
round	O
with	O
a	O
garter	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
Collings	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
garter	O
on	O
:	O
Collings	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
the	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
sack	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
coals	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
large	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
clean	O
as	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pit	O
;	O
then	O
Haslet	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
Haslet	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Collings	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Haslet	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Collings	O
'	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
coal-heaver	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
bag	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
three-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
Essex-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
garter	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
round	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Haslet	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
coals	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Essex-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
in	O
a	O
milk	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
milk	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
May	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
some	O
coals	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
718	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COPES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Battell	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Battell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Stanley	B-pers
Batten	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Winfield	O
Plain	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
high	O
sheriff	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
mare	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
in	O
Windsor	B-place
Forest	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Cranbourn	I-place
Lodge	I-place
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
white	O
star	O
in	O
her	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
white	O
snip	O
on	O
her	O
nose	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
white	O
heels	O
behind	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
mare	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
advertisement	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
public	O
office	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
describing	O
my	O
mare	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
13th	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Wrestlers	O
,	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
mare	O
was	O
stopt	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
mare	O
;	O
the	O
clerk	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopt	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
directly	O
by	O
Huxley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
very	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
mare	O
?	O
Battell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
her	O
myself	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huxley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
stealing	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
a	O
plated	O
bit	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
at	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
mare	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Wrestlers	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
bridle	O
man	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
bridle	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
bridle	O
before	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spurs	O
and	O
bit	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
advertised	O
the	O
mare	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
mare	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
mare	O
from	O
Windsor	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leybourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
Huxley	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
advertised	O
the	O
mare	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Lancashire	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
near	O
Slough	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
mare	O
was	O
tied	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
her	O
to	O
ride	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Wrestlers	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
mare	O
up	O
there	O
thinking	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
come	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
719	O
,	O
720	O
,	O
721	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Herd	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
id	O
John	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
October	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Herd	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
st	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Tottenham	O
to	O
Cannonbury	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
near	O
Newington	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
collar	O
of	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
they	O
cried	O
your	O
money	O
!	O
her	O
money	O
!	O
I	O
struck	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
wrenched	O
myself	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
stick	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
they	O
broke	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
thick	O
end	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
one	O
very	O
hard	O
with	O
the	O
bit	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
expected	O
they	O
would	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
produce	O
any	O
arms	O
;	O
seeing	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
arms	O
,	O
I	O
attacked	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Newington	O
Green	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
thirds	O
over	O
that	O
field	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
,	O
Ward	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
escape	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
by	O
getting	O
through	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
Newington	O
Green	O
stopt	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
there	O
are	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
attacked	O
you	O
?	O
Herd	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Islington	O
on	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Herd	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
seize	O
Mr.	O
Herd	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
use	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
``	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
!	O
''	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
he	O
robbed	O
by	O
such	O
blackguards	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Herd	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
screamed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
raised	O
many	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stumbled	O
against	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
and	O
began	O
beating	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Evans	O
called	O
Charles	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
722	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
EVAN	B-pers
MAURICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
and	O
feloniously	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
one	O
Sophia	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
figures	O
following	O
,	O
The	O
8th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
1772	O
,	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Evan	B-pers
Maurice	I-pers
or	O
Order	O
upon	O
demand	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
&	O
three	O
pound	O
ten	O
shilling	O
value	O
received	O
Sophia	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
103:10	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
Sophia	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
before	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
Castles	O
,	O
at	O
Puddle	O
dock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
keeps	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
call	O
for	O
taylors	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
resorted	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
;	O
Maurice	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Charing-cross	O
and	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
having	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
dined	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
call	O
;	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
Mr.	O
Maurice	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Magpye	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
I	O
objected	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
he	O
wrote	O
something	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
about	O
three	O
inches	O
square	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
before	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
conversation	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
pass	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
receipt	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
so	O
trifling	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
deception	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
receipt	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
then	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
dated	O
8th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
immediately	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
smaller	O
box	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
promissory	O
notes	O
for	O
small	O
sums	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
I	O
think	O
for	O
five	O
pounds	O
or	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
whose	O
note	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
show	O
you	O
the	O
deception	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
receipt	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
had	O
signed	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
the	O
written	O
receipt	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
slightly	O
gumed	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
paper	O
;	O
he	O
separated	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
made	O
it	O
into	O
two	O
;	O
there	O
stood	O
on	O
one	O
paper	O
the	O
bare	O
receipt	O
without	O
any	O
name	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
blank	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
excepting	O
only	O
an	O
L	O
,	O
a	O
figure	O
of	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
scratches	O
above	O
and	O
below	O
the	O
figure	O
of	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
Sophia	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
promissory	O
note	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
from	O
it	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
blank	O
paper	O
over	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
payable	O
to	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
date	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
altered	O
the	O
figures	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
1	O
and	O
an	O
0	O
before	O
the	O
figure	O
of	O
3	O
which	O
made	O
103	O
and	O
added	O
a	O
1	O
to	O
the	O
0	O
which	O
made	O
10	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
it	O
103	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
intention	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
of	O
hurting	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
meant	O
only	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
aside	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
present	O
that	O
note	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
marry	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
man	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
face	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
injure	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
imagined	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
procure	O
bail	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
consent	O
to	O
marry	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
this	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
frequented	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
casually	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
several	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
occasionally	O
drank	O
together	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
Maurice	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
I	O
was	O
struck	O
with	O
great	O
surprise	O
;	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
what	O
then	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
my	O
friend	O
(	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
)	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
his	O
advice	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Skinner	O
,	O
her	O
attorney	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
information	O
concerning	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
now	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
Maurice	O
;	O
Maurice	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
this	O
note	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
clear	O
of	O
the	O
date	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
witness	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
should	O
I	O
ever	O
be	O
called	O
upon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
copy	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
that	O
copy	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
name	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
that	O
meant	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
receipt	O
off	O
the	O
floor	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Maurice	O
know	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
receipt	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
receipts	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
sealed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Maurice	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
's	O
chambers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
had	O
conveyed	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
Mayhew	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
matter	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Maurice	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
attended	O
with	O
dangerous	O
consequences	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
in	O
case	O
this	O
marriage	O
had	O
ever	O
taken	O
effect	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
laid	O
the	O
least	O
trust	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
farthing	O
whatever	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
had	O
you	O
no	O
expectation	O
of	O
getting	O
something	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
succeded	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
describe	O
this	O
dividing	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
came	O
of	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
ease	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
gumed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
gum	O
wet	O
or	O
dry	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
clear	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
or	O
dry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
gum	O
had	O
been	O
dry	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
pealed	O
off	O
so	O
easily	O
would	O
it	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
black	O
line	O
drawn	O
along	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
that	O
receipt	O
which	O
hindered	O
any	O
fight	O
of	O
there	O
being	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
paper	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
gummy	O
substance	O
at	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	O
Castles	O
,	O
in	O
Black-friars	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Moore	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
call	O
for	O
journeymen	O
taylors	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
often	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Maurice	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
going	O
down	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
business	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
further	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
chamber	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
a	O
lady	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
good	O
morrow	O
to	O
you	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
said	O
good	O
morrow	O
to	O
you	O
Mr.	O
Maurice	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
your	O
friend	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Mayhew	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
proceed	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
Maurice	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
the	O
attorney	O
said	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
for	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
plantiff	O
and	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
clerk	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
plantiff	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
talk	O
about	O
bringing	O
an	O
action	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
(	O
taking	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
-	O
the	O
note	O
is	O
read	O
)	O
endorsed	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
Evan	B-pers
Maurice	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
mentioned	O
that	O
the	O
action	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
in	O
Underwood	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
Underwood	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
Mayhew	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
slip	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Magpye	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
Mayhew	O
said	O
,	O
does	O
she	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
Maurice	O
must	O
indorse	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
security	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
Maurice	O
,	O
and	O
Maurice	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
the	O
sum	O
was	O
in	O
figures	O
,	O
and	O
Mayhew	O
had	O
signed	O
it	O
only	O
with	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
not	O
mentioning	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
back	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
writing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
sum	O
should	O
be	O
specified	O
in	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
put	O
his	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
write	O
a	O
letter	O
;	O
Maurice	O
put	O
the	O
receipt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
;	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
was	O
this	O
contracted	O
?	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
supposed	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
wife	O
's	O
affair	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
right	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
Moore	O
saw	O
her	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
farther	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
every	O
day	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Moore	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
received	O
a	O
certain	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
for	O
swearing	O
against	O
me	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
When	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
friends	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
expressed	O
to	O
them	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dobson	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
turned	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
desperate	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
admitted	O
me	O
any	O
where	O
for	O
subsistence	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
friends	O
,	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
be	O
supported	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
live	O
on	O
the	O
air	O
.	O
They	O
voluntarily	O
agreed	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
support	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
only	O
allow	O
me	O
a	O
subsistence	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
receive	O
five	O
guineas	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
or	O
her	O
friends	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
security	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
more	O
upon	O
conviction	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
more	O
,	O
as	O
Maurice	O
says	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
defray	O
my	O
expences	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
are	O
you	O
to	O
receive	O
that	O
other	O
five	O
guineas	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
Upon	O
demand	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
ill	O
will	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Maurice	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
mentioned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
arrested	O
.	O
-	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
receipt	O
delivered	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
sealed	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
put	O
his	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Moore	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
receipt	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
paper	O
by	O
Maurice	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
gumed	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
edge	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
easily	O
separated	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Asto	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Armstrong	O
followed	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Armstrong	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
writ	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
arrested	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
sait	O
of	O
Underwood	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
bail	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
Maurice	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
's	O
,	O
after	O
waiting	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Maurice	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
this	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
vastly	O
confused	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
meant	O
to	O
hurt	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
respect	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
ever	O
owe	O
you	O
a	O
farthing	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
?	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
any	O
such	O
question	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
as	O
to	O
arrest	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
base	O
man	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
then	O
supposed	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
discovered	O
Moore	O
's	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
receipt	O
when	O
she	O
signed	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
supposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
signed	O
the	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
contents	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
or	O
her	O
friends	O
,	O
knew	O
his	O
heart	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
happy	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
themselves	O
easy	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
discoursed	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
any	O
thing	O
material	O
.	O
Moore	O
(	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Dobson	O
informed	O
us	O
he	O
knew	O
more	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
)	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
Mr.	O
Maurice	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
Moore	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Moore	O
sent	O
for	O
us	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
breast	O
to	O
discover	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
attended	O
with	O
loss	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
expected	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
sum	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
ten	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
proposed	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
our	O
offer	O
but	O
his	O
request	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
note	O
run	O
?	O
Asto	O
.	O
It	O
ran	O
,	O
we	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
trouble	O
or	O
loss	O
of	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
in	O
it	O
on	O
conviction	O
?	O
Asto	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Cooke	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Maurice	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
,	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
his	O
circumstances	O
?	O
Cooke	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
then	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
was	O
wrote	O
first	O
before	O
she	O
signed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
deceive	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Keyland	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
best	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
any	O
attorney	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
recommended	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
chambers	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mayhew	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
gentleman	O
wanted	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Keyland	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
note	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
house	O
and	O
be	O
imprisoned	O
without	O
a	O
warrant	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Dobson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Powel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
behaviour	O
has	O
been	O
such	O
that	O
none	O
could	O
object	O
to	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Asto	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
society	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
poor	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
Cooke	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
words	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
723	O
,	O
724	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
and	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
and	O
apothecary	O
,	O
at	O
Highgate	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
servant	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
attacked	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Highgate	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
horse	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
shot	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
heard	O
the	O
word	O
,	O
stop	O
!	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
quite	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
two	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
my	O
maid	O
was	O
on	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
step	O
or	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
;	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
containing	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
loose	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
a	O
queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
half	O
crown	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
A	O
carriage	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
men	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
distinguished	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
young	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
very	O
lusty	O
;	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
broad	O
neckcloth	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
pistols	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
fired	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
slightly	O
wounded	O
in	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
a	O
stone	O
button	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
button	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
pocket	O
;	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
button	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bridgeford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Constable	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
children	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
pistol	O
a	O
wound	O
under	O
my	O
right	O
eye	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
two	O
on	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
He	O
that	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
youngish	O
man	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
brownish	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
pistols	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
heard	O
the	O
report	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
flash	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
eighteen	O
years	O
old	O
next	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
painter	O
and	O
glazier	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
is	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Johnson	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
coat	O
button-maker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Westminster	O
to	O
these	O
two	O
lads	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
Tothill-street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
more	O
for	O
them	O
than	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
whores	O
and	O
thieves	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
girl	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
set	O
off	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
pistol	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
hid	O
after	O
that	O
robbery	O
,	O
that	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
these	O
lads	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
this	O
pistol	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
near	O
Fig-lane	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
!	O
the	O
lads	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
main	O
spring	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
said	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
I	O
do	O
that	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
I	O
robbed	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
purse	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
loose	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
robbing	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
coach	O
or	O
something	O
.	O
They	O
ran	O
away	O
directly	O
as	O
I	O
fired	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
jumped	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
cut	O
her	O
pocket	O
off	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
by	O
chance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
them	O
what	O
you	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
know	O
you	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
them	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
alamode	O
beef	O
for	O
supper	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Thirteen	O
Cantoons	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
or	O
they	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
paid	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
give	O
a	O
supper	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
we	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
mend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
taken	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
concern	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Wiggins	O
and	O
Savage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sign	O
an	O
information	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
about	O
all	O
these	O
robberies	O
.	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
signed	O
an	O
information	O
to	O
Savage	O
's	O
and	O
Wiggins	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
about	O
your	O
robbing	O
this	O
lady	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
upon	O
these	O
two	O
young	O
lads	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
I	O
fired	O
the	O
pistol	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
mention	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
here	O
for	O
other	O
robberies	O
besides	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
nothing	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
merely	O
because	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
fired	O
the	O
pistol	O
yourself	O
,	O
therefore	O
you	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoners	O
:	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
the	O
greatest	O
villain	O
I	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
here	O
in	O
your	O
information	O
you	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
you	O
knew	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
this	O
informant	O
,	O
robbed	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Fig-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
either	O
the	O
said	O
Griffiths	O
or	O
Johnson	O
fired	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
the	O
said	O
woman	O
.	O
''	O
Evans	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
me	O
that	O
did	O
that	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
information	O
is	O
upon	O
oath	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
now	O
upon	O
oath	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
a	O
lye	O
.	O
Evans	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
have	O
spoken	O
here	O
is	O
all	O
true	O
and	O
just	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
must	O
be	O
something	O
done	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
such	O
flagrant	O
villany	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humpedge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lay	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
not	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
?	O
Humpedge	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Humpedge	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Humpedge	O
.	O
Never	O
but	O
that	O
once	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Humpedge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Evans	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
they	O
are	O
apprentices	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
questioned	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
laugh	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
gave	O
them	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
change	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
d.	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
lie	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Humpedge	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Michaelmas	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
there	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
?	O
Humpedge	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
Griffiths	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Johnson	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
