TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1773	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
L.	O
)	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
Parker	B-pers
Carrier	I-pers
William	B-pers
Turvey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wager	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Brow	I-pers
William	B-pers
Farm	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Sheen	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jasker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
Theophillus	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cressey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Naish	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Aylward	I-pers
Hosea	B-pers
Olney	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mullis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
John	B-pers
French	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
Sampson	B-pers
Rainsforth	I-pers
George	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
George	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
David	B-pers
Dewsberry	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Yatman	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Whitridge	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hitchen	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Figg	I-pers
George	B-pers
Killam	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Dewsberry	I-pers
;	O
Andrew	B-pers
Purcel	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
T.	O
Yateman	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Nay	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Willington	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
George	B-pers
Coupland	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Inman	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Brickleton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Callcott	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
James	B-pers
Corrall	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Purcell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Brickleton	I-pers
.	O
511	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
NATHAN	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
glass	O
bottle	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
glass	O
decanter	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
glass	O
quart	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
two	O
half	O
pint	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
half	O
pint	O
glass	O
tumblers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
glass	O
cruets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cut	O
glass	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
cut	O
glass	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
and	O
Creighton	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
21st	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Stratford	B-place
in	I-place
Essex	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
son-in-law	O
Creighton	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Horne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
glasses	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
are	O
our	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
can	O
tell	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
is	O
blind	O
:	O
his	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
desk	O
broke	O
open	O
last	O
Saturday	O
fortnight	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
footman	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
without	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Creighton	O
Francis	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
Farrell	O
,	O
to	O
execute	O
the	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
glasses	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
aunt	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
below	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
his	O
brother	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
glass	O
ware	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
recollect	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
ever	O
if	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
like	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
officer	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
cup	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Balkay	O
;	O
she	O
objected	O
to	O
it	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
shape	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
remained	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
cup	O
has	O
a	O
peculiarity	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clubb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
under-clerk	O
and	O
warehouse-man	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Russell	O
and	O
Horne	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
glasses	O
;	O
the	O
warehouse	O
is	O
constantly	O
open	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
may	O
have	O
access	O
to	O
it	O
except	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
recollect	O
giving	O
one	O
glass	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
use	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Maurice	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
falts	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
tumblers	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
some	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
any	O
for	O
himself	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
tumbler	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
use	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
which	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
bar	O
these	O
men	O
gave	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
beer	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
from	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
both	O
denied	O
ever	O
having	O
drank	O
at	O
his	O
cost	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
512	O
,	O
513	O
,	O
514	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ASHBY	I-pers
,	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LUNDY	I-pers
M'DONALD	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ANDREW	B-pers
LATIMER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
eight	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
eleven	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
forty-eight	O
copper	O
farthings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
)	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Oxford-street	B-place
.	O
Between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
screamed	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
fore	O
room	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
locks	O
of	O
bureaus	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lock	O
of	O
a	O
nest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
day	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
any	O
man	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
discovered	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Ashby	O
wanted	O
to	O
turn	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
before	O
that	O
recommended	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
turn	O
evidence	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
will	O
pass	O
that	O
over	O
.	O
When	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wished	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Macdonald	O
said	O
suppose	O
you	O
had	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
chucked	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cordwainer	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
At	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
up	O
directly	O
and	O
saw	O
Ashby	O
on	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
landing	O
of	O
the	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
landing	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
to	O
lock	O
his	O
doors	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
cellar	O
stairs	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
steps	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
before	O
Bailey	O
could	O
lock	O
his	O
door	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
Ashby	O
escaped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
.	O
After	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
among	O
the	O
butts	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
they	O
hollow	O
'd	O
out	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
his	O
dress	O
and	O
apparel	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gee's-court	O
,	O
Oxford-street	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
turning	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
Ashby	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
blasted	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
his	O
limbs	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
'	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
one	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
landing	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
in	O
the	O
Ambury	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
forty	O
quid	O
;	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
that	O
word	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
venemous	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
in	O
case	O
any	O
thing	O
happened	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
Ashby	O
confessed	O
that	O
what	O
I	O
swore	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
truth	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bailey	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
before	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
turn	O
evidence	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
hear	O
that	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
without	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
describe	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Ashby	O
next	O
day	O
answer	O
the	O
description	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
exactly	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Monro	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
supper	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
directly	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
one	O
I	O
saw	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
just	O
saw	O
his	O
shadow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
plain	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
day	O
or	O
candle	O
light	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
Candle	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
directly	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
his	O
dress	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
his	O
coat	O
buttoned	O
over	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
very	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
day	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
him	O
without	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
candle	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
two	O
steps	O
to	O
the	O
little	O
passage	O
;	O
his	O
foot	O
gave	O
a	O
slip	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
these	O
people	O
come	O
out	O
directly	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
and	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
up	O
when	O
you	O
heard	O
your	O
wife	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
both	O
rooms	O
forwards	O
and	O
backwards	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
and	O
the	O
shoemaker	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
Before	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
picked	O
M'Donald	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
twenty	O
men	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
pitched	O
upon	O
him	O
he	O
nodded	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
done	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Monro	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
describe	O
him	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
crookedish	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
nose	O
and	O
a	O
comical	O
look	O
with	O
his	O
eyes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
from	O
her	O
description	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary-le-bone	O
:	O
I	O
and	O
Hartley	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
were	O
applied	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Westminster	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
we	O
found	O
Ashby	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
our	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
from	O
the	O
information	O
we	O
had	O
from	O
Ashby	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
M'Donald	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Ambury	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
hand-cuffed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
country	O
booby	O
as	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
minded	O
it	O
if	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
m	O
en	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
forty	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
pistols	O
about	O
him	O
for	O
to	O
shoot	O
such	O
a	O
country	O
flat	O
as	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
coachman	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
knife	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
several	O
marks	O
upon	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
the	O
drawers	O
of	O
the	O
instrument	O
with	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
knife	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
when	O
the	O
girl	O
challenged	O
him	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
:	O
the	O
girl	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Denman	O
her	O
aunt	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
buttoned	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
sticking	O
out	O
upon	O
each	O
side	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
her	O
two	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
Ashby	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
seemed	O
to	O
hesitate	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
M'Donald	O
was	O
then	O
locked	O
down	O
below	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
watch-house	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
people	O
of	O
all	O
sorts	O
;	O
she	O
directly	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
pointed	O
way	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
quite	O
unexpectedly	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
people	O
's	O
backs	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
and	O
introduced	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
they	O
bid	O
her	O
look	O
round	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
saw	O
Ashby	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
M'Donald	O
in	O
Tothil-street	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
what	O
is	O
your	O
authority	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
clapped	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
resist	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
King	O
every	O
moment	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Hartley	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Hartley	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
if	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
we	O
could	O
take	O
two	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Horceridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Latimer	O
in	O
the	O
Ambury	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Darts	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
picking	O
pockets	O
.	O
-	O
Parrot	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
Latimer	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Ashby	O
to	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
to	O
lock	O
his	O
doors	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
so	O
thick	O
about	O
me	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
me	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
candle	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
bar	O
from	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Opposite	O
;	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
so	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
yards	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
four	O
yards	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
rather	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
yards	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
him	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
lights	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
drinking	O
room	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
people	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
round	O
him	O
how	O
could	O
he	O
see	O
me	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
shelf	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
where	O
the	O
pots	O
stand	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
shelf	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
candles	O
,	O
which	O
commanded	O
a	O
prospect	O
above	O
the	O
people	O
's	O
heads	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
landing	O
place	O
is	O
higher	O
than	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
highest	O
upon	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
fasten	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
then	O
could	O
I	O
get	O
out	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
lock	O
his	O
door	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
goes	O
with	O
a	O
spring	O
lock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
he	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Which	O
door	O
did	O
you	O
lock	O
first	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
confused	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
fastened	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
M'Donald	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
drank	O
share	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Ashby	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
ASHBY	O
and	O
M'DONALD	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
LATIMER	O
acquitted	O
.	O
515	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MATHEW	B-pers
HART	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
copper	O
rivets	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
:	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Millan	I-pers
;	O
I	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
Millan	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
more	O
at	O
Richard	B-pers
Bun	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
nails	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
copper	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
them	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
no	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
C	O
upon	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
voluntarily	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Whitebread	O
's	O
brewhouse	O
where	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
our	O
work	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
16	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
there	O
thinking	O
them	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Whitebread	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
some	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
my	O
father	O
brought	O
Millan	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
nails	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
nail	O
with	O
our	O
marking	O
tool	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
and	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
copper	O
produced	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
that	O
is	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
done	O
working	O
there	O
pretty	O
near	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
rubbish	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whitebread	O
these	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Cave	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
our	O
work	O
unfinished	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
516	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PHILIP	B-pers
SHORT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Yeates	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
9	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Yeates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Mill-hill	B-place
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
into	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
gate	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
high	O
road	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
flung	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
9	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
likewise	O
was	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Yeates	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
under-waistcoat	O
on	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
positively	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
throttled	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
my	O
shop	O
together	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
lane	O
to	O
gether	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
back	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
black	O
binding	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
some	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
working	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
by	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
such	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
under	O
a	O
hedge	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
field	O
distance	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
9	O
s.	O
piece	O
in	O
his	O
shoe	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
shillings	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
half	O
crowns	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shillings	O
he	O
changed	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
for	O
some	O
tobacco	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
between	O
drunk	O
and	O
sober	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
517	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Jacob	B-pers
Price	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	O
Price	O
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
518	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HERRING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
traiterously	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
her	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
case	O
knife	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
throat	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
Aug.	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Darling	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Thistle	I-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
King	I-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
meat	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
bread	O
;	O
you	O
bougre	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
bread	O
with	O
my	O
meat	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
her	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
bread	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
you	O
foutre	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
eat	O
it	O
without	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
behind	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
them	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
Close	O
behind	O
the	O
box	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
not	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
picking	O
a	O
bone	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
lick	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
struck	O
the	O
knife	O
into	O
his	O
throat	O
;	O
the	O
blood	O
immediately	O
spouted	O
out	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
butcher	O
had	O
killed	O
a	O
pig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
the	O
bone	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
remain	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
this	O
did	O
this	O
man	O
die	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
killed	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
quarrel	O
between	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
!	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
!	O
the	O
first	O
word	O
that	O
was	O
spoke	O
was	O
what	O
I	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
told	O
us	O
all	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
Every	O
word	O
from	O
my	O
heart	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
it	O
happened	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
one	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
eat	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
salmon	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Tell	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
?	O
Darling	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
even	O
of	O
any	O
blows	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
stab	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
from	O
carrying	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
do	O
the	O
rash	O
action	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
stab	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
thus	O
(	O
describing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
straight	O
thrust	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
neck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
appear	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
on	O
purpose	O
?	O
Darling	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
spill	O
his	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
him	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
more	O
before	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
,	O
sigh	O
,	O
or	O
groan	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
supported	O
him	O
pinched	O
his	O
wound	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
bleeding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
husband	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Darling	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
knife	O
down	O
,	O
clasped	O
her	O
hands	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
!	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
!	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
tileing	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
box	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
passage	O
between	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
where	O
they	O
sat	O
;	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sat	O
opposite	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bone	O
of	O
mutton	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
jawing	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
jawing	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
upon	O
my	O
heel	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
knife	O
drop	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
spurted	O
over	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
herself	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
strike	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
murder	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
killed	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
wound	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
man	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
blood	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
bleed	O
till	O
a	O
surgeon	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
staggered	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
farther	O
;	O
he	O
dropt	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
air	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
alive	O
then	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
dying	O
,	O
I	O
closed	O
his	O
eyes	O
and	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
round	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
alive	O
a	O
minute	O
when	O
the	O
surgeon	O
came	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
struck	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
till	O
he	O
died	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
husband	O
strike	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
no	O
words	O
pass	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
?	O
Duncan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
one	O
word	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Pidley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
near	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
quite	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
throat	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
knife	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
opened	O
him	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
inches	O
deep	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
large	O
blood	O
vessel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
?	O
Pidley	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
apprehend	O
that	O
the	O
wound	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
then	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Blythe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
wound	O
;	O
a	O
large	O
blood	O
vessel	O
was	O
intirely	O
divided	O
by	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Darling	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
common	O
case	O
knife	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
the	O
accident	O
happened	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
bad	O
from	O
his	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
they	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
eleven	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
bitches	O
and	O
whores	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
every	O
little	O
thing	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
apartment	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
a	O
fork	O
into	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
shewn	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
every	O
shape	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Darling	O
's	O
who	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
spite	O
against	O
me	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
person	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
part	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
meat	O
was	O
made	O
ready	O
he	O
eat	O
his	O
belly	O
full	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
come	O
and	O
eat	O
a	O
bit	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
overjoyed	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
eat	O
with	O
him	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
joy	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
kingdom	O
of	O
heaven	O
this	O
moment	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
pipe	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
box	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
knife	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
fatal	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
ask	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Darling	O
whether	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
spite	O
against	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
Darling	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
word	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
quarrel	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
prior	O
to	O
this	O
stroke	O
?	O
Darling	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
none	O
nor	O
saw	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
in	O
my	O
business	O
constantly	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
laid	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
nap	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
jangling	O
order	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
blows	O
,	O
much	O
less	O
to	O
this	O
unhappy	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Darling	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
threaten	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
nose	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
beer	O
being	O
thrown	O
over	O
her	O
?	O
Darling	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
indeed	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
woman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
bad	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
quart	O
pots	O
;	O
stick	O
forks	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
do	O
many	O
violent	O
things	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hagen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
and	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
opposite	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
call	O
out	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
turned	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
without	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Darling	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Darling	O
say	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Hagen	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Darling	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
her	O
?	O
Darling	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Boyle	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
husband	O
throw	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Boyle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Rounson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
terrible	O
manner	O
among	O
the	O
workmen	O
that	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
discharge	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
lest	O
they	O
should	O
do	O
any	O
mischief	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rounson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
home	O
and	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
poker	O
without	O
a	O
handle	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
beating	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
left	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
strike	O
me	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
husband	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
wife	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
pleaded	O
pregnancy	O
:	O
a	O
jury	O
of	O
matrons	O
were	O
immediately	O
impannel	O
'd	O
,	O
whose	O
verdict	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
quick	O
child	O
.	O
She	O
received	O
sentence	O
immediately	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
following	O
words	O
,	O
``	O
This	O
court	O
awards	O
,	O
that	O
``	O
you	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
are	O
to	O
be	O
led	O
from	O
``	O
hence	O
to	O
the	O
Gaol	O
from	O
whence	O
you	O
came	O
;	O
``	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
next	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
on	O
``	O
a	O
hurdle	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
execution	O
;	O
where	O
``	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
with	O
fire	O
until	O
you	O
are	O
``	O
dead	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
law	O
was	O
executed	O
upon	O
her	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
sentence	O
.	O
519	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMSON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
M'KENZIE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
diamond	O
ear-rings	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Farquharson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
July	O
14th	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Farquharson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
jeweller	O
's	O
and	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
ear-rings	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
exchange	O
for	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
things	O
;	O
nothing	O
gave	O
him	O
satisfaicton	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
these	O
diamond	O
ear-rings	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
satisfaction	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
tickets	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bespoke	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
a	O
mahogany	O
case	O
with	O
green	O
handle	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
16	O
,	O
Mead's-court	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
and	O
manner	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
such	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
naturally	O
concluded	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
every	O
attempt	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
afterwards	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
,	O
whose	O
shop	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
met	O
him	O
by	O
accident	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
clear	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
very	O
strongly	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
unhappy	O
circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
Farquharson	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
no	O
particular	O
promise	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
indulgent	O
as	O
the	O
law	O
would	O
allow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurted	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
Farquharson	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
expence	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
shewed	O
these	O
ear-rings	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Farquharson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Farquharson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
shewn	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
else	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Farquharson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
nobody	O
else	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Farquharson	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
multiplicity	O
of	O
things	O
one	O
does	O
not	O
so	O
soon	O
miss	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Farquharson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
;	O
he	O
named	O
the	O
name	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
mention	O
it	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
locket	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
these	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
six	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
locket	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
very	O
genteelly	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
suspicion	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
but	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
pledged	O
the	O
locket	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
appeared	O
very	O
genteel	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ear-rings	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
if	O
I	O
delivered	O
up	O
his	O
pocket	O
book	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurted	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
law	O
obliged	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
indicted	O
capitally	O
,	O
only	O
for	O
transportation	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
he	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
A	O
lightish	O
sky	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
showy	O
waistcoats	O
embroidered	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Much	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Farquharson	O
has	O
described	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMSON	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
diamond	O
and	O
emerald	O
breast	O
buckle	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
and	O
goldsmith	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
genteel	O
appearance	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
several	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
jewellery	O
way	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
this	O
buckle	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
stayed	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
ever	O
returned	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
buckle	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Compton-street	O
.	O
-	O
Grant	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
buckle	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charlton	O
,	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
.	O
The	O
buckle	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
some	O
person	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
gave	O
their	O
words	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
laid	O
capitally	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
where	O
the	O
properties	O
were	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
520	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
O'BRIEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
,	O
privately	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
O'BRIEN	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
picture	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
waistcoat	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
from	O
a	O
room	O
my	O
master	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
adjoining	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
buttons	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
hay	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
buttons	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
being	O
in	O
there	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
cieling	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Fairbrother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
broke	O
the	O
cieling	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
King	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
long	O
passage	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
window	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
broke	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
broke	O
through	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
communication	O
to	O
several	O
hay	O
losts	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
cieling	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
through	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
wants	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
521	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRIETTA	B-pers
GRAY	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
nineteen	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
and	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
;	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
she	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
bound	O
shoes	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
these	O
shoes	O
were	O
not	O
of	O
those	O
entrusted	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
bind	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
standing	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
within	O
reach	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
shoes	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
pawn	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pair	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
.	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
are	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
pawn	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
mark	O
is	O
upon	O
both	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
me	O
to	O
bind	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
522	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rippon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
sheets	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Rippon	I-pers
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Rippon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-Gravel-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
four	O
nights	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
bed	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
with	O
one	O
Truss	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Truss	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
sheets	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
an	O
R	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
523	O
,	O
524	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
RUSSEL	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HICKS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
live	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
live	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10th	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
525	O
,	O
526	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
GREAR	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Grear	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19th	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sea-faring	O
man	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Grear	O
:	O
two	O
women	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
from	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
my	O
neck	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
and	O
waked	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
sober	O
then	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
in	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
bed	O
and	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
husband	O
from	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
woman	O
a	O
bed	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
wake	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
first	O
my	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
about	O
for	O
a	O
stick	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
defend	O
myself	O
if	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
slipped	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
where	O
she	O
ran	O
to	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
fetched	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
about	O
;	O
we	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
women	O
lay	O
naked	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
Smith	O
had	O
Mrs.	O
Grear	O
's	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
on	O
;	O
Grear	O
had	O
her	O
clothes	O
on	O
;	O
Smith	O
was	O
fitting	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
corner	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
lifting	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
watchman	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
buckles	O
by	O
where	O
she	O
sat	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
further	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
other	O
buckle	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
tobacco	O
box	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
basket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Grear	I-pers
in	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
stand	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
Smith	O
waked	O
you	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
by	O
Hughes	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
buckle	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
within	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Smith	O
;	O
she	O
stood	O
partly	O
over	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Puckeridge	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
Sunday	O
night	O
and	O
Monday	O
morning	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
court	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
Grear	O
and	O
Smith	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
confused	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
dressed	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
young	O
women	O
lay	O
quite	O
naked	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
as	O
ever	O
they	O
were	O
born	O
;	O
Smith	O
seemed	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
sham	O
sleep	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
basket	O
of	O
broken	O
bottles	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
old	O
bottles	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
looking	O
further	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee	O
buckle	O
and	O
the	O
tobacco	O
box	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
five	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
fixed	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
Grear	I-pers
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
ordered	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
Grear	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
;	O
then	O
some	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
Grear	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
informed	O
me	O
she	O
rented	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Puckeridge	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Grear	O
live	O
?	O
Puckeridge	O
.	O
In	O
Swan-alley	O
,	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
Ball	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Puckeridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
house	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Puckeridge	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Grear	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
527	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HASSELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Isabella	B-pers
Delaporte	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
528	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
CORDEROY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
steel	O
shoe	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
July	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
529	O
,	O
530	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
BURNHAM	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MACDONALD	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dycher	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dycher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
parish	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
parish	I-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
White-Lion	O
,	O
Red-Lion-street	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
coming	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
treat	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
or	O
rum	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
consented	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
a	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
candle	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
one	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
recollected	O
that	O
my	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
and	O
halfpence	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
separate	O
them	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
gold	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
either	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
or	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
counted	O
it	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
separate	O
the	O
gold	O
from	O
the	O
silver	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
both	O
the	O
women	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
recollect	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
enquire	O
after	O
these	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
night	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
recommended	O
me	O
to	O
one	O
Simmons	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
people	O
;	O
before	O
Simmons	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Simmons	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
Simmons	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
persons	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Macdonald	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
paid	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
was	O
too	O
light	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rolfe	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
paid	O
for	O
this	O
gown	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rolfe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
s	O
tone	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
change	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
first	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
dropt	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
them	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
531	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Charles	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
by	O
three	O
foot-pads	O
;	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
arms	O
?	O
Sheffield	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
that	O
cost	O
me	O
40	O
l	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
few	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Sheffield	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
and	O
seal	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
seal	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
produced	O
)	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
chain	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
principal	O
part	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
seal	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
seal	O
fixed	O
to	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
?	O
Sheffield	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
separate	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
seal	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
very	O
dirty	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
doubtful	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
coarse	O
sort	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
like	O
a	O
workman	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
doubted	O
first	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
now	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
seal	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
apron	O
;	O
when	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
no	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Maddison	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
chain	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
on	O
Saturday	O
July	O
the	O
17th	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
blue	O
apron	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
mind	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
chain	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
mine	O
was	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
now	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
before	O
said	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
d	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
One	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
this	O
man	O
:	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
was	O
executed	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
Kensington	O
and	O
Knightsbridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
person	O
robbed	O
?	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
:	O
Brown	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Field	O
robbed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
chain	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Morris	O
and	O
Cross	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
traced	O
to	O
your	O
hands	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
information	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
sold	O
them	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Brown	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
seal	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
chain	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Cross	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Cross	O
's	O
shop	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
In	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
and	O
seal	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
that	O
chaise	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
A	O
painter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
follows	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
trade	O
a	O
milkman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
was	O
sold	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
one	O
piece	O
was	O
sold	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
melted	O
down	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
below	O
Hatton-Garden	O
on	O
Holborn	O
Hill	O
;	O
one	O
piece	O
I	O
sold	O
myself	O
in	O
Grafton	O
street	O
by	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Church	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
melted	O
down	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Brown	B-pers
any	O
arms	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
together	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
met	O
accidentally	O
together	O
;	O
Field	O
threatened	O
to	O
shoot	O
us	O
through	O
the	O
head	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
intention	O
to	O
rob	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
was	O
that	O
man	O
and	O
you	O
concerned	O
in	O
any	O
robberies	O
before	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Remember	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
you	O
that	O
is	O
superior	O
to	O
all	O
human	O
judicature	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
one	O
Moses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
for	O
three	O
guineas	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
,	O
three	O
doors	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
Holborn	O
Bridge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
chain	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
bought	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
Grove	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
buy	O
it	O
?	O
Grove	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
compared	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
chain	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
matched	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Whether	O
there	O
are	O
not	O
many	O
chains	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
urn	O
in	O
the	O
division	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
twelve	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
532	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MILSOM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
louisdore	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
miles	O
beyond	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
by	O
a	O
single	O
highwayman	O
;	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
louisdore	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
silver	O
;	O
besides	O
I	O
believe	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
giving	O
it	O
him	O
he	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
sorrel	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
horse	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
colour	O
and	O
marks	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
the	O
description	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
thin	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
pale	O
faced	O
,	O
in	O
brown	O
clothes	O
;	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
either	O
a	O
wig	O
or	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
tied	O
behind	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
described	O
him	O
as	O
middle	O
sized	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
the	O
robbery	O
take	O
up	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Only	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
asking	O
me	O
those	O
two	O
questions	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
;	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
;	O
it	O
wanted	O
but	O
three	O
days	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
full	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
almost	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
its	O
being	O
by	O
moon	O
light	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
mind	O
to	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
or	O
does	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
correspond	O
with	O
the	O
idea	O
you	O
have	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
mind	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Every	O
time	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
him	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
August	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
yourself	O
recollect	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
night	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
was	O
you	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
of	O
spirits	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stop	O
the	O
horses	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
respecting	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
rainy	O
night	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
it	O
particularly	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
recollection	O
does	O
not	O
serve	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
night	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
robbery	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
about	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
apprehension	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stop	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
night	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
what	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
particularly	O
shy	O
and	O
spirited	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
ride	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
shy	O
,	O
spirited	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
middle	O
sized	O
men	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
day	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
middle	O
sized	O
man	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
remarkably	O
tall	O
or	O
remarkably	O
short	O
:	O
you	O
can	O
hardly	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
seeing	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
by	O
moon	O
light	O
you	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
coat	O
by	O
day	O
light	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Hendon	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
pockets	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
loaded	O
pistols	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
loaded	O
pistol	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
purses	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
chain	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
since	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sorrel	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
pretty	O
spirited	O
,	O
and	O
jumps	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
put	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
the	O
stable	O
near	O
Long	O
Acre	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
ascertain	O
the	O
horse	O
(	O
the	O
horse	O
is	O
sent	O
for	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
The	O
pistol	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
longer	O
than	O
either	O
of	O
there	O
that	O
are	O
produced	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
and	O
Heley	O
return	O
into	O
Court	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
out	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
the	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
natural	O
spirit	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Heley	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
horse	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
has	O
now	O
seen	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Heley	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
horse	O
of	O
one	O
Hawkes	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Paddington	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
since	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
Hawkes	O
's	O
father	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
fair	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bought	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
Hawkes	O
here	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
escaped	O
out	O
of	O
gaol	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
horse	O
since	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
detained	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Bucks	O
.	O
533	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
ABBOT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
stone	O
seals	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
;	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
neck-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plated	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
buckles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ben	B-pers
.	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Benj	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
I	O
live	O
in	O
George	O
Yard	O
,	O
Soho	O
Square	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
Westminster	B-place
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
immediately	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
effects	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
more	O
than	O
usual	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
first	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
among	O
some	O
rags	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
herself	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smallshaw	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Snipes	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
black	O
neckcloth	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
now	O
produced	O
;	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
one	O
Nichols	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
neckcloth	O
and	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
Snipes	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pay	O
the	O
prisoner	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
534	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
at	O
Worcester	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
1773	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
names	O
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
thereunto	O
subscribed	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
six	O
months	O
after	O
the	O
date	O
thereof	O
,	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
forty	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
forge	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
thereon	O
an	O
indorsement	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
indorsement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
The	O
mark	O
X	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Witness	O
R	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Second	O
Count	O
for	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
indorsement	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
Third	O
Count	O
for	O
forging	O
the	O
indorsement	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
count	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
Fourth	O
Count	O
for	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
indorsement	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
The	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
challenged	O
the	O
juries	O
that	O
had	O
tried	O
the	O
other	O
Middlesex	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
jury	O
were	O
sworn	O
upon	O
this	O
trial	O
.	O
Thorpe	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Arpin	I-pers
Andrew	B-pers
Hercules	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
James	B-pers
Wilchin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Vobe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mawson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hollingsworth	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Killinsworth	I-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
shewn	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
name	O
Grey	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
name	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
hand	O
writing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
offered	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
as	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
holder	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
discharge	O
for	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
her	O
competency	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
was	O
objected	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
stating	O
the	O
objection	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
under	O
the	O
present	O
circumstances	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
competent	O
witness	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carleton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Priddle	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
Office	O
?	O
Carleton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
this	O
note	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
there	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
indorsement	O
?	O
Carleton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
except	O
in	O
a	O
mark	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
has	O
made	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
note	O
shewn	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Carleton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
question	O
being	O
put	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
magistrates	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
indorsed	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
magistrates	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
special	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
or	O
some	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
magistrates	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
only	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
place	O
of	O
security	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
that	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Barnfather	O
was	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
offered	O
him	O
that	O
indulgence	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
power	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
apprehend	O
that	O
every	O
attorney	O
has	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
indorse	O
over	O
notes	O
that	O
he	O
shall	O
receive	O
or	O
any	O
security	O
for	O
his	O
clients	O
:	O
upon	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
,	O
approbation	O
,	O
and	O
consent	O
of	O
that	O
client	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
it	O
was	O
law	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
note	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
care	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
by	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
magistrates	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
have	O
read	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
News-papers	O
about	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
usual	O
to	O
proceed	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
to	O
examine	O
a	O
man	O
against	O
himself	O
?	O
Carleton	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
examination	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
information	O
being	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
magistrates	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
for	O
the	O
Magistrates	O
at	O
your	O
Office	O
to	O
be	O
collecting	O
evidence	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
against	O
himself	O
?	O
Carleton	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
out	O
voluntarily	O
without	O
any	O
matter	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
pushing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Jacobs	O
brought	O
this	O
note	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
