TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
:	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1773	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
,	O
Second	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKSTONE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGERT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
L.	O
)	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
William	B-pers
Foxwell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Robson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Hougham	I-pers
George	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
William	B-pers
Heathfield	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Phane	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
William	B-pers
Roderick	I-pers
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Dewen	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Buxton	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lovett	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
D'Rippe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
David	B-pers
Fontaine	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Richard	O
Wall	O
.	O
163	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
DOYLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
nine	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Assay-office	O
in	O
Goldsmith's-hall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
some	O
company	O
in	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
to	O
Islington	B-place
;	O
the	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
were	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Barkwith	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
driving	O
very	O
slow	O
between	O
the	O
New	B-place
River	I-place
and	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
both	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
were	O
opened	O
by	O
somebody	O
from	O
without	O
in	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
instant	O
;	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
boarded	O
made	O
it	O
quite	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
opening	O
the	O
doors	O
let	O
in	O
light	O
upon	O
us	O
;	O
immediately	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
doors	O
a	O
pistol	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
and	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
``	O
Come	O
sir	O
,	O
come	O
sir	O
!	O
''	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
remarkable	O
having	O
a	O
long	O
screw	O
barrel	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
it	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pistol	O
afterwards	O
produced	O
that	O
answered	O
that	O
description	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
highwayman	O
was	O
engaged	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
short	O
round	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
snatched	O
the	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
and	O
finished	O
his	O
robbery	O
;	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
near	O
five	O
minutes	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thrust	O
half	O
his	O
body	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Now	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
now	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
''	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
exact	O
sum	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
alarmed	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
pretty	O
near	O
my	O
mouth	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hern	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
another	O
indictment	O
for	O
the	O
robbery	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
your	O
own	O
robbery	O
now	O
.	O
Bell	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eyes	O
steadily	O
upon	O
his	O
countenance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
clear	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
moon	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
light	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
by	O
opening	O
both	O
doors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
dress	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
to	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
attention	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
only	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
shriek	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Islington-road	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
pistol	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hern	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Maber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
St.	O
John-street	O
;	O
hearing	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
murder	O
!	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
pocket	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
``	O
Do	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
earned	O
it	O
by	O
hard	O
labor	O
.	O
''	O
Hern	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
Maber	O
.	O
Upon	O
further	O
searching	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
bullet	O
and	O
flint	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
also	O
the	O
rammer	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
loose	O
gun	O
powder	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
-	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
brought	O
people	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
from	O
four	O
till	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
witnesses	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
164	O
,	O
165	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
LAWLESS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PLUNKETT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
166	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
RADFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
and	O
silver	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
Dec.	O
2d	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
167	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
MOXHAM	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
drawer	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
60	O
halfpence	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
yard	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Millisen	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24th	O
.	O
*	O
Millisen	O
Fenn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
great	B-place
Earl-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
till	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
Christmas	O
Eve	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
bell	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
till	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
lamp	O
I	O
kept	O
burning	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
thrown	O
down	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tubb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
rotation	O
office	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
several	O
suspected	O
persons	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Fenn	O
's	O
with	O
this	O
till	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
the	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
shop	O
where	O
her	O
till	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Ratford	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
till	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
RATFORD	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
MOXHAM	O
acquitted	O
.	O
168	O
,	O
169	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
CASSOY	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
HAGAN	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
baker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Salt	O
Peter-bank	O
,	O
hearing	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
glass	O
houses	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
any	O
person	O
that	O
worked	O
in	O
a	O
glass	O
house	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
curiosity	O
to	O
see	O
glass	O
blown	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Cassoy	I-pers
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
seeking	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
glass-blower	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
might	O
shew	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
twitched	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
upon	O
no	O
other	O
subject	O
but	O
glass-blowing	O
?	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
no	O
familiar	O
conversation	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
called	O
Hagan	O
;	O
Cassoy	O
then	O
threw	O
herself	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Hagan	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
catch	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
neighbours	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
170	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
CORNELIUS	B-pers
O'CONNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
horse	O
whip	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Ryford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
to	O
sell	O
two	O
loads	O
of	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
coachman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
good	O
leather	O
breeches	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
his	O
beer	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
whip	O
immediately	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
Aunt	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
:	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
without	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
pawned	O
it	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SUMNERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
diaper	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
~	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
long	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
russia	O
diaper	O
containing	O
17	O
ells	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
these	O
callico	O
shirts	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
different	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
172	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
READ	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
MARGARET	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Sumner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
beaver	O
hoods	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
~	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
cook	O
maid	O
in	O
our	O
family	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
more	O
particularly	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
searched	O
Sumner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
entertained	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
intimacy	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
different	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
assisted	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
Sumner	O
told	O
her	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
another	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
173	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROADS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
Francis	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
)	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
new	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
of	O
new	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
daughter	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
being	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
for	O
these	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
only	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
His	O
own	O
buckles	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
ones	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
difference	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
buckles	O
he	O
was	O
cheapening	O
but	O
another	O
pair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
174	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
cutting	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
said	O
lead	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
dwelling	O
house	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roiley	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Cow-cross	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
rest	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
pump	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
hindered	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Rutt	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Rutt	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
brother	O
to	O
examine	O
Mr.	O
Rutt	O
's	O
buildings	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
by	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
desire	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rutt	O
;	O
it	O
exactly	O
fitted	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
some	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roiley	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
from	O
many	O
circumstances	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
lead	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
175	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Petrie	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Petrie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
,	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
remove	O
he	O
assisted	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
which	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
about	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
repair	O
;	O
the	O
dial	O
plate	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
amongst	O
some	O
dirt	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
have	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
176	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
OSBORN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
reading	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
eleven	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Teddington	B-place
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
about	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
town	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
message	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
my	O
maid	O
servant	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
locks	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
judged	O
from	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
somebody	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
stair-case	O
window	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
shutters	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
scrole	O
iron	O
work	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
body	O
getting	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
and	O
wrenched	O
the	O
scrole	O
iron	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
smith	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
form	O
again	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
lay	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
at	O
Kingston	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hutchins	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
goods	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
neckcloth	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Collsell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
reading	O
glass	O
,	O
two	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
pressed	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
whether	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
company	O
would	O
quit	O
the	O
room	O
perhaps	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
more	O
open	O
in	O
his	O
confession	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
desired	O
the	O
company	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bent	O
the	O
irons	O
at	O
that	O
window	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hid	O
the	O
coffee	O
pot	O
in	O
some	O
furzes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
holland	O
sheet	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Plymouth	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
directions	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Holland	O
sheet	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Bunely	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
177	O
,	O
178	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
RADFORD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
-	O
Beard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
a	O
shoe	O
warehouse	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
broke	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Peale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
who	O
has	O
left	O
me	O
took	O
in	O
these	O
shoes	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
Jones	B-pers
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
and	O
Martin	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Peale	O
's	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
shoes	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
broken	O
pane	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Thompson	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Martin	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
MARTIN	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
RADFORD	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
166	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
180	O
,	O
181	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PHILIP	B-pers
DOUGHTY	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Coley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19th	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Coley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
beef	O
from	O
my	O
stall	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Hannah	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
Harrison	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
beef	O
;	O
Doughty	O
came	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
with	O
the	O
beef	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
so	O
low	O
a	O
price	O
that	O
raised	O
my	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Coley	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
beef	O
.	O
Doughty	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
beef	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
Harrison	O
is	O
quite	O
innocent	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
182	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Linner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
stable-yard	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ewer	O
is	O
a	O
farmer	O
:	O
my	O
teem	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
stable-yard	O
.	O
His	O
man	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
hay	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
suspecting	O
him	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hay	O
in	O
his	O
stable	O
;	O
upon	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
pardon	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
183	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
GREGORY	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Monro	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Monro	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Short	B-place
's	I-place
Gardens	I-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
some	O
person	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
permitted	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
some	O
linen	O
in	O
our	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
gown	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Maguire	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
to	O
Anthony	B-pers
Gatell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Monro	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
fetch	O
something	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
missed	O
her	O
clothes	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Maguire	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Gatell	I-pers
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
184	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DENNIS	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cane	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
head	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Gaul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
,	O
we	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
greatly	O
hurt	O
and	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
lost	O
a	O
gold	O
headed	O
cane	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cane	O
with	O
the	O
head	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Gaul	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
his	O
cypher	O
E.	O
C.	O
Frances	O
Solomon	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
cane	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
and	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Stratford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
King-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fray	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knock	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
down	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
engraved	O
this	O
cypher	O
upon	O
this	O
head	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
.	O
-	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
this	O
head	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
engraved	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
cypher	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
both	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
cane	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bull's-head	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
about	O
Sunday	O
five	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
broken	O
cane	O
with	O
a	O
head	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
King-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Newton's-lane	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
up	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
broken	O
cane	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
there	O
being	O
charged	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
with	O
committing	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gaul	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
cane	O
without	O
my	O
giving	O
him	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
provocation	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
scuffle	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
Bull's-head	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Bull's-head	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
185	O
,	O
186	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRANNON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vaux	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
child	O
's	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
jams	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
;	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
quilt	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
trimmed	O
with	O
fir	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
Brannon	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Vaux	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gun-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
adjoining	O
to	O
Gun-street	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
drawers	O
gone	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Vaux	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
by	O
told	O
us	O
our	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
drawers	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
place	O
stript	O
.	O
A	O
Jew	O
came	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Tinsdale	I-pers
,	O
the	O
city	O
marshal	O
.	O
One	O
Levi	B-pers
Ashur	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cumberford	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Adget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
goods	O
from	O
them	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Vaux	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Ashur	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
week	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
sell	O
them	O
off	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
because	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
every	O
crown	O
for	O
selling	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
goods	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Brannon	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
stopt	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
are	O
produced	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cumberford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
little	O
jams	O
,	O
of	O
Levi	B-pers
Ashur	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Twelfth-day	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tinsdale	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
(	O
pointing	O
them	O
out	O
)	O
of	O
Levi	B-pers
Ashur	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Tinsdale	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cragget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Levi	B-pers
Ashur	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
small	O
things	O
to	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
myself	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
then	O
Brannon	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Dean	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
city	O
marshal	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
having	O
stole	O
the	O
clothes	O
I	O
had	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tinsdale	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
mentioned	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
observe	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
clothes	O
and	O
stole	O
others	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Brannon	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
trouble	O
before	O
.	O
If	O
my	O
witnesses	O
were	O
here	O
I	O
could	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
187	O
,	O
188	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MALE	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
MAY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Grignion	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Grignion	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hampstead	O
stage	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
coach	O
Mr.	O
Mackey	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Park	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Curtis	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
all	O
six	O
persons	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
by	O
three	O
persons	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
pistol	O
shewn	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
Grignion	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
pistol	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
brighter	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
!	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
was	O
frightened	O
at	O
that	O
?	O
Grignion	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
so	O
often	O
lately	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
frightened	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
flung	O
my	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
that	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
take	O
your	O
pistol	O
away	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
discern	O
his	O
countenance	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
Samuel	B-pers
Male	I-pers
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
July	O
preceeding	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
a	O
watch	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
.	O
Gilbert	O
Park	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
passengers	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
three	O
foot-pads	O
;	O
two	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
deliver	O
;	O
one	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Grignion	O
give	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Humphreys	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
civilly	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
pistol	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
very	O
civilly	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Macky	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
and	O
watches	O
;	O
having	O
never	O
been	O
robbed	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
confoundedly	O
frightened	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Grignion	O
put	O
some	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
foggy	O
evening	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Humphreys	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Kentish	O
town	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
Joyce	O
,	O
a	O
farrier	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
began	O
talking	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
three	O
people	O
quitted	O
the	O
box	O
immediately	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
dishonest	O
persons	O
upon	O
seeing	O
them	O
start	O
up	O
on	O
this	O
conversation	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
mug	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
liquor	O
left	O
;	O
that	O
confirmed	O
my	O
suspicion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
their	O
liquor	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Nowland	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
conversed	O
with	O
Nowland	O
about	O
the	O
robbery	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
Humphreys	O
got	O
out	O
immediately	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
wait	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
drank	O
twice	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
Humphreys	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
mug	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
quart	O
mug	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
rather	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
in	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Male	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
persons	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
cheek	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Castle	O
.	O
Three	O
young	O
men	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
quart	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
dusk	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
relation	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
committed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
their	O
persons	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Joyce	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
cheek	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
whenever	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Joyce	O
's	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
that	O
expression	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Merriman	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
London	O
with	O
the	O
patrole	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
bank	O
on	O
the	O
London	O
side	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Male	O
and	O
Humphreys	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
field	O
as	O
coming	O
a-cross	O
the	O
road	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
aloud	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
pursuing	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
saying	O
that	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
going	O
toward	O
Hampstead	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
somebody	O
follow	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
came	O
very	O
quietly	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
surrendered	O
and	O
were	O
took	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
were	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
but	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Branger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kentish	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
patrole	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
before	O
and	O
some	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Wilson	O
jumped	O
down	O
the	O
bank	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
still	O
holding	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
met	O
Halliburton	O
and	O
Bond	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
.	O
Wilson	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
information	O
made	O
on	O
Thursday	O
se'ennight	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
that	O
night	O
upon	O
the	O
Kentish	O
town	O
road	O
;	O
next	O
night	O
three	O
men	O
were	O
sent	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
to	O
wait	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Battlebridge	O
turnpike	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
stirring	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
nothing	O
occurred	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
method	O
was	O
pursued	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
at	O
Battlebridge	O
turnpike	O
,	O
which	O
commanded	O
several	O
different	O
roads	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
Halliburton	O
and	O
Taylor	O
were	O
posted	O
at	O
Battle-bridge	O
turnpike	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
an	O
information	O
was	O
received	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
coach	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
Hampstead	O
road	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
and	O
Jennings	O
came	O
immediately	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
us	O
of	O
the	O
account	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
near	O
Fig	O
lane	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
being	O
stopt	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Hampstead	O
road	O
near	O
the	O
mile	O
stone	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
come	O
by	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
opened	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
and	O
jumped	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Humphreys	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
over	O
a	O
gate	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
described	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
early	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
dropped	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
weapons	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
gate	O
in	O
some	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
loaded	O
with	O
a	O
slug	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
powder	O
and	O
primed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
farther	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
the	O
men	O
run	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
cutlass	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
se'ennight	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
at	O
Kentish	O
town	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
hearing	O
the	O
conversation	O
about	O
a	O
robbery	O
I	O
had	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
followed	O
me	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
beer	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
Kentish	O
town	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
robbed	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
this	O
cutlass	O
;	O
May	O
had	O
this	O
pistol	O
;	O
Wilson	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
putting	O
the	O
point	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
they	O
concealed	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
hanger	O
;	O
Male	O
presented	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
Male	O
opened	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
away	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
gate	O
I	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
cutlass	O
,	O
but	O
Male	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
pistol	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
cutlass	O
now	O
produced	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
cutlass	O
we	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
why	O
we	O
run	O
away	O
upon	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
coach	O
stopping	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
by	O
the	O
pace	O
:	O
a	O
common	O
stage	O
goes	O
much	O
faster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
you	O
been	O
connected	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Wilson	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
Male	O
longer	O
,	O
Male	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
quietly	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
somebody	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
these	O
people	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
tobacco	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
afterwards	O
.	O
For	O
Wilson	O
.	O
-	O
Brooksbank	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Wilson	O
from	O
his	O
childhood	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
draw	O
beer	O
;	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Wilson	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
an	O
industrious	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
one	O
time	O
waiter	O
at	O
a	O
tavern	O
;	O
afterwards	O
a	O
stone	O
cutter	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
since	O
at	O
sea	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
that	O
worked	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
the	O
stone	O
cutter	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
For	O
some	O
weeks	O
last	O
past	O
his	O
father	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Rainbow	O
tavern	O
,	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
time	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
as	O
children	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
industrious	O
lad	O
.	O
-	O
Manch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
known	O
Wilson	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
anything	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bild	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
lad	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
A	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
can	O
you	O
earn	O
a	O
week	O
at	O
your	O
trade	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
Fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine	O
pence	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MALE	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
MAY	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Robert	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
Jan	O
6	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
a	O
returned	O
pot	O
chaise	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
week	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hampstead	O
road	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Big-lane	B-place
,	O
two	O
footpads	O
stopt	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
down	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
which	O
frightened	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
observation	O
on	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cotterell	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Loran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
moon	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Humphrey	I-pers
.	O
Male	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
stopt	O
a	O
returned	O
post	O
chaise	O
with	O
two	O
persons	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
got	O
down	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
?	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
escape	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Loran	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
Loran	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Halliburton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Wilson	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
upon	O
Wilson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
two	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
trials	O
of	O
Male	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
556	O
and	O
699	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
189	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
CORMANT	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Tearman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Tearman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
quitted	O
my	O
service	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
wages	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
another	O
woman	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
?	O
Tearman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
?	O
Tearman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
190	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
191	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
,	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Horse	I-place
in	I-place
Aldersgate-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
some	O
mutton	O
chops	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Aldesey	I-pers
.	O
Dewy	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Dewy	O
,	O
Suspecting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stubbs	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
had	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
when	O
these	O
two	O
pots	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
192	O
,	O
193	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
SMITHERS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
BRACKET	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
thread	O
button	O
and	O
loop	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Yeates	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9th	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Yeates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
paper	O
stainer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
Smithers	O
snatched	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
Wide-gate-alley	O
;	O
she	O
slipped	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hat	O
lie	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
down	O
Bracket	O
;	O
they	O
demanded	O
five	O
shillings	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
cleave	O
my	O
skull	O
if	O
I	O
dare	O
take	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
familiar	O
pass	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
Yeates	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
fun	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
decoy	O
you	O
into	O
this	O
place	O
?	O
Yeates	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
decoy	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudgson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoners	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
does	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
behaved	O
?	O
Hudgson	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
order	O
and	O
propriety	O
.	O
SMITHERS	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
BRACKET	O
acquitted	O
.	O
194	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
BARNARD	B-pers
KILROY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
sir	O
timber	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Alexandar	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
master	O
builder	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
American-square	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Minories	I-place
;	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
timber	O
in	O
question	O
lying	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
materials	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Minories	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
from	O
America	O
square	O
with	O
two	O
sir	O
planks	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
so	O
ill	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
handcuff	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Leniton	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
195	O
,	O
196	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
KITCHENSIDE	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
REEVES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
legs	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Newport-market	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
legs	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shop	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
my	O
meat	O
was	O
in	O
White-chapel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
meat	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
cutting	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Major	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
meat	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
HERRING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9th	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Exeter-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
all	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
silk	O
purse	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
.	O
My	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
neck-cloth	O
and	O
hat	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
This	O
hat	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
girl	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
neckcloth	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
198	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
gilt	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nathaniel	O
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
between	O
the	O
Pantheon	B-place
and	O
the	O
London	B-place
Spaw	I-place
,	O
by	O
two	O
foot-pads	O
:	O
one	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
pistol	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
myself	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
delivering	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Staines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Bray	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
Bray	O
had	O
the	O
cutlass	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
Bray	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
silver	O
afterwards	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
employment	O
as	O
myself	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
employed	O
by	O
Justice	O
Camper	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
offered	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Conway	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
Bray	O
and	O
Staines	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
Bray	O
and	O
Staines	O
;	O
Staines	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
watches	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
Bray	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
conversation	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
by	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
decoyed	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
Wellclose-square	O
;	O
when	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
watches	O
;	O
Bray	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
metal	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
called	O
it	O
gold	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Camper	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
both	O
Staines	O
and	O
Bray	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Camper	O
;	O
and	O
Bray	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
the	O
metal	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
Staines	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
as	O
taken	O
by	O
Philip	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
which	O
Bray	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
Conway	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
Staines	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
metal	O
watch	O
in	O
Bray	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
both	O
went	O
together	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
Conway	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
compass	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
hook	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Dec.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Shepherdess	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
footpads	O
;	O
one	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
me	O
this	O
silver	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
)	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
one	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
painting	O
in	O
the	O
dial	O
plate	O
;	O
the	O
account	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
the	O
master	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
watch	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
without	O
a	O
chain	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
some	O
witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pinfold	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
chain	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
the	O
same	O
witnesses	O
as	O
before	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
Being	O
in	O
the	O
Islington	O
stage	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
two	O
footpads	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Staines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
stopt	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
Bray	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
stage	O
coachman	O
that	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
robbed	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
observation	O
enough	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
them	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
upon	O
the	O
accomplice	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
produced	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
by	O
Conway	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
same	O
witnesses	O
as	O
before	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
199	O
,	O
200	O
,	O
201	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PATRICK	B-pers
TRANER	I-pers
,	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DARLING	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
LEWIN	I-pers
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DARLING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
fine	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30th	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
bell	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
missed	O
this	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
sugar	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
three	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
changed	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Lyons	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
sugar	O
and	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
first	O
in	O
a	O
striped	O
jacket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
changed	O
his	O
dress	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
by	O
the	O
bell	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
confession	O
was	O
first	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
when	O
I	O
confessed	O
;	O
they	O
threatened	O
to	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
irons	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
203	O
,	O
204	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PATRICK	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
BRAY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
16th	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Onley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
's	O
stables	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
saw	O
Dunn	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
some	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
where	O
his	O
stables	O
are	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
Bray	O
?	O
Onley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
ten	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
Dunn	O
owned	O
next	O
morning	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
hay	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
's	O
stables	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Some	O
tiles	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
roof	O
that	O
night	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
with	O
hay	O
upon	O
their	O
backs	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
Dunn	O
's	O
person	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
DUNN	O
guilty	O
.	O
BRAY	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
205	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ARTHUR	B-pers
BRADLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
pick	O
axes	O
with	O
wooden	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
wooden	O
hods	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
iron	O
shovels	O
with	O
wooden	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elkin	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
at	O
Marybone	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
prevarication	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Elkin	O
's	O
stables	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elkin	I-pers
.	O
Only	O
these	O
two	O
hods	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOBBS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
containing	O
ten	O
gallons	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wollaston	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wollaston	O
,	O
a	O
distiller	O
,	O
on	O
Holborn-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
some	O
gin	O
and	O
other	O
liquors	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
other	O
orders	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
cut	O
and	O
the	O
cask	O
of	O
Geneva	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
the	O
vessel	O
was	O
staved	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
gallons	O
was	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
twice	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
catched	O
at	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
whip	O
.	O
William	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
a	O
shop	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
cart	O
stood	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cask	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
staved	O
the	O
cask	O
and	O
then	O
Morris	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cask	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
sell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
its	O
head	O
for	O
fear	O
the	O
liquor	O
should	O
run	O
out	O
.	O
Morris	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
indifferent	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
READ	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
deal	O
boards	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Maggot	B-pers
William	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12th	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
other	O
deals	O
,	O
Dec.	O
14th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
geese	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Turpin	B-pers
Barket	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Turpin	O
Barket	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
geese	O
cry	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
Green	O
had	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
another	O
into	O
the	O
sack	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
poker	O
;	O
he	O
himself	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
sack	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
dark	O
?	O
Barket	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
geese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
goose	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
my	O
head	O
very	O
badly	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
his	O
geese	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HUMPHRYS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
said	O
notes	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hobsendorf	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Second	O
Court	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hobsendorf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
notes	O
from	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
judge	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
church	O
;	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
church	O
was	O
locked	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
one	O
door	O
opening	O
to	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
was	O
locked	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
42	O
l.	O
there	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
taken	O
out	O
as	O
amounts	O
to	O
20	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
bank	O
notes	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
two	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hardigram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
chapel	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
pictures	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
separate	O
from	O
each	O
other	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
staid	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
dress	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
five	O
minutes	O
must	O
have	O
passed	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
separated	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
seeing	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
form	O
any	O
opinion	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
custom	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
always	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
his	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
chamber	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
but	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
cash	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
relying	O
for	O
my	O
security	O
upon	O
the	O
doors	O
always	O
being	O
kept	O
locked	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
never	O
left	O
open	O
but	O
for	O
her	O
making	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
always	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
.	O
Hardigram	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
suffered	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
separation	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
-	O
Warr	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
a	O
stone	O
stock	O
buckle	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
payment	O
for	O
it	O
passed	O
off	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
its	O
marks	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
a	O
hosier	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Warr	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Payne	O
,	O
bankers	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Payne	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
that	O
bank	O
note	O
now	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
's	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
always	O
do	O
write	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
receive	O
bank	O
notes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
tellers	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
note	O
paid	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
by	O
Smith	O
and	O
Payne	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Basket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
War	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
tea	O
,	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
15	O
l.	O
was	O
paid	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
claimed	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hobsendorf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
directions	O
from	O
my	O
uncle	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
note	O
paid	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
denied	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
Bank	O
note	O
;	O
then	O
afterwards	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
thorough	O
search	O
would	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bank	O
notes	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
and	O
bed	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
opened	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
about	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
and	O
the	O
stock	O
buckle	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
remained	O
of	O
the	O
produce	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Golden-square	O
;	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
refer	O
to	O
your	O
books	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
referred	O
to	O
my	O
books	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	O
Grab	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Humphrey	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
and	O
I	O
together	O
;	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
notes	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
notes	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
farther	O
in	O
his	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
and	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
produce	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
promised	O
me	O
favour	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Claudius	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Laycock	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
afterwards	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Humphrey	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hobsendorf	I-pers
say	O
,	O
confess	O
,	O
confess	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
servant	O
maid	O
.	O
I	O
introduced	O
this	O
gentleman	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
own	O
it	O
and	O
be	O
clear	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Hobsendorf	I-pers
and	O
Grub	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
promise	O
,	O
or	O
use	O
any	O
threats	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
this	O
confession	O
.	O
Both	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
none	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
that	O
declaration	O
voluntarily	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
the	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
eight	O
guineas	O
were	O
the	O
product	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
before	O
any	O
promise	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Hobsendorf	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
and	O
we	O
may	O
bush	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
that	O
confession	O
before	O
that	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
210	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
KELLY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Brockuls	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
MARRIAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
~	O
Isabella	O
Cummings	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tafe	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
house-keeper	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
linen	O
shift	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
clothes	O
basket	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Tafe	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
bed	O
gown	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
place	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
six	O
months	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
continued	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Runner	O
of	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
by	O
getting	O
through	O
a	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
as	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
old-clothes-man	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
night	O
precisely	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
hole	O
by	O
the	O
chimney	O
which	O
a	O
person	O
might	O
get	O
through	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HERMAN	B-pers
LIMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
,	O
Savoy-hill	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Barleymow	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
Norris	O
's	O
pocket	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Barleymow	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
two-pence	O
or	O
two-pence	O
halfpenny	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
brother	O
;	O
Norris	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Barleymow	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
brought	O
Norris	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Barleymow	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
landlord	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
till	O
Norris	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Whentley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
key	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Barleymow	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
sell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
liquor	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
enough	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Sawtill	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
mens	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Sawtill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
hats	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sudden	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
the	O
hats	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Weal	O
;	O
one	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Doharty	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Weal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hat-maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
hats	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
another	O
that	O
I	O
stopped	O
.	O
(	O
