TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
JUNE	O
,	O
1773	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
L.	O
)	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
Morgan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
John	B-pers
Winstone	I-pers
William	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
James	B-pers
James	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Haskew	I-pers
William	B-pers
Furrier	I-pers
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
John	B-pers
Meane	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whittingbury	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Drewitt	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Grammar	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Sandwell	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
James	B-pers
Forsyth	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
George	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Evett	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Day	I-pers
James	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
James	B-pers
Blyth	I-pers
William	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Raine	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bramble	I-pers
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
486	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
CONNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
120	O
half-pence	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19th	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
upon	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
stockings	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
check	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
inform	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
5	O
s.	O
worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
found	O
the	O
half-pence	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
half-pence	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
her	O
mother	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
charge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
487	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
iron	O
streaks	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
17th	O
.	O
+	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
wheeler	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
wheels	O
about	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
near	O
White-Conduit-house	O
,	O
knocking	O
some	O
streaks	O
off	O
a	O
wheel	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
same	O
field	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
knocking	O
some	O
iron	O
off	O
of	O
another	O
wheel	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Wellings	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dodd	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
any	O
wheels	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Welling	O
's	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
breaking	O
up	O
a	O
wheel	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welling	O
's	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laying	O
the	O
iron	O
together	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
and	O
found	O
six	O
streaks	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
the	O
fellies	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
streaks	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
bird	O
's	O
claw	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
streaks	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
breaking	O
up	O
the	O
wheel	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
488	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
96	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
489	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
STARLING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
note	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
Feb.	O
27th	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Queen-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
three	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
book	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
notes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
into	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
40	O
l.	O
note	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
my	O
other	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
any	O
note	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Plumpton	O
,	O
a	O
mercer	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plumpton	O
's	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
produced	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
in	O
the	O
bank	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
because	O
my	O
note	O
was	O
payable	O
to	O
Dean	O
and	O
Co	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
date	O
or	O
number	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
indorsment	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
John	B-pers
Gennings	I-pers
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
hand	O
writing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
lost	O
this	O
note	O
at	O
Blackheath	O
or	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
?	O
Crofts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
my	O
garden	O
at	O
Blackheath	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fado	I-pers
.	O
I	O
paid	O
this	O
note	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
who	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
whoever	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
wrote	O
John	B-pers
Gennings	I-pers
upon	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Silverthorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crofts	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
often	O
talked	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
this	O
note	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
thought	O
would	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
several	O
times	O
asked	O
me	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
whether	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plumpton	O
's	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
note	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
15	O
s.	O
she	O
owed	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
servants	O
trifles	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
this	O
raised	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
at	O
Blackheath	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
Silverthorn	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
otherwise	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
490	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
LEVI	B-pers
ASHER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
black	O
down	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gate-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
black	O
down	O
silk	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
drawn	O
from	O
the	O
padlock	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
people	O
below	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
examination	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
this	O
lad	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
the	O
silk	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
silk	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
1	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
that	O
Craddock	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
silk	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
silk	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
this	O
silk	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Craddock	I-pers
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Asher	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
silk	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Asher	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
behave	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
honour	O
his	O
parents	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
child	O
,	O
or	O
chick	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
portering	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
491	O
,	O
492	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
MONK	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LUSHBY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thitchener	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
sixteen	O
muslin	O
neck-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Thitchener	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	B-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
great	I-place
Newport-street	I-place
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
the	O
cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
forcing	O
the	O
hinges	O
off	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
till	O
full	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
the	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
keys	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hanby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
had	O
the	O
top	O
bolt	O
bolted	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
padlock	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
was	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
young	O
mistress	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Hanby	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
spoons	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
daughter	O
in	O
law	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cordee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
:	O
these	O
four	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Monk	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Cordee	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
Monk	O
had	O
hired	O
a	O
horse	O
for	O
an	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
it	O
two	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
two	O
balls	O
;	O
these	O
picklock	O
keys	O
and	O
this	O
tinder	O
box	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
(	O
producing	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
)	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
gloves	O
in	O
a	O
coat	O
pocket	O
at	O
Monk	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
gloves	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Monk	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
tinder	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lock-smith	O
by	O
trade	O
and	O
constantly	O
carry	O
pick	O
locks	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Grubb	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
tinder	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
advertisement	O
described	O
the	O
buckskin	O
gloves	O
as	O
having	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shot	O
holes	O
and	O
tears	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
these	O
had	O
.	O
Monk	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
not	O
any	O
holes	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Grubb	O
is	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
gloves	O
.	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Lushby	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
sold	O
china	O
;	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
brought	O
by	O
Monk	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
his	O
brother	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Monk	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Lushby	O
live	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Monk	O
lodge	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
In	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Lushby	O
bring	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Grubb	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
in	O
Monk	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
gloves	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Monk	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
two	O
shot	O
holes	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
gloves	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
night	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
these	O
shot	O
holes	O
in	O
them	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
them	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
shot	O
holes	O
.	O
Monk	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
gloves	O
from	O
my	O
brother	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
Lushby	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
odd	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
these	O
marks	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
a	O
cup	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
amends	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Lushby	O
called	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
Whitmore	O
Wilson	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
from	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Lattrum	I-pers
nine	O
years	O
;	O
-	O
Pettigree	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
five	O
years	O
;	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
four	O
years	O
;	O
Mark	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Candling	I-pers
some	O
time	O
.	O
Monk	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hugh	I-pers
ten	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
493	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
494	O
,	O
495	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
CONNOR	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
pinchbeck	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
in	O
Half-Moon-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
play	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
picked	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
my	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
her	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
Dover	B-place
passage	I-place
;	O
James	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
Connor	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
wind	O
pipe	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
tight	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Hoare	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
seeing	O
the	O
woman	O
go	O
off	O
without	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
;	O
they	O
released	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
out	O
after	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Berkeley-street	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
Connor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
this	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
take	O
Connor	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
I	O
felt	O
them	O
pull	O
at	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
string	O
;	O
it	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
seal	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
play	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
;	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
whom	O
does	O
the	O
family	O
consist	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
The	O
father	O
,	O
mother	O
and	O
brother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
you	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
strolling	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
intent	O
to	O
strole	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
fine	O
night	O
and	O
nobody	O
was	O
in	O
town	O
:	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
road	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Albermarle-street	O
from	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
's	O
arm	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
refused	O
and	O
turned	O
back	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
they	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Dover-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
walked	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
cross	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
seeing	O
me	O
stand	O
there	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
reeled	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
toward	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
Cellar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
presently	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
the	O
passage	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
down	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
like	O
a	O
person	O
strangling	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Connor	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
little	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
Connor	O
made	O
a	O
stroke	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
blow	O
upon	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
second	O
stroke	O
and	O
missed	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
off	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
into	O
Berkeley-street	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
this	O
Connor	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Old	O
Pye-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
Connor	O
lodges	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
no	O
know	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
neither	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
sometimes	O
I	O
might	O
happen	O
to	O
lie	O
a	O
night	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
296	O
,	O
297	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PLASTOW	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
dimity	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Doggin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Queen-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
breakfast	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
two	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
the	O
numbers	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bill	O
which	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
cash	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
desk	O
in	O
the	O
compting	O
house	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
the	O
table	O
cloths	O
and	O
petticoats	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
thieves	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
tap	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
or	O
nailed	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
believe	O
both	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
who	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
About	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
petticoats	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Doggin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
hat	O
from	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
.	O
-	O
Dalton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
the	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jeffereys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
tap	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Evans	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
tap	O
house	O
with	O
Wilson	O
at	O
near	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
James	O
Wilson	O
went	O
as	O
we	O
thought	O
out	O
;	O
Evans	O
was	O
or	O
pretended	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
;	O
he	O
waked	O
,	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
till	O
near	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
said	O
next	O
morning	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Wilson	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
George	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
that	O
evening	O
upon	O
some	O
company	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
:	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Wilson	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Jeffereys	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
about	O
a	O
foot	O
square	O
that	O
the	O
beer	O
is	O
handed	O
through	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
petticoats	O
and	O
shoes	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Bloomsbury-market	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Plastow	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
house	O
do	O
you	O
lodge	O
?	O
Burford	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hookham	O
's	O
.	O
Percival	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
Wilson	O
said	O
Plastow	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-market	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
petticoats	O
and	O
shoes	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burford	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
Plastow	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
a	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Halliburton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
three	O
pistol	O
bullets	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
second	O
search	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
behind	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Murthwaite	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
:	O
Charles	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
pledged	O
this	O
hat	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
.	O
Dogget	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
hat	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
.	O
-	O
Gray	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
hat	O
for	O
Dogget	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
on	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Paxton	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Titchfield-street	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
the	O
scheme	O
was	O
,	O
Paxton	O
was	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
knock	O
the	O
maid	O
down	O
as	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
saw	O
us	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
secrete	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap	O
;	O
the	O
Captain	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Jeffereys	O
's	O
cellar	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
which	O
parts	O
the	O
two	O
cellars	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
bar	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
;	O
then	O
Evans	O
and	O
Plastow	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Captain	O
shoved	O
the	O
sash	O
back	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
away	O
some	O
table	O
linen	O
and	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
Evans	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
taken	O
about	O
20	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
;	O
the	O
Captain	O
gave	O
Evans	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Little	O
Queen-street	O
together	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
night	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
;	O
then	O
Evans	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
George's-fields	O
;	O
afterwards	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
Plastow	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
gave	O
Evans	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
get	O
it	O
altered	O
;	O
Evans	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
got	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
some	O
buckles	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
Plastow	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shoes	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
some	O
children	O
's	O
petticoats	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Burford	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
petticoats	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Q.	O
Plastow	O
lodged	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
lodgings	O
when	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
lodgings	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
asleep	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bullets	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
any	O
bank	O
notes	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
got	O
one	O
bank	O
note	O
but	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burford	I-pers
.	O
Plastow	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
how	O
long	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
?	O
Burford	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
coat	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
?	O
Burford	O
.	O
Plastow	O
's	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
belonged	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
was	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Burford	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
pistols	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
Plastow	O
lodged	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Burford	O
.	O
Six	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Both	O
lodged	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
?	O
Burford	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Plastow	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
that	O
night	O
till	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
very	O
fuddled	O
:	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistols	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Evan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Wilson	O
going	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Jefferys	O
's	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
complied	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
Wilson	O
had	O
another	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
upon	O
a	O
message	O
for	O
Jefferys	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
and	O
drink	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
beer	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
head	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
Wilson	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
Long-lane	O
I	O
met	O
Wilson	O
:	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
Catherine-street	O
,	O
Wilson	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
making	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
constables	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
frightened	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
at	O
Murthwaite	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
and	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
Plastow	O
's	O
lodgings	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
play	O
at	O
skittles	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
service	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
For	O
Plastow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
17	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
muffin-baker	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
master	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
bear	O
any	O
than	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
service	O
to-morrow	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
WARBEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
weather	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Story	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tottenham-high-cross	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
sheep	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
grounds	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
mutton	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
his	O
house	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
whole	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
sheep	O
and	O
a	O
sheep	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
:	O
upon	O
his	O
examination	O
he	O
fully	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
field	O
,	O
killed	O
a	O
weather	O
sheep	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
mutton	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
who	O
his	O
partner	O
was	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
another	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
sheep	O
,	O
a	O
leg	O
,	O
shoulder	O
and	O
neck	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
sack	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
pond	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
confession	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
made	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
freely	O
and	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
mutton	O
wrapped	O
up	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
friends	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
299	O
,	O
300	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOWS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
27	O
gallons	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
:	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
beer	O
stole	O
from	O
a	O
store-cellar	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
brewer	O
starts	O
beer	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
beer	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
it	O
is	O
started	O
the	O
brewer	O
puts	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
account	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
bringing	O
beer	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
store	O
cellar	O
in	O
Woodsclose	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
pail	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
pail	O
full	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Hows	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
surly	O
answers	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
secured	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
followed	O
Jones	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
with	O
a	O
pail	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Bell-yard	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
pail	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
in	O
securing	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
two	O
gallons	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
pail	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
How	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
pulled	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
and	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
Mon	O
.	O
301	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
GORMAN	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
laced	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
eleven	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
~	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
a	B-place
back	I-place
garret	I-place
in	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
,	I-place
facing	I-place
Brownlow-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
sleeves	O
and	O
cloak	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
drawer	O
was	O
locked	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
counterpane	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
fore	O
garret	O
door	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
things	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
them	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
things	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
down	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
raised	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
and	O
committed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Miln	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
had	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
dropt	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
wash.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
two	O
loads	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Red-Lion-square	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
,	O
who	O
owed	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
's	O
rent	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
wrong	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
302	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
David	B-pers
Crussell	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
seal	O
made	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
.	O
*	O
David	B-pers
Crussell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
fields	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
with	O
pale	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
behind	O
me	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
A	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Layton	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
Star-light	O
,	O
but	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
information	O
in	O
at	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
men	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Camper	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
In	O
blue	O
clothes	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
seal	O
,	O
or	O
key	O
again	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Crussell	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
immediately	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
there	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
him	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pick	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
he	O
shewn	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
fi	O
ve	O
or	O
six	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
and	O
stature	O
in	O
my	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2481	O
,	O
William	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
makers	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
near	O
six	O
weeks	O
after	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
men	O
they	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
hand-cuffed	O
?	O
Crussell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Edward	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
read	O
at	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
,	O
blue	O
clothes	O
and	O
jacket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hand-cuffed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
man	O
challenged	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
hand-cuffed	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
hospital	O
,	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
my	O
disorder	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
leg	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
distemper	O
.	O
The	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
hospital	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
admission	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
patients	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
lordship	O
's	O
order	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
The	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
quite	O
sober	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
sober	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
court	O
whose	O
house	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
40	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
place	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
he	O
gave	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
is	O
about	O
twice	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
quite	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
burying	O
go	O
by	O
;	O
the	O
coaches	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
Till	O
he	O
wrote	O
out	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
bread	O
both	O
of	O
his	O
uncle	O
and	O
uncle	O
's	O
father	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
diligent	O
sober	O
man	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
otherwise	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
303	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
VAUGHAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
live	O
cock	O
turkey	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
live	O
hen	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
eleven	O
eggs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
's	O
gardener	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
fowls	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
safe	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
hen	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
some	O
eggs	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
from	O
the	O
roost	O
,	O
a	O
house	O
almost	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Another	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
's	O
servants	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
house	O
door	O
was	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
A	O
watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
he	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
contained	O
five	O
turkeys	O
,	O
two	O
ducks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hen	O
,	O
and	O
eleven	O
eggs	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
also	O
found	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
some	O
matches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
picklock	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
's	O
servants	O
came	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
saw	O
these	O
turkeys	O
and	O
other	O
fowls	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
fowls	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Harrow	O
:	O
they	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
barn	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
laughing	O
about	O
the	O
plunder	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
they	O
talked	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
about	O
the	O
dog	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
acceptable	O
to	O
my	O
children	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
no	O
victuals	O
to	O
eat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
intending	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
304	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chisholm	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
six	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chisholm	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
11th	O
mile	O
stone	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
he	O
then	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
coming	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
further	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
servants	O
on	O
horse	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
highwaymen	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
two	O
servants	O
I	O
met	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
him	O
as	O
having	O
a	O
slouched	O
hat	O
;	O
nothing	O
more	O
particularly	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Chisholm	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
slouched	O
hat	O
and	O
a	O
brown	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Chisholm	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
we	O
overtook	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Longford	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
him	O
on	O
horse	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Morsoot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Phillips	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Chisholm	O
stopped	O
his	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
fight	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Longford	O
on	O
foot	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
11th	O
mile	O
stone	O
;	O
we	O
rode	O
gently	O
on	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walked	O
gently	O
on	O
.	O
A	O
Mr.	O
Bullion	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
chaise	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
did	O
you	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
for	O
we	O
would	O
see	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
either	O
with	O
my	O
whip	O
or	O
horse	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Cranford-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
four	O
slugs	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
knife	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
produces	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Reading	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
miles	O
out	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
horses	O
tumbled	O
over	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
horse	O
pond	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
resist	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bullin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chair-maker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
worked	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
within	O
a	O
day	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
holiday	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
lad	O
as	O
ever	O
worked	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
way	O
of	O
accounting	O
for	O
this	O
strange	O
conduct	O
?	O
Bullin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
connections	O
that	O
had	O
involved	O
him	O
in	O
debt	O
?	O
Bullin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
pistol	O
?	O
Bullin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
305	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
LONE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slapp	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
barley	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
bread	O
cakes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
..	O
and	O
three	O
glass	O
fountains	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slapp	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Slapp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slapp	I-pers
:	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
shop	O
near	B-place
Carnaby-market	I-place
:	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
watchman	O
alarmed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
pinned	O
;	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
one	O
shutter	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
butcher	O
's	O
cleaver	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
alarm	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
alarmed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
cleaver	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
slaughter-house	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
over	O
head	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
person	O
with	O
the	O
cleaver	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
returning	O
home	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Hopkins-street	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
went	O
a	O
few	O
steps	O
,	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
the	O
sixtieth	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
moment	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
in	O
Carnaby-street	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
two	O
fountains	O
were	O
thrown	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
dropped	O
.	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Slapp	O
deposes	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
portering	O
to	O
Newgate-market	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
frightened	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
entirely	O
for	O
want	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
starving	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Silly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
drawn	O
beer	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
pretty	O
near	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
time	O
in	O
Great-White-Lion-street	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
only	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
306	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Lamb	O
Smith	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
shift-sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
;	O
one	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hoxton	B-place
:	O
I	O
hold	O
a	O
lease	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
communication	O
with	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
family	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
A	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
I	O
permitted	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
habitation	O
till	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
:	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
labour	O
daily	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
large	O
garden	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
works	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
coming	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
up	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
all	O
up	O
stairs	O
together	O
at	O
supper	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
o'clock	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
apron	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
After	O
nine	O
;	O
then	O
Catherine	O
Hyde	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
my	O
apartments	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
missing	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
part	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
but	O
the	O
bed	O
quilt	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
down	O
what	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
at	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
giving	O
in	O
my	O
information	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
that	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
being	O
forced	O
open	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
being	O
broke	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
sold	O
in	O
Fashion-street	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
washed	O
my	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
till	O
eight	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
lodgers	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
all	O
the	O
evening	O
there	O
till	O
Wright	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
alarm	O
about	O
the	O
apron	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
your	O
things	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
A	O
gown	O
and	O
two	O
shifts	O
were	O
folded	O
for	O
ironing	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
line	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
state	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
lock	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
it	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
think	O
you	O
locked	O
it	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
sure	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
then	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
steps	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
upon	O
them	O
and	O
called	O
Kitty	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
some	O
fish	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
apron	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
.	O
Were	O
your	O
things	O
safe	O
when	O
you	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Hyde	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
tied	O
upon	O
the	O
line	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
old	O
sheets	O
and	O
three	O
shifts	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Jarvis	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
three	O
weeks	O
next	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
at	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
sheets	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
shifts	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
White	O
and	O
Smith	O
before	O
?	O
Jarvis	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
White	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
Smith	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
buried	O
her	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sell	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
6	O
s.	O
White	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
bid	O
7	O
s.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
Fashion-street	O
?	O
Jarvis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elliston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
watchmen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
goods	O
in	O
Leg-alley	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Holywell-street	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
White	O
lodged	O
at	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
one	O
Mr.	O
White	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
given	O
information	O
before	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
being	O
robbed	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
Elliston	O
brought	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
White	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
gown	O
or	O
cardinal	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Wright	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Thursday	O
following	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
his	O
examination	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
knowing	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
.	O
White	O
told	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
sold	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Smith	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
A	O
weaver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
connected	O
together	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
to	O
be	O
connected	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
this	O
business	O
I	O
understand	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
only	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Weavers	O
Arms	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
when	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Lamb	O
Smith	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
Lamb	O
Smith	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
door	O
is	O
fast	O
,	O
lend	O
me	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
had	O
several	O
false	O
keys	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
Lamb	O
Smith	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
as	O
many	O
things	O
as	O
his	O
apron	O
would	O
hold	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
afterwards	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
three	O
shifts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
A	O
gown	O
,	O
cardinal	O
,	O
apron	O
,	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
bed	O
quilt	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
;	O
nothing	O
was	O
sold	O
but	O
the	O
three	O
sheets	O
and	O
shifts	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
robbing	O
such	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
seeing	O
no	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
nobody	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
nobody	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
E.	O
Wright	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
stocking	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
;	O
the	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
gown	O
is	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
not	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
nor	O
are	O
they	O
all	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Every	O
thing	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
belongs	O
to	O
either	O
the	O
girl	O
or	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
spare	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
along	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
carry	O
this	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
sheets	O
and	O
three	O
shifts	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
Fashion-street	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
will	O
you	O
say	O
these	O
are	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
because	O
this	O
woman	O
knows	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
sorry	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
poverty	O
;	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
stolen	O
I	O
consented	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
ask	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
that	O
man	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
Butcher	O
,	O
Chapman	O
and	O
Flanagan	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
Crab-tree-row	O
,	O
Hackney	O
,	O
or	O
Bethnal-green	O
,	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
persuaded	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
swear	O
false	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
Charles	B-pers
Flanagan	I-pers
touched	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
swear	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
dubious	O
;	O
Flanagan	O
stooped	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elliston	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
when	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
examined	O
?	O
Elliston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Flanagan	O
there	O
?	O
Elliston	O
.	O
White	O
and	O
Smith	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
round	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
oath	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
about	O
Flanagan	O
?	O
Elliston	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
E.	O
Wright	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
complain	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Flanagan	O
's	O
wanting	O
men	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Chapman	O
gave	O
Wright	O
written	O
down	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Chapman	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
write	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Elliston	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Chapman	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
these	O
instructions	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
swear	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
concerning	O
being	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
this	O
Smith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
this	O
?	O
Elliston	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
first	O
public	O
house	O
beyond	O
the	O
blacksmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
towards	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Examine	O
his	O
pockets	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
any	O
thing	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
searched	O
but	O
no	O
paper	O
is	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
307	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
STRAHAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
chariot	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
inn-keeper	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
:	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gard	O
's	O
chariot	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
or	O
Friday	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
thing	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
when	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
Ranelagh	O
to	O
send	O
their	O
chariots	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
they	O
want	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
horses	O
from	O
the	O
chariot	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
outside	O
carriage	O
next	O
the	O
row	O
;	O
it	O
went	O
away	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
a	O
glass	O
was	O
missed	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Starkey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
ostler	O
:	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
Mr.	O
Gard	O
's	O
chariot	O
was	O
set	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
remained	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
it	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
standing	O
by	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
whistling	O
by	O
through	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
stopped	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
doing	O
so	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
chariot	O
glass	O
,	O
the	O
frame	O
broken	O
off	O
,	O
concealed	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
The	O
glasses	O
were	O
safe	O
when	O
the	O
chariot	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
308	O
,	O
309	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
ETHERIDGE	I-pers
and	O
CHARLOTTE	B-pers
BEARD	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BUTCHER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacque	B-pers
D'Aubigny	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
.	O
*	O
Jacque	B-pers
D'Aubigny	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
the	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
these	O
creatures	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Beard	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
evidence	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Peter's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Mitchel	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
undress	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
and	O
soon	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
waked	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
clothes	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mitchell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
some	O
clothes	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
lent	O
me	O
some	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
waked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
three	O
women	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
?	O
D'Aubigny	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
D'Aubigny	O
.	O
In	O
Old	O
Bond-street	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
cook	O
to	O
Lord	O
Buckinghamshire	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Murthwaite	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
breeches	O
,	O
hat	O
,	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Murthwaite	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
eight	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jeyes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
hat	O
was	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
:	O
I	O
serve	O
Mary	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
)	O
with	O
bread	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Mrs.	O
Manning	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
girl	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
buckles	O
of	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
there	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
buckles	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Heeling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
neckcloth	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Beard	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
nine-pence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Peter's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
chimney	O
sweeper	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
lodgings	O
;	O
Etheridge	O
and	O
Wilson	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
Beard	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
room	O
?	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
Up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
backwards	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
that	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
clothes	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
his	O
friends	O
for	O
some	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
or	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
?	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
bring	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
they	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Beard	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Etheridge	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
we	O
lived	O
together	O
a	O
week	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Mitchel	O
's	O
.	O
Four	O
of	O
us	O
together	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
met	O
this	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Beard	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
very	O
willingly	O
with	O
you	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Beard	O
undressed	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
neckcloth	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
;	O
Etheridge	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
stood	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
undressed	O
him	O
,	O
Etheridge	O
and	O
Jackson	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
purl	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
purl	O
;	O
Sarah	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
went	O
out	O
and	O
met	O
George	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
;	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Maiden-head	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Williams	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
pawned	O
the	O
hat	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
Beard	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
concern	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
Mitchel	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
Etheridge	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
neckcloth	O
.	O
Etheridge	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stripped	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
more	O
shame	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
Beard	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
mother	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Carnaby-street	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
lodgers	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
service	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Feathers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Beard	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
baby	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
310	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LADE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
tail	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
white	O
down	O
his	O
nose	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
field	O
last	O
Friday	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Great	O
Stanmore	O
on	O
Friday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
hollowed	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
Lawrence	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Shenton	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Dick	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
that	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
two-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
turnpikes	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
horse	O
wherever	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
money	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
Dodd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
part	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
the	O
summer	O
without	O
work	O
.	O
-	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
calling	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
two-pence	O
and	O
a	O
halter	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
horse	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
horse	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
311	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRITT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
18th	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Purl	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
put	O
my	O
carriage	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
harness	O
from	O
the	O
horses	O
when	O
Skelton	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coach-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
Skelton	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Northumberland-passage	O
with	O
this	O
coat	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
(	O
produces	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
Skelton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach-house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
dark	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Purl	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
corner	O
of	O
Northumberland-passage	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Another	O
man	O
fell	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
this	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
and	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
M	O
.	O
312	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Langfer	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
corals	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
two	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
small	O
iron	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
thirty	O
crowns	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
dollars	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
topaz	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
mock	O
garnet	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
hair	O
pins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
tofful	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
soup	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
and	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Langfer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Langfer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Lemon	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
from	O
my	O
country	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
information	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robbed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
drawers	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
chamber	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
bed	O
burnt	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
back	O
chamber	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
wainscot	O
was	O
burnt	O
through	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
fire	O
all	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
my	O
drawers	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
several	O
bank	O
notes	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
cash	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
signs	O
of	O
a	O
breaking	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
door	O
or	O
window	O
with	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
somebody	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
that	O
morning	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
but	O
your	O
bed	O
room	O
?	O
Langfer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
double	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
hangs	O
in	O
the	O
workshop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
where	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
easily	O
get	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
work-shop	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
dog	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
dog	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dog	O
knew	O
him	O
I	O
suppose	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
does	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
difficulty	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
