TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
.	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1773	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JAMES	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
L.	O
)	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Finden	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Bodlidge	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Milne	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lardner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Banner	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bonus	I-pers
James	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wm	I-pers
.	I-pers
Preston	I-pers
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heatley	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Flagman	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Metcalfe	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Whywall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
Clark	B-pers
Durnford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
James	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
Packer	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
David	B-pers
Davids	I-pers
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Archibald	I-pers
Mark	B-pers
Toole	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Brittan	I-pers
William	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
Arthur	B-pers
Stroder	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Villiers	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lillingston	I-pers
William	B-pers
Decly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pinnock	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
George	B-pers
Knelham	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
353	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHRISTOPHER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
four	O
corded	O
dimity	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
fix	O
damask	O
linen	O
clouts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
coat	O
of	O
a	O
toilet	O
table	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
breakfast	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
fix	O
linen	O
dusting	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six-linen	O
pillowbiers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
harrateen	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
check	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
woollen	O
packing	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
lawn	O
ruffle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Moulds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
Kingsland-green	B-place
;	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
town	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dobbs	O
lives	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
gate	O
unlocked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
double	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
nothing	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
(	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
gate	O
unlocked	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
double	O
locked	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cupboard	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
bedding	O
and	O
the	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
;	O
the	O
locks	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
all	O
opened	O
but	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
keys	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
a	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
fast	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
dog	O
bark	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
still	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
?	O
Moulds	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
begging	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Niece	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dobbs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
town	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Moulds	O
's	O
husband	O
came	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
things	O
missing	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
inventory	O
of	O
them	O
myself	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
thro	O
'	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
I	O
by	O
accident	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
hanging	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
an	O
Old-clothes-shop	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
own	O
mark	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
said	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
two	O
constables	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Shaw	B-pers
I	O
insisted	O
she	O
should	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
one	O
lawn	O
ruffle	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
besides	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
produced	O
;	O
the	O
ruffle	O
was	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
always	O
passed	O
the	O
door	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
would	O
attend	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
point	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
attend	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Moulds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Shaw	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Miss	O
Davis	O
.	O
This	O
ruffle	O
is	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
a	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
bed-chamber	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
,	O
my	O
aunt	O
wore	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shaw	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bruin	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
sheets	O
,	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
night	O
shift	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Dobbs	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
unmade	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
cambrick	O
cut	O
into	O
slips	O
,	O
and	O
pretty	O
near	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
cambrick	O
besides	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
sold	O
me	O
this	O
ruffle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
this	O
ruffle	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fetched	O
it	O
back	O
.	O
Seven	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
mole	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
ruffle	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dobbs	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
new	O
cambrick	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
slips	O
of	O
lawn	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bruin	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
4	O
s.	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
half	O
pence	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
old-clothes	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
such	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Miss	O
Davis	B-pers
I	O
knew	O
who	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
came	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
four	O
hours	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bruin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
exactly	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
Mr.	O
Dobbs	O
swears	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
coarse	O
sheets	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
black	O
silk	O
to	O
mark	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
family	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
26	O
s.	O
for	O
one	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
cambrick	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
a	O
blue	O
china	O
gown	O
.	O
Bruin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Percival	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Dobbs	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
his	O
hands	O
fast	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
curtain	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
picklock	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
it	O
will	O
open	O
most	O
doors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
common	O
picklock	O
key	O
?	O
Phillips	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
sort	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
curtain	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
false	O
direction	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
Miss	O
Davis	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Moulds	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
curtain	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Dobbs	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
old	O
clothes	O
in	O
Ragg-fair	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
curtain	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
lame	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
thing	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
picklock	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
354	O
.	O
(	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Stancey	I-pers
TONGE	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Tonge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Gunston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
51	I-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
narrow	O
blood	O
laces	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
parcel	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
(	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
inches	O
wide	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
long	O
)	O
upon	O
it	O
was	O
pinn	O
'd	O
a	O
pattern	O
of	O
blond	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
that	O
would	O
match	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
serched	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
which	O
matched	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
it	O
finer	O
and	O
broader	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
had	O
nothing	O
nearer	O
then	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
severals	O
cards	O
of	O
blond	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
sort	O
of	O
lace	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prices	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
odd	O
cards	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
other	O
pattern	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
s.	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
about	O
that	O
price	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
drawer	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
from	O
where	O
she	O
stood	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
which	O
had	O
the	O
patterns	O
pinn	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
laces	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
lowest	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
which	O
matched	O
her	O
pattern	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
was	O
the	O
lowest	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
whole	O
card	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
parcel	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
laces	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
manner	O
which	O
struck	O
my	O
attention	O
as	O
it	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
laces	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
under	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
close	O
underneath	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
over	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
stiff	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
directly	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
seeing	O
the	O
parcel	O
going	O
in	O
this	O
stiff	O
manner	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
look	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
with	O
pretence	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
quantity	O
of	O
that	O
little	O
edging	O
would	O
trim	O
a	O
little	O
cap	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
depended	O
upon	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
cap	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
cut	O
me	O
three-quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
half	O
an	O
ell	O
will	O
be	O
enough	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
coarse	O
cat-gut	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
coarse	O
cat-gut	O
:	O
we	O
keep	O
the	O
cat-gut	O
in	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
lift	O
the	O
parcel	O
off	O
while	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
parcel	O
off	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
drew	O
back	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
parcel	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
in	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
quick	O
motion	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
moment	O
she	O
had	O
disengaged	O
her	O
hands	O
from	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
her	O
hand	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
this	O
parcel	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
stiff	O
before	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
hung	O
very	O
carelessly	O
upon	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
cat-gut	O
came	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
7	O
1/2	O
d.	O
seeing	O
all	O
these	O
operations	O
confirmed	O
me	O
very	O
strongly	O
in	O
my	O
suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
then	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
lowest	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
want	O
a	O
dozen	O
and	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
must	O
send	O
my	O
young	O
woman	O
for	O
to-morrow	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
wished	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
she	O
went	O
:	O
the	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
found	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
she	O
then	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
sash	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
turning	O
round	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Ma'am	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
that	O
do	O
n't	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
counting-house	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
besides	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
serving	O
two	O
ladies	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
directly	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
motion	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
disengage	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
pulled	O
her	O
up	O
rather	O
rough	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
chair	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
put	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
gown	O
by	O
and	O
she	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
sticking	O
out	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
was	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
has	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
.	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
felt	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
on	O
return	O
from	O
a	O
milliner	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
still	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
which	O
she	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
accept	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
this	O
affair	O
secret	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
secured	O
her	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
came	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
counting	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
name	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Shipley	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
an	O
attorney	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
ladies	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
could	O
be	O
your	O
motive	O
for	O
doing	O
this	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
poverty	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
impossible	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
gold	O
here	O
in	O
plenty	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
seem	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
distress	O
;	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
distress	O
there	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
family	O
:	O
almost	O
directly	O
she	O
clasped	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
mention	O
every	O
little	O
circumstance	O
!	O
you	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
ladies	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
under	O
these	O
circumstances	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Tonge	O
said	O
,	O
Ma'am	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Tonge	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
said	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
falsity	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
card	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
of	O
what	O
it	O
cost	O
us	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
marking	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
lace	O
and	O
did	O
buy	O
it	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
like	O
that	O
you	O
describe	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
lay	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
attempt	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
any	O
impropriety	O
you	O
observed	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
nor	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
wanted	O
to	O
lift	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
removed	O
it	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
particular	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
saw	O
nothing	O
under	O
the	O
parcel	O
itself	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Not	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
mentioned	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
always	O
talked	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
this	O
story	O
as	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Or	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
moved	O
it	O
across	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
hang	O
down	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
card	O
was	O
pinn	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
lace	O
is	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
card	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
put	O
other	O
lace	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
card	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
;	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
destroy	O
the	O
old	O
mark	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
another	O
on	O
again	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
extravagant	O
else	O
to	O
use	O
a	O
card	O
to	O
every	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
marked	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
have	O
been	O
marked	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
before	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
marked	O
when	O
that	O
lace	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
card	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
for	O
your	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
when	O
the	O
lace	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
card	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
used	O
before	O
,	O
we	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
old	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
mark	O
it	O
afresh	O
with	O
what	O
that	O
cost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
own	O
cards	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
ask	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
prime	O
cost	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
know	O
what	O
profit	O
to	O
ask	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
sell	O
a	O
whole	O
card	O
you	O
sell	O
card	O
and	O
all	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
we	O
sell	O
it	O
card	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
sometimes	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
is	O
the	O
box	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
inches	O
deep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
laid	O
the	O
laces	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
farthest	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
put	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
drawer	O
next	O
you	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
the	O
laces	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
I	O
certainly	O
took	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
parcel	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
gloves	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
then	O
you	O
do	O
;	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
under	O
my	O
stays	O
,	O
so	O
help	O
me	O
God	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
yards	O
was	O
upon	O
this	O
piece	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Seventeen	O
yards	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
11	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
asked	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
dozen	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
a	O
narrow	O
edging	O
she	O
was	O
bargaining	O
for	O
,	O
not	O
for	O
this	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
satisfied	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
do	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
every	O
circumstance	O
confirmed	O
my	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
whether	O
it	O
gave	O
rise	O
to	O
a	O
suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
you	O
convinced	O
in	O
your	O
mind	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
convinced	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gauze	O
weaver	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
does	O
she	O
bear	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Very	O
honestly	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
1761	O
;	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
has	O
kept	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
way	O
of	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
dealt	O
fairly	O
and	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Burcher	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
character	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
mine	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
business	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
cloaks	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
litigious	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pass	O
by	O
such	O
evidence	O
as	O
this	O
without	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
what	O
Gunston	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
?	O
Burcher	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
owing	O
to	O
a	O
mistake	O
?	O
Burcher	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
had	O
many	O
mistakes	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
ladies	O
have	O
carried	O
things	O
into	O
their	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
under	O
their	O
stays	O
?	O
Burcher	O
.	O
In	O
their	O
laps	O
some	O
how	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
suppose	O
a	O
fine	O
lady	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
should	O
miss	O
some	O
jewels	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
them	O
afterwards	O
,	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
their	O
stays	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
a	O
mistake	O
.	O
Burcher	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
found	O
this	O
mistake	O
and	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
believe	O
,	O
supposing	O
that	O
gentleman	O
has	O
swore	O
true	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
?	O
Burcher	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
amazed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
do	O
you	O
put	O
such	O
a	O
construction	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Burcher	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wendover	O
,	O
in	O
Bucks	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lace-maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
always	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
till	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
always	O
bear	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
?	O
Barnet	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
live	O
at	O
Wendover	O
?	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
every	O
week	O
or	O
fortnight	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
left	O
lace	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
?	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
any	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
from	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
200	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
lace	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
might	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
dealt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
sealed	O
?	O
Barnet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
tied	O
or	O
buckled	O
with	O
a	O
strap	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
a	O
card	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
a	O
dozen	O
or	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
a	O
card	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
those	O
cards	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
opened	O
an	O
account	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Sherwood	O
and	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
Coventry	O
ribbon	O
ware-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
?	O
Patterson	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
come	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
goods	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
sent	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
always	O
paid	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
honesty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Patterson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sumpter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
upon	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
her	O
character	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lace-man	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Radcliffe-cross	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
with	O
her	O
time	O
after	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
received	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Witbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
morcer	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Witbridge	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
this	O
twelve-month	O
past	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ellway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milliner	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
three	O
years	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
eleven	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Ellway	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
a	O
just	O
way	O
of	O
dealing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
bear	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
?	O
Ellway	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
imputation	O
upon	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hern	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
attorney	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
used	O
to	O
invite	O
her	O
for	O
weeks	O
together	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
before	O
she	O
kept	O
this	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
generally	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
examination	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Tonge	O
,	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
said	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
lace	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
parcel	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
card	O
stick	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
card	O
was	O
his	O
word	O
.	O
Nebemiab	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
light	O
upon	O
the	O
examination	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
has	O
given	O
his	O
oath	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
parcel	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
card	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
hang	O
down	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
coming	O
here	O
upon	O
words	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
this	O
gentleman	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
different	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
said	O
;	O
now	O
can	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
As	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
expression	O
of	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
card	O
being	O
seen	O
under	O
the	O
parcel	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
paper	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
hang	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
word	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
partly	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
word	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
mind	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
evidence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Sawbridge	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
stiff	O
moving	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
discover	O
any	O
thing	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
low	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
card	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
master	O
here	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
quaker	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
ladies	O
here	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
necessity	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
here	O
;	O
they	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
spoke	O
about	O
her	O
person	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
L.	O
)	O
SARAH	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Stancey	O
TONGE	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Thomas	O
Tonge	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
,	O
March	O
30th	O
.	O
+	O
-	O
Holyer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
;	O
they	O
are	O
haberdashers	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
their	O
shop	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
near	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
to	O
her	O
person	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
article	O
called	O
glossy	O
cat-gut	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
one	O
yard	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
at	O
20	O
d.	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
paper	O
of	O
cat-gut	O
was	O
contained	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
like	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whom	O
had	O
you	O
that	O
piece	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gunston	I-pers
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
just	O
this	O
minute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
piece	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
was	O
there	O
your	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
put	O
the	O
paper	O
up	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
cat-gut	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
whether	O
the	O
gauze	O
was	O
gone	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Gunston	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Nine	O
doors	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
without	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
was	O
shewn	O
me	O
by	O
Gunston	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
young	O
men	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
Samuel	B-pers
Raymes	I-pers
for	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Three	O
minutes	O
at	O
the	O
farthest	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
cat-gut	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
like	O
this	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
much	O
to	O
be	O
released	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
To	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
off	O
free	O
without	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
present	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
first	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
accord	O
upon	O
hearing	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
pen	O
,	O
ink	O
and	O
paper	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
assign	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
grataity	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
she	O
meant	O
all	O
her	O
effects	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
She	O
kneeled	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Knowing	O
there	O
were	O
ladies	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
I	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
of	O
having	O
ladies	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
wanted	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
begged	O
you	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
We	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
gauze	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
confessed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
gauze	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
William	B-pers
Gunston	I-pers
's	O
possession	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
produces	O
it	O
now	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
gauze	O
since	O
.	O
Holyer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
ever	O
any	O
charge	O
made	O
of	O
this	O
gauze	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
no	O
charge	O
against	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
indictment	O
;	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
alderman	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
this	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Because	O
Gunston	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
applied	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
gauze	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
desired	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
applied	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Nobody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
is	O
extraordinary	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
Gunston	O
was	O
enough	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
deny	O
the	O
gauze	O
being	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gunston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
gown	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
this	O
gauze	O
sticking	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
part	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
between	O
the	O
stays	O
and	O
her	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
hollow	O
!	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
some	O
gauze	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
odd	O
manner	O
to	O
take	O
gauze	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
ladies	O
under	O
your	O
stays	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
somewhere	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
gauze	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
a	O
little	O
parcel	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
buying	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
glossy	O
cat-gut	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
for	O
our	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
enquire	O
who	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
lady	O
that	O
cat-gut	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
sold	O
any	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langstone	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Holyer	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Addington	O
both	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Holyer	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gauze	O
to	O
Holyer	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
forget	O
whether	O
Addington	O
and	O
he	O
both	O
went	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
,	O
but	O
Addington	O
brought	O
the	O
parcel	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
Holyer	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
parcel	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Paris	O
net	O
in	O
this	O
parcel	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
our	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
parcel	O
was	O
opened	O
and	O
the	O
Paris	O
net	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
that	O
gauze	O
or	O
Paris	O
net	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Paris	O
net	O
gauze	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
rumpled	O
.	O
Gunston	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
from	O
that	O
hour	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
One	O
would	O
have	O
apprehended	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
tumbled	O
:	O
how	O
far	O
up	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
About	O
thus	O
high	O
(	O
describing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
her	O
stays	O
)	O
;	O
that	O
gauze	O
will	O
not	O
rumple	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Holyer	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
Gunston	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Langstone	O
and	O
Chambers	O
's	O
before	O
any	O
other	O
shop	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
before	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
lady	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
glossy	O
cat-gut	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
some	O
Paris	O
net	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
imagine	O
is	O
stole	O
from	O
somebody	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
Holyer	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
for	O
this	O
paper	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
lady	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
lady	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
Holyer	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
sent	O
you	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
paper	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Gunston	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
or	O
whether	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
fetch	O
the	O
paper	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
hardly	O
recollect	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
paper	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
paper	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
that	O
gauze	O
in	O
that	O
paper	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
We	O
always	O
keep	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
gauze	O
and	O
glossy	O
cat-gut	O
,	O
and	O
plain	O
gauze	O
in	O
that	O
paper	O
;	O
either	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
said	O
will	O
fetch	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
I	O
forget	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
perfectly	O
well	O
the	O
paper	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
glossy	O
kind	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
that	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Holyer	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
paper	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
immediately	O
ran	O
for	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
open	O
it	O
at	O
your	O
own	O
shop	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
compting-house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
glossy	O
cat-guts	O
,	O
and	O
plain	O
gauze	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
any	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
to	O
make	O
over	O
all	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Langstone	O
,	O
the	O
owners	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
gauze	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
said	O
all	O
the	O
glossy	O
gauze	O
and	O
cat-gut	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
paper	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
gauze	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
variety	O
of	O
gauzes	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
glossy	O
gauze	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
we	O
keep	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
gauze	O
or	O
Paris	O
net	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Paris	O
net	O
gauze	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
gauze	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
plain	O
gauze	O
and	O
figured	O
gauze	O
of	O
various	O
denominations	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
we	O
always	O
call	O
Paris	O
net	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
is	O
it	O
gauze	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
barbarously	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
counsel	O
to	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
gauze	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
so	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
charged	O
her	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
affair	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nothing	O
was	O
mentioned	O
then	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
mention	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
gauze	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
parcel	O
she	O
bought	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Langstone	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
wanted	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
all	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
alderman	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
part	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Holyer	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
shew	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
glossy	O
gauze	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
that	O
paper	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
customer	O
?	O
Holyer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
paper	O
was	O
not	O
opened	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
compting-house	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Addington	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
opened	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
shewn	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
went	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
?	O
Addington	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
there	O
and	O
back	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
near	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
has	O
a	O
particular	O
spite	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
people	O
in	O
court	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
say	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
;	O
her	O
mistress	O
was	O
uneasy	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
surprised	O
,	O
as	O
all	O
the	O
world	O
must	O
about	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
my	O
reputation	O
:	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
trusted	O
with	O
thousands	O
.	O
In	O
regard	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
lady	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
frightened	O
with	O
the	O
news	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
pins	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
desperate	O
things	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Sumpter	O
has	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
material	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
better	O
rely	O
upon	O
her	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
woman	O
has	O
stated	O
this	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
either	O
retract	O
it	O
or	O
endeavour	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Gunston	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
declared	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
power	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
said	O
she	O
deserved	O
the	O
full	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
and	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
about	O
hanging	O
her	O
,	O
cost	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
one	O
indictment	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
?	O
Gunston	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
offender	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
if	O
lenity	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
affair	O
was	O
only	O
laid	O
for	O
transportation	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
at	O
large	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
laid	O
capital	O
,	O
she	O
may	O
get	O
off	O
for	O
transportation	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
may	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kingdom	O
.	O
For	O
I	O
cast	O
one	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
obtained	O
a	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gauze	O
weaver	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
,	O
five	O
,	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burchall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
sixty-one	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burchall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
milliner	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
mine	O
as	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
rent	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
the	O
most	O
industrious	O
creature	O
I	O
ever	O
knew	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
deal	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
are	O
more	O
confirmed	O
in	O
your	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
this	O
afternoon	O
than	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Burchall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
intention	O
of	O
saying	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
convicted	O
upon	O
a	O
former	O
indictment	O
?	O
Burchall	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
laceman	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
;	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
very	O
frequently	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
lace	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
from	O
50	O
to	O
200	O
l.	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
lace	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
chamber	O
when	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Bowlen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
laceman	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
received	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warten	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
laceman	O
,	O
in	O
Butcher-row	O
,	O
Temple	O
bar	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
one	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
year	O
1767	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lampter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
this	O
against	O
her	O
character	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
ribbon	O
wate-house	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Messrs.	O
Sherwood	O
and	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
us	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
not	O
lately	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whitbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk-mercer	O
:	O
she	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
Whitbridge	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
credit	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
wanted	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ellway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
gauze	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
BREAKSPEAR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
ham	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16th	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oil-man	O
in	O
King's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
hams	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
come	O
in	O
we	O
lay	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
gross	O
scales	O
:	O
last	O
Monday	O
evening	O
I	O
counted	O
the	O
hams	O
and	O
missed	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
out-door	O
servants	O
;	O
I	O
taxed	O
the	O
porter	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
lost	O
another	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
the	O
hams	O
but	O
seven	O
,	O
five	O
large	O
and	O
two	O
small	O
ones	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
small	O
ones	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
might	O
thereby	O
detect	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
salt	O
;	O
she	O
flung	O
down	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
salt	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hams	O
gone	O
since	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
tea	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
for	O
the	O
salt	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
and	O
put	O
an	O
apron	O
over	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
watch	O
her	O
motions	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
ready	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
the	O
salt	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pop	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hams	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
little	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
something	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
by	O
her	O
cloak	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
ham	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITEFOOT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
effects	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Miss	O
Anna	O
Maria	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
a	O
carriage	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Wigmor-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
;	O
the	O
blinds	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
were	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
say	O
.	O
your	O
money	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
rob	O
you	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
asking	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
stopped	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
on	O
foot	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Miss	O
Clark	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
coach	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Wimpole-street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
exactly	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
demand	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
lady	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
bid	O
the	O
coachman	O
stop	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
saw	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
his	O
opening	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
said	O
hollow	O
,	O
hollow	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
!	O
he	O
cocked	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
!	O
and	O
directly	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
shoot	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
pistol	O
missed	O
fire	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
Wimpole-street	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
into	O
Wallbeck-street	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
dunghill	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
found	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
into	O
Wallbeck-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
watch	O
in	O
Bentick-street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
Wallbeck-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
immediately	O
;	O
this	O
chairman	O
,	O
Weaver	O
,	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Sampson	O
Hodghis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
Weaver	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
seemingly	O
in	O
a	O
pause	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
turn	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
or	O
right	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
from	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
led	O
into	O
the	O
Meuse	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
ing	O
into	O
the	O
Meuse	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
got	O
ground	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
them	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropt	O
back	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
something	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagined	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
a	O
short	O
turn	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
which	O
is	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Wigmore-street	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
ladies	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
pistol	O
I	O
found	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
small	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
Wigmore-street	O
into	O
Wallbeck-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Little	O
Wallbeck-street	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
a	O
dunghill	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
dyer	O
,	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cracknall	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
dyer	O
,	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-le-grand	O
,	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
dyer	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
indecent	O
or	O
ungenteel	O
,	O
or	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
bad	O
;	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
work	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
357	O
,	O
358	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
IVERS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
dark	O
lantern	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Younger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
IVERS	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
pot	O
spouts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
pot	O
chains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
shovels	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
fourteen	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
eight	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
five	O
check	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
HALL	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
defect	O
of	O
evidence	O
on	O
this	O
trial	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
360	O
,	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DOWLING	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
catting	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
300	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
43	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
,	O
gent	O
.	O
and	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
charged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Society	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
affixed	O
to	O
their	O
house	O
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
bricklayer	O
to	O
the	O
society	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
measure	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
to	O
measure	O
some	O
lead	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
tallied	O
in	O
length	O
and	O
breadth	O
with	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
This	O
lead	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
yesterday	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
grand	O
jury	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
till	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
Edges	O
with	O
this	O
lead	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
in	O
Hog-lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
from	O
the	O
quantity	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
Edges	O
told	O
me	O
Coleman	O
and	O
Dowling	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Mutton-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Dowling	O
confessed	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
ladder	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
feet	O
high	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
staircase	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
,	O
with	O
about	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
Dowling	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
ladder	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
13	I-place
,	I-place
Lincoln	I-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
:	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
stole	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ladder	O
on	O
the	O
stair-case	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Dowling	O
,	O
Coleman	O
,	O
and	O
Edges	O
on	O
the	O
staircase	O
the	O
17th	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
being	O
stole	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brinley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
employed	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
a	O
ladder	O
,	O
a	O
board	O
of	O
mortar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hammer	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
the	O
trap	O
door	O
going	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
leads	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
cutting	O
instrument	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
hammer	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Coleman	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Bates	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
their	O
clothes	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
Dowling	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
Dowling	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
shovel	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
holey	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
birch	O
broom	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
mend	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
said	O
that	O
?	O
Bates	O
.	O
Coleman	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Dowling	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
shovel	O
?	O
B	O
ates	O
.	O
That	O
boy	O
brought	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Coleman	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
us	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
away	O
?	O
Bates	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Coleman	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Dowling	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
they	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drop	O
a	O
trifle	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
362	O
,	O
363	O
.	O
(	O
2	O
d.	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
WEBB	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KINGDON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Peter	B-pers
Munie	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brown	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
,	O
Feb	O
,	O
20th	O
.	O
*	O
Peter	B-pers
Munie	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
Bow-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
;	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
my	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
closed	O
upon	O
me	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arms	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Webb	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
light	O
?	O
Munie	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
sky	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
the	O
lamp	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
Webb	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
held	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
?	O
Munie	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
uncase	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
walked	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
produce	O
any	O
pistol	O
?	O
Munie	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
read	O
about	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
an	O
advertisement	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
watch-house	O
keeper	O
at	O
Mary-le-bone	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
great	O
coat	O
off	O
Webb	O
's	O
back	O
on	O
Sunday	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
advertized	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
the	O
coat	O
belonged	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
man	O
up	O
stairs	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
Webb	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
coat	O
himself	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
Waters	O
robbed	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Wimpole-street	O
;	O
he	O
impeached	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Waters	O
said	O
Kingdon	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
before	O
they	O
robbed	O
this	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Webb	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
Covent-garden	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fray	O
,	O
the	O
mob	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Kingdon	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
For	O
Webb	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Charter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stable	O
keeper	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Webb	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
drove	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
:	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
twelve	O
month	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Duckery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
coals	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
.	O
Webb	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
winter	O
before	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jordain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stable-keeper	O
,	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Webb	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ezektel	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
coals	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Webb	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Webb	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
uncle	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
turnes	O
and	O
chair-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
all	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
WEBB	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
KINGDON	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
364	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
ANGELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
4th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
365	O
,	O
366	O
,	O
367	O
,	O
368	O
,	O
369	O
(	O
2	O
d.	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUFFEY	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BOLTON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
PATRICK	B-pers
TRAINER	I-pers
,	O
ALICE	B-pers
DUFFEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
SHIELDS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
five	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
butter	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
tin	O
tea	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
mahogany	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
Ann	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	O
;	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
one	O
shagreen	O
watch	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
case	O
for	O
needles	O
and	O
thread	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
Henly	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
bed	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
callico	O
bed	O
grown	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
work	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Bruffels	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
trimmed	O
with	O
squirrel	O
skin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
cloak	O
sringed	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
one	O
black	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
chip	O
hat	O
covered	O
with	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
with	O
two	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
propery	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
Ann	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
;	O
Patrick	B-pers
Trainer	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
three	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
butter	O
boat	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
Alice	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
callico	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
know-them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
trimmed	O
with	O
squirrel	O
skin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
Jane	B-pers
Colls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
Miss	O
Henley	O
's	O
:	O
they	O
live	O
in	O
James-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bedford-row	I-place
,	O
they	O
are	O
three	O
maiden	O
sisters	O
:	O
they	O
inhabit	O
a	O
house	O
jointly	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
drawers	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
bolt	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
person	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
in	O
general	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
:	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
were	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
staple	O
and	O
bolt	O
were	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
:	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
parlour	O
doors	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
kept	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
sash	O
open	O
and	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
staple	O
broke	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
chissel	O
there	O
and	O
a	O
tinder	O
box	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tindall	I-pers
.	O
Trainer	O
offered	O
to	O
fell	O
me	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
Duffey	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
concern	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
Duffey	O
and	O
Trainer	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
found	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Duffey	O
and	O
Trainer	O
had	O
some	O
plate	O
;	O
Trainer	O
had	O
it	O
but	O
Duffey	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
Duffey	O
said	O
the	O
plate	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Trainer	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
searched	O
their	O
lodgings	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
producing	O
two	O
connisters	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
sattin	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
with	O
some	O
lace	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Bolton	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Miss	O
Henley	O
's	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Rumble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
Alice	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
bed	O
gowns	O
and	O
petticoat	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
This	O
black	O
cloak	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
was	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
squirrel	O
skin	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrixes	O
)	O
.	O
Balton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Duffey	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
one	O
morning	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
five	O
o'clock	O
as	O
I	O
always	O
did	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Purpool	O
lane	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
parcels	O
lay	O
,	O
we	O
kicked	O
something	O
white	O
,	O
which	O
contained	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
lodgings	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
somebody	O
would	O
swear	O
we	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
every	O
body	O
knows	O
we	O
follow	O
an	O
honest	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
our	O
bread	O
.	O
Duffey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
Bolton	O
has	O
said	O
is	O
very	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Trainer	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
fell	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Perrot	O
.	O
Trainer	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lumley	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
tossing	O
up	O
.	O
This	O
Perrot	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
Linch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
fence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
bought	O
stolen	O
things	O
for	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
that	O
word	O
meant	O
.	O
Meeting	O
with	O
this	O
Tindall	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Perrott	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
offered	O
ten	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
offered	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
another	O
house	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
four	O
children	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Shield	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
along	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
cloak	O
for	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
Bolton	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woollidge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
to	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
honesty	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
?	O
Woollidge	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
say	O
otherwise	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Bolton	O
and	O
Duffey	O
two	O
years	O
:	O
they	O
lived	O
directly	O
fronting	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
hard	O
working	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
very	O
regularly	O
at	O
a	O
coal	O
merchants	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Quimay	O
in	O
our	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
by	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
every	O
night	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
Alice	B-pers
Duffey	I-pers
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
drawers	O
and	O
things	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUFFEY	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
BOLTON	O
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
TRAINER	O
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
ALICE	B-pers
DUFFEY	I-pers
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
SHIELDS	O
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
.	O
370	O
,	O
371	O
,	O
372	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OATS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SPOONER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
pint	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt-seller	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
bodkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
blue	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Bath	O
beaver	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
mourning	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
:	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Ranelagh	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
fast	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
shutters	O
bolted	O
,	O
the	O
sashes	O
put	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
padlocks	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
sashes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
and	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
and	O
he	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
from	O
the	O
wind	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
high	O
;	O
my	O
parlour	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
(	O
Oates	O
)	O
immediately	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
blast	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
stir	O
or	O
speak	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
loaded	O
pistol	O
here	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pillow	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
mouth	O
to	O
squeeze	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
murder	O
me	O
!	O
take	O
what	O
you	O
find	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
burn	O
a	O
rush	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
mistake	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
own	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
out	O
both	O
lights	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
sore	O
parlour	O
and	O
fetched	O
their	O
tinder	O
box	O
,	O
flint	O
and	O
steel	O
and	O
turn	O
screws	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
where	O
the	O
escrutore	O
was	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
time	O
Oates	O
was	O
kneeling	O
on	O
my	O
bedside	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
bureau	O
and	O
took	O
what	O
money	O
they	O
found	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
12	O
l.	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
it	O
over	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
paid	O
his	O
men	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
pieces	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
Collins	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
rum	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
bottles	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
Collins	O
then	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
:	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
as	O
Oates	O
was	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
Collins	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Strangle	O
the	O
bitch	O
,	O
blast	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
Oates	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
left	O
Oats	O
centinel	O
over	O
me	O
whilst	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
an	O
escrutore	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
tray	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
with	O
about	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
or	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
(	O
Repeats	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
.	O
Oats	O
still	O
kept	O
guard	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
candles	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
hook	O
that	O
the	O
chain	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
kneeling	O
on	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
stirred	O
or	O
made	O
an	O
noise	O
for	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
your	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
lock	O
you	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
blast	O
you	O
,	O
somebody	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
unbolted	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
great	O
difficulty	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
three-quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
Oates	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
my	O
eyes	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
never	O
forget	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
slept	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
was	O
pitted	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
clear	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
informed	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Collins	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
the	O
moment	O
he	O
spoke	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
I	I-pers
should	O
know	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
knelt	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	O
put	O
several	O
questions	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
hear	O
his	O
voice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
knew	O
Collins	O
's	O
voice	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
voice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
to	O
his	O
voice	O
?	O
+	O
+	O
Collins	O
has	O
a	O
remarkably	O
deep	O
voice	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
speak	O
;	O
he	O
lighted	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
