TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
1774	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
down	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
BELL	O
,	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX	O
PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKES	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Weald	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
John	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
John	B-pers
William	I-pers
Gallabine	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jewell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bromly	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Higley	I-pers
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Cleane	I-pers
John	B-pers
Browne	I-pers
Thorpe	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
David	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Emmett	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Reddish	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Suffolk	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Bainton	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Hogard	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Armitage	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jerquet	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Featherstone	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
OXTOBY	I-pers
,	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HORTON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
the	O
first	O
three	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assult	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
And	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
October	O
17th	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Stoke	O
Newington	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
attacked	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
between	O
Ball	B-place
's	I-place
Pond	I-place
and	O
Kingsland	B-place
turnpikes	I-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
three-quarters	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
bludgeons	O
or	O
sticks	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
s.	O
after	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
forward	O
and	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
another	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
and	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
style	O
towards	O
Newington	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
knew	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Consider	O
the	O
lives	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
are	O
at	O
stake	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
sufficient	O
observation	O
of	O
their	O
persons	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Gill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
and	O
clear	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
persons	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
great	O
observation	O
of	O
them	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
clear	O
moon-light	O
night	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wellsman	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Newington	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
from	O
Ball	O
's	O
Pond	O
turnpike	O
towards	O
Kingsland	O
turnpike	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Rogers	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
life	O
or	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
off	O
the	O
causeway	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
any	O
more	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
patience	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
if	O
my	O
pocket	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
s.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
feel	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
more	O
,	O
then	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
side	O
or	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
which	O
,	O
while	O
Rogers	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
had	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gill	O
was	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
any	O
but	O
Rogers	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Rogers	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
darkish	O
,	O
reddish	O
great	O
coat	O
with	O
a	O
velvet	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
wore	O
his	O
hat	O
cocked	O
up	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
and	O
flapped	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mackaway	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
these	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
Charles	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
lend	O
8	O
s.	O
they	O
were	O
dissatisfied	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
Taylor	O
returned	O
again	O
alone	O
and	O
took	O
8	O
s.	O
Taylor	O
produced	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Gill	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
buckles	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tubb	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
Rogers	O
,	O
Oxtoby	O
,	O
and	O
Horton	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
near	O
Portland	O
Square	O
.	O
Rogers	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brick-maker	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bucker	O
's	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
a-bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
For	O
Rogers	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Rogers	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
very	O
hard	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Adelphi	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Levingston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Adams	O
'	O
brick-kilns	O
at	O
Totenham-court	O
.	O
Rogers	O
and	O
Oxtoby	O
worked	O
there	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
summer	O
:	O
Horton	O
has	O
worked	O
there	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
no	O
other	O
crime	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
being	O
honest	O
men	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Upshot	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Kingsland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
both	O
Rogers	O
and	O
Oxtoby	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Ferne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Padmore	I-pers
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
slight	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Rogers	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Oxtoby	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
buckles	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Horton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Oxtoby	O
when	O
he	O
pawned	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
ROGERS	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
OXTOBY	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
HORTON	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
TAYLOR	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
They	O
were	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wintle	I-pers
,	O
November	O
4th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wintle	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
between	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
but	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
wiped	O
my	O
face	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
through	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
LEWIS	B-pers
SHARKEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Skuse	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Skuse	I-pers
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Yorkshire	O
shoe-warehouse	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
burst	O
the	O
upper	O
leather	O
of	O
his	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
credit	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
man	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
credit	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
several	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
whose	O
names	O
he	O
mentioned	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
distressed	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
himself	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Skuse	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
misfortune	O
with	O
his	O
shoe	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
foot	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
upper	O
leather	O
of	O
his	O
shoe	O
was	O
burst	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
sit	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
misfortune	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
credit	O
and	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Collins	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
pair	O
I	O
fitted	O
on	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
,	O
I	O
fetched	O
another	O
pair	O
,	O
tried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
other	O
shoes	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
stooping	O
and	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
new	O
shoes	O
and	O
putting	O
on	O
his	O
old	O
ones	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
shoes	O
about	O
him	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shoes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Essex-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
several	O
shops	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
thought	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
defraud	O
somebody	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
through	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
returned	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shop-man	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
reaching	O
another	O
pair	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
put	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
informed	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
many	O
people	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Stottle	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
printer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
failed	O
in	O
trade	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ANDREW	B-pers
ELDER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
steel	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Gabrial	B-pers
Sprouls	I-pers
,	O
October	O
29th	O
.	O
++	O
Gabrial	O
Sprouls	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
dozen	O
razors	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	B-place
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
them	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
conveying	O
the	O
razors	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
whity	O
brown	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
paper	O
of	O
razors	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
Razors	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILSH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lewessee	B-pers
Cortall	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Cowles	I-pers
,	O
October	O
31st	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Cowles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
and	O
jeweller	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cortall	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
apples	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
down	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
spoon	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
ass	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
panniers	O
on	O
the	O
ass	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
boy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cowles	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
panniers	O
,	O
amongst	O
the	O
litter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
stop	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
PURVISS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
November	O
26th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MINNS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
ounce	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Adrian	B-pers
Easting	I-pers
,	O
November	O
21st	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
hempen	O
yarn	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sir	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Raymond	I-pers
,	I-pers
baronet	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
baronet	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
October	O
22d	O
.	O
+	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
go	O
towards	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
and	O
company	O
's	O
warehouse	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
dark	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
warehouse	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
yarn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
afterwards	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
yarn	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
LEWIS	B-pers
LEGAY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
diamonds	O
set	O
therein	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
October	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
footman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
this	O
ring	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
having	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
empty	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
procured	O
some	O
intelligence	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
trace	O
this	O
ring	O
through	O
several	O
hands	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warree	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
ring	O
to	O
one	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
-	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
ring	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Warree	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Polock	O
.	O
Polock	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
ring	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plank	O
.	O
Plank	O
.	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
ring	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
diamond	O
and	O
the	O
setting	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Polock	O
.	O
-	O
Polock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
diamond	O
so	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
setting	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Henderson	O
.	O
Henderson	O
produced	O
the	O
setting	O
and	O
Diamonds	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
setting	O
and	O
diamonds	O
,	O
the	O
setting	O
is	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
fashion	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
fancy	O
.	O
-	O
Henderson	O
.	O
I	O
originally	O
set	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
one	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
before	O
nor	O
since	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
setting	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
it	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
see	O
it	O
one	O
day	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
once	O
see	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
ring	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Quick	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
amethyst	O
,	O
pearl	O
,	O
and	O
garnet	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Rapley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
.	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Rapley	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
satisfied	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Stewart	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rapley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Stewart	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
positively	O
to	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
notion	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
Stewart	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
Stewart	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
shirt	O
buckles	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
which	O
contained	O
buckles	O
and	O
rings	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
shirt	O
buckles	O
and	O
shook	O
them	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
from	O
his	O
manner	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
other	O
purpose	O
than	O
to	O
buy	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
shirt	O
buckle	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
his	O
two	O
campanions	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
each	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
maid	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
would	O
advance	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
ring	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
recollection	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
ring	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
plainly	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ring	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
recollected	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
bargaining	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
sleeve	O
,	O
which	O
confirmed	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
suspicions	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
concluded	O
the	O
maid	O
saw	O
something	O
which	O
made	O
her	O
suspect	O
them	O
.	O
Question	O
from	O
Stewart	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
my	O
dress	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
brown	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
whereas	O
I	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
scarlet	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
his	O
dress	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Daw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rapley	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
stairs	O
upon	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Stewart	O
and	O
Jones	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
Jones	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
bargaining	O
for	O
shirt	O
and	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
Stewart	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
circumstance	O
;	O
Stewart	O
having	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
shirt	O
buckle	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
money	O
enough	O
nor	O
the	O
other	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
proposed	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sent	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
who	O
would	O
advance	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
New-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Stewart	O
turned	O
into	O
Bedford-bury	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bedford-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
third	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
Stewart	O
:	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
alone	O
with	O
Jones	O
;	O
Jones	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Constitution	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Bedford-street	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
me	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Stewart	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
he	O
might	O
probably	O
make	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
to	O
wait	O
any	O
longer	O
for	O
Steward	O
for	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
pretending	O
to	O
lay	O
out	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
ring	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
(	O
The	O
ring	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Timothy	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
the	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Rapley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
workman	O
and	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
work	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
confident	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
ring	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rapley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
ring	O
.	O
Barker	O
.	O
This	O
ring	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
by	O
Stewart	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
send	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
stept	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
for	O
something	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Stewart	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Stewart	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
bridle	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
one	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
stirrup	O
as	O
if	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
mounting	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
disengaged	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
instantly	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
overtook	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
talked	O
of	O
carrying	O
him	O
immediately	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
first	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rapley	O
said	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
ring	O
,	O
Question	O
from	O
Stewart	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
ring	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Barker	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
suchthing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
finisher	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Stewart	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
Stewart	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Lemon-tree	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
which	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pledge	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
step	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
connexion	O
with	O
Stewart	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
mere	O
accident	O
,	O
having	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
;	O
whether	O
Stewart	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Stewart	O
did	O
leave	O
us	O
as	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bedfordbury	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
fathers	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
likely	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
Stewart	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
Jones	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
,	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SAMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
blankets	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
frying	O
pan	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
check	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
October	O
10th	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
on	O
her	O
trial	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
in	O
extenuation	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
reduced	O
to	O
the	O
the	O
greatest	O
distress	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
oder	O
to	O
furnish	O
her	O
absolute	O
necessities	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
declared	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
paid	O
his	O
rent	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FENBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hand	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pannel	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
key	O
hole	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
smoothing	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
stock	O
and	O
drill	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
chissel	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
grinding-stone	O
handle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
iron	O
stay	O
hooks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
hundred	O
iron	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
sash	O
line	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
glue	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Matthew	O
,	O
Bethnal-Green	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Paynes	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
steward	O
to	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Neave	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
with	O
two	O
locks	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
tools	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
wall	O
,	O
nine	O
feet	O
high	O
before	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
loose	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
locks	O
wrenched	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
yard	O
which	O
the	O
work	O
shop	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
laths	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
broke	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
shop	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
several	O
tools	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
tools	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bundy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonards	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
tools	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
saw	O
between	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Bethnall-Green	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
partner	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
so	O
late	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
T.	O
F.	O
upon	O
the	O
plane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
different	O
mark	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
110	O
,	O
in	O
Skinner-street	O
,	O
whereas	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
69	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
highest	O
number	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
at	O
an	O
ale-house	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
tools	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
leave	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
LUTFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
November	O
23d	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stationer	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
my	O
clerk	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pigeons	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
water	O
butt	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
afterwards	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Emmery	O
's	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilsmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pigeons	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
Everitt	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
feed	O
the	O
pigeons	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
New-Road	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
sent	O
word	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Emery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Emery	O
's	O
in	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
pigeons	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
hoped	O
his	O
master	O
would	O
not	O
transport	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
for	O
theft	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Everitt	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
cart	O
wheel	O
and	O
cut	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
cart	O
wheel	O
under	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fruiterer	O
in	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
brought	O
the	O
pigeons	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pigeons	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
17	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
PATRICK	B-pers
COGGAN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
one	O
silver	O
pap	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
sixteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
called	O
silver	O
sizes	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
thirty-three	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
October	O
18th	O
.	O
Second	O
count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
one	O
other	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
bank	O
notes	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
committing	O
the	O
said	O
felony	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
payable	O
and	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
the	O
proprietor	O
thereof	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
George	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Bunch	I-place
of	I-place
Grapes	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
third	O
gate	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Traitors	O
Bridge	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
out	O
my	O
licences	O
from	O
the	O
justices	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
division	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
called	O
for	O
three	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
news	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
liquor	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Coggan	O
stand	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
any	O
answer	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
door	O
open	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
inner	O
rooms	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
the	O
door	O
came	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
then	O
turning	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Williams	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
inner	O
rooms	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
farthest	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Coggan	I-pers
,	O
Williams	O
slipt	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
Coggan	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
below	O
to	O
stop	O
Williams	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
stopped	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
box	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
inner	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
cupboard	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
it	O
contained	O
two	O
bank	O
notes	O
of	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
seven	O
guineas	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
seven	O
guineas	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
in	O
another	O
p	O
art	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
silver	O
sizes	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
grenadier	O
who	O
had	O
stopped	O
Williams	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
grenadier	O
then	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
with	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
silver	O
sizes	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
missed	O
thirteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
in	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
they	O
kept	O
Williams	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
found	O
on	O
Williams	O
,	O
the	O
grenadier	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
Williams	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
grenadier	O
brought	O
you	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
grenadier	O
said	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
come	O
in	O
together	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
describe	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
,	O
what	O
parish	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
pay	O
no	O
taxes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
these	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
numbers	O
,	O
had	O
they	O
not	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
numbers	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
so	O
often	O
change	O
for	O
my	O
neighbours	O
I	O
never	O
take	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
numbers	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
bank	O
notes	O
[	O
producing	O
them	O
]	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
,	O
directly	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
notes	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
sum	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
purse	O
delivered	O
back	O
to	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
grenadier	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
At	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
purse	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
purse	O
with	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
the	O
table	O
spoon	O
from	O
the	O
grenadier	O
,	O
the	O
spoon	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
board	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kerrison	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
water-gate	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Venables	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
that	O
fellow	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Williams	O
;	O
seeing	O
me	O
he	O
retreated	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
about	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
deliver	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
Mr.	O
Venables	O
was	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
notes	O
and	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Venables	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Venables	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
half	O
crowns	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
crowns	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
Mrs.	O
Venables	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
shillings	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
coronation	O
medal	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Kerrison	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
spoon	O
with	O
the	O
half	O
crowns	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
another	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
keys	O
,	O
another	O
person	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
keys	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
wards	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Coggan	O
and	O
Williams	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
Williams	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Somebody	O
told	O
me	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
served	O
with	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
:	O
somebody	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
warder	O
held	O
his	O
sword	O
before	O
Williams	O
,	O
Williams	O
told	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
me	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
my	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
thirteen	O
pounds	O
in	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
five	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pounds	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpences	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
it	O
put	O
down	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
reckoned	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
half	O
crowns	O
stand	O
in	O
pounds	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
reckon	O
them	O
?	O
Venables	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
exactly	O
those	O
particular	O
sums	O
:	O
the	O
two	O
pounds	O
fifteen	O
and	O
sixpence	O
being	O
finer	O
silver	O
than	O
common	O
,	O
I	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Venables	O
'	O
:	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
I	O
met	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
coming	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
warders	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
Vaughan	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
thing	O
that	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
warder	O
said	O
,	O
done	O
what	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
up	O
stairs	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Venables	O
'	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
immediately	O
and	O
saw	O
Kerrison	O
and	O
Williams	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
Kerrison	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
shoved	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
gentleman-warder	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
three	O
papers	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
to	O
Kerrison	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
gentleman-warder	O
said	O
,	O
search	O
his	O
pockets	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
something	O
weighty	O
;	O
Williams	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Venables	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
half	O
crowns	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
her	O
the	O
half	O
crowns	O
I	O
took	O
five	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
Coggan	O
was	O
.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
fire	O
arms	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
This	O
key	O
[	O
producing	O
it	O
]	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Williams	O
's	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Venables	O
call	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
grenadier	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Coggan	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
and	O
scratching	O
the	O
ashes	O
over	O
something	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
hiding	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
chissel	O
under	O
the	O
ashes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
doing	O
the	O
robbery	O
with	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
scratch	O
the	O
ashes	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
Williams	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
Coggan	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Coggan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
three	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
almost	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
(	O
Williams	O
)	O
before	O
.	O
WILLIAMS	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
COGGAN	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
parish	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
's	I-pers
,	O
October	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
Count	O
.	O
Laying	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Mabberly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hewson	I-pers
.	O
3	O
d	O
Count	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
4th	O
Count	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BUNCOMB	I-pers
and	O
ISAAC	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
skains	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Bengal	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dutch	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
November	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DAVIES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
lappets	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
narrow	O
lace	O
edging	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
;	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
white	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
a	O
velvet	O
collar	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
a	O
lace	O
robbin	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
white	O
farsnett	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Lesinne	I-pers
.	O
December	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
24	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
yarn	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stranger	I-pers
,	O
November	O
9th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
26	O
,	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
STREET	I-pers
,	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
coining	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
and	O
lawful	O
money	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
November	O
9th	O
.	O
+	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
29	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BAILIS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
coining	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
,	O
feigned	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
copper-money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
legal	O
copper-money	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
December	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Day	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
which	O
opens	O
into	O
a	O
Tenter-Ground	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
mistake	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
wrong	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Day	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
Parker	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
which	O
key	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
breeches-fob	O
a	O
punchin	O
,	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
to	O
stamp	O
a	O
die	O
,	O
the	O
reverse	O
of	O
an	O
Irish	O
half-penny	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
unlocked	O
a	O
cellar	O
door	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
cellar	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
instrument	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
large	O
coining	O
engine	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
fixed	O
and	O
ready	O
for	O
working	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
dies	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
between	O
the	O
dies	O
;	O
the	O
halfpenny	O
is	O
made	O
in	O
imitation	O
of	O
the	O
copper	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
halfpenny	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
dies	O
,	O
some	O
finished	O
halfpence	O
lying	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
blanks	O
ready	O
cut	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
a	O
kettle	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
blanks	O
in	O
the	O
kettle	O
,	O
the	O
blanks	O
are	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
kettle	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
boil	O
off	O
the	O
scurf	O
which	O
is	O
upon	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
prevents	O
the	O
impression	O
being	O
made	O
so	O
strong	O
by	O
the	O
instrument	O
as	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
punchin	O
for	O
a	O
die	O
for	O
the	O
reverse	O
of	O
an	O
English	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
press	O
which	O
may	O
be	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
for	O
the	O
cuting	O
out	O
of	O
round	O
blanks	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
blank	O
lodged	O
in	O
this	O
press	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
blanks	O
round	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Day	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bailis	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
Bailis	O
,	O
wife	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
seive	O
,	O
which	O
seive	O
is	O
likewise	O
an	O
instrument	O
they	O
do	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
process	O
of	O
coining	O
copper-money	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Day	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
missed	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
surrender	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Day	O
's	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
Day	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
cleared	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
want	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Bailis	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
an	O
old	O
fool	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
such	O
a	O
scrape	O
as	O
this	O
in	O
your	O
old	O
age	O
?	O
Bailis	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
Bailis	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
and	O
without	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
take	O
the	O
key	O
from	O
Day	O
which	O
opened	O
the	O
cellar	O
:	O
Day	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
Day	O
in	O
custody	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
instrument	O
fixed	O
with	O
the	O
halfpence	O
and	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Percival	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
garrett	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cuting	O
out	O
instrument	O
there	O
and	O
the	O
blanks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
parcel	O
of	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Bailis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
so	O
black	O
and	O
without	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
coining	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
carrying	O
coals	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
found	O
me	O
.	O
Day	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
key	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
opened	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
key	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
lock	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
AMOS	B-pers
MERRITT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellicott	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
shagreen	O
tea	O
chest	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
sugar	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
sauce	O
boats	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
twelve	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
sauce	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
filligree	O
quadrille	O
pool	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
chased	O
watch	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
chased	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
stone	O
snuff	O
box	O
mounted	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
paper	O
machie	O
snuff	O
box	O
mounted	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
miniture	O
picture	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
an	O
enamelled	O
locket	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
garnet	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
garnet	O
spriggs	O
for	O
the	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
purses	O
.	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
shagreen	O
pocket	O
book	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
clasp	O
and	O
pencil	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bead	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
stone	O
earring	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
four	O
metal	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
medals	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
gilt	O
metal	O
etwee	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
walking	O
cane	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
head	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
walking	O
cane	O
with	O
a	O
metal	O
head	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
two	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Mr	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellicott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hornsey-lane	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Highgate	I-place
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
,	O
Islington	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
judge	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
noise	O
that	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
servants	O
were	O
moving	O
the	O
tables	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
dark	O
.	O
She	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
heard	O
some	O
people	O
coming	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
word	O
I	O
heard	O
was	O
,	O
come	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
We	O
jumped	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ellicott	O
,	O
slept	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
nearest	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
)	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
bloods	O
we	O
will	O
murder	O
every	O
soul	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ellicott	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
almost	O
immediately	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
is	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
fastens	O
with	O
a	O
drop-bolt	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
and	O
somebody	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
pushed	O
it	O
close	O
;	O
I	O
hurried	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
murder	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
which	O
voice	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
speak	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
pushed	O
it	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
put	O
to	O
prevent	O
our	O
shutting	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
Merritt	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
some	O
others	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
come	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
then	O
was	O
attempted	O
with	O
a	O
considerable	O
force	O
:	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hanger	O
with	O
a	O
scabbard	O
put	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
post	O
)	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
;	O
how	O
many	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
force	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
keep	O
them	O
from	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ellicott	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
reach	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
loaded	O
pistols	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
my	O
bed	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
again	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
at	O
first	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Ellicott	O
tried	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
bell	O
being	O
rung	O
,	O
the	O
servants	O
who	O
lay	O
over	O
our	O
heads	O
came	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
the	O
door	O
fast	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
then	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
closer	O
than	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
drop	O
the	O
bolt	O
down	O
and	O
fasten	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
thieves	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
own	O
three	O
servants	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
their	O
shirts	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
servants	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
dressed	O
themselves	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
on	O
horseback	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
robbers	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
raised	O
some	O
carpenters	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
also	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
information	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
Respecting	O
the	O
thirty-hour	O
alarum	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
news-paper	O
some	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
near	O
the	O
sluice-house	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
remarkably	O
well	O
secured	O
;	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
is	O
a	O
strong	O
deal-shutter	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
strong	O
iron	O
bar	O
that	O
goes	O
across	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
upon	O
finding	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
rabbit	O
of	O
that	O
joint	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
;	O
was	O
cut	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hinges	O
were	O
forced	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
apprehend	O
they	O
had	O
bent	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
slide	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
behind	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
vacancy	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
(	O
they	O
are	O
folding	O
shutters	O
)	O
this	O
let	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
comes	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
kitchen	O
into	O
the	O
common	O
kitchen	O
is	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
they	O
wrenched	O
that	O
bolt	O
quite	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
let	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
common	O
kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
kitchen	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
bolted	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
likewise	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
plate	O
left	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
My	O
orders	O
are	O
always	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
plate	O
should	O
be	O
carried	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
made	O
on	O
purpose	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
servants	O
lie	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
footman	O
negligently	O
left	O
them	O
below	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
squeezing	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
so	O
fast	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
the	O
scabbard	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
scabbard	O
behind	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hanger	O
found	O
without	O
a	O
scabbard	O
that	O
fits	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
scabbard	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
observed	O
when	O
the	O
scabbard	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Ellicott	O
tried	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
hanger	O
goes	O
in	O
just	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
hadgone	O
quite	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
bent	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
hanger	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
scabbard	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Mrs.	O
Ellicott	O
attempted	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
them	O
attempt	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drawn	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
hanger	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
Merrit	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Mill-yard	O
,	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Winn	O
.	O
One	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
that	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
tools	O
there	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
some	O
chissels	O
,	O
picklocks	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Frank	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
.	O
+	O
+	O
Talbort	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
executed	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
cupboard	O
door	O
that	O
is	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
it	O
appears	O
upon	O
examination	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
chissels	O
exactly	O
fits	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
claw	O
which	O
answers	O
exactly	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
small	O
end	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
gap	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
even	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
that	O
gap	O
upon	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
's	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
waked	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sleep	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
which	O
confused	O
me	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
;	O
we	O
supposed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
more	O
voices	O
I	O
believe	O
than	O
one	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
voice	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
distinctly	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Being	O
waked	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
somewhat	O
flurried	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
nobody	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
too	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
as	O
most	O
people	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
something	O
agitated	O
,	O
especially	O
at	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
alarmed	O
at	O
that	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
could	O
keep	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
alarmed	O
then	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
But	O
against	O
so	O
many	O
men	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
stout	O
fellows	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
besides	O
myself	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
voices	O
heard	O
than	O
one	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
the	O
voice	O
in	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Merritt	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
only	O
voices	O
I	O
heard	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
lie	O
still	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
you	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
?	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
The	O
voice	O
I	O
heard	O
at	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
Question	O
to	O
Winn	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
search	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Winn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Merritt	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
and	O
one	O
Stewart	O
;	O
Stewart	O
was	O
discharged	O
after	O
Miller	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Miller	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Miller	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
?	O
Winn	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
alarmed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
bell	O
ring	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
alarum	O
bell	O
to	O
ring	O
for	O
the	O
servants	O
,	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
landing	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Miller	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
hall	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
Miller	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
Very	O
sure	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
What	O
compass	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
A	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
other	O
cloaths	O
,	O
snuff	O
coloured	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
night	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
Very	O
moon	O
light	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
more	O
persons	O
than	O
one	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Miller	O
's	O
voice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
m	O
you	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
Miller	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
since	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
place	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
First	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
the	O
ladder	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
gate	O
at	O
a	O
carpenter	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
this	O
ladder	O
from	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
they	O
pulled	O
the	O
sash	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
aside	O
the	O
shutter	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cook	O
maid	O
bar	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
the	O
bolt	O
off	O
that	O
kitchen	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
best	O
kitchen	O
,	O
from	O
there	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
those	O
doors	O
were	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
footman	O
bolt	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
great	O
chest	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
footman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
.	O
The	O
sauce	O
boats	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
the	O
tea-cannisters	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
the	O
sugar	O
basket	O
,	O
sauce	O
boats	O
,	O
ladle	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
above	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
below	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
desert	O
spoons	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
knife	O
case	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
kitchen	O
doors	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
bolts	O
were	O
forced	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
?	O
Garnet	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
gardener	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
him	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
one	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
,	O
the	O
coachman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
down	O
the	O
gun	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
find	O
you	O
guns	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
Near	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Winn	B-pers
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
drawn	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
and	O
discharged	O
,	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
somebody	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
tools	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
Miller	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
attend	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
offices	O
?	O
Paget	O
.	O
Occasionally	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
they	O
sometimes	O
send	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
assist	O
them	O
.	O
Miller	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
gave	O
a	O
start	O
back	O
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Dearn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ellicot	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
garret	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
footman	O
,	O
bring	O
the	O
gun	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
come	O
along	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
guns	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Dearn	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
speak	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Dearn	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
or	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
the	O
gardner	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
candle	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
week	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
fellow	O
of	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
found	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Miss	O
Ellicot	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
rather	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
more	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
jew	O
ladies	O
;	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
a	O
cant	O
term	O
to	O
break	O
a	O
house	O
open	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
A	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
That	O
not	O
doing	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
should	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
Hornsey-lane	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Yapper	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Nimmey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
,	O
Matshuinet	O
,	O
and	O
Amos	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
.	O
We	O
saw	O
a	O
new	O
brick-house	O
,	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
at	O
some	O
buildings	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
or	O
two	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Nimmey	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
from	O
there	O
we	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
two	O
silver	O
butter	O
boats	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dresser	O
drawer	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
broke	O
another	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
fore	O
parlour	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
some	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
parlour	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
under	O
a	O
table	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sugar	O
bason	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
cannisters	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
headed	O
cane	O
and	O
a	O
clock	O
;	O
the	O
clock	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
wooden	O
box	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cabinet	O
;	O
Hatchman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
trinkets	O
and	O
medals	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch-case	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
every	O
thing	O
out	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
great	O
box	O
,	O
that	O
alarmed	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
rung	O
a	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
bell	O
was	O
rung	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ellicot	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
our	O
way	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ellicot	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
,	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
books	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
William	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
went	O
into	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Ellicots	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
shoved	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
or	O
Abraham	B-pers
Matshumet	I-pers
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
stair-case	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Yapper	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
flurry	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Hatchman	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
punctually	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
shuting	O
the	O
door	O
fast	O
,	O
the	O
hanger	O
came	O
out	O
without	O
the	O
sheath	O
.	O
They	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
sheath	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
thrust	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
gun	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
their	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
our	O
escape	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
towards	O
some	O
fields	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
our	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
clock	O
and	O
tea	O
chest	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cane	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ellicot	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Half	O
a	O
mile	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
What	O
arms	O
were	O
you	O
provided	O
with	O
.	O
Miller	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
all	O
cut-lashes	O
and	O
pistols	O
,	O
Hatchman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Nimmey	O
,	O
had	O
all	O
a	O
lash	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
Yapper	O
had	O
a	O
cutlash	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
carries	O
about	O
him	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
has	O
returned	O
from	O
transportation	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
went	O
last	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
bits	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
that	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
lock	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
my	O
flurry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
use	O
any	O
expressions	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
body	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
find	O
guns	O
for	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
them	O
guns	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
expressions	O
used	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
we	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
make	O
haste	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Hatchman	O
,	O
or	O
Matshumet	O
said	O
that	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
expressions	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
flurry	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
or	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
either	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
Yapper	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
when	O
we	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
stair-case	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
's	O
door	O
except	O
Yapper	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
tell	O
all	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
plate	O
?	O
Question	O
.	O
One	O
Abraham	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Fise	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Abrahams	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
In	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
for	O
a	O
truth	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
and	O
buried	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
metal	O
we	O
thought	O
gold	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
silver	O
washed	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
all	O
sell	O
for	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
About	O
thirty-one	O
guineas	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
guineas	O
:	O
Hatchman	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
receiving	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
mine	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
others	O
theirs	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
arms	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bad	O
in	O
his	O
limbs	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
use	O
any	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
away	O
in	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
big	O
apron	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
our	O
pockets	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Who	O
carried	O
you	O
this	O
apron	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
It	O
belonged	O
to	O
Yapper	O
and	O
Hatchman	O
,	O
or	O
James	B-pers
Nimmey	I-pers
carried	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
chissel	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
socket	O
chissel	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
that	O
chissel	O
you	O
had	O
there	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
Fises	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
ladies	O
:	O
they	O
brought	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
hanger	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
hanger	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
hanger	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
hanger	O
that	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
every	O
one	O
a	O
lash	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
when	O
Merritt	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship-ale-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
nearest	O
way	O
into	O
Goodman's-fields	O
:	O
Pagett	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
a-cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
dragged	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
throwed	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
Farrell	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
teeth	O
down	O
my	O
throat	O
or	O
kill	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
quietly	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
so	O
help	O
me	O
God	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Merritt	O
lives	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
does	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
but	O
twice	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
so	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
listen	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
the	O
place	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
a-cross	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Merritt	O
's	O
door	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
steps	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
narrow	O
place	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
thoughts	O
of	O
calling	O
on	O
Merritt	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
Merritt	O
's	O
drawer	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Who	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
chissel	O
that	O
was	O
used	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
Fises	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
hanger	O
you	O
own	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Merritt	O
's	O
drawer	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
Fises	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
left	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
mine	O
were	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
Question	O
to	O
Pagett	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
you	O
ran	O
a-cross	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Pagett	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
on	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
going	O
on	O
or	O
stopping	O
?	O
Pagett	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
right	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hammock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Miller	O
?	O
Hammock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
they	O
always	O
behaved	O
civil	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
Bill	B-pers
Hatchman	I-pers
and	O
Nimmy	O
,	O
and	O
Matshumet	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
a	O
Jew	O
ladies	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
poorly	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
work	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
best	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Jew	O
ladies	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Jew	O
maid	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
Yapper	O
is	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Jew	O
maid	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
Jew	O
maid	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Highgate	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
all	O
fastened	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
ado	O
to	O
walk	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
down	O
Hornsey-Lane	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Ellicott	O
's	O
robbery	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
without	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
any	O
other	O
business	O
:	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
Lordship	O
would	O
ask	O
Miller	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
stair-case	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
to	O
swear	O
punctually	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
out	O
last	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
together	O
that	O
night	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
we	O
met	O
in	O
two	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
All	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
All	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
or	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
went	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
last	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
how	O
many	O
went	O
out	O
before	O
you	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Dou	O
you	O
recollect	O
whether	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
stair-case	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
help	O
to	O
bring	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
I	O
and	O
Hatchman	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
Yapper	O
brought	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
clock	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
we	O
put	O
in	O
our	O
pocket	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Answer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
nothing	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
our	O
pockets	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
this	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Miller	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
ago	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
