TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1774	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Frederick	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
down	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
39	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FREDERICK	B-pers
BULL	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
PERROTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
||	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Patrick	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Purvis	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
William	B-pers
Aldrad	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Pawley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Beake	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pawley	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
John	B-pers
Boyton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ovens	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edmondson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Ruffsage	I-pers
John	B-pers
Keightly	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilchin	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Showell	I-pers
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Showell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Vardy	I-pers
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
William	B-pers
Nicols	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
James	B-pers
Box	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
James	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
551	O
,	O
552	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NORBURY	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
VINER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
engraved	O
plates	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
thirty-nine	O
engraved	O
plates	O
of	O
pewter	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
plates	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
27th	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
copper-plate	O
musick	O
printer	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brownlow-street	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
or	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
thirty-nine	O
musick	O
plates	O
and	O
two	O
copper-plates	O
belonging	O
to	O
this	O
work	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
musick	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
two	O
copper-plates	O
here	O
;	O
one	O
cost	O
three	O
guineas	O
the	O
other	O
one	O
guinea	O
engraving	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
intelligence	O
of	O
Graves	O
;	O
Viner	O
had	O
been	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
glasier	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
my	O
business	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
in	O
Whitsun	O
holidays	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
skittles	O
at	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
of	O
one	O
Check	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
hanged	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
sessions	O
paper	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
Viner	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
he	O
would	O
lend	O
it	O
us	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
?	O
Graves	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harper	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
Viner	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Brownlow-street	O
,	O
and	O
Norbury	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
borrow	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
very	O
heavy	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
across	O
Drury-lane	O
down	O
King-street	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
Two	O
Sugar	O
Loaves	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
into	O
Parker's-lane	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
lodgings	O
;	O
Norbury	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Viner	O
left	O
us	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
Norbury	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
I	O
opened	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
musical	O
plates	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
forty-one	O
or	O
forty-two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
these	O
two	O
copper-plates	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
figures	O
;	O
Norbury	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
all	O
day	O
and	O
melted	O
down	O
the	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
pewter	O
to	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
's	O
room	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
Viner	O
met	O
us	O
;	O
Parker	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
shops	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Parker	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
steps	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
one	O
parcel	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
seventy	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
Norbury	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
woman	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
sixpence	O
;	O
Parker	O
cheated	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
Viner	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
debt	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
pewter	O
;	O
Norbury	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
copper	O
plates	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
in	O
Long	O
acre	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
his	O
room	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
throw	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
pond	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
Parker	O
's	O
room	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
two	O
fields	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Norbury	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
these	O
plates	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ground	O
himself	O
;	O
Parker	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
bringing	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
things	O
not	O
being	O
produced	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
Norbury	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
;	O
Parker	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
these	O
plates	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Norbury	O
about	O
them	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
direction	O
.	O
Norbury	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
slip	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
NORBURY	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
VINER	O
acquitted	O
.	O
553	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
BRISTOW	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BURY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
fifty-three	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
and	O
four	O
pounds	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Still	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
BRISTOW	I-pers
otherwise	O
BURY	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
January	O
9th	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
554	O
,	O
555	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
PRICE	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
French	O
crown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4th	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
sir	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
dear	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
objected	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
consented	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
tavert	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Price	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
sister	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
then	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
deprived	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
my	O
girl	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
go	O
somewhere	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
she	O
would	O
sit	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
some	O
shrub	O
,	O
I	O
drank	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
about	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
my	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
which	O
contained	O
notes	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
ticket	O
of	O
an	O
annuity	O
for	O
eight	O
pound	O
a	O
year	O
for	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
discovered	O
that	O
they	O
destroyed	O
them	O
going	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
till	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
round	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
bedfellow	O
gone	O
too	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
woman	O
up	O
that	O
rents	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
but	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wilde	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrington	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Benjamin-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
man	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
himself	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
pawn	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
him	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
not	O
before	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
business	O
not	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
thieves	O
that	O
come	O
to	O
pawn	O
things	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
spoil	O
your	O
trade	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
no	O
interest	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
helps	O
the	O
trade	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
exceedingly	O
so	O
.	O
Wilde	O
.	O
No	O
person	O
is	O
to	O
foreswear	O
himself	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
youngish	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
somewhat	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
part	O
does	O
he	O
resemble	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
resemble	O
him	O
in	O
dress	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
was	O
dressed	O
well	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
watch-maker	O
is	O
here	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Poldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
lodgings	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Chatham	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
this	O
affair	O
happening	O
?	O
Poldon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Poldon	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
was	O
a-bed	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
was	O
he	O
a-bed	O
in	O
?	O
Poldon	O
.	O
A	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
that	O
this	O
woman	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
are	O
two	O
brothers	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Edwards	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
lay	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
consulting	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
was	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
Martha	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Martha	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
was	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
a-bed	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
Price	O
and	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
gentleman	O
in	O
bed	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
person	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
same	O
person	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
afterwards	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
obstinate	O
and	O
rob	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Chatham	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
their	O
business	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
No	O
further	O
business	O
than	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
directly	O
down	O
to	O
Dark-house-lane	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
at	O
Chatham	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Gravesend	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
the	O
notes	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Price	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
rob	O
the	O
gentleman	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Price	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
had	O
them	O
.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
she	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
property	O
through	O
the	O
key	O
hole	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
?	O
Polden	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
first	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
she	O
mentioned	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
things	O
down	O
to	O
Chatham	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
the	O
witness	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Russell	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Price	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
gentleman	O
brought	O
Martha	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
home	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Edwards	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Chatham	O
for	O
some	O
fishing	O
rods	O
.	O
Edwards	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Russell	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
dispute	O
taking	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
father	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
as	O
he	O
called	O
himself	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Russell	O
.	O
The	O
father	O
lives	O
but	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Wilde	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
father	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
Not	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
but	O
seven	O
doors	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
here	O
upon	O
some	O
occasion	O
before	O
.	O
Wilde	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Russell	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
several	O
good	O
things	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
dispute	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
why	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
cloathed	O
as	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
look	O
very	O
thin	O
.	O
Russell	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
office	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Russell	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
meaning	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
clear	O
me	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Court	O
will	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
my	O
father	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
nothing	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
his	O
endeavour	O
to	O
hang	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Wilde	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
several	O
good	O
things	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
then	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
housekeeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
lamp-lighter	O
and	O
tin	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Price	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
knowledge	O
I	O
have	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
woman	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
several	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
work	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
wait	O
upon	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
in	O
service	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
like	O
a	O
service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
wait	O
sometimes	O
upon	O
one	O
gentleman	O
and	O
sometimes	O
upon	O
another	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
wait	O
upon	O
a	O
gentleman	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
father	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Andrew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
man	O
offered	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
girl	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
but	O
pay	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
man	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
Russell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
A	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
guinea	O
!	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
their	O
phrase	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Edwards	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
often	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Downes	O
.	O
No	O
great	O
matters	O
,	O
no	O
otherwise	O
than	O
I	O
used	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
father	O
uses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
father	O
better	O
than	O
him	O
?	O
Downes	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
within	O
these	O
eight	O
months	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
lodge	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Downes	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
he	O
more	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
Downes	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
this	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
behaved	O
honest	O
and	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Edwards	O
,	O
used	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
lamp	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
by	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
honest	O
and	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
work	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprentice	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
well	O
behaved	O
man	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aylesbury-street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
a	O
twelve-months	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
brought	O
his	O
work	O
home	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
deficient	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wilde	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
pawned	O
in	O
?	O
Wilde	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
mention	O
that	O
before	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Edwards	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
might	O
pawn	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
abroad	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
more	O
guilty	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Henry	O
Wilde	O
received	O
a	O
very	O
severs	O
reprimand	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
the	O
impropriety	O
of	O
his	O
conduct	O
.	O
556	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
MARK	B-pers
OLDBURY	I-pers
(	O
a	O
black	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hams	O
,	O
weighing	O
23	O
lb	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
49	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ismay	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20th	O
.	O
-	O
Griffiths	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ismay	O
,	O
who	O
keep	O
the	O
Provision	O
Warehouse	O
in	O
Salisbury	B-place
Court	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
writing	O
desk	O
chipped	O
and	O
cut	O
as	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
or	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
twenty-five	O
or	O
twenty-six	O
shillings	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
amazed	O
at	O
first	O
how	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
recollected	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
floor	O
where	O
hay	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
hay	O
wrick	O
for	O
a	O
horse	O
:	O
the	O
buildings	O
had	O
been	O
formerly	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
from	O
his	O
knowing	O
the	O
house	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
him	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
Snell	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
side	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
two	O
hams	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
bacon	O
and	O
hams	O
to	O
one	O
Luke	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Wych-street	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Leicester	O
carried	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
warehouse	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
next	O
morning	O
on	O
Black-Friars-bridge	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
arches	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
bacon	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
hams	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
thirty-six	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
bacon	O
at	O
one	O
White	O
's	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hams	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
ham	O
and	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
bacon	O
in	O
one	O
Hopwood	O
's	O
yard	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
gave	O
both	O
to	O
Leicester	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Leicester	O
is	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
hams	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
bacon	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
Luke	B-pers
Leicester	I-pers
was	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bacon	O
,	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ham	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
bacon	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
my	O
servants	O
came	O
backwards	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
suffer	O
a	O
flitch	O
of	O
bacon	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
mentioning	O
Leicester	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
coachman	O
that	O
uses	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
coachman	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
bacon	O
in	O
two	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
eggs	O
dressed	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
remained	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
557	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
POLLETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sandall	I-pers
,	O
August	O
13th	O
.	O
~	O
William	B-pers
Sandall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
going	O
through	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
sudden	O
tug	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
under	O
a	O
smock	O
frock	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
rebuilding	O
Newgate	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
a	O
cellar	O
by	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
William	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
have	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
the	O
brushmaker	O
's	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
558	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KENNATY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
August	O
16th	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
while	O
some	O
carts	O
passed	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
-	O
Griffin	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
seize	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
559	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
GUN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stafford	B-pers
Greenway	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1st	O
.	O
~	O
Stafford	O
Greenway	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn-hill	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
clapped	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
shoulder	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
then	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
several	O
other	O
people	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
stop	O
him	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
motion	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
being	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
afterwards	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
handed	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
area	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
an	O
area	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
oculist	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
and	O
was	O
falsely	O
charged	O
with	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
560	O
,	O
561	O
,	O
562	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
BAILISS	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BOWDEN	I-pers
,	O
SARAH	B-pers
KING	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
BRYAN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
harbouring	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
felony	O
,	O
July	O
26th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
I	O
saw	O
fourteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
girls	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
on	O
a	O
fish	O
stall	O
;	O
Bailiss	O
and	O
King	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
wine	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
night	O
and	O
were	O
almost	O
ready	O
to	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
entreated	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
reputable	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Dolphin	O
tavern	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
since	O
christened	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
tavern	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
waiter	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
shewn	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
red	O
port	O
,	O
the	O
waiter	O
brought	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
immediately	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
some	O
indecencies	O
which	O
I	O
resisted	O
;	O
then	O
Bailiss	O
clapped	O
her	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
thigh	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
feeling	O
about	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
side	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
drew	O
their	O
chairs	O
nearer	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
clapped	O
their	O
hands	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Bailiss	O
got	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
money	O
chink	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
wrenched	O
myself	O
from	O
them	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
barefaced	O
robbery	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
waiter	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
the	O
waiter	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
reputation	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
call	O
his	O
master	O
for	O
any	O
such	O
fellow	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
again	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
master	O
or	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
or	O
somebody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
worth	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
the	O
girls	O
then	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
they	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
girls	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
waiter	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
actually	O
see	O
them	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
so	O
done	O
he	O
called	O
them	O
whoring	O
bitches	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
purse	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
my	O
side	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
where	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
here	O
,	O
shewing	O
her	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
there	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
feel	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
empty	O
purse	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
contents	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
the	O
girls	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Bailiss	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
called	O
for	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
nothing	O
left	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
waiter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
in	O
you	O
believed	O
you	O
said	O
the	O
waiter	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
would	O
reward	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
blackguard	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
necessary	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Nelson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
totally	O
false	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
King	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
if	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
Union	O
coffee	O
house	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
Nelson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Smith	O
:	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
when	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
Nelson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
keep	O
that	O
house	O
now	O
?	O
Nelson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
-	O
Swift	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Dolphin	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
girls	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Smith	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
girls	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nobody	O
but	O
the	O
waiter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
if	O
the	O
waiter	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
not	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
stripped	O
the	O
girls	O
to	O
their	O
shifts	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
chairs	O
and	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
rung	O
for	O
the	O
waiter	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
some	O
silver	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Bailiss	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
King	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Dolphin	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
only	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
waiter	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
wine	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
waiter	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
call	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
than	O
what	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
wine	O
.	O
King	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Union	O
coffee	O
house	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
three	O
watchmen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
watchmen	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
reward	O
me	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Smith	O
called	O
two	O
women	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BAILISS	O
and	O
KING	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
SMITH	O
acquitted	O
.	O
563	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HYANSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
dimity	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26th	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
my	O
porter	O
and	O
he	O
quarreled	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
dropped	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
master	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
before	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
dimity	O
?	O
Markey	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
quilting	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
customer	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
dimity	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
muslin	O
;	O
the	O
dimity	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
brought	O
me	O
any	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
her	O
sister	O
had	O
the	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
564	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
FENLY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
20th	O
.	O
++	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
going	O
along	O
Upper	B-place
Thames-street	I-place
,	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
clap	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
565	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ARABELLA	B-pers
HART	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Upham	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Upham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Gravel-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Houndsditch	I-place
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
girl	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
by	O
main	O
force	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleeve	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
the	O
buttons	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
buttons	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
sixpence	O
and	O
buttons	O
for	O
lying	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
another	O
six-pence	O
for	O
the	O
buttons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
pass	O
?	O
Upham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Upham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
happened	O
by	O
accident	O
to	O
be	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dragged	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
searched	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
called	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
and	O
-	O
Williams	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
dragged	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pulled	O
him	O
in	O
by	O
force	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
swore	O
false	O
;	O
that	O
Williams	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
bawd	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
against	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
women	O
called	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Mackey	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
as	O
honest	O
women	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
566	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
AYRES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
July	O
12th	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	O
Hill	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	B-place
,	I-place
just	I-place
by	I-place
Field-lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
567	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
FLATHERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Sept.	O
2d	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
568	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALSOM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Aug.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
load	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
after	O
the	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
publican	O
with	O
whom	O
be	O
lodged	O
in	O
Theobald's-row	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
569	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pinder	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
31st	O
.	O
~	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pinder	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
banker	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
a	O
lad	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
tapped	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
pocket	O
had	O
been	O
picked	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
jack-ass	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
boy	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
plumbs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
something	O
came	O
against	O
my	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
was	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nigh	O
the	O
gentleman	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
570	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BEEM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
eleven	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9th	O
.	O
~	O
Ann	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
:	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Alderman	O
Kirkman	O
in	O
the	O
silk-winding-way	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
church	I-place
yard	I-place
for	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
pease	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
my	O
basket	O
with	O
my	O
work	O
and	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
lad	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lad	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
through	O
Bishopsgate	O
church	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
halfpence	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
brown	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
[	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Thirteen	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
would	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
a	O
Court	O
of	O
Justice	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Spencer	O
put	O
her	O
basket	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
pea	O
cart	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
halfpence	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
the	O
paper	O
was	O
not	O
tied	O
up	O
but	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
It	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
the	O
work	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
any	O
body	O
might	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stoop	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Bishopsgate	O
church	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
woman	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
running	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
running	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
her	O
all	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
a-cross	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
-	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
halfpence	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
halfpence	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
in	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
some	O
dropped	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
halfpence	O
by	O
the	O
wheel	O
of	O
the	O
pea	O
cart	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
by	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
halfpence	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
Barber	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
571	O
;	O
572	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
CARN	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
HINCHLEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
Scotch	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
in	O
Hanway-yard	B-place
,	I-place
Tottenham-court-road	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
printed	O
linens	O
;	O
I	O
handed	O
down	O
one	O
piece	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pieces	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
was	O
the	O
lowest	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
twenty-one	O
pence	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
less	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
saw	O
Hinchley	O
hold	O
her	O
left	O
leg	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
them	O
back	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Hinchley	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Scotch	O
cloth	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warrener	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Hanway-yard	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
call	O
the	O
prisoners	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
supposed	O
they	O
had	O
bid	O
for	O
something	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
returned	O
back	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
fall	O
.	O
Hinchley	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Hinchley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Hinchley	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
Mary	B-pers
Carn	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
CARN	O
acquitted	O
.	O
HINCHLEY	O
guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
573	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	B-pers
HART	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
riding	O
habit	O
with	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
trimmed	O
with	O
gold	O
fragments	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
12th	O
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
574	O
,	O
575	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
and	O
BRIDGET	B-pers
DAILEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
July	O
26th	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
576	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Ham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
dyer	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
knots	O
of	O
silk	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
feel	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
feel	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
wrapped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
silk	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
punish	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
law	O
should	O
take	O
its	O
course	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
to	O
one	O
Gawthorn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
jacket	O
hangs	O
up	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
they	O
want	O
a	O
chaw	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
hobble	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
577	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
guinea	O
,	O
nine	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Vanberg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
July	O
16th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
578	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
(	I-pers
a	I-pers
negro	I-pers
)	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BLACK	I-pers
JOE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Christopher	B-pers
Fernando	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
ninety-two	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	O
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
579	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
pattens	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
plum	O
pudding	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
quart	O
earthen	O
pan	O
filled	O
with	O
alamode	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stockdell	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
13th	O
.	O
++	O
Stockdell	B-pers
Anne	I-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
A	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
a	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
received	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
often	O
employed	O
to	O
pawn	O
things	O
by	O
her	O
mother	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
.	O
Another	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
two	O
bad	O
girls	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
580	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillowbier	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Winifred	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Winifred	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
:	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
except	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
stockings	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
chamber	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alaram	O
of	O
my	O
chimney	O
being	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
linen	O
to	O
pawn	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartments	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
same	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
581	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PETER	B-pers
HARCOURT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
582	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
AMBROSE	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Peckham	O
with	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
are	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
583	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
CLEMENTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
sallad	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
the	I-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28th	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
584	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EDWARD	I-pers
STANTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
mode	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
Barcelona	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
moreen	O
coloured	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
mitts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
jam	O
cloth	O
mitts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
blond	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
beaver	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
gauze	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
an	O
India	O
fan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
tape	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Harvey	B-pers
Berrow	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
585	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Mailey	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
copper	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
Aug	O
29th	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
586	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BICKLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
woollen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Cosgrave	I-pers
;	O
a	O
woollen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27th	O
.	O
*	O
Owen	B-pers
Cosgrave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
Dyer-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
bundles	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
landlord	O
with	O
two	O
bundles	O
in	O
which	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
prosecutor	O
(	O
Marshall	O
's	O
)	O
goods	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cosgrave	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
being	O
awake	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
two	O
bundles	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
awaked	O
Cosgrave	O
and	O
rose	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
presently	O
missed	O
my	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
two	O
bundles	O
down	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
these	O
bundles	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
587	O
,	O
588	O
,	O
589	O
,	O
590	O
,	O
591	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
PERKINS	I-pers
,	O
LAWRENCE	B-pers
FLOOD	I-pers
,	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
NEWSOM	I-pers
,	O
EDWARD	B-pers
FOSSETT	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HIGGINS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
4th	O
.	O
||	O
Frederick	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
my	O
men	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
pigs	O
;	O
we	O
waited	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
pigs	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
pigs	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
.	O
The	O
inhabitants	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
do	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
thieves	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
lodging	O
house	O
;	O
Perkins	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
different	O
apartments	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Cummins	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
these	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
up	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
crying	O
of	O
two	O
pigs	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
drive	O
the	O
pigs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
wall	O
into	O
their	O
own	O
yard	O
;	O
Fossett	O
was	O
the	O
chief	O
man	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
pigs	O
followed	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newsom	I-pers
helped	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
Higgins	O
helped	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
Perkins	O
or	O
Flood	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
gave	O
intelligence	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cummins	O
's	O
people	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cummins	O
;	O
Hatch	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
said	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
several	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cummins	O
's	O
men	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
men	O
looked	O
down	O
into	O
an	O
open	O
cellar	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
saw	O
some	O
pigs	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
hogs	O
stuck	O
;	O
one	O
hung	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
search	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hogs	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pointer	O
,	O
a	O
fox	O
hound	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
spaniel	O
;	O
the	O
pointer	O
was	O
hanged	O
.	O
Newsom	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
fowls	O
in	O
this	O
young	O
fellow	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
pigs	O
were	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
nine	O
of	O
the	O
eggs	O
;	O
I	O
drove	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
hogs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
stick	O
them	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Perkin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Higgins	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
drive	O
the	O
pigs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Newsom	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
another	O
witness	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
pigs	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
that	O
morning	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
accord	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
bearing	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
PERKINS	O
,	O
FLOOD	O
,	O
and	O
NEWSOM	O
acquitted	O
.	O
FOSSETT	O
and	O
HIGGINS	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
592	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
August	O
9th	O
.	O
~	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Richmond	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
we	O
ought	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
coaches	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
opposite	O
the	O
watch	O
box	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
being	O
tired	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
chain	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
before	O
I	O
fell	O
a	O
sleep	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
somebody	O
pulling	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
missing	O
my	O
watch	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
well	O
tell	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
immediately	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
and	O
called	O
watch	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
resolute	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
we	O
both	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
fell	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
watch	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
again	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
over	O
his	O
left	O
shoulder	O
about	O
a	O
foot	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
together	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Silver-street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
watch	O
called	O
twice	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
call	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
five	O
doors	O
down	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
saw	O
Hall	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
both	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
Hall	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
it	O
over	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
they	O
were	O
struggling	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
about	O
a	O
foot	O
from	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
asleep	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
near	O
his	O
stand	O
?	O
Vernon	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
stand	O
before	O
me	O
who	O
went	O
off	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
asleep	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
.	O
Vernon	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Silver-street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
who	O
was	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
post	O
boy	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Little	O
Axe	O
,	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
watchman	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
the	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
hurt	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lying	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
leg	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
right	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Silver-street	O
to	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
watch	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
pretty	O
loud	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
Silver	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
lanthorn	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
amiss	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
watchman	O
standing	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
poor	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
watchmen	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
drink	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
himself	O
no	O
further	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
main	O
shoring	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
,	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
593	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
one	O
woman	O
's	O
cane	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
July	O
30th	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Lambeth	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
to	O
visit	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
and	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
thence	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Westminster	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Surry	I-place
side	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
followed	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
bridge	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
crossed	O
over	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
tavern	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
where	O
the	O
watermen	O
ply	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
they	O
were	O
looking	O
out	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
coming	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
coaches	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
bridge	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
passengers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
neither	O
before	O
nor	O
after	O
he	O
squeezed	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
hat	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
cane	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
ribbon	O
about	O
it	O
and	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
attack	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
Parliament-street	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noakes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
by	O
another	O
watchman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Parliament-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
following	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
pursuing	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
an	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
by	O
Lady	O
Dacre	O
's	O
Alm's-houses	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
can	O
run	O
as	O
fast	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
three-pence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
round	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
woman	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
not	O
being	O
present	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
remanded	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
by	O
business	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
all	O
hours	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
liable	O
to	O
be	O
insulted	O
by	O
these	O
common	O
prostitutes	O
;	O
this	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
barge	O
of	O
corn	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
work	O
hard	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
and	O
drank	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
having	O
no	O
victuals	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
got	O
rather	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
coming	O
over	O
Westminster-bridge	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
woman	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
Westminster	O
Bridge	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
speak	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
somebody	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
up	O
along	O
side	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
along	O
directly	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
aside	O
her	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Parliament-street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
terrified	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
any	O
constable	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
marks	O
in	O
your	O
throat	O
by	O
this	O
squeeze	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
throat	O
was	O
very	O
sore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
complain	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
fight	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
and	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
594	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
July	O
10th	O
.	O
++	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
farmer	O
Brooks	O
at	O
Isleworth	B-place
:	O
my	O
master	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
barn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countrywoman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Hampshire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
other	O
lodging	O
than	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Gather	O
pease	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
came	O
into	O
the	O
barn	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
A	O
bargeman	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
rude	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
sister	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
tucked	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
had	O
three-pence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
gown	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
:	O
finding	O
assistance	O
coming	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
knife	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
heard	O
assistance	O
just	O
coming	O
;	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
took	O
his	O
knife	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
taking	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
there	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
:	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
that	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
.	O
Fry	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
all	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
He	O
entered	O
my	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
With	O
what	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
With	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
first	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
He	O
began	O
pulling	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
breeches	O
down	O
and	O
pulled	O
by	O
my	O
coats	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
With	O
you	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
ravished	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
A	O
quarter	O
may	O
be	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
murder	O
ever	O
so	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
resisted	O
and	O
struggled	O
all	O
you	O
could	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
had	O
breath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
through	O
mere	O
weakness	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
entered	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
His	O
nature	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
while	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Questions	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
barn	O
or	O
hay	O
loft	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Four	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
;	O
two	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
or	O
before	O
me	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Nobody	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
four	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
two	O
women	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
four	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Watson	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
young	O
man	O
left	O
his	O
hat	O
behind	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
bound	O
round	O
it	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Nobody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
you	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
laid	O
down	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
left	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
hat	O
was	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
Nobody	O
's	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
standing	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
?	O
Fry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
lying	O
down	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
and	O
prayed	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
her	O
alone	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
unless	O
somebody	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
She	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
quiet	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
served	O
so	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
A	O
Mr.	O
Fielder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Fielder	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
A	O
waterman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
there	O
before	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
first	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
more	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
three	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
drawn	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
take	O
care	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
nigh	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
drawn	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
desired	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
nigh	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
herself	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
woman	O
they	O
call	O
Peggy	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
two	O
vile	O
fellows	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
Clements	O
set	O
them	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
beadle	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
waked	O
Lewis	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
Lewis	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
barn	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Clements	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
saw	O
Lewis	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
two	O
vile	O
fellows	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
killed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
barn	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
keep	O
the	O
cart	O
down	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
round	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
Watson	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
dragged	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Fielder	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
now	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
feeling	O
?	O
round	O
the	O
barn	O
again	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lying	O
among	O
some	O
straw	O
;	O
I	O
shook	O
him	O
;	O
hollow	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
sleep	O
here	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
outside	O
the	O
barn	O
door	O
;	O
Lewis	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
stir	O
I	O
