TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
1774	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Frederick	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
39	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FREDERICK	B-pers
BULL	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ASHUST	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
||	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
LONDON	O
JURY	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skillbeck	I-pers
John	B-pers
Plaw	I-pers
Humphry	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
Luke	B-pers
Adlington	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Plumpton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Cover	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wickers	I-pers
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
will	O
be	O
given	O
in	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
181	O
,	O
182	O
,	O
183	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHMOND	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLAYTON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
ROSS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
thirty	O
womens	O
necklaces	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
||	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
lighted	O
candles	O
,	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
any	O
person	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
the	O
candles	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
fitting	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
blood	O
upon	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
the	O
blood	O
was	O
quite	O
fresh	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
some	O
silk	O
ribbands	O
and	O
some	O
head	O
necklaces	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
are	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
thing	O
very	O
particular	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
remnants	O
of	O
different	O
colours	O
,	O
two	O
blues	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
but	O
different	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
shade	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
pink	O
coloured	O
remnant	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
that	O
day	O
all	O
three	O
on	O
one	O
block	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
just	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
When	O
Clayton	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
his	O
finger	O
was	O
cut	O
;	O
it	O
then	O
appeared	O
quite	O
fresh	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
brother	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
at	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
window	O
break	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
immediately	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nobody	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
perceive	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
low	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
my	O
brother	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
likewise	O
the	O
blood	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
:	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
somebody	O
about	O
them	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
few	O
shillings	O
over	O
,	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
uncertain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
before	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
shirt	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
afternoon	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
swear	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
now	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
other	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
carried	O
there	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
find	O
is	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
reckoning	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
frequent	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
by	O
a	O
chance	O
.	O
James	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
fifteen	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
particularly	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
a	O
going	O
to	O
Marybone	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
till	O
;	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
ribbons	O
and	O
laces	O
caught	O
our	O
eyes	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
a	O
chymill	O
's	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
broke	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
wires	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
hooked	O
the	O
ribbons	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
wires	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
his	O
fore-finger	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
I	O
think	O
with	O
his	O
knife	O
;	O
Richmond	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
Clayton	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
immediately	O
to	O
Richmond	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
ten	O
or	O
twenty	O
turns	O
;	O
Richmond	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
for	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ribbons	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
balls	O
of	O
ribbons	O
and	O
five	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
.	O
Richmond	O
took	O
three	O
cards	O
and	O
eight	O
balls	O
of	O
ribbons	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
necklaces	O
to	O
Evans	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
breakfasted	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
Murphy	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
burnt	O
the	O
ribband	O
blocks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cards	O
we	O
threw	O
away	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
about	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
removed	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
under	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
Richmond	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
wires	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
Clayton	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Richmond	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
message	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
through	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Parish	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
stop	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
Ross	O
and	O
him	O
together	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
take	O
this	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
ribbons	O
,	O
necklaces	O
,	O
and	O
laces	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Coventry-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
and	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
where	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
for	O
Parish	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
wire	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Ross	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Three	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Clayton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
playing	O
with	O
my	O
play-fellows	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
chopping	O
an	O
apple	O
and	O
chopped	O
my	O
knuckle	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Ross	O
called	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
RICHMOND	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
CLAYTON	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
ROSS	O
acquitted	O
.	O
184	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
fish	O
skin	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
.	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surveyer	O
of	O
the	O
excise	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Titchfield-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
excise	O
books	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bed	O
gown	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
done	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kenrick	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
spectacles	O
and	O
two	O
excise	O
books	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kenrick	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
claimed	O
as	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Kenrick	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
black	O
coat	O
and	O
these	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
spectacles	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
there	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
that	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
coat	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
it	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
this	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
this	O
pocket	O
book	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
Horner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
daughter	O
:	O
my	O
father	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
about	O
one	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Horner	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
tea	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
a	O
chapter	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
locked	O
then	O
?	O
Horner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
windows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Horner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
upon	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
whether	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
thought	O
you	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
unlatch	O
?	O
Horner	O
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
read	O
the	O
chapter	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
a	O
more	O
bulkey	O
man	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
greatly	O
frightened	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
it	O
took	O
my	O
speech	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
directly	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
neighbours	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
nothing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
but	O
the	O
sheet	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
Kenrick	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
bed	O
top	O
and	O
sheet	O
are	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Kenrick	I-pers
.	O
A	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
this	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
this	O
Sunday	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
two	O
men	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
they	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
immediately	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Windsor	O
Castle	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
found	O
abundance	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
this	O
old	O
black	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
and	O
spectacles	O
now	O
produced	O
.	O
Seeing	O
the	O
book	O
contained	O
entries	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
tallow	O
chandler	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
to	O
an	O
excise-man	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Horner	O
's	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
mean	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Horner	O
's	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
these	O
robbers	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
Holborn	O
I	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
In	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Brown	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
with	O
that	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Poppin's-alley	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
hand	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
drink	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
185	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowswell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
~	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rowswell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
at	O
eight	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
in	O
Vine-street	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
back	I-place
of	I-place
Chandois	I-place
street	I-place
;	O
she	O
was	O
absent	O
nine	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
evening	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
suffer	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
of	O
an	O
evening	O
?	O
Rowswell	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
did	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
or	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ringwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
one	O
morning	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
a	O
favour	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
the	O
pillowbier	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
pawn	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rochfort	O
's	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
for	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Rochfort	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-court	O
:	O
this	O
Ringwood	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
pillowbiers	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
she	O
pledged	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
these	O
sheets	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
when	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
lodging	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Whether	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
but	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
?	O
Rowswell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
have	O
clean	O
linen	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murthwaite	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
check	O
curtains	O
and	O
a	O
bed	O
quilt	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
are	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
pawned	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Ringwood	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
proposed	O
to	O
compromise	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
denied	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
186	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
PUGH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Shingle	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Daniel	B-pers
Shingle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
's	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
while	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Shingle	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
clothes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
these	O
clothes	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
of	O
these	O
clothes	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
those	O
offered	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Shingle	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
questions	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
detained	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Shingle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
are	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
187	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
TIBBALLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty-three	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boodger	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boodger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Long	B-place
Acre	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
from	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
morning	O
exposed	O
several	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
a	O
stall	O
;	O
among	O
them	O
was	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
.	O
-	O
Harman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
goods	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
informed	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
down	O
into	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cloth	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
write	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
every	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
I	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
upon	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
the	O
cloth	O
up	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
188	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
shew	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
brass	O
cocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
wooden	O
scale	O
boxes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brind	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Brind	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Turnstile	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
wooden	O
boxes	O
and	O
four	O
brass	O
cocks	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
?	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
box	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shew	O
glass	O
and	O
its	O
contents	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
some	O
boys	O
hollowed	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
job	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
till	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
189	O
,	O
190	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
STANFORD	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Cavernor	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cavernor	O
Tate	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
.	O
Cavernor	O
Tate	O
is	O
my	O
husband	O
:	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
sea-faring-man	O
;	O
our	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Coal	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
St	I-place
.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
window	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
very	O
much	O
alarmed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
chamber	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
garret	O
window	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
garret	O
window	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
under	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
?	O
Tate	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
's	O
father	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
concerned	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
made	O
her	O
escape	O
.	O
My	O
property	O
was	O
packed	O
under	O
Mrs.	O
Stanford	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
there	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
as	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
left	O
by	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Tate	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Tate	O
cry	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
moon	O
shone	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
exactly	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
nobody	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
shadow	O
of	O
some	O
woman	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
tiles	O
from	O
one	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
which	O
was	O
Stanford	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
upon	O
the	O
tiles	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
saw	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
stand	O
trembling	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Bet	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
robbed	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
thieves	O
were	O
gone	O
by	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
broke	O
her	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
frightened	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
is	O
turned	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Bet	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
her	O
cousin	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
with	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
drawn	O
over	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
Hartly	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
Stanford	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
are	O
esteemed	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
.	O
-	O
Hartly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanford	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
tea	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
In	O
Cloth	O
Fair	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
and	O
cannisters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
the	O
night	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tate	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
Stanford	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
before	O
Lewis	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Just	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
hid	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
Stanford	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
Stanford	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
women	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
informed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lewis	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
searched	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Lewis	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
key	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
of	O
any	O
consequence	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
key	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Tate	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
case	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
ship	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Stanford	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
191	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GORDON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
stuff	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lockwood	O
,	O
in	O
Edward-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
coach	O
from	O
the	O
stable	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shadow	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
toward	O
Cavendish-square	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
from	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
coat	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
wrote	O
on	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
192	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DODSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
pannel	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
tenant	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17th	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
chest	O
locked	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
two	O
saws	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
.	O
My	O
chest	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
two	O
others	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
saws	O
,	O
particularly	O
these	O
two	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
one	O
saw	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Alderst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cordee	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
saws	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
saws	O
cost	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
tenant	O
saw	O
cost	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
something	O
of	O
saws	O
,	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Squires	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
pawned	O
the	O
saws	O
for	O
one	O
Barnsby	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
a	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
193	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILLET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oilman	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
shopman	O
:	O
I	O
suspected	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
not	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
got	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
and	O
Robert	O
Hughes	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
marked	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
out	O
three	O
shillings	O
a-piece	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
till	O
and	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
marked	O
money	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
possession	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
suffer	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
give	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
hole	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
silver	O
through	O
;	O
the	O
shillings	O
were	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
notch	O
in	O
the	O
edge	O
above	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Collyer	O
to	O
get	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
compting	O
house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Collyer	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
dishonest	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wondered	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
about	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Collyer	O
picked	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
marked	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
marked	O
shillings	O
that	O
were	O
laid	O
out	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
could	O
detect	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
queen	O
Annis	O
shillings	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fancy	O
to	O
the	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
any	O
shillings	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
marked	O
ones	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
put	O
other	O
shillings	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
ten	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
194	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
GODFREY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31st	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sea-faring-man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Rag-fair	B-place
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
accosted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
from	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Streights	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
a	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wild	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
throwing	O
his	O
money	O
away	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
gamble	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
his	O
money	O
as	O
another	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
'squire	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
money	O
enough	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
'squire	O
and	O
another	O
began	O
gaming	O
,	O
by	O
naming	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
put	O
under	O
a	O
candlestick	O
;	O
the	O
'squire	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
among	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
barbers	O
,	O
taylors	O
,	O
and	O
weavers	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
every	O
one	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
every	O
guinea	O
he	O
can	O
produce	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
what	O
money	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
'squire	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
?	O
Leman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
some	O
motions	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
candles	O
were	O
all	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
landlady	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
any	O
particular	O
complaint	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
enquired	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
began	O
the	O
gambling	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
lately	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
relations	O
?	O
Leman	O
.	O
His	O
relations	O
wanted	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
money	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
offered	O
me	O
eight	O
guineas	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
wife	O
if	O
the	O
company	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
what	O
particularly	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
the	O
Justices	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
office	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warrant	O
out	O
from	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
crossing	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
at	O
play	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
afterwards	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
paid	O
their	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
i	O
n	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
searce	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cranfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
within	O
this	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
Leman	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
for	O
four	O
more	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Cranfield	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
?	O
Cranfield	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Cranfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
they	O
offered	O
me	O
eight	O
guineas	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
195	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
locket	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Jan.	O
15th	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
taking	O
in	O
plain	O
work	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
gold	O
chain	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
played	O
the	O
rogue	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
next	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
about	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
-	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
society	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
who	O
meet	O
once	O
a	O
week	O
upon	O
business	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
brought	O
this	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
money	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
whisper	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
;	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elcock	O
I	O
believed	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
a	O
chain	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
chain	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
-	O
Jackson	O
,	O
a	O
master	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
worked	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
196	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
stuff	O
called	O
morine	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
++	O
-	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouse-man	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
,	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
morine	O
,	O
about	O
forty-eight	O
yards	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
morine	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
inn	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Hagley	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
instant	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
stealing	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
George-yards	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Bugden	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Rounds	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Bugden	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
;	O
Bugden	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
piece	O
he	O
stole	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
morine	O
from	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Bugden	O
's	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rowe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
morine	O
in	O
Bugden	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
-	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
cut	O
the	O
mark	O
off	O
that	O
we	O
always	O
make	O
to	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
our	O
goods	O
by	O
the	O
colour	O
.	O
-	O
Longsden	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
George	O
inn	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
answerable	O
for	O
whatever	O
is	O
brought	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
by	O
theHagley	O
waggon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
SOLOMONS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
half	O
firkin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
24	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
;	O
I	O
drive	O
the	O
Greenwich	O
stage	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
and	O
some	O
cheese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
butter	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
call	O
two	O
passengers	O
.	O
Whatever	O
is	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
I	O
am	O
answerable	O
for	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gadsden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Brown	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
attending	O
upon	O
some	O
passengers	O
while	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
cheese	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
the	O
passengers	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
stepping	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
tumbled	O
down	O
between	O
the	O
wheel	O
and	O
the	O
wheel	O
iron	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
tustle	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
butter	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
horses	O
heads	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
butter	O
into	O
the	O
boot	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
hit	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
over	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
numbed	O
me	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
my	O
hold	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
changed	O
hands	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
;	O
we	O
fought	O
together	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
where	O
Brown	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
passengers	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tustle	O
with	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
more	O
assistance	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
cask	O
that	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
?	O
Gadsden	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Looks	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
for	O
the	O
mark	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
made	O
it	O
?	O
Gadsden	O
.	O
Not	O
when	O
it	O
went	O
away	O
but	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Gadsden	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
direction	O
when	O
it	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
John	O
somebody	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
at	O
that	O
distance	O
to	O
distinguish	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
have	O
seen	O
any	O
body	O
at	O
that	O
distance	O
that	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
he	O
slipped	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very-sure	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
hay	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
for	O
his	O
rabbits	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
sold-oranges	O
and	O
lemons	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
198	O
,	O
199	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ASHFORD	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THURGOLAND	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Alexander	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stew-pan	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
covered	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
kept	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
my	O
house	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
I	O
found	O
wanting	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
and	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
was	O
at	O
Thurgoland	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
stew-pan	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
's	O
necessary	O
house	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
were	O
found	O
some	O
suspicious	O
tools	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
houses	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
both	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
the	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
was	O
at	O
Thurgoland	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stew-pan	O
pawned	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
described	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
very	O
tea-kettle	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
tea-kettle	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
the	O
stewpan	O
was	O
pawned	O
by	O
one	O
Robinson	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stew-pan	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
pawned	O
the	O
stew-pan	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
direction	O
.	O
ASHFORTH	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
THURGOLAND	O
acquitted	O
.	O
200	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
LONG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
Finch-lane	B-place
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
buckles	O
;	O
she	O
held	O
her	O
head	O
down	O
so	O
that	O
her	O
hat	O
was	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
three	O
pair	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
trying	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
returned	O
one	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
her	O
cloak	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
dropped	O
out	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
she	O
ever	O
did	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
buckles	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DENNIS	B-pers
DOYLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
d	O
.	O
two	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
hempen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
double-locked	O
the	O
middle	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
doors	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
I	O
left	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
We	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cawser	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Swan	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
too	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Swan	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Swan	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Swan	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
bundled	O
up	O
,	O
not	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
any	O
wrapper	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
strewed	O
them	O
about	O
upon	O
the	O
shop	O
floor	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Swan	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
time	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
stout	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
blue	O
clothes	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
scales	O
to	O
weigh	O
silver	O
;	O
a	O
question	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
asked	O
before	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
it	O
affected	O
me	O
so	O
I	O
dropped	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
discharged	O
by	O
the	O
Thatched-house	O
society	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
prison	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
an	O
execution	O
for	O
twenty-eight	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
drew	O
me	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
something	O
of	O
attempting	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
Ireland	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
a	O
lad	O
of	O
:	O
but	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
giving	O
satisfactory	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
questions	O
put	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
respecting	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
door	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
unlatch	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
never	O
mind	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
knock	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
put	O
a	O
round	O
thing	O
into	O
the	O
key	O
hole	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
locked	O
myself	O
into	O
the	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EUSFACE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
4th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
WYNN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
thirteen-and-sixpenny	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
base	O
six-and-ninepenny	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WALSOM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Poter-street	B-place
:	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
instant	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
till	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
;	O
the	O
wash-house	O
is	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
At	O
half	O
after	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
breaking	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
wash-house	O
;	O
the	O
building	O
all	O
joins	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
undone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
entirely	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
split	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash-house	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
clear	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
alarmed	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
upon	O
my	O
premises	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
all	O
the	O
places	O
are	O
yours	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
communicate	O
with	O
other	O
houses	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sheds	O
all	O
along	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
alley	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
common	O
to	O
three	O
houses	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Story	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
stick	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
wash-house	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Warren	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
instant	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Warren	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
back	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dodson	O
's	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
rather	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
ten	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
would	O
draw	O
no	O
more	O
liquor	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Wheatsheaf	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
money	O
enough	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
back	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
Peter-street	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
alley	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
case	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
stop	O
a	O
bit	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
for	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
the	O
alley	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
entirely	O
a	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lay	O
a	O
wager	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
cast	O
me	O
for	O
death	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Justice	O
ask	O
Warren	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
Watchman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
money	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
Warren	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
read	O
the	O
account	O
you	O
gave	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
there	O
you	O
said	O
Walsom	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
without	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
Walsom	O
went	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
between	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
and	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
;	O
Walsom	O
pulled	O
down	O
a	O
window	O
light	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
light	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
wash-house	O
of	O
one	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
both	O
which	O
places	O
were	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Walsom	O
in	O
your	O
sight	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
wash-house	O
window	O
;	O
Walsom	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
bearing	O
a	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
two	O
made	O
off	O
together	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Walsom	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash	O
house	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
Walsom	O
left	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
the	O
wash-house	O
that	O
he	O
borrowed	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
was	O
that	O
account	O
then	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
account	O
you	O
have	O
now	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
true	O
one	O
?	O
Warren	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
mention	O
to	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
let	O
the	O
window	O
down	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
told	O
a	O
lie	O
before	O
him	O
?	O
Warren	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Maylin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
iron	O
founder	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Saffron	O
hill	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Charter-house-lane	O
,	O
drinking	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
watchman	O
in	O
blue	O
drinking	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
company	O
was	O
jeering	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
blood	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
laugh	O
or	O
do	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
his	O
life	O
away	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
tap	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
a	O
wager	O
with	O
Jemmy	O
Stanford	O
,	O
a	O
currier	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
Walsom	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Cliffe	O
and	O
Murrell	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
now	O
under	O
sentence	O
of	O
death	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
committed	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
105	O
,	O
106	O
,	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARK	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-five	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
clasps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
boatswain	O
's	O
silver	O
call	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
stock	O
buckle	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
studs	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
broaches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
locket	O
and	O
six	O
silver	O
thimbles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
seventy-two	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
hair	O
sprig	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
ten	O
other	O
broaches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
seventy-two	O
pair	O
of	O
gilded	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
stone	O
crosses	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shew	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Jan.	O
18th	O
.	O
||	O
Richard	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-street	B-place
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
and	O
hardware	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
my	O
shew	O
glass	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
lies	O
upon	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
My	O
shew	O
glass	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
quantity	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
about	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Boddington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
you	O
lost	O
were	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
?	O
Boddington	O
.	O
They	O
stood	O
me	O
in	O
about	O
sixty-five	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
print	O
hand	O
bills	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
would	O
make	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
secreted	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation	O
office	O
;	O
there	O
Clark	O
took	O
me	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
while	O
the	O
Justices	O
were	O
examining	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
property	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
this	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
evidence	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
;	O
Fitzgerald	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
.	O
Warren	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
Ratcliff	O
highway	O
,	O
looking	O
for	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
rob	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
places	O
that	O
we	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
we	O
thought	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
was	O
in	O
Burr-street	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
that	O
house	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
with	O
an	O
undertaker	O
's	O
hatch	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
shew	O
glass	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
places	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
into	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
Brown	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
Warren	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Mulberry	O
Gardens	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartman	I-pers
in	O
Winfield	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
us	O
a	O
white	O
bag	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartman	I-pers
?	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
rightly	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
no	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
?	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
a	O
room	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
thief	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
Clarke	O
and	O
Warren	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Fise	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
nick	O
name	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
other	O
name	O
,	O
some	O
call	O
him	O
Scampe	O
.	O
Boddington	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
receiving	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
bail	O
.	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
unknown	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
only	O
buy	O
the	O
plate	O
of	O
them	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Warren	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
all	O
but	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
money	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
mutton	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
had	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
without	O
they	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
a	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Fise	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
talking	O
Dutch	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
saw	O
the	O
stones	O
must	O
be	O
knocked	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
;	O
Warren	O
gave	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
a	O
guinea	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Hartman	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
letting	O
him	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
These	O
buckles	O
and	O
buttons	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Boddington	O
.	O
We	O
kept	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
Warren	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Fise	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
all	O
back	O
but	O
these	O
buckles	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
lining	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Warren	O
.	O
Fitzgerald	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
picking	O
pockets	O
,	O
but	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
hand-cuffs	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
.	O
About	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
Fitzgerald	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
silver	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
silver	O
and	O
stone	O
buckles	O
and	O
silver	O
things	O
of	O
different	O
sorts	O
;	O
Fitzgerald	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Hartman	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
silver	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Hartman	O
lend	O
them	O
that	O
bag	O
?	O
Bigg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
boiled	O
a	O
pudding	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
tear	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
Hartman	O
;	O
Fitzgerald	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Bigg	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
Fitzgerald	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
pick	O
out	O
which	O
pair	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
property	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
that	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
thief-catchers	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bird	O
cage	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
bread	O
?	O
Bigg	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
old	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
married	O
?	O
Bigg	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Hartman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hartman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Fitzgerald	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
were	O
those	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
take	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Mulberry	O
Gardens	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
case	O
in	O
the	O
Mulberry	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Hartman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Mayland	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
belonging	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Fitzgerald	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mayland	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
with	O
Fitzgerald	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Fitzgerald	O
first	O
;	O
Fitzgerald	O
and	O
Clark	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Brand	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brand	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
all	O
by	O
sight	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
Warren	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
Fitzgerald	O
and	O
Brown	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
Warren	O
and	O
Clark	O
were	O
out	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
drank	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
Warren	O
never	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
eleven	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
they	O
had	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
there	O
?	O
Brand	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
Hartman	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Hartman	O
and	O
Bigg	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
recollected	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
they	O
use	O
your	O
house	O
much	O
;	O
how	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
together	O
?	O
Brand	O
.	O
Not	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Warren	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
myself	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Brand	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
in	O
particular	O
whether	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mayland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
them	O
;	O
Hartman	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Mulberry	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
silver	O
buttons	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
rings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
He	O
named	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
?	O
Mayland	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
and	O
Digby	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stone	O
breast	O
buckle	O
on	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Clark	O
and	O
Fitzgerald	O
in	O
one	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
solid	O
silver	O
buttons	O
and	O
some	O
seals	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
Hartman	O
's	O
girl	O
(	O
Bigg	O
)	O
had	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
produces	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
taken	O
on	O
Fitzgerald	O
;	O
the	O
stone	O
cross	O
taken	O
under	O
Clark	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
Hartman	O
's	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
Mulberry	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Warren	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
evidence	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
concerns	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
stuck	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
living	O
:	O
I	O
sell	O
things	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
potatoes	O
and	O
greens	O
.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
concern	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Brown	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
uncle	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Clark	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
108	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
JOHN	I-pers
PITTAWAY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
,	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
31st	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
College-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
char-woman	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
my	O
wife	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
whilst	O
she	O
was	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
nothing	O
without	O
advice	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
by	O
her	O
daughter	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Diana	B-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
in	O
Angel-court	O
;	O
she	O
mentioned	O
two	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
A	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
daughter	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Tothil-street	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bengough	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Broad	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
things	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Diana	O
Dye	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
three	O
shirts	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
(	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
pledge	O
the	O
two	O
saucepans	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bengough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
three	O
sheets	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Diana	O
Dye	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
silver	O
spoons	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pittaway	I-pers
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
raise	O
money	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
under	O
an	O
execution	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
replace	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
109	O
,	O
110	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
BEAN	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRUDELL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
1st	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Thacker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hung	O
this	O
gown	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
about	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
looking	O
about	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
observed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bounced	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
in	O
particular	O
what	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
stood	O
watching	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
two	O
men	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
cutting	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
400	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
said	O
lead	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling	O
house	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Peart	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Peart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
some	O
neighbours	O
that	O
live	O
opposite	O
an	O
uninhabited	O
house	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
Thomas	B-place
Apostle	I-place
,	O
informed	O
me	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
workmen	O
repairing	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
there	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
bolted	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
Having	O
a	O
scaffold	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
had	O
entered	O
by	O
the	O
garret	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
lead	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
stacks	O
,	O
the	O
gutter	O
and	O
eve	O
lead	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
wait	O
there	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
padlock	O
and	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stracy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
discerned	O
the	O
leaden	O
pipes	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
me	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
follow	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
adjoining	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
garret	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
cock	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
padlock	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
his	O
tools	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
I	O
knocked	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rangle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Peart	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Peart	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
an	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
examination	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
confessed	O
where	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
got	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
story	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
discover	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
112	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Strokes	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17th	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
execute	O
at	O
St.	O
Martin's-le-grand	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
