TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1774	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fourteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Frederick	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
down	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
39	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FREDERICK	B-pers
BULL	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
Charles	B-pers
Birkhead	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Heathcote	I-pers
John	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
Humphrey	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Avery	B-pers
Vokins	I-pers
Owen	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Catman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Affleck	I-pers
John	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hawter	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Grieve	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bain	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Whittaker	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Laiton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lambe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
John	B-pers
Musgrave	I-pers
Ignatius	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Morris	B-pers
Marsault	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Boyfield	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Laiton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
358	O
,	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
DYER	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
KELLY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tip-staff	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Feb.	O
21st	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
clasp	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Macormack	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
21st	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Salt	B-place
Petre	I-place
Bank	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
who	O
were	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
one	O
caught	O
me	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
my	O
arms	O
;	O
they	O
rifled	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
my	O
mouth	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
about	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tip-staff	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
)	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
they	O
swore	O
sadly	O
,	O
and	O
Dyer	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
struggling	O
because	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
hands	O
fast	O
they	O
did	O
cut	O
me	O
a-cross	O
the	O
fingers	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
A	O
pin	O
perhaps	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
pin	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
or	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
go	O
into	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
things	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
people	O
I	O
knew	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
five	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
Peg	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
taken	O
together	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
first	O
two	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
over	O
night	O
the	O
other	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
took	O
her	O
aside	O
afterwards	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
principal	O
concerned	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
admit	O
her	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
offer	O
some	O
little	O
reward	O
for	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
next	O
day	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
keeps	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
girls	O
company	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
pretty	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
women	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
Salt-Petre-Bank	O
acquaintance	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
business	O
five	O
years	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
these	O
people	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
business	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Nightingale	O
lane	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
upon	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
deal	O
in	O
watches	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
extraordinary	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
two	O
watches	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
on	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
home	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
following	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
again	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
since	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
rescued	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
going	O
through	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
fancy	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
in	O
earnest	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
keeper	O
belonging	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
things	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
women	O
left	O
you	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
immediately	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
but	O
was	O
very	O
sensible	O
and	O
knew	O
every	O
transaction	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
Dyer	O
.	O
Farrell	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
lad	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Farrell	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Farrell	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
never	O
mind	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
we	O
want	O
first	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
women	O
lest	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
women	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
get	O
them	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
women	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Dyer	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Macormack	I-pers
.	O
Blundell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
first	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
separately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
took	O
Macormack	O
and	O
Jones	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
Blundell	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
people	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Macormack	O
and	O
Jones	O
?	O
Blundell	O
It	O
was	O
Farrell	O
's	O
doing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
looks	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
mistaken	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Knightly	I-pers
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
said	O
if	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
admit	O
her	O
an	O
evidence	O
she	O
would	O
produce	O
the	O
two	O
watches	O
and	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
destroy	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
and	O
dash	O
the	O
two	O
watches	O
to	O
pieces	O
before	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
Knightly	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Knightly	O
.	O
In	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Near	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
?	O
Knightly	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
moved	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
curiosity	O
?	O
Knightly	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
upon	O
some	O
other	O
business	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
Farrell	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
publickly	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Farrell	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
bringing	O
him	O
there	O
on	O
a	O
foolish	O
errand	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
denied	O
saying	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
Farrell	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Dobree	I-pers
,	O
April	O
29th	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
William	I-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
follow	O
a	O
gentleman	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
passed	O
my	O
window	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
stoop	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
pick	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Pudding-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
something	O
white	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
breast	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
this	O
shirt	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
a	O
carman	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
gentleman	O
and	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Wilkes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dobree	O
deposed	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dobree	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kingdom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Thames-street	O
the	O
witness	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Laurence	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lain	O
several	O
nights	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
dishonest	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cutler	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
maker	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
failed	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
journey	O
work	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
pains	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
education	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
bushels	O
of	O
wheat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
four	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lyons	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
362	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Brockland	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
21st	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Brockland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Northampton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Southern	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Northampton-street	O
,	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
:	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
left	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
dirty	O
foot	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
soot	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
chimney	O
sweeper	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
Morris	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gown	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
at	O
the	O
call	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
(	O
they	O
are	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
chimneys	O
to	O
sweep	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
where	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sweep	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
his	O
bag	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
somebody	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
his	O
bag	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sweep	O
a	O
chimney	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
363	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DODD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
firkin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Desante	I-pers
,	O
May	O
12th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
364	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HAWKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Croucher	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
July	O
28th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
365	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
366	O
,	O
367	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
MECUM	I-pers
and	O
HENRY	B-pers
NEWLAND	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
brown	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Colin	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
April	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
Colin	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
?	O
Bruce	O
.	O
Newland	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
ship-mate	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
thank	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
mate	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	I-place
Tower-hill	I-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mecum	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
tossing	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
of	O
wagering	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
against	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Mecum	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
clothes	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
Newland	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
quite	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
clothes	O
again	O
?	O
Bruce	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
toss	O
up	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Bruce	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
bundle	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
threatned	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
disturbance	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
gaol	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
called	O
guineas	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
there	O
but	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
landlord	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
has	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
Mecum	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
threaten	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
if	O
be	O
made	O
any	O
disturbance	O
you	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
gaol	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
clothes	O
at	O
gaming	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
laid	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
against	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
named	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
three	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
four	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
as	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
gaming	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bruce	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
hear	O
what	O
this	O
man	O
says	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
true	O
?	O
Bruce	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
understand	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gaming	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
gaming	O
among	O
themselves	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
clothes	O
by	O
gaming	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
;	O
my	O
brother	O
complained	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
.	O
Mecum	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
Bruce	O
;	O
Bruce	O
and	O
I	O
tossed	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
Bruce	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
toss	O
up	O
for	O
any	O
more	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bet	O
his	O
clothes	O
against	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
betted	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
against	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
won	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
won	O
them	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
won	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
not	O
opened	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
.	O
Newland	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
ship-mate	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
mistake	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mecum	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
tossing	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
Bruce	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
to	O
toss	O
for	O
another	O
pint	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
they	O
ageed	O
to	O
toss	O
for	O
the	O
clothes	O
against	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
the	O
sum	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
before	O
two	O
proper	O
witnesses	O
of	O
the	O
Surry	O
militia	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
won	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
gaming	O
,	O
or	O
gambling	O
,	O
or	O
correspondence	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
Surry	O
militia	O
.	O
Newland	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
368	O
,	O
369	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MORLEY	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HANDBY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13th	O
.	O
~	O
Alexander	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
Bank-street	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Sun	O
Fire	O
Office	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
and	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
boy	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
Fire	O
Office	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
a	O
coachman	O
got	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
number	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Duncastle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
picking	O
pockets	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
knowing	O
the	O
biggest	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
notorious	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
them	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
attempt	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
both	O
stopped	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
stood	O
opposite	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
St.	O
Mildred	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
Fire	O
Office	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Morley	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
attempted	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
catched	O
him	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
borrowed	O
a	O
coachman	O
's	O
whip	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
myself	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Morley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Handby	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
lad	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
the	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Hanby	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
370	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
CONNERLY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Arder	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Arder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
:	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
house	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Arder	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
stranger	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
breeches	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
pulled	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
breeches	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
but	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
dropped	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
rag	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
governor	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
positively	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
guineas	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
light	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
guineas	O
is	O
not	O
much	O
bigger	O
than	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
money	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
371	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	B-pers
GRAY	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
GRAVES	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow	O
bier	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
garnet	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11th	O
.	O
++	O
Isabella	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Milk-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Dean-street	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
my	O
payments	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
suspected	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
my	O
husband	O
insisted	O
on	O
her	O
being	O
searched	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
saw	O
her	O
open	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
silk	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
-	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
called	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
while	O
he	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
muslin	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
pillow	O
bier	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
muslin	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
372	O
,	O
373	O
,	O
374	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
CAMPBELL	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TINGEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
LONSDALE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
indigo	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mather	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
12th	O
.	O
*	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
375	O
.	O
376	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GUNSTON	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HATFIELD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
wooden	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
quart	O
glass	O
bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
pepper	O
mint	O
water	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
28th	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
377	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
BURN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cort	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
tea	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Cort	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
him	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
lying	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bundle	O
produced	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
378	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
April	O
3d	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
379	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
three-quarters	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
five	O
yards	O
and	O
three-quarters	O
of	O
silk	O
mode	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
ermine	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
quilted	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
4th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
73	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
bordered	O
quilting	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Michael	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mess	O
.	O
Owen	O
and	O
Foot	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
linen	O
draper	O
s.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
begged	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goslin	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Leigh-street	O
,	O
Red	O
Lion-square	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
would	O
be	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
immediately	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
just	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
money	O
immediately	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
I	O
apprehended	O
her	O
:	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
this	O
she	O
sent	O
us	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
directing	O
us	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
in	O
Bear-street	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
that	O
we	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
might	O
be	O
obtained	O
directly	O
by	O
applying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
might	O
arrest	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
cause	O
depending	O
in	O
Westminster-hall	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
her	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
designed	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
with	O
two	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
or	O
starve	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
380	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
80	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
used	O
with	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
April	O
8th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2000	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lancashire	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
his	O
building	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
April	O
8th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
used	O
with	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
April	O
8th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
381	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
(	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
being	O
therein	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
nankeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Pimlico	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
a	O
nankeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
three	O
stocks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
sister	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Rice	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Five	O
Fields	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Holmes	O
's	O
window	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
two	O
bundles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
put	O
one	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
them	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
another	O
bundle	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
watch	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
stripped	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
bundles	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
suspicions	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
these	O
two	O
bundles	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
pig	O
sty	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
bundles	O
were	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundles	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
the	O
nankeen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
shoes	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
people	O
running	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
till	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
parlour	O
was	O
stripped	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
thief	O
a-cross	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Williams	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
clothes	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
382	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
BROCKHOUSE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
thirty-seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Schiroli	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Bourgesis	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
383	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
LEVY	B-pers
SAMUEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
signed	O
Andrew	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
1773	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
said	O
note	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
,	O
three	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
did	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Levy	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
Dec.	O
13th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
384	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
box	O
lock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rachael	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Butts	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Butts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christopher	B-pers
Han	I-pers
,	O
April	O
20th	O
.	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
385	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
ruffled	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
plain	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Donald	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
386	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JANE	B-pers
CORNFORTH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
her	O
male	O
bastard	O
child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
certain	O
privy	O
belonging	O
to	O
Paul	B-pers
Cauldwell	I-pers
,	O
thereby	O
giving	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
child	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
belly	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
navel	O
,	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
wound	O
the	O
said	O
child	O
did	O
die	O
,	O
Feb.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
*	O
Paul	B-pers
Cauldwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
cook	O
maid	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
1774	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
my	O
servant	O
man	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
that	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
Jenny	O
,	O
the	O
cook	O
,	O
knew	O
best	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
kept	O
her	O
room	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
in	O
cleaning	O
the	O
grate	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
got	O
up	O
without	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
something	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
carpenter	O
to	O
pull	O
up	O
the	O
vault	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
alive	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
in	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
bring	O
the	O
child	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
accordingly	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
who	O
had	O
wives	O
fetched	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
dress	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
all	O
in	O
their	O
power	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
life	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dressed	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
alive	O
and	O
a	O
male	O
child	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mackerness	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
necessary	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tingle	I-pers
bid	O
me	O
step	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
hear	O
something	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
there	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
Williams	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
could	O
this	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
he	O
listened	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
same	O
noise	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
hole	O
,	O
looked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
say	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
unless	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
again	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
move	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
vault	O
was	O
knocked	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
reached	O
up	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
apron	O
and	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
alive	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tingle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
candle	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
stick	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
this	O
that	O
appeared	O
white	O
,	O
pushing	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
vaults	O
one	O
behind	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
stick	O
as	O
if	O
something	O
was	O
guiding	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Mackerness	I-pers
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
step	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
we	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
Williams	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
candle	O
and	O
looked	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
perceived	O
the	O
hand	O
move	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
we	O
said	O
take	O
care	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
dangerous	O
thing	O
,	O
acquaint	O
our	O
master	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
Williams	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
the	O
vault	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stick	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
afterwards	O
,	O
with	O
soil	O
six	O
inches	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
fetch	O
Mackerness	O
's	O
wife	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
Williams	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
apron	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Tingle	O
and	O
Mackerness	O
told	O
me	O
something	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
that	O
occasioned	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
look	O
down	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
hands	O
moving	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
its	O
face	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
this	O
necessary	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
Jenny	O
knew	O
best	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
vault	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
apron	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Tingle	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
then	O
alive	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mark	O
about	O
its	O
navel	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
entrails	O
were	O
out	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackerness	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
in	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tingle	I-pers
's	O
wife	O
's	O
lap	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
and	O
clean	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wash	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
heart	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
then	O
alive	O
;	O
I	O
washed	O
it	O
,	O
cleaned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
dressed	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mistress	O
sent	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
rag	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
the	O
belly	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
navel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bowels	O
out	O
about	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
pint	O
pot	O
full	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
doctor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Olive	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
the	O
entrails	O
;	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
so	O
small	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
bigger	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
sewed	O
up	O
the	O
wound	O
with	O
three	O
stitches	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
at	O
the	O
work-house	O
dead	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tingle	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
my	O
husband	O
fetched	O
me	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
accident	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cauldwell	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
brought	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
coals	O
and	O
ashes	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wound	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
its	O
navel	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
washed	O
and	O
cleaned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
desired	O
the	O
doctor	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
entrails	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
groaned	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cauldwell	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Jenny	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
strange	O
to	O
me	O
you	O
could	O
commit	O
an	O
act	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
you	O
into	O
the	O
hospital	O
to	O
lie-in	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
acquainted	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
answer	O
she	O
made	O
to	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
what	O
could	O
she	O
do	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tingle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
stained	O
with	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
after-burthen	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
coarse	O
apron	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mackerness	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Tingle	O
when	O
she	O
examined	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
bed	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
condition	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
if	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
lain-in	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
washing	O
tub	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
midwife	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
after-burthen	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
burthen	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
sacking	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
coarse	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
alive	O
at	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
mistress	O
where	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
dirtied	O
in	O
her	O
labour	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Tingle	O
and	O
Mackerness	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
were	O
then	O
washing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
only	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
head	O
ach	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
growth	O
;	O
had	O
its	O
hair	O
and	O
nails	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cut	O
a-cross	O
the	O
belly	O
above	O
the	O
navel	O
;	O
the	O
bowels	O
were	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
confusions	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
such	O
as	O
to	O
kill	O
,	O
only	O
bruise	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
stick	O
she	O
poked	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
throw	O
ashes	O
in	O
upon	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
because	O
she	O
thought	O
the	O
soil	O
was	O
not	O
deep	O
enough	O
to	O
cover	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Olive	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
this	O
child	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
lap	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cauldwell	O
's	O
kitchen	O
;	O
a	O
considerable	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
intestines	O
came	O
through	O
a	O
small	O
wound	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
above	O
the	O
navel	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
return	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
abdomen	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
dilated	O
the	O
wound	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
cleaned	O
and	O
returned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
stitched	O
up	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
difficulty	O
in	O
reducing	O
these	O
intestines	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
some	O
few	O
ashes	O
or	O
cinders	O
were	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
wounded	O
:	O
the	O
wound	O
appeared	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
with	O
a	O
sharpish	O
instrument	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
too	O
irregular	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
particular	O
marks	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
wound	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
blunt	O
stick	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
by	O
meeting	O
some	O
sharp	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
soil	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
throwing	O
the	O
child	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
a	O
nail	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
wound	O
and	O
the	O
intestines	O
being	O
so	O
long	O
exposed	O
to	O
the	O
cold	O
air	O
were	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
death	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
coroner	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
plainly	O
discover	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
intestines	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
exposed	O
to	O
the	O
cold	O
air	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
discoloured	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
lived	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
hours	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
wound	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
think	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
impossible	O
but	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
intestines	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
wounded	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
life	O
was	O
lost	O
by	O
this	O
wound	O
and	O
the	O
intestines	O
coming	O
so	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
body	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
work-house	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
saving	O
two	O
lives	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
preserve	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
it	O
lived	O
till	O
half	O
past	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
commit	O
so	O
rash	O
an	O
action	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
the	O
wound	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
belly	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
poking	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
senses	O
when	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
by	O
accident	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
tender	O
,	O
humane	O
,	O
good	O
natured	O
girl	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
some	O
new	O
linen	O
about	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
Christmas	O
day	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
humane	O
tender	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
for	O
her	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cauldwell	O
's	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Sunday	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
she	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
warning	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
very	O
particular	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
humane	O
tender	O
girl	O
.	O
Lydia	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
a	O
tender	O
humane	O
girl	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
tender	O
and	O
affectionate	O
to	O
wards	O
children	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
humane	O
and	O
charitable	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
though	O
but	O
little	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
tender	O
good	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
girl	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
warm	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
eight	O
months	O
:	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
charitable	O
and	O
humane	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
kind	O
to	O
children	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
immediately	O
received	O
sentence	O
(	O
this	O
being	O
Saturday	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
body	O
to	O
be	O
afterwards	O
dissected	O
and	O
anatomized	O
,	O
which	O
sentence	O
was	O
executed	O
upon	O
her	O
accordingly	O
.	O
387	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHARLES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
Herrington	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
April	O
30th	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Herrington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
the	O
bars	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
nothing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
stopped	O
and	O
whispered	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
running	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
each	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
clapped	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
another	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
town	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
very	O
great	O
expences	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
twopence	O
farthing	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
I	O
will	O
cut	O
off	O
your	O
head	O
!	O
he	O
ordered	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
presently	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
would	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
cut	O
you	O
limb	O
from	O
limb	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
terrified	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
dressed	O
in	O
sailors	O
dresses	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
more	O
sideways	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Dark-house-lane	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
houses	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Antigallican	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
company	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
challenge	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
you	O
be	O
not	O
upon	O
some	O
rig	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
we	O
were	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
had	O
happened	O
he	O
would	O
assist	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
all	O
appearance	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
high	O
time	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
keys	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
took	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
knife	O
:	O
the	O
knives	O
that	O
were	O
held	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
were	O
one	O
large	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
small	O
;	O
the	O
small	O
knife	O
was	O
like	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
had	O
which	O
knife	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
only	O
for	O
my	O
blue	O
jacket	O
?	O
Herrington	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
say	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
and	O
his	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Abednego	O
Lambert	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
for	O
the	O
Tower	O
Royalty	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
being	O
attacked	O
upon	O
the	O
hill	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
blue	O
jackets	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
off	O
our	O
watch	O
coats	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
upon	O
some	O
rig	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
assist	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
first	O
said	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
an	O
Indianman	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Pilgrim	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
two	O
;	O
that	O
could	O
hardly	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
three	O
.	O
The	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Pilgrim	O
did	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
examined	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Lambert	O
,	O
confirmed	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
Antigallican	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
never	O
did	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
he	O
did	O
challenge	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
Farrel	O
and	O
Lambert	B-pers
both	O
deposed	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
false	O
charge	O
against	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Pilgrim	O
in	O
Holborn	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Rainbow	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
money	O
from	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
coat	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Pilgrim	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
supped	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
so	O
late	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
,	O
meaning	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
challenged	O
me	O
because	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
blue	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
challenge	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
navy	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
defence	O
good	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
house	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
but	O
none	O
appeared	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
388	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOUGHTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-four	O
guineas	O
,	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Brakewell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10th	O
.	O
*	O
Israel	B-pers
Brakewell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Penny	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Fox	I-place
in	I-place
Duke-street	I-place
;	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
waiter	O
there	O
ten	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Farmer	O
,	O
a	O
brewer	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
twenty-four	O
guineas	O
,	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
kept	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
bladder	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Penny	O
's	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Penny	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
guinea	O
was	O
like	O
one	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
this	O
money	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
,	O
concealed	O
behind	O
the	O
plaster	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
lodging	O
room	O
;	O
twenty-six	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
guineas	O
and	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
:	O
(	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bladder	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Penny	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
information	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
Bacon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
information	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
between	O
the	O
laths	O
and	O
plaster	O
twenty-three	O
guineas	O
and	O
six	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bladder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
put	O
that	O
money	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Brakewell	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
Brakewell	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
pretty	O
near	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
money	O
stole	O
;	O
my	O
door	O
is	O
open	O
;	O
persons	O
that	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
might	O
readily	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
without	O
being	O
observed	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two-guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Bacon	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
lay	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
planted	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
over	O
three	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
plaster	O
over	O
these	O
three	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
nineteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Penny	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Penny	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
behave	O
amiss	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
389	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HAWKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Charles	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
and	O
seven	O
halfpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
March	O
28th	O
.	O
+	O
[	O
Charles	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
May	O
's	O
Buildings	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
and	O
myself	O
were	O
stopped	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
near	O
the	O
Half-way-house	O
leading	O
from	O
Knights-bridge	B-place
to	O
Walham	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
by	O
one	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
glass	O
down	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
preserved	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
nothing	O
but	O
halfpence	O
!	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
interim	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
was	O
moving	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
from	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
bank	O
notes	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
twenty-six	O
or	O
twenty-seven	O
,	O
guineas	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
he	O
refused	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
!	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
fire	O
upon	O
you	O
immediately	O
!	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
fire	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
fire	O
within	O
four	O
inches	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
confusion	O
on	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
's	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
nothing	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
horse	O
flew	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
feeling	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
for	O
another	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
opposite	O
door	O
,	O
jumped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
shoot	O
my	O
horses	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
you	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
read	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
his	O
coach	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
745	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
read	O
it	O
aloud	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
spoke	O
it	O
loud	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
coachman	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
pockets	O
in	O
his	O
coach	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
replied	O
there	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
stick	O
beat	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
scoundrel	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
second	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
the	O
shortness	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
presented	O
as	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
confess	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
going	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
his	O
horse	O
again	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
was	O
till	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
little	O
swish	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
the	O
trigger	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
pistol	O
at	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
something	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
missed	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
a	O
stone	O
at	O
him	O
on	O
its	O
missing	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
immediately	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
hour	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
;	O
the	O
moon	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
full	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
with	O
us	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
stopping	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
quite	O
clear	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
his	O
dress	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
charge	O
my	O
memory	O
,	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
flapped	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hair	O
hanging	O
loose	O
about	O
his	O
ears	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
its	O
identity	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
dark	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hold	O
the	O
horse	O
by	O
the	O
bridle	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
was	O
striking	O
the	O
horse	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
from	O
your	O
account	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Cunningham	O
's	O
behaviour	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
excessively	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
captain	O
off	O
from	O
provoking	O
him	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
nearer	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
captain	O
?	O
Hart	O
.	O
He	O
embarked	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
for	O
his	O
regiment	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
where	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
a-bed	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pistols	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
the	O
bed	O
side	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Court	O
,	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
watches	O
and	O
other	O
matters	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
other	O
indictments	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
:	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
entirely	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
this	O
honourable	O
Court	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
affairs	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
by	O
trade	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
twenty-three	O
years	O
old	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
small	O
children	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
390	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
CONSTABLE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Bowle-yard	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
earl	O
of	O
Warwick	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pockets	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
;	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
a	O
lodger	O
who	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
said	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
lend	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
:	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Duard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
after	O
nine	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
keys	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
padlock	O
lying	O
with	O
the	O
staple	O
drawn	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
wicked	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
padlock	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
with	O
him	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
missed	O
three	O
gowns	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
four	O
pawnbrokers	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
's	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
gowns	O
,	O
the	O
white	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
describe	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
gown	O
on	O
,	O
snaggled	O
teeth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
scar	O
over	O
her	O
eye	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
swore	O
to	O
her	O
person	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Henshaw	O
's	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
gowns	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
all	O
the	O
marks	O
before	O
I	O
opened	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
expence	O
to	O
withdraw	O
her	O
recognizance	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
quarrel	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
been	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
recognizance	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
A	O
servant	O
to	O
Henshaw	O
produced	O
three	O
gowns	O
that	O
were	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
five	O
weeks	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
these	O
three	O
gowns	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bargain	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
Thomas	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
Thomas	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Bail	O
Dock	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
pressing	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
thing	O
on	O
myself	O
,	O
left	O
Thomas	O
should	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Duard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bail	O
Dock	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
so	O
often	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cort	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Bail	O
Dock	O
,	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
Duard	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bail	O
Dock	O
to-day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
gowns	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
left	O
Thomas	O
should	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Corpe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
390	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
seven	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
seven	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tokelove	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tokelove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Snow	O
's	O
in	O
Church	B-place
passage	I-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
that	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
except	O
one	O
spoon	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Murthwaite	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
two	O
girls	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
by	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
in	O
Tothillfields	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
being	O
disorderly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Slee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Murthwaite	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Oxford-street	O
;	O
this	O
spoon	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
spoon	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
W	O
M	O
T	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
flight	O
acquaintance	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
that	O
is	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
392	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
PATRICK	B-pers
DOGGARTY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marin	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
15th	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
last	O
Sunday	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
beds	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
waked	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
breeches	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
because	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
lodging	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
hearing	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Barleymow	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
he	O
uses	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drunk	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
at	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
about	O
again	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
left	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
somewhere	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drunk	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Clear-court	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
393	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
this	O
Kingdom	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
a	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
quarter	O
sessions	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
Town	O
and	O
Borough	O
of	O
Southwark	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Surry	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Beavis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Borough	O
compter	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
Borough	O
sessions	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
Thompson	O
!	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
having	O
an	O
intimation	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
at	O
large	O
and	O
people	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
returned	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
understand	O
I	O
was	O
bred	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
from	O
my	O
infancy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
dependence	O
for	O
my	O
livelihood	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Borough	O
Compter	O
has	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
in	O
no	O
wife	O
deny	O
that	O
in	O
one	O
respect	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
when	O
your	O
Lordship	O
considers	O
how	O
the	O
case	O
has	O
turned	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
favourable	O
light	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
London	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
transport	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
