TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
JULY	O
1775	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
BELL	O
,	O
at	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
:	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKES	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
.	O
The	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
.	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
||	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justice	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
:	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Norsell	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Ridgeway	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hackney	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Balderoy	I-pers
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Darwin	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hobcraft	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Calderwood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Winstanley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Rempell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Greenall	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Norgrove	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
John	B-pers
Deval	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Tubb	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Oxlee	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
501.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GRINDAL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
one	O
other	O
Promissory	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
one	O
other	O
Promissory	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
one	O
other	O
Promissory	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Notes	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Churles	O
Bates	O
,	O
June	O
19th	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
and	I-place
Lion	I-place
,	I-place
Little	I-place
Britain	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
cloaths	O
to	O
mend	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
afterward	O
,	O
I	O
recollected	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
with	O
three	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
bank	O
note	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
for	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
unbuttoned	O
the	O
pocket	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
before	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
notes	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
vexed	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bates	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
cloaths	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
and	O
bank	O
notes	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
remember	O
the	O
numbers	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
just	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
notes	O
for	O
cash	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
cloaths	O
to	O
the	O
taylor	O
's	O
to	O
mend	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
bank	O
notes	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
taylor	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
grey	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
bank	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
passed	O
him	O
in	O
Honey-lane	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
presently	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
came	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
an	O
inside	O
pocket	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
with	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
in	O
notes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
bank	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
note	O
.	O
The	O
clerks	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
still	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
a	O
dangerous	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
sundry	O
notes	O
for	O
the	O
ten	O
pounds	O
he	O
received	O
at	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
hearing	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Hopkins	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
compter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
breakfast	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
to	O
repair	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
breakfast	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
cloaths	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
the	O
pockets	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
note	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
cash	O
for	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
note	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
writing	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
had	O
writing	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
note	O
I	O
could	O
almost	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
changed	O
no	O
other	O
note	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Boults	O
.	O
On	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
to	O
the	O
bank	O
for	O
payment	O
.	O
This	O
bank	O
note	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
accountant	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
it	O
examined	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
mark	O
for	O
payment	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
on	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
Brown	O
,	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
May	O
fair	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
wrote	O
Brown	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Christian	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
John	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
word	O
John	O
to	O
Brown	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Boults	O
on	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
note	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
ten	O
or	O
fifteen	O
minutes	O
before	O
to	O
describe	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
taylor	O
was	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Haywood	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
bank	O
note	O
you	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
?	O
Haywood	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
by	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
writings	O
that	O
are	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scruple	O
when	O
I	O
changed	O
this	O
note	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
writing	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
names	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waldon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
this	O
note	O
for	O
payment	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
examined	O
;	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
May	O
fair	O
;	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
suspected	O
had	O
these	O
notes	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Boults	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
step	O
after	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
turning	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
which	O
leads	O
to	O
Honey-lane	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
described	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
soon	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
dress	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
their	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
bank	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
George	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
teller	O
at	O
the	O
bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ten	O
pound	O
note	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Brown	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
cloaths	O
to	O
mend	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
pockets	O
whence	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
ripped	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
wanted	O
several	O
places	O
mending	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
what	O
is	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
wanted	O
doing	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
that	O
morning	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
White-street	O
,	O
and	O
measured	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
for	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
him	O
till	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
proceeded	O
through	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
on	O
Snowhill	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bank	O
before	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Little	O
Wild-Street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
recollected	O
the	O
day	O
particularly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
jobs	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
measure	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
mountain	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
drink	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
past	O
eleven	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
part	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Tudor	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Luker	I-pers
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
four	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
Fountain	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
man	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
:	O
the	O
Fountain	O
is	O
near	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
across	O
Fleet-market	O
and	O
parted	O
on	O
Snowhill	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
home	O
;	O
it	O
then	O
wanted	O
but	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
of	O
twelve	O
by	O
the	O
church	O
clock	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
's	O
and	O
staid	O
and	O
drank	O
some	O
liquor	O
till	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
of	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
we	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Grindal	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
met	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
twelve	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Luker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Tudor	O
,	O
and	O
Hunter	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
,	O
near	O
Clare-market	O
three	O
hours	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
then	O
wanted	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
eight	O
other	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
502	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-nine	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Mayor	B-pers
,	I-pers
Commonalty	I-pers
and	I-pers
Citizens	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
city	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
lead	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
their	O
property	O
,	O
June	O
5th	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Houndsditch	B-place
opposite	O
the	O
premises	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
and	O
then	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
lead	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
stable	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
tallied	O
exactly	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
stable	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
all	O
safe	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
weighed	O
the	O
lead	O
myself	O
it	O
was	O
thirty-nine	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chancellor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
employed	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Round	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sarand	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grub-Street	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
503	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Sabella	B-pers
Parkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Folgar	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
++	O
-	O
Maclamare	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Folgar	O
?	O
Maclamare	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
church	O
of	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
.	O
Maclamare	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
Examination	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
``	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Folgar	O
,	O
lodged	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
``	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
``	O
much	O
interrupted	O
by	O
her	O
parents	O
,	O
which	O
drove	O
``	O
him	O
from	O
her	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
.	O
''	O
Daniel	B-pers
Gunston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
register	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
an	O
exact	O
copy	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Sabella	B-pers
Parkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
married	O
?	O
Parkins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
twenty-one	O
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Tavernner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
parish	O
clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
being	O
married	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
her	O
person	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
register	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
examined	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
register	O
book	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Motley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Folgar	O
,	O
her	O
maiden	O
name	O
was	O
Ann	B-pers
Folgar	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
name	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
now	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
again	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
witness	O
)	O
was	O
neither	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
nor	O
second	O
marriage	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Folgar	O
,	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Frazier	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
marry	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
504	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
table	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
one	O
table	O
knife	O
value	O
nine-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
23d	O
+	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Botley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
twelve	O
forks	O
and	O
one	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
my	O
tap-room	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Knife	O
and	O
forks	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
some	O
forks	O
falling	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
afterwards	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
yards	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Wm	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
sixteen	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
charged	O
with	O
theft	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
breach	O
of	O
duty	O
,	O
owing	O
to	O
his	O
getting	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
505	O
,	O
506	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BURDELL	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
COX	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
of	O
wrought	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
||	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
507	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bushel	O
of	O
horsebeans	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6th	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
508	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
LYNCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
trunk	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
value	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
another	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6th	O
++	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
trunk	O
with	O
some	O
watches	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
:	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
coach	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
boot	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Love	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
drove	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
paper	O
trunk	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
Blackheath	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
stopped	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Fleetmarket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gundy	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
oil	O
shop	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
hamper	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gundy	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an-hamper	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
untie	O
the	O
hamper	O
,	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
stooped	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
legs	O
by	O
the	O
fore-wheel	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
somebody	O
rummaging	O
the	O
boot	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
directly	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
trunk	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
lad	O
go	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
rags	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
clouts	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
booty	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
watches	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
horses	O
feet	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Turnkey	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Counter	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
used	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
509	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
KING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
and	O
480	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26th	O
++	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-market	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fruiterer	O
.	O
Upon	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell-Savage-Inn	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
pocket	O
apron	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
the	O
Six	O
Bells	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
decoy	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Gloucestershire	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Emery	O
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Newgate	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
man	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
lie	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
served	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
Newgate	O
market	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
roundhouse	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
in	O
Newgate	O
market	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
Mr.	O
Emery	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Fleet	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
halfpence	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Emery	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
His	O
friends	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
sent	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
cleared	O
I	O
will	O
employ	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
510	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PAGGETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
23d	O
.	O
++	O
At	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
any	O
house	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
jar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
pushed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
watch	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
mantle	O
piece	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
The	O
table-cloth	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
over	O
the	O
fence	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
bag	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dan	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Chesterman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
down	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
murder	O
!	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
somebody	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
garden	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
gathered	O
upon	O
the	O
occasion	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
throw	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
watch	O
away	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
as	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
does	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
and	O
afterwards	O
cry	O
out	O
thieves	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
pretty	O
still	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
his	O
hands	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
fetched	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
thrown	O
over	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Chesterman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Chesterman	O
)	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
keys	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
trial	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
opened	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
pails	O
and	O
jumped	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
her	O
watch	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
none	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Carraway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cow-heel	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Cradle-court-road	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
clamour	O
of	O
murder	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
jump	O
over	O
the	O
pails	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pulled	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
over	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
watch	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Judith	O
Carraway	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
on	O
the	O
pails	O
;	O
whether	O
he	O
fell	O
over	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
pulled	O
him	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
watch	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
jumped	O
on	O
the	O
pails	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jenny	B-pers
Haskin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
trusted	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
well-behaved	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
took	O
two	O
shillings	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
511	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
made	O
signed	O
,	O
and	O
subscribed	O
for	O
the	O
governor	O
and	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
note	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Place	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Timothy	B-pers
Place	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
,	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Buckston	O
,	O
June	O
21st	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
513	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
O'BRIAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
;	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
June	O
25th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
514	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
DAWES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowdall	I-pers
,	O
June	O
19th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
515	O
,	O
516	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BURDEL	I-pers
and	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYHUE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
white	O
lawn	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
black	O
sattin	O
cardinals	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
callimanco	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
five	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
seven	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
April	O
23d	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
517	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
forty-nine	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9th	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
cellar	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
we	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
purse	O
and	O
forty-nine	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
absconded	O
on	O
Monday	O
afternoon	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Newman	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
private	O
lodging	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
(	O
the	O
money	O
produced	O
by	O
Wright	O
)	O
Here	O
is	O
one	O
guinea	O
particularly	O
marked	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
A	O
goldsmith	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
clip	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shears	O
,	O
I	O
prevented	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
run	O
the	O
risque	O
of	O
getting	O
rid	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
H.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
very	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
saved	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
different	O
services	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
with	O
his	O
things	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
His	O
things	O
were	O
tied	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
eleven	O
winesses	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
518	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
-	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
159	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ANNE	B-pers
BUTLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
hair	O
dresser	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Hay	O
,	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
in	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
;	O
whether	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
undressed	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Flack	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
wake	O
'till	O
the	O
waiter	O
called	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
dressed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
searched	O
?	O
Flack	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
watch	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
combs	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
money	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
:	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
shoe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Flack	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
?	O
Flack	O
.	O
Eighteen	O
pence	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Morgan	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
at	O
near	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
rum	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
six-pence	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
waked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
called	O
the	O
New	O
Castle	O
upon	O
Tyne	O
,	O
near	O
Cambridgestreet	O
:	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
guineas	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
callico	O
and	O
lining	O
of	O
her	O
shoe	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
ragg	O
,	O
pined	O
to	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
her	O
shoe	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
friends	O
in	O
Ireland	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
quarterns	O
of	O
rum	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Williams	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
asleep	O
when	O
you	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
2d	O
quatern	O
?	O
Mould	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
520	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ANNE	B-pers
UNDERWOOD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tortoise	O
shell	O
snuff	O
box	O
with	O
gold	O
hinges	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
New	B-place
prison	I-place
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
words	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
night	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
offered	O
her	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
chucked	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
farthing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
box	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
she	O
pledged	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
for	O
six	O
pence	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
521	O
,	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
YARDLEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
YARDLEY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
traiterously	O
forging	O
,	O
counterfeiting	O
and	O
coining	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
,	O
feigned	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
and	O
coin	O
to	O
the	O
likeness	O
and	O
similitude	O
of	O
the	O
current	O
money	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
against	O
their	O
allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
June	O
30th	O
,	O
+	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
523	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
PITMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Theodore	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporeal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
bed	O
hook	O
,	O
value	O
two-pence	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
a	O
crystal	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Theodore	O
,	O
June	O
3d	O
,	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
524	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
JOSEPHS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
525	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYHUE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
stuff	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
flock	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cracknell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
526	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BADGER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9th	O
,	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
527	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
FARMER	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Devereux	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Susanna	O
.	O
Against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
528	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ELISHA	B-pers
RASSIT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
twenty-four	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9th	O
,	O
~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
529	O
.	O
530	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
M'ALLESTER	I-pers
and	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
GIRDWOOD	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
puting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Davis-Street	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Mount-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Berkeley	O
Square	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
in	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
with	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
,	O
between	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Brentford	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
horse	O
back	O
,	O
met	O
the	O
chaise	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
between	O
the	O
fifth	O
and	O
sixth	O
mile	O
stone	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Gunnersbury-Lane	B-place
;	O
they	O
separated	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
seperation	O
might	O
be	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
boy	O
running	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
thought	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
chaise	O
stopped	O
instantly	O
,	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
claped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
's	O
breast	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
down	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
past	O
it	O
,	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
shewed	O
me	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
present	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
other	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
about	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
distress	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
silver	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
upon	O
your	O
honour	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
watch	O
or	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
upon	O
my	O
honour	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
boy	O
drive	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
.	O
Edridge	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
M'Allester	I-pers
,	O
I	O
only	O
heard	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
entirely	O
engaged	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
us	O
with	O
civility	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
swearing	O
or	O
abuse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
Edridge	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
remarkably	O
fine	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
light	O
a	O
night	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
M'Aliester	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
Edridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
opportunities	O
than	O
one	O
of	O
seeing	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
first	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
full	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
that	O
two	O
person	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
M'Allester	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
M'Allester	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
doubt	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
me	O
till	O
you	O
put	O
on	O
your	O
spectacles	O
.	O
Edridge	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
near	O
sighted	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
as	O
to	O
distinguish	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
natural	O
eye	O
;	O
sometime	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
oath	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
further	O
distance	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
distance	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
spectacles	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
near	O
with	O
my	O
natural	O
eye	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
hired	O
from	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
look	O
down	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
M'Allester	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
prompted	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fieldings	I-pers
men	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Edridge	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
M'Allester	O
was	O
upon	O
?	O
Edridge	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
sprightly	O
he	O
over-shot	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Star	O
in	O
Blackman	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
to	O
hire	O
horses	O
;	O
Girdwood	O
had	O
hired	O
horses	O
at	O
out	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
Girdwood	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
himself	O
to	O
hire	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
ride	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
usually	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
twelve	O
or	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
generally	O
returned	O
at	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
but	O
never	O
later	O
;	O
sometimes	O
,	O
indeed	O
they	O
kept	O
them	O
till	O
next	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
their	O
having	O
horses	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
account	O
:	O
the	O
horse	O
M'Allester	O
rode	O
upon	O
was	O
dark	O
brown	O
bay	O
,	O
with	O
cropt	O
ears	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
rode	O
hardly	O
any	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
bright	O
bay	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
stripe	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edridge	O
.	O
Before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
this	O
witness	O
produced	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
specifying	O
the	O
days	O
when	O
he	O
let	O
them	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
has	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
give	O
the	O
account	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
puts	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
took	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
account	O
and	O
he	O
puts	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dinmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Girdwood	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
property	O
I	O
have	O
does	O
not	O
relate	O
to	O
that	O
robbery	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pocket	O
pistols	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
)	O
M'Allester	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
and	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
horses	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
we	O
rode	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
Westminster	O
bridge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
at	O
Bromley	O
,	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
at	O
a	O
clergyman	O
's	O
widow	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
stayed	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
town	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Girdwood	O
by	O
appointment	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
our	O
horses	O
to	O
the	O
borough	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
left	O
Girdwood	O
and	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
Westminster	O
to	O
dinner	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
Girdwood	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
For	O
M'Allester	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Howell	O
,	O
a	O
clergyman	O
's	O
widow	O
,	O
at	O
Bromley	O
in	O
Kent	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
M'Allester	O
's	O
mother	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
sit	O
of	O
the	O
gout	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
son	O
might	O
be	O
wrote	O
to	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
by	O
dinner	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
helping	O
me	O
to	O
administer	O
hot	O
clouts	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
kitchen	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
an	O
hour	O
together	O
all	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
town	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
committed	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
M'Allester	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Girdwood	O
acquitted	O
.	O
531	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
M'ALLESTER	O
and	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
GIRDWOOD	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gainsborough	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
puting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
covered	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
June	O
7th	O
.	O
||	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
M'ALLESTER	O
and	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
GIRDWOOD	I-pers
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	O
Christian	O
Bach	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
2	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
June	O
7th	O
.	O
+	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
Bach	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
on	O
a	O
mile	O
,	O
beyond	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
a	O
highwayman	O
:	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
or	O
your	O
watch	O
!	O
That	O
waked	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
my	O
carriage	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
business	O
was	O
very	O
soon	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
9	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
confinement	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Holmer	O
's	O
in	O
Kent	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
borough	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Holmer	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Holmer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Holmer	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
with	O
five	O
drawers	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holmer	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Holmer	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
recollected	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Girdwood	O
,	O
by	O
Dinmore	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
key	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
drawer	O
,	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
watch	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
description	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bach	O
's	O
mouth	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
balls	O
and	O
some	O
powder	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
large	O
drawers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bach	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
borough	O
;	O
Girdwood	O
lodged	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
or	O
two	O
months	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
M'Allester	O
had	O
lodged	O
there	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
;	O
Girdwood	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
lodging	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
out	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
drawers	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
some	O
powder	O
and	O
ball	O
also	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dinmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Girdwood	O
,	O
first	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
key	O
produced	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
gold	O
chain	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
seals	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Bach	O
.	O
The	O
chain	O
and	O
the	O
seals	O
were	O
together	O
when	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Girdwood	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
particular	O
;	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Bach	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
particular	O
on	O
that	O
chain	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Bach	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
particular	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
seals	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
chain	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Mc	O
Allester	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Girdwood	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
532	O
,	O
533	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BYROM	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
534	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BYROM	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BYROM	I-pers
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Westfield	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26th	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Westfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
petticoat	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
night	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
we	O
slept	O
with	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
a	O
garden	O
.	O
-	O
Westfield	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
black	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
near	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
we	O
slept	O
with	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
petticoat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
missing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
27th	O
or	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
the	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
taking	O
some	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Riper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
carried	O
this	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
535	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BEREAU	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
tenor	O
following	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
1773	O
.	O
42	O
:	O
One	O
month	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
forty-two	O
pounds	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
.	O
Levi	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
.	O
Rose-alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
With	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
George	B-pers
Andrew	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
note	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
intention	O
,	O
June	O
7th	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
given	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
336	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
TUFFNELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
June	O
17th	O
.	O
++	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Change-alley	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
by	O
the	O
Union	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
apron	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Change-alley	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
537	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DOWDY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11th	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Token-house-yard	B-place
yesterday	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
yesterday	O
noon	O
,	O
near	O
Token-house-alley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Token	O
house-Yard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
538	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
lb	O
of	O
Vermilion	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1st	O
.	O
++	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Puncheon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
,	O
an	O
oil-merchant	O
and	O
soap-maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
minutes	O
before	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
warehouse	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
bags	O
of	O
vermilion	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
such	O
bags	O
missing	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
cask	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
his	O
service	O
about	O
April	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
watchmen	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
breaking	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
in	O
Great	O
St.	O
Helen	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
with	O
tinder	O
;	O
a	O
flint	O
,	O
steel	O
,	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
matches	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
candle	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
taking	O
this	O
vermillion	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
their	O
names	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
this	O
key	O
from	O
him	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
which	O
opens	O
the	O
padlock	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Frincis	B-pers
Whetherick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Great	O
St.	O
Helen	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
warehouse	O
is	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
rattle	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
taking	O
off	O
the	O
staple	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
bags	O
of	O
vermillion	O
at	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
making	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
another	O
watchman	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
tried	O
to	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Whetherick	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
who	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
,	O
got	O
their	O
things	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
gambled	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
there	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
had	O
won	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pritchard	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
appeared	O
honest	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
539	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOVRIDGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
540	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MATHIAS	B-pers
M'MAHOAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
puting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
pound	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
June	O
22d	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
541	O
.	O
542	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
AISTE	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
AISTE	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Richdale	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
fifty-six	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
543	O
,	O
544	O
,	O
545	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
,	O
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
EMANUEL	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
odd	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shilings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8th	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
a	O
part	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
working	O
silver	O
smith	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
eight	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
we	O
lost	O
some	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shew-glass	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
pairs	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
odd	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
window	O
as	O
if	O
trying	O
a	O
key	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
:	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
two	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
buttons	O
,	O
two	O
remained	O
at	O
the	O
shew-glass	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
church-yard	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
men	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
desirous	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
buttons	O
;	O
then	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
Hunt	O
and	O
Cox	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
more	O
were	O
learning	O
over	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
why	O
their	O
acquaintance	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
stay	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Emanuel	O
followed	O
him	O
immediately	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
the	O
other	O
remained	O
then	O
before	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
my	O
child	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
glass	O
broke	O
;	O
when	O
Emanuel	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
two	O
mourning	O
rings	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
and	O
perceived	O
that	O
the	O
shew-glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
one	O
should	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
Emanuel	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
,	O
blood	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
buttons	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
be	O
gone	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Hunt	O
produced	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
produced	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
Cox	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
gave	O
information	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
Ward	O
;	O
for	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
Ward	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
parade	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Ward	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
regimentals	O
:	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
manner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
daughter	O
;	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
twelve	O
in	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
,	O
if	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
sworn	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
Salmon	O
.	O
Destruction	O
to	O
the	O
soul	O
.	O
(	O
she	O
is	O
sworn	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
at	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Hunt	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
,	O
sometime	O
before	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
mamma	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
buttons	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
glasses	O
:	O
the	O
Jew	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Ward	O
;	O
my	O
pappa	O
,	O
came	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
Emanuel	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
directly	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
two	O
mourning	O
rings	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
leaning	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
some	O
buckles	O
into	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
those	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shew	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
beckoned	O
my	O
pappa	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
:	O
then	O
my	O
mamma	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
:	O
as	O
to	O
Cox	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
buttons	O
.	O
Cox	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Hunt	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
buttons	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
a	O
dozen	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
bargained	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
waistcoat	O
buttons	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
buttons	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
they	O
fetched	O
over	O
a	O
green	O
grocer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Emanuel	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
asking	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
ring	O
to	O
suit	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
mourning	O
was	O
wore	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
was	O
rubbing	O
the	O
buttons	O
upon	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leather	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
your	O
two	O
guineas	O
weight	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
he	O
snatched	O
up	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
glass	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
imagined	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
gang	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
:	O
we	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
wife	O
out	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
insure	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
they	O
should	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
the	O
green	O
grocer	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
:	O
one	O
Marks	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
father	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
villain	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
beg	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Glasses	O
.	O
For	O
Emanuel	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Nathan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Emanuel	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
any	O
way	O
wrong	O
in	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
parcels	O
.	O
For	O
Ward	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wotton	I-pers
.	O
Ward	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
colonel	O
is	O
willing	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
acquitted	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
546	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
WALTER	B-pers
GIBBONS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grabham	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6th	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Grabham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
country	O
fellow	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
enquiring	O
for	O
a	O
place	O
about	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
M'Oris	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
being	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
Gibbons	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
M'Oris	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
began	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
M'Oris	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
for	O
the	O
abuse	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hoop	O
and	O
Horse	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
shaking	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
candlestick	O
;	O
then	O
M'Oris	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
Gibbons	O
would	O
do	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
gentleman	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
every	O
guinea	O
he	O
could	O
show	O
;	O
then	O
M'Oris	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
M'Oris	O
said	O
,	O
Gibbons	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
countrymen	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
every	O
guinea	O
they	O
could	O
shew	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
landlord	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
they	O
played	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
M'Oris	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
that	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
has	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
by	O
him	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
?	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
M'Oris	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
into	O
Gibbons	O
's	O
hat	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
walked	O
together	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
loose	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
;	O
then	O
M'Oris	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
waiting	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
for	O
swindling	O
somebody	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Gibbons	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
M'Oris	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
Gibbons	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
coal	O
tub	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
money	O
nor	O
watch	O
after	O
they	O
walked	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
cooper	O
's	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
three	O
fellows	O
overtook	O
me	O
on	O
London	O
bridge	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
release	O
Gibbons	O
out	O
of	O
prison	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
the	O
chain	O
,	O
seals	O
and	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
pockets	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
one	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
attempt	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
lest	O
they	O
should	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
use	O
me	O
ill.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
to	O
an	O
innocent	O
man	O
before	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
.	O
Grabham	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
h	O
e	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
departed	O
the	O
room	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Linnakan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hoop	O
and	O
Horse	O
Shoe	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
M'Oris	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
sharpers	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
M'Oris	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
purse	O
of	O
counters	O
into	O
the	O
coal	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
draught	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Linnakan	O
,	O
the	O
publican	O
,	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
he	O
believed	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
men	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
purse	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
draught	O
upon	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Cockin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
coal	O
basket	O
found	O
a	O
purse	O
of	O
counterfeit	O
guineas	O
.	O
The	O
counterfeits	O
and	O
the	O
draught	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
accidentally	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
M'Oris	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
play	O
;	O
M'Oris	O
is	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
myself	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
M'Oris	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
up	O
another	O
person	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
positively	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dobsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
positively	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
defrauded	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
one	O
Sunday	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
offer	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
prosecution	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
his	O
recognizance	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
Mr.	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
like	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
you	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
without	O
consulting	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Vine-Street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Every	O
word	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
totally	O
false	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
on	O
Gibbons	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
liked	O
being	O
there	O
better	O
than	O
swindling	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
people	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
547	O
,	O
548	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNES	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WATER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
she	O
ass	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10th	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
549	O
,	O
550	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
WATKINS	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
BATHWAY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1st	O
,	O
+	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
551	O
,	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
and	O
forty-five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Peraedge	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21st	O
,	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
552	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
TOWN	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
coin	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
four	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ducker	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
,	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Ducker	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
we	O
lodged	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lighted	O
her	O
candle	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
only	O
just	O
long	O
enough	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
candle	O
;	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
