TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
2d	O
,	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
1775	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
down	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
BELL	O
,	O
at	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKES	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKSTONE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
~	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
2d	O
L	O
)	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kidman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
William	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
William	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Abraham	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chamberlin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
William	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Burnley	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
James	B-pers
Cowden	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Frances	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Calcott	I-pers
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
James	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
William	B-pers
Birkes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pembertley	I-pers
George	B-pers
Bride	I-pers
Eleazear	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Light	I-pers
Rice	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
Godolph	B-pers
Hyme	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sheercroft	I-pers
.	O
264	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trebble	O
linen	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
hat	O
pin	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
scissars	O
with	O
silver	O
bows	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
sixty	O
copper	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petty	B-place
France	I-place
Westminster	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
writings	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
soldiers	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
they	O
assisted	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
some	O
to	O
one	O
place	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
drummer	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
payment	O
for	O
removing	O
the	O
goods	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
it	O
into	O
Pye	O
Street	O
for	O
safety	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
That	O
box	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
box	O
:	O
he	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
in	O
Rochester	O
Row	O
,	O
Tottlefields	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
(	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
burned	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
.	O
Rochester	O
Row	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Pye	O
Street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
removed	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
aunt	O
's	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
conveyed	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
without	O
my	O
privity	O
or	O
knowledge	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
265	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MILESTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
fifteen	O
half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooksley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
266	O
.	O
267	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gover	I-pers
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mare	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
263	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BOWERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
lead	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
January	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
in	O
Chamber	B-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
seemingly	O
cutting	O
a	O
roll	O
of	O
lead	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
shirt	O
sleeves	O
tucked	O
up	O
above	O
his	O
elbows	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hair	O
tied	O
behind	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wrickets	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
returning	O
from	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
passing	O
by	O
this	O
house	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
keyhole	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
shirt	O
sleeves	O
up	O
above	O
his	O
elbows	O
cutting	O
lead	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
,	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
by	O
the	O
dresser	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
neighbours	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
woman	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
we	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
lead	O
:	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
escape	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
sink	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lead	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
dropped	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
lead	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
parcels	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
escaping	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
keys	O
and	O
the	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Siddon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
through	O
the	O
key-hole	O
,	O
cutting	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
assistance	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
PETER	B-pers
HARCOTT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Butcher	B-place
's	I-place
Arms	I-place
in	I-place
Carnaby	I-place
Market	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
wound	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
awaked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
having	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicate	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
pawned	O
this	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Wife	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
draw	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
beer	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wise	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
at	O
the	O
necessary	O
?	O
Wise	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
stirred	O
off	O
my	O
seat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
270	O
.	O
271	O
.	O
272	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COXON	I-pers
,	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ANDREWS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRANT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
eleven	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
castor	O
top	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
273	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
MAYBRICK	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
JOHN	I-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grear	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
~	O
John	B-pers
Grear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Newport	B-place
Street	I-place
.	O
In	O
December	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Leighton	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Wardour	O
Street	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
were	O
offered	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
that	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
of	O
some	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
shoes	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leighton	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Wardour	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
to	O
pawn	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
knowing	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
shoes	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
pair	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
Priestman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
January	O
and	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
shoes	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Little	O
Poultney	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
rather	O
failed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
removed	O
to	O
Wardour	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
worked	O
sometime	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
customers	O
.	O
These	O
shoes	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
because	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
274	O
.	O
275	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
GREGORY	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BARRETT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
puting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
~	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
five	O
weeks	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
from	O
Bath	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
Patridge	O
's	O
at	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
of	O
horses	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
over	O
Hounslow-heath	B-place
before	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
fresh	O
horses	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
pair	O
that	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
in	O
60	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
stay	O
tea	O
:	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
just	O
after	O
sun	O
set	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
dark	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
drove	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
in	O
three	O
minutes	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
four	O
minutes	O
Mr.	O
Penwarne	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
servant	O
rode	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
enterance	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
heath	O
towards	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
find	O
since	O
,	O
is	O
called	O
Butcher	B-place
's	I-place
Grove	I-place
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
the	O
enterance	O
into	O
the	O
heath	O
within	O
five	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Heath	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
they	O
road	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
on	O
at	O
a	O
moderate	O
rate	O
towards	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Heaths	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
miles	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
moderately	O
on	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
mile	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
within	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
heads	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
one	O
dropped	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
cried	O
Holloa	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chaise	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
since	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
Barret	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
situation	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
hair	O
over	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
dropped	O
my	O
own	O
glass	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
so	O
fast	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
done	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
seconds	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
cried	O
holloa	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
down	O
with	O
your	O
door	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
glass	O
was	O
let	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
run	O
a	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
Pike	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
short	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
barrel	O
in	O
the	O
old	O
fashion	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
leaned	O
forward	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
behave	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
presently	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
suppose	O
pleased	O
at	O
my	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
be	O
quick	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
lifting	O
my	O
pistol	O
to	O
fire	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
myself	O
in	O
great	O
danger	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
drunken	O
man	O
:	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
the	O
pistol	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
instantly	O
;	O
finding	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
desist	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
pistol	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
avoid	O
shewing	O
their	O
faces	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
more	O
than	O
five	O
shillings	O
:	O
Gregory	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
Barrett	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
purse	O
to	O
Barrett	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
your	O
purse	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
your	O
side	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
reeled	O
upon	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
falling	O
from	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
your	O
purse	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
five	O
shillings	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Barrett	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
off	O
.	O
Barrett	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
well	O
,	O
very	O
decent	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
so	O
violent	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
apprehend	O
myself	O
in	O
so	O
much	O
danger	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
Gregory	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
drunken	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
inadvertently	O
fired	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
pistol	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
inches	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
Barrett	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
Gregory	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
now	O
for	O
your	O
watches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
both	O
demand	O
your	O
watches	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
say	O
upon	O
your	O
honour	O
.	O
To	O
comply	O
with	O
his	O
whim	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
upon	O
my	O
honour	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
so	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
driver	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
driver	O
drove	O
on	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
lusty	O
young	O
fellows	O
standing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
lods	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
this	O
moment	O
robbed	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
forty	O
pounds	O
a	O
piece	O
reward	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
They	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
driver	O
to	O
get	O
fresh	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
fatigued	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
Bridgwater	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
near	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
miles	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
London	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
coffee	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
clerks	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
or	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
and	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
from	O
my	O
conscience	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
from	O
that	O
positive	O
evidence	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
require	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
Perfectly	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
undertake	O
to	O
say	O
positively	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
saying	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
one	O
rode	O
upon	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
upon	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
side	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
or	O
a	O
more	O
:	O
the	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
rode	O
upon	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
they	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
Five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
respecting	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Littleton	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
evidence	O
.	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
it	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
wrote	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
mention	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
circumstance	O
of	O
any	O
disadvantage	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
five	O
weeks	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
had	O
sent	O
to	O
several	O
people	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
That	O
letter	O
was	O
left	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Reddington	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Fenchurch	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
letter	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-Street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Barrett	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
flaxen	O
hair	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
irons	O
over	O
his	O
hands	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
both	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
only	O
one	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Barrett	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
Barrett	O
there	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
recollect	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
such	O
a	O
recollection	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
say	O
with	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
certainty	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
verily	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
his	O
hair	O
was	O
then	O
loose	O
about	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
introduced	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
Sir	O
John	O
was	O
sitting	O
:	O
Barrett	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
outer	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hair	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
crooked	O
sixpence	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
in	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
altogether	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
When	O
Sir	O
John	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
farthings	O
taken	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bad	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
money	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
sixpence	O
,	O
that	O
sixpence	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Barrett	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
the	O
chaise	O
at	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
.	O
Pike	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
;	O
might	O
it	O
not	O
be	O
near	O
six	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
was	O
nearer	O
six	O
than	O
five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
very	O
fortunate	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
of	O
horses	O
;	O
that	O
went	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
miles	O
an	O
hour	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
drove	O
a	O
mile	O
in	O
three	O
minutes	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
you	O
be	O
coming	O
from	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
suppose	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
quite	O
fifty	O
minutes	O
coming	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
portmanteau	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Hounslow	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
seven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
set	O
out	O
at	O
near	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
pretty	O
near	O
seven	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
Hounslow	O
?	O
Pike	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
drove	O
pretty	O
fast	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
from	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
sixty	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q.	O
Partridge	O
's	O
is	O
about	O
the	O
twenty-second	O
mile-stone	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
twelve	O
miles	O
,	O
from	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
these	O
men	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
chaise	O
was	O
going	O
at	O
a	O
prodigious	O
great	O
rate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glasses	O
were	O
up	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
make	O
much	O
observation	O
upon	O
them	O
then	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
clearly	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
avoided	O
shewing	O
their	O
faces	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
They	O
passed	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
cried	O
,	O
holloa	O
stop	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
observe	O
you	O
give	O
your	O
evidence	O
with	O
great	O
caution	O
of	O
the	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
prejudice	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
feel	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Penwarne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
dubious	O
of	O
our	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Heath	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
at	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
nearer	O
six	O
than	O
five	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
Salt	O
Hill	O
:	O
we	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Partridge	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
of	O
horses	O
to	O
put	O
us	O
over	O
the	O
Heath	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
for	O
four	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
danger	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
horses	O
that	O
would	O
carry	O
us	O
over	O
exceeding	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
passed	O
over	O
the	O
greater	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Heath	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Heath	O
,	O
towards	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
entering	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Heath	B-pers
I	I-pers
saw	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
came	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
came	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
take	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
short	O
round	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
glass	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
put	O
down	O
your	O
glass	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
think	O
rather	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
delivered	O
your	O
money	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
Barrett	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
money	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
light	O
colour	O
beaver	O
surtout	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
what	O
cloaths	O
he	O
had	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
buttoned	O
;	O
his	O
hair	O
hung	O
about	O
his	O
ears	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pinned	O
at	O
the	O
sides	O
;	O
his	O
hair	O
hung	O
down	O
very	O
strait	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
after	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
honour	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
honour	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
watch	O
.	O
Barrett	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
delay	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
driver	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
driver	O
went	O
on	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
Barrett	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
recollected	O
him	O
that	O
very	O
moment	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Gregory	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
he	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
detain	O
us	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
:	O
he	O
behaved	O
as	O
civil	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
hair	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
condition	O
as	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
remarked	O
his	O
hair	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
Gregory	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
talk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
before	O
seven	O
;	O
we	O
drove	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
rate	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
what	O
his	O
errand	O
was	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
horse	O
was	O
Barrett	O
on	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
It	O
struck	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
his	O
face	O
clearly	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
very	O
clearly	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Partridge	O
's	O
at	O
near	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
and	O
pair	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
miles	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
an	O
hour	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
miles	O
:	O
the	O
horses	O
set	O
off	O
a	O
gallop	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
stopped	O
galloping	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
Cramford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
you	O
be	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
About	O
fifty	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
twelve	O
miles	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
came	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
surprised	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
he	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
Gregory	O
;	O
Gregory	O
was	O
not	O
easily	O
contented	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
very	O
good	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
him	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
directly	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
chaise	O
door	O
still	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
hair	O
or	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
both	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Though	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Penwarne	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
:	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Grove	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
Barrett	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
Barrett	O
rode	O
a	O
brown	O
bay	O
horse	O
:	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
Barrett	O
twice	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
;	O
the	O
driver	O
pulled	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
your	O
glasses	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
up	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
driver	O
's	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
cried	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
glasses	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
immediately	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
:	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
minute	O
Gregory	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
driver	O
with	O
another	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
stir	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
single	O
pistol	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
blow	O
Barrett	O
's	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Barrett	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fire	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
unbolted	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Gregory	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
round	O
by	O
the	O
wheel	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
fronting	O
the	O
hind	O
wheel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
stirred	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
,	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
Barrett	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
Gregory	O
demanded	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
Q.	O
Barrett	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
deliver	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
:	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
Barrett	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
hair	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
up	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Barrett	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
Barrett	O
;	O
his	O
hair	O
was	O
hanging	O
strait	O
over	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
forty	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
he	O
Justice	O
's	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
recollected	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
chimney	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
cloaths	O
had	O
he	O
on	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
A	O
light	O
coloured	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
at	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
Gregory	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
lightish	O
coat	O
on	O
too	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
face	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
your	O
master	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
minutes	O
before	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
heath	O
,	O
it	O
then	O
wanted	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
seven	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
how	O
long	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
the	O
mile	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
given	O
directly	O
as	O
the	O
glasses	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
after	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
Barrett	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
watches	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Penwarne	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
watches	O
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
honour	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
honour	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
the	O
driver	O
drive	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
Barrett	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
his	O
hair	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
features	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
head	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
chaise	O
stopped	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
could	O
distinguish	O
his	O
face	O
before	O
the	O
chaise	O
stopped	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
Gregory	O
was	O
there	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Barrett	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
hair	O
was	O
in	O
drop	O
curls	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
pounds	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
said	O
something	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
knew	O
them	O
both	O
by	O
their	O
hair	O
and	O
features	O
?	O
Crow	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
light	O
?	O
Crew	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
their	O
faces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
dark	O
wet	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
clear	O
sky	O
.	O
Crew	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sun	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
very	O
bright	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
post	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Patridge	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Patridge	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
stopped	O
on	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
they	O
held	O
their	O
heads	O
so	O
down	O
on	O
their	O
horses	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
remember	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
being	O
robbed	O
:	O
have	O
you	O
always	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
rate	O
did	O
you	O
drive	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
miles	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
chaise	O
stopped	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
About	O
dusk	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
stopped	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dusk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
quite	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
crown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
or	O
stop	O
any	O
where	O
first	O
?	O
Godfrey	O
.	O
We	O
stopped	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pike	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
met	O
some	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
light	O
had	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
?	O
Pike	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dusk	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
people	O
under	O
the	O
trees	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
who	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bryant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
attend	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Heath	O
.	O
And	O
Mungo	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
name	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
by	O
)	O
drove	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Godfrey	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
his	O
hair	O
about	O
his	O
ears	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
from	O
his	O
horse	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
mounted	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
let	O
blood	O
.	O
Upon	O
receiving	O
this	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
two	O
such	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
Heath	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
tell	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
thousand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Othen	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Berkley	O
's	O
keeper	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
on	O
horseback	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Longford	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
landlady	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
men	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
describing	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
supped	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
just	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
blood	O
,	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
another	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
speaking	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
hostler	O
brought	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
at	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
exactly	O
matched	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
bad	O
sixpence	O
,	O
eight	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
farthings	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Othen	O
took	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
out	O
of	O
Barrett	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
usual	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
travel	O
with	O
pistols	O
?	O
Bryant	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Bryant	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
miles	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Othen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Lord	O
Berkley	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
information	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
Longford	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
post-boy	O
gave	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Othen	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
we	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
informed	O
us	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
the	O
post	O
boy	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
post	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
little	O
men	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
something	O
about	O
his	O
hair	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Bryant	O
to	O
Longford	O
:	O
I	O
enquired	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
at	O
Longford	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
two	O
such	O
men	O
as	O
I	O
described	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
such	O
young	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Bryant	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Barrett	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
pistols	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
are	O
produced	O
.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barrett	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Alysbury	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
engaged	O
with	O
a	O
company	O
of	O
comedians	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
horse	O
was	O
taken	O
lame	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
proceed	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
Longford	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
there	O
,	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
we	O
were	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
they	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
Bow	O
Street	O
.	O
Barrett	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
engaged	O
in	O
a	O
party	O
with	O
a	O
company	O
of	O
comedians	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
accompany	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
dined	O
at	O
Kew	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
stayed	O
till	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
accordingly	O
we	O
set	O
forward	O
;	O
my	O
horse	O
became	O
lame	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
bled	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
sixpence	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
bled	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
dusk	O
;	O
accordingly	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Gregory	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
keep	O
up	O
a	O
sharp	O
pace	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
very	O
late	O
before	O
we	O
come	O
to	O
any	O
place	O
:	O
we	O
rode	O
on	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
dark	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
two	O
miles	O
over	O
the	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
would	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
we	O
come	O
at	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
rainy	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
repent	O
of	O
my	O
undertaking	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
rainy	O
day	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
riding	O
fastish	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
intimidated	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
pistols	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
defend	O
yourself	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
therefore	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Longford	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
horses	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
:	O
the	O
lame	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
ostler	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
lame	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
proceed	O
on	O
the	O
journey	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
we	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
early	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
Lord	O
Berkley	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
people	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
collared	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
his	O
reason	O
for	O
searching	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
on	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
imagined	O
we	O
were	O
the	O
perpetrators	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
well	O
knowing	O
my	O
innocence	O
,	O
readily	O
consented	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
must	O
execute	O
his	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
I	O
consented	O
to	O
it	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
tried	O
to-day	O
,	O
my	O
witnesses	O
are	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
For	O
Gregory	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lovybond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
,	O
opposite	O
Great	O
Turnstile	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gregory	O
six	O
years	O
or	O
upwards	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
with	O
his	O
father-in-law	O
,	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
in	O
Leather	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gregory	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
father-in-law	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
attorney	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Done	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gregory	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
friends	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wharton	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Holborn	O
Bars	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
an	O
attorney	O
's	O
clerk	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gregory	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Capon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gate	O
Street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gregory	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
276	O
,	O
277	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
WINTER	I-pers
and	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Euphen	B-pers
Witherspoon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
yellow	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
quilted	O
calimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
fly	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
linen	O
under	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
thirteen	O
cheque	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
fine	O
flowered	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stocking	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
on	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
an	O
odd	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
plain	O
white-silk	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
flowered	O
white	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
deffield	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
eight	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
eight	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
eight	O
linen	O
dusters	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
seven	O
linen	O
night	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
laced	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
single	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
single	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
double	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
double	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Selisia	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
flannel	O
ironing	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
plain	O
book	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
small	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
mourning	O
ring	O
with	O
two	O
diamond	O
sparks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chrystal	O
stone	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
stone	O
rings	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Euphen	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
278	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GREGORY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
thread	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
five	O
moidore	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
three	O
pounds-twelve	O
piece	O
,	O
three	O
five	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
four	O
two	O
guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
eighteen	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Faikney	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
February	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
279	O
,	O
280	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PERKIS	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SANGO	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
~	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
281	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
TENNANT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
check	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawle	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
~	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
partner	O
's	O
proved	O
the	O
muslin	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
and	O
his	O
partners	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Covard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
who	O
are	O
partners	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
(	O
last	O
Saturday	O
)	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
cotton	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Rawle	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
twenty	O
yards	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
282	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
JEREMIAH	I-pers
STACEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flowered	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boorer	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Boorer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
January	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
MARGARET	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
STACEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boorer	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
January	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
283	O
.	O
284	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRANSGROVE	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
JAMES	I-pers
TERRY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
bed-quilt	O
,	O
value	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
pound	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
thickset	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
:	O
a	O
a	O
pink	O
shaloon	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
one	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
band	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
two-pence	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
three	O
silk	O
ribbands	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
fourpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Northolt	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Watford	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
owned	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Watford	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
:	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Henry	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrole	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoners	O
with	O
these	O
bundles	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Street	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
things	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
two	O
boxes	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
Northolt	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
nurse	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
:	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
from	O
the	O
hay-rick	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
craved	O
mercy	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
ladder	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
brother	O
patrole	O
has	O
told	O
your	O
lordship	O
.	O
Bransgrove	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Terry	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
so	O
before	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
285	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buck-skin	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
:	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
paper	O
maker	O
at	O
Hare-field	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
family	O
but	O
a	O
son-in-law	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
safe	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
casement	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
old	O
ragged	O
cloaths	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
string	O
I	O
observed	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
that	O
hung	O
down	O
below	O
his	O
frock	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son-in-law	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
great	O
coat	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Holden	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
286	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
AARONSHAW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
February	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
287.	O
CONSTANTINE	B-pers
MOLLOY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bladen	B-pers
Hawke	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
;	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
288.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PALMER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
a	O
callico	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
pence	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
four-pence	O
,	O
two	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
crimson	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
seven	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
four-pence	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
four-pence	O
,	O
forty	O
half-pence	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
:	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
two-pence	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
two-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clock	O
maker	O
in	O
King	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Old	I-place
Street	I-place
Square	I-place
.	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
house	O
secure	O
,	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
things	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brookes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
home	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
starried	O
,	O
knowing	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
neighbours	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
light	O
was	O
removed	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
unlocked	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
run	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
blew	O
their	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
snuff	O
was	O
a-light	O
:	O
hearing	O
them	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
wrenched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
rushed	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
,	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
tripped	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
tripped	O
up	O
and	O
taken	O
by	O
Hudson	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
wrenched	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
double	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
shirt	O
unmade	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
dropped	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
tool	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brookes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
when	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
light	O
move	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
returned	O
with	O
Campion	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
:	O
she	O
seemed	O
slurried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
speed	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
eyes	O
off	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
proper	O
people	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
besides	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Camplon	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Chapman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
somebody	O
in	O
their	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
come	O
out	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
's	O
custody	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
coal-shed	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
coal-shed	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Chapman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
further	O
confirms	O
her	O
evidence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brookes	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
fetched	O
home	O
about	O
nine	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
sheet	O
;	O
my	O
drawers	O
were	O
all	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
fastened	O
my	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bundle	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
)	O
these	O
things	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
an	O
apron	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
apron	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
described	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
picklock	O
keys	O
,	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
a	O
stint	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
,	O
some	O
matches	O
and	O
this	O
apron	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
others	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
whose	O
names	O
are	O
George	O
Hartley	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Pagget	I-pers
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
evidence	O
he	O
might	O
save	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
289	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOOLEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Ruthvin	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
nineteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
;	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	O
WOOLEY	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Urquhart	I-pers
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
and	O
instrument	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
Against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
March	O
24	O
,	O
*	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Urquhart	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
out	O
from	O
my	O
chambers	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
air	O
:	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Camplin	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
I	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
,	O
my	O
nephew	O
,	O
a	O
studentin	O
physic	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
walk	O
.	O
We	O
set	O
off	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
seven	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Fig-lane	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
staid	O
behind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
duskish	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
Urquhart	O
.	O
Rather	O
dark	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
.	O
The	O
men	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lagged	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
bank	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
high	O
bank	O
,	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
foot-path	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
passed	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Camplin	O
and	O
my	O
nephew	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
foremost	O
men	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
said	O
stop	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
alarmed	O
at	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
your	O
life	O
or	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
scarcely	O
finished	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
nephew	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
the	O
pistol	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
that	O
surprized	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
run	O
any	O
risk	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
beat	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
seized	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
neck	O
and	O
arm	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
nephew	O
knocked	O
them	O
about	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
necessity	O
of	O
creeping	O
off	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
neck	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
like	O
a	O
stone	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
lucky	O
blow	O
the	O
young	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
recovered	O
a	O
little	O
from	O
his	O
blows	O
,	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
my	O
nephew	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Camplin	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Kentish	O
town	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Blackhorse	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
came	O
about	O
;	O
my	O
nephew	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
conveyed	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
round-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
afterwards	O
committed	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
pistol	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
plainly	O
knocked	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
Blackhorse	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
went	O
with	O
lanthorns	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Urquhart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
presented	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
by	O
mere	O
chance	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
fought	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
and	O
honest	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
regular	O
hours	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Steward	O
's	O
Rents	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tyner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hands	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hairdresser	O
and	O
peruke-maker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
going	O
on	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
290	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hampshire	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8th	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
291	O
.	O
292	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
CONWAY	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
IRISH	I-pers
MICK	I-pers
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
M'DONALD	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
stone	O
ring	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bird-street	B-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Wapping	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
shut	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
kitchen	O
is	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
area	O
goes	O
down	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
watchman	O
cry	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Hunter	O
,	O
(	O
my	O
lodger	O
)	O
squeal	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
words	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
spoken	O
by	O
somebody	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
nothing	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
bell	O
was	O
twisted	O
off	O
my	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
next	O
morning	O
by	O
the	O
scavengers	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Henderson	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Theobald	I-pers
;	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
surprized	O
at	O
that	O
and	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
Conway	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
sword	O
or	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
ceased	O
from	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
myself	O
still	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Theobald	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
lay	O
me	O
)	O
attempted	O
to	O
scream	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
bed	O
cloaths	O
over	O
our	O
heads	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
shifted	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
begged	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
air	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
keys	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
they	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
head	O
off	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
riffled	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
Conway	O
particularly	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
there	O
and	O
swore	O
bitterly	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
offered	O
to	O
move	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
off	O
our	O
heads	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Henderson	O
's	O
wife	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
keys	O
from	O
me	O
they	O
rumaged	O
my	O
drawers	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
small	O
stone	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
from	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
alarm	O
given	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
ring	O
or	O
buckles	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
justice	O
Camper	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
Conway	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
M'Donald	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
kitchen	O
window	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
hinges	O
had	O
been	O
wrenched	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
way	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Theobald	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
bed	O
fellow	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hunter	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
awaked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleep	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
between	O
sleep	O
and	O
awake	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
it	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
candle	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
off	O
go	O
both	O
your	O
heads	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
held	O
a	O
naked	O
sword	O
over	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
stopped	O
my	O
mouth	O
first	O
with	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
then	O
with	O
the	O
bed-cloaths	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
nothing	O
particularly	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
riffled	O
Mrs.	O
Hunter	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
ring	O
from	O
her	O
finger	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
from	O
her	O
shoes	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Hunter	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Hunter	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
returned	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
that	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
her	O
a	O
breakfast	O
;	O
this	O
they	O
did	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
accord	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
asked	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
but	O
were	O
interrupted	O
by	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
who	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
,	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
we	O
are	O
gone	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
and	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
M'Donald	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
justices	O
you	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Theobald	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
greater	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
than	O
Conway	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
am	O
absolutely	O
positive	O
to	O
M'Donald	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
likewise	O
to	O
Conway	O
.	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
voices	O
of	O
people	O
talking	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
enquire	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
shift	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
through	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
were	O
broke	O
off	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
were	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
safe	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
shut	O
it	O
myself	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
watchman	O
going	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
assistance	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
thieves	O
were	O
alarmed	O
and	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
justice	O
Camper	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
information	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Conway	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
when	O
this	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
M'Donald	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
unborn	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
293	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pound	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
cornclian	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen-pence	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
++	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
NATHANIAL	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
seven	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
garnet	O
necklaces	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
ear	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
twopence	O
,	O
three	O
French	O
beads	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
hair	O
pins	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
stay-hook	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
garnet	O
studs	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
necklace	O
of	O
cut	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
callico	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
lawn	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
laced	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
tucken	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
