TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1775	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
down	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
BELL	O
,	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
To	O
of	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKES	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	B-pers
STAFFORD	I-pers
SMITHE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas||	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
,	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Oades	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Ebenezer	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
James	B-pers
Coby	I-pers
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Crump	I-pers
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
George	B-pers
Seaton	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lovett	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
Lawrence	B-pers
D'Rippe	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Carten	I-pers
David	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
William	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
Norton	B-pers
Tyles	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cavill	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Johannett	I-pers
.	O
94	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
UPHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
delph	O
bowls	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
two	O
looking	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
delph	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
four-pence	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cordwainer	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
at	O
Fulham	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
:	O
and	O
all	O
were	O
fast	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
at	O
seven	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
to	O
a	O
shed	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
to	O
my	O
parlour	O
door	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
often	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
knows	O
my	O
house	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
myself	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
me	O
at	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
your	O
house	O
lately	O
?	O
Oram	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
these	O
last	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Castleman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
and	O
attend	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
rotation	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
his	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
goods	O
were	O
at	O
one	O
Silva	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
informed	O
by	O
one	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
offence	O
,	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Silva	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
glasses	O
,	O
four	O
bowls	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
delph	O
dish	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Silva	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
a	O
gardiner	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
china	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Sunday	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
eighteen-pence	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
glasses	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Silva	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
person	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Meredith	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Castleman	O
to	O
Silvia	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
A	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
himself	O
Robert	O
Upham	O
,	O
sold	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Oram	O
.	O
Those	O
are	O
the	O
shoes	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
concerned	O
in	O
robbing	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Silva	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
95	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
stock	O
and	O
feather	O
bed	O
.	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
wollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
coverlid	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
wooden	O
chairs	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
pail	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
tin	O
kettles	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
December	O
23d	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
lane	I-place
that	O
I	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
of	O
that	O
lodging	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
christmas	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
room	O
stripped	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Some	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
another	O
lodging	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
lodgers	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
stand	O
in	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
96	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOLLAND	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
thirty-shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Sowerby	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
December	O
10th	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	B-pers
Sowerby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Round-court	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
stept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
lace	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
half-pennyworth	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
called	O
silk	O
galloon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
of	O
himself	O
?	O
Sowerby	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
a	O
paper	O
stainer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
two-penny	O
lodging	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
``	O
is	O
a	O
green-grocer	O
in	O
Covent	O
garden	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
``	O
had	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
in	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
``	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
always	O
behaved	O
I	O
,	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
97	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
ten-shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woolen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
six-shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
ten-shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
ten-shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
-	O
Crosby	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
collecting	O
the	O
poors	O
rates	O
,	O
in	O
New	B-place
Inn	I-place
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
No	O
.	O
1.	O
a	O
person	O
let	O
himself	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
brushed	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
this	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
wrong	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crosby	O
's	O
evidence	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
cloths	O
produced	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
chambers	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
that	O
is	O
very	O
high	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
bannisters	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
one	O
must	O
stand	O
upon	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
whilst	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
2.	O
at	O
Lyon's-Inn	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
98	O
,	O
99	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
DUGARD	I-pers
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BANFIELD	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Dodding	B-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
with	O
menaces	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
forceable	O
and	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
feloniously	O
demanding	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Dodding	B-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Bruce	I-pers
to	O
steal	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
December	O
14	O
.	O
||	O
Dodding	B-pers
Jonathan	I-pers
Bruce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
in	O
Hanover-Street	B-place
,	O
by	O
four	O
persons	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
first	O
surrounded	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
some	O
indecent	O
language	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
Pain	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
coming	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
take	O
care	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
taller	O
than	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
said	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
pain	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
your	O
life	O
or	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
Upon	O
saying	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
fist	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knocked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
smallest	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
(	O
Banfield	O
)	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
at	O
their	O
first	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
perceive	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
any	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
long	O
knife	O
in	O
Dugard	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
aimed	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
I	O
believe	O
have	O
stabbed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
heart	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
stab	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
penetrated	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
bone	O
would	O
admit	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
ear	O
,	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
,	O
which	O
broke	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
it	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
blood	O
is	O
yet	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
Dugard	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dugard	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
almost	O
immediately	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
begin	O
the	O
conversation	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
defence	O
?	O
Bruce	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
begin	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Bruce	O
.	O
As	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
Hanover-street	O
,	O
four	O
persons	O
attacked	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
surrounded	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
something	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
terrified	O
,	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
knife	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Bruce	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
ear	O
and	O
head	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
pass	O
by	O
my	O
watch-house	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
attacked	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Bruce	O
call	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
rung	O
my	O
rattle	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
their	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Bruce	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
spent	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
hold	O
of	O
Dugard	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Dugard	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bruce	O
attacked	O
us	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
least	O
provocation	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
dropped	O
our	O
hats	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
he	O
put	O
mine	O
on	O
instead	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
his	O
head	O
bloody	O
.	O
Banfield	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
or	O
he	O
blowed	O
a	O
wistle	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
us	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Question	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bruce	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
blow	O
a	O
wistle	O
.	O
Bruce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Question	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
Dugard	O
's	O
head	O
bloody	O
?	O
Hood	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
DOBENEA	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
DALLOW	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
traced	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
civil	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
me	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
goods	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
promise	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
informed	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
to	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
before	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
101	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
BRIDGET	B-pers
SINGLETON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
filigree	O
measure	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
;	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
December	O
21st	O
.	O
++	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	O
I	O
now	O
live	O
in	O
Rathbone	O
Place	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
suspecting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Hankey	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
young	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
seventeen	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Aldersey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
shift	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Atherton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
-	O
Lane	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
persons	O
with	O
him	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
no	O
good	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
motion	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
sezed	O
him	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Two	O
chaps	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
my	O
face	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
containing	O
eleven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
containing	O
nine	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Herbert	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Witter	I-pers
,	O
December	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Herbert	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Witter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
who	O
were	O
then	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
secured	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shopman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
from	O
dinner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
apprentice	O
was	O
shewing	O
the	O
prisoners	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
I	O
had	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
serve	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
being	O
determined	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
narrowly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
convey	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
or	O
apron	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
:	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
dropped	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
dropped	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
Smith	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Jones	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Jones	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Smith	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
containing	O
eleven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeremy	I-pers
,	O
December	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	O
Egan	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
linen	O
draper	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
showed	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
turning	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
secrete	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Maiden	O
Lane	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
witness	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
apron	O
.	O
Egan	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
totally	O
false	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
T	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Kehan	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	B-pers
Kehad	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hawker	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
separately	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
waylaid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
snatched	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
found	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Clare	O
Market	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Tho	O
'	O
he	O
``	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
``	O
liquor	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
from	O
``	O
his	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
tell	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
the	O
``	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
''	O
Robert	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	B-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
linen	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Kehan	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
cloth	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
damaged	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
selvige	O
was	O
tore	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
drawing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
near	O
Clare	O
Market	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Blackmore	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
described	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
cloth	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
:	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
has	O
produced	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Kehan	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
nor	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
cloth	O
for	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
probable	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
neighbourhood	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
persons	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
frequently	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquors	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
degree	O
;	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Kehan	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offer	O
to	O
lend	O
you	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
Kehan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
:	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
violently	O
nor	O
of	O
putting	O
the	O
person	O
in	O
fear	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
106	O
,	O
107	O
,	O
108.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FREE	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PINKSTONE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Peter	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
,	O
December	O
25th	O
++	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
near	O
Sadler	B-place
's	I-place
Wells	I-place
;	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
an	O
apprehension	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
robbed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
Pinkston	O
had	O
a	O
cutlash	O
and	O
Free	O
and	O
Brown	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
there	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
persons	O
and	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
another	O
a	O
large	O
flapt	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
loosely	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
their	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
counsel	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
received	O
an	O
injury	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
eyes	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
an	O
injury	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
sight	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
hurt	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
exceeding	O
well	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
persons	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
two	O
had	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
loose	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
flapped	O
hat	O
;	O
Dignam	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
joined	O
by	O
one	O
Kipping	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
we	O
immediately	O
attacked	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Brown	O
throw	O
away	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
Kipping	O
seized	O
Pinkston	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
a	O
pistol	O
likewise	O
,	O
Free	O
had	O
a	O
remarkable	O
large	O
slapped	O
hat	O
,	O
Brown	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
exactly	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
described	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
hold	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dignam	I-pers
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
information	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
gave	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
upon	O
Kipping	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
three	O
to	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
passed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
passed	O
Pinkston	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
Brown	O
and	O
Free	O
,	O
Kipping	O
secured	O
Pinkston	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
Free	O
to	O
Dixon	O
.	O
Brown	O
had	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
loosely	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
Free	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
flapped	O
hat	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
seized	O
Brown	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
this	O
pistol	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
kirb	O
stone	O
which	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pistol	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
broke	O
by	O
a	O
blow	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Kipping	I-pers
.	O
I	O
secured	O
Pinkon	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
something	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
``	O
The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
``	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
``	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
``	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
``	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
``	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
when	O
``	O
the	O
prisoners	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
``	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
tell	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
``	O
just	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
``	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
ascertain	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
``	O
robbed	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
``	O
only	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
Brown	O
and	O
Pinkston	O
,	O
called	O
many	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Free	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
witnesses	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Head	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
December	O
29th	O
||	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Head	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Enfield	O
,	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
waggon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
sixpence	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
three-quarters	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
observe	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
his	O
hair	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Blacksmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
having	O
taken	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
described	O
to	O
them	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
dress	O
,	O
and	O
hair	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
with	O
my	O
teem	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
Head	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
moon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bunch	O
head	O
of	O
hair	O
and	O
rough	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
in	O
straw	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
from	O
the	O
description	O
Head	O
had	O
given	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Edwards	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
,	O
then	O
Mole	O
and	O
Banks	O
joined	O
us	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
he	O
made	O
resistance	O
:	O
he	O
turned	O
himself	O
round	O
,	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
horse	O
pistol	O
and	O
flashed	O
it	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
officer	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
tore	O
me	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
blacksmith	O
's	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
his	O
watch	O
home	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
from	O
the	O
smith	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
quite	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
satisfied	O
then	O
from	O
the	O
description	O
Head	O
had	O
given	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
induced	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
attempt	O
to	O
shoot	O
Woodland	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
pistol	O
missed	O
fire	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Mole	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
hearing	O
so	O
me	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
they	O
joined	O
Woodland	O
and	O
Edwards	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
They	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Woodland	O
and	O
Edwards	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
happened	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
.	O
Who	O
attends	O
at	O
justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
sixpence	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
)	O
and	O
some	O
gunpowder.	O
``	O
Thomas	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
``	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
.	O
''	O
William	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drew	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
fire	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
swan	O
shot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ponder	O
's	O
End	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
coming	O
back	O
three	O
men	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
supposed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
highwayman	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
them	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
pistols	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
cock	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
down	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pistols	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Stamford-Hill	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
112	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spearing	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
;	O
two	O
linen	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Spearing	I-pers
+	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Spearing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crispin-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
walking	O
over	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
fastened	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stand	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
one	O
Sligh	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
)	O
When	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
rushed	O
towards	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
struggle	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sligh	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
struggled	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sligh	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
your	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
Spearing	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
wife	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
tried	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
wife	O
put	O
her	O
arm	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Spearing	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
door	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
lock	O
of	O
my	O
chest-of	O
drawers	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Sligh	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Spearing	I-pers
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Gosset	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Robinson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
113	O
,	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
FLINT	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
quarters	O
of	O
linseed	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Thoruton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Dec.	O
13th	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
employ	O
Flint	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
honest	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
seed	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Featherston	I-pers
Haugh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Barrow	O
and	O
Smith	O
;	O
Mason	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
some	O
linseed	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
quarters	O
or	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
30	O
s.	O
per	O
quarter	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
much	O
less	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
I	O
agreed	O
for	O
it	O
for	O
26	O
shillings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Messrs.	O
Barrow	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
linseed	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
Mill	O
Stairs	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
directions	O
and	O
they	O
delivered	O
13	O
quarters	O
into	O
my	O
lighter	O
.	O
The	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
note	O
acknowledging	O
the	O
delivery	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
name	O
I	O
should	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
,	O
Smith	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Sherrard	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
compting-house	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
Stokes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
proprietor	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
linseed	O
was	O
stole	O
I	O
lett	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
directions	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
one	O
but	O
Flint	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
unless	O
by	O
his	O
or	O
Mr.	O
Paterson	O
's	O
orders	O
in	O
writing	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
loading	O
a	O
cast	O
with	O
the	O
linseed	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Flint	O
was	O
dismissed	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
's	O
service	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
loaded	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
Flint	O
locked	O
the	O
warehouse	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stokes	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
Flint	O
said	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
for	O
some	O
linseed	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Mason	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
Flint	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Flint	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
115	O
,	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOYLE	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BURNHAM	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ANN	B-pers
VERNON	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
leather	O
pocket	O
books	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Aaron	O
*	O
And	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
felonously	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
pocket	O
books	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOYLE	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
BURNHAM	O
,	O
and	O
ANN	B-pers
VERNON	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
printed	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
books	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
||	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GARRETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
mounted	O
with	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gun	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
behind	O
my	O
bar	O
door	O
:	O
sometime	O
after	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
gun	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hanney	O
's	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hanney	O
's	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
gun	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
gun	O
at	O
Peter	B-pers
Hanney	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
information	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hanney	O
's	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Hanney	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
gun	O
lay	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
ship	O
in	O
Little	O
Sanctuary	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hanney	O
gave	O
Garrett	B-pers
the	O
money	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
eleven-pence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hanney	O
,	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
his	O
reckoning	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
redeem	O
the	O
gun	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hanney	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gun	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
T	O
.	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JAMES	I-pers
CHESTERFIELD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
two-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stoke	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
five-shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warwicker	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
120	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
and	O
HANNAH	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
,	O
December	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
cloak	O
that	O
hung	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
cloak	O
:	O
Hannah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
confessed	O
``	O
she	O
``	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
``	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
``	O
drink	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
constable	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
cloak	O
thrown	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Edanor	O
Freer	O
confirmed	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
Acquitted	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
M'CLOUGH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
men	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
December	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beverley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
's	O
gateway	O
with	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
with	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
hat	O
against	O
the	O
India-house	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
:	O
(	O
the	O
hat	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
gate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
122	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BENNINGTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
wheaten	O
flour	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
meal-man	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
take	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
pounds	O
of	O
flour	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
meal-market	O
,	O
in	O
Queen-hithe	B-place
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
taking	O
a	O
little	O
flour	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
pudding	O
:	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
starving	O
:	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
tenpence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
123	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BUTTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
I	O
went	O
to	O
button	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
forgivness	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
through	O
necessity	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
124	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pound	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
,	O
December	O
23d	O
,	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
Hand-Alley	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
wife	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
continued	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Hounsditch	B-place
,	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
through	O
her	O
persuasion	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drank	O
it	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
women	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
then	O
I	O
will	O
call	O
in	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
women	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
'll	O
guinea	O
you	O
,	O
blast	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
they	O
stopt	O
my	O
mouth	O
with	O
the	O
bed	O
cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
take	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Bacchus	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
my	O
witnesses	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
lordship	O
will	O
ask	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Bacchus	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
sent	O
after	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
law	O
should	O
take	O
its	O
course	O
,	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
125	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
EDMUND	B-pers
ABELL	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pound	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
certain	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
December	O
12th	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
126	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
FRANCES	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
December	O
19th	O
.	O
++	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
they	O
behaved	O
very	O
indecent	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
peace	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
sharing	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Figgins	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
Ellis	O
's	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
found	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Figgins	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
they	O
dropped	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Figgins	I-pers
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
:	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
white	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
they	O
seemed	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
please	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
parcel	O
to	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
there	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
a	O
hum	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
ordered	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
stole	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Ellis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
with	O
that	O
young	O
woman	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Frances	O
Bailey	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
were	O
tried	O
upon	O
another	O
indictment	O
for	O
stealing	O
silk	O
stockings	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
another	O
Hosier	O
when	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
the	O
same	O
verdict	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
trial	O
.	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BROWN	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
KIRKMAN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
~	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
Saturday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
se'nnight	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
locked	O
up	O
her	O
room	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
's	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
sheets	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
a	O
sheet	O
which	O
``	O
he	O
deposed	O
was	O
pawned	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
``	O
prisoner	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
sheet	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
Margaret	B-pers
Greme	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
crape	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
,	O
December	O
13th	O
.	O
||	O
Margaret	B-pers
Greme	I-pers
.	O
My	O
coach	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
King's-Road	B-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
my	O
daughter	O
was	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
down	O
her	O
glass	O
immediately	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
attention	O
was	O
engaged	O
to	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
another	O
man	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
opened	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
purses	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
gave	O
them	O
our	O
purses	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
second	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
given	O
our	O
purses	O
already	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
he	O
swore	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
leaned	O
my	O
head	O
back	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
prevent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
the	O
violence	O
of	O
the	O
blow	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
fist	O
,	O
struck	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
eye	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
this	O
eye	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
little	O
girl	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
upon	O
the	O
temple	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
hand	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
back	O
stunned	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
demanded	O
our	O
watches	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
threatened	O
very	O
violently	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
upon	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
avoided	O
the	O
blows	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
I	O
felt	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
eye	O
.	O
He	O
searched	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
girls	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
threatened	O
to	O
blow	O
our	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
and	O
pity	O
,	O
my	O
daughters	O
begged	O
him	O
to	O
spare	O
their	O
mamma	O
,	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
blow	O
their	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
they	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
twice	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Greme	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
terrified	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
or	O
moon	O
light	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Greme	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
moon	O
light	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observation	O
,	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
or	O
little	O
man	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Greme	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
man	O
.	O
Miss	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Greme	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
my	O
mama	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
begged	O
mercy	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
both	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
each	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
step	O
upon	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
entirely	O
into	O
it	O
?	O
Miss	O
Greme	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
quite	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
aunts	O
fingers	O
for	O
rings	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
almost	O
in	O
my	O
lap	O
,	O
they	O
felt	O
our	O
hands	O
for	O
rings	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
them	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
mourning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
mourning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
strike	O
my	O
mamma	O
three	O
blows	O
,	O
I	O
begged	O
him	O
to	O
spare	O
my	O
mama	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
``	O
Be	O
quiet	O
John	O
,	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
''	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
any	O
attention	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
our	O
cloaks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
size	O
man	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
say	O
was	O
almost	O
in	O
your	O
lap	O
?	O
Miss	O
Greme	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
man	O
.	O
One	O
had	O
a	O
crape	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
something	O
over	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
once	O
bid	O
the	O
coachman	O
drive	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
footman	O
for	O
his	O
wacth	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
cloak	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
my	O
purse	O
the	O
instant	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Allpress	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
on	O
these	O
people	O
stopt	O
the	O
coach	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
Eve	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
coach	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
ladies	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observations	O
upon	O
the	O
persons	O
or	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
their	O
faces	O
.	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
black	O
crape	O
over	O
their	O
faces	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
I	O
cant	O
tell	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
do	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
arms	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
lightish	O
,	O
or	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
plain	O
enough	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
size	O
men	O
were	O
they	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
be	O
cautious	O
what	O
you	O
speak	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
size	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
belief	O
is	O
founded	O
only	O
upon	O
the	O
size	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
or	O
a	O
wig	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
both	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
their	O
own	O
hair	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
away	O
directly	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
them	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
four	O
cloaks	O
?	O
They	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
eye	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
four	O
cloaks	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
fetched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
three	O
cloaks	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
a	O
neighbour	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
raise	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
``	O
(	O
The	O
cloaks	O
produced	O
by	O
Halliburton	O
,	O
)	O
``	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
cloaks	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
``	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
dirty	O
.	O
''	O
Mrs.	O
Greme	O
deposed	O
to	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kirke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
cloak	O
for	O
Miss	O
Biddy	O
Graham	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
washed	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
blood	O
both	O
upon	O
the	O
robing	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
Brown	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
wash	O
out	O
any	O
blood	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Allpress	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
struck	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
hanger	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
a	O
man	O
struck	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hanger	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
hanger	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
hanger	O
produced	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Dinmore	I-pers
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
that	O
hanger	O
before	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
At	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
:	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
hilt	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
held	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
handle	O
?	O
Allpress	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dinmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
hanger	O
from	O
Lydia	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
and	O
done	O
some	O
mischief	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
running	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Dinmore	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
broken	O
pistol	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
somebody	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
my	O
hurry	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
to	O
whom	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
who	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hartrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hanger	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Hunt	O
had	O
broke	O
my	O
windows	O
;	O
a	O
school	O
boy	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drew	B-pers
the	O
hanger	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
boy	O
twice	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Dinmore	O
)	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
.	O
Dinmore	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
Hartrey	O
.	O
Dinmore	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
hanger	O
?	O
Hartrey	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hanger	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
to	O
it	O
particularly	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
a	O
girl	O
came	O
running	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
followed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Hunt	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
lying	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
daughter	O
of	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
but	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
the	O
girl	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
struggled	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
Thomas	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
fall	O
;	O
immediately	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
door	O
fast	O
Hunt	O
dashed	O
a	O
pistol	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
such	O
violence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
sash	O
frame	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
stuck	O
in	O
a	O
butter	O
tub	O
that	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
barrel	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Dinmore	O
.	O
Brown	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
butt	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
the	O
hanger	O
.	O
Halliburton	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
butt	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
pistol	O
that	O
is	O
produced	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Hartrey	O
at	O
Lydia	O
Hall	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
her	O
maiden	O
name	O
,	O
her	O
married	O
name	O
is	O
Brown	O
.	O
Foreman	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
are	O
in	O
doubt	O
.	O
if	O
this	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
pistol	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
glass	O
that	O
appears	O
in	O
the	O
butt	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
or	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hartrey	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kipping	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
two	O
lads	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
not	O
wanted	O
for	O
the	O
robbery	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
a	O
phrase	O
for	O
being	O
taken	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Kipping	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
away	O
immediately	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
hanger	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Dinmore	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Cow	O
Cross	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
's	O
heads	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
called	O
Dinmore	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
coming	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
partly	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Dinmore	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
pistol	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
rolled	O
up	O
and	O
chewed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
five	O
years	O
to	O
a	O
barbre	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
left	O
off	O
the	O
trade	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
Lydia	O
Hall	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
and	O
bad	O
language	O
:	O
the	O
master	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
got	O
me	O
a	O
lodging	O
on	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
.	O
That	O
Brown	O
's	O
husband	O
was	O
convicted	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
of	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
saw	O
me	O
buy	O
the	O
cloaks	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister-in-law	O
to	O
Lydia	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
sister	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
four	O
cloaks	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
sister	O
buy	O
them	O
off	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
over	O
mud	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
disputing	O
about	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
a	O
brother	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
your	O
brother	O
been	O
tried	O
this	O
sessions	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Ye	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Brown	O
,	O
Free	O
and	O
Pinckston	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
106	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
your	O
sister	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
cloaks	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Thirty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
condition	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
dirty	O
.	O
Dinmore	O
.	O
Brown	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
cloaks	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
asked	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
the	O
coachman	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
which	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
court	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
sad	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stood	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
prevented	O
his	O
turning	O
round	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
observation	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
quarts	O
of	O
claret	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
quarts	O
of	O
Champaign	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
quarts	O
of	O
Maderia	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
quart	O
of	O
old	O
hock	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
one	O
quart	O
of	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
quart	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Beauvais	I-pers
,	O
December	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Lewis	B-pers
Beauvais	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Germain	B-place
Street	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
wine-vaults	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
all	O
my	O
cellars	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
:	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
outer	O
cellar	O
where	O
the	O
wine	O
was	O
kept	O
for	O
daily	O
sale	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
store	O
cellar	O
was	O
locked	O
with	O
a	O
padlock	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
access	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
France	O
I	O
brought	O
a	O
boy	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
clerk	O
orders	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
my	O
cellar	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
;	O
I	O
hire	O
a	O
coach-house	O
near	O
Golden-square	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
keep	O
for	O
washing	O
bottles	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
boy	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
coach-house	O
washing	O
bottles	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
cellars	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
questions	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
soul	O
wine	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
store	O
cellars	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
any	O
wine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
prepared	O
any	O
wine	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
wine	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
had	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
store	O
cellars	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
cellars	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
wine	O
upon	O
the	O
lees	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
this	O
soul	O
wine	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
or	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
heap	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
different	O
places	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
both	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
wine	O
.	O
I	O
supposed	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
both	O
Burgundy	O
,	O
Claret	O
,	O
and	O
Champaign	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
foul	O
wine	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
store	O
cellar	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
boy	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
cellar	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
:	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
with	O
some	O
empty	O
bottles	O
and	O
a	O
hamper	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
the	O
bottles	O
into	O
the	O
hamper	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
empty	O
bottles	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
empty	O
bottles	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wad	O
of	O
straw	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
straw	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
full	O
bottle	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
Champaign	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
motion	O
to	O
kneel	O
down	O
and	O
ask	O
my	O
pardon	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
scruple	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
magistrate	O
asked	O
how	O
many	O
bottles	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
touched	O
one	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
to	O
the	O
coach-house	O
for	O
his	O
drinking	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
washing	O
the	O
bottles	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
somebody	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clerk	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
five	O
bottles	O
of	O
claret	O
,	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
Champaign	O
,	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
Maderia	O
,	O
one	O
bottle	O
of	O
old	O
hock	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
sweet	O
oil	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
last	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
:	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
wrong	O
things	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
my	O
master	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
out	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
Charles-Street	O
:	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
coach-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
empty	O
bottles	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
three	O
dozen	O
hamper	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
empty	O
bottles	O
to	O
the	O
coach-house	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
:	O
the	O
basket	O
was	O
put	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
we	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
inventory	O
of	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Joackim	O
Lienel	O
.	O
The	O
wine	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
removed	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
foul	O
wine	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
two	O
bottles	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Champaign	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
other	O
bottles	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
Maderia	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
seal	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
W	O
.	O
131	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
thirty-seven	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tawlin	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
he	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
cotton	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
said	O
cotton	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
++	O
++	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
91	O
,	O
Last	O
session	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
manufactured	O
this	O
cotton	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
one	O
Welch	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
fortnight	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
wife	O
coming	O
by	O
Hogg-Lane	O
,	O
they	O
live	O
near	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
blanket	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
home	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
husband	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
only	O
some	O
old	O
blankets	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
lodgers	O
,	O
this	O
have	O
some	O
old	O
houses	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
husband	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
poh	O
,	O
poh	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
only	O
some	O
old	O
blankets	O
,	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
shew	O
you	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
raised	O
my	O
suspicion	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
opened	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
sack	O
under	O
the	O
blankets	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
was	O
the	O
cotton	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
way	O
.	O
William	O
Edward	O
's	O
cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
worked	O
up	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
and	O
whether	O
this	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
some	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
Welch	O
stole	O
.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
up	O
fifty	O
pieces	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
Welch	O
stole	O
were	O
finished	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
finished	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
pieces	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
``	O
Moulson	O
Hodges	O
.	O
Deposed	O
that	O
the	O
cotton	O
``	O
produced	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Tawlin	O
``	O
and	O
Emerson	O
,	O
whom	O
Mr.	O
Edward	O
's	O
work	O
for	O
.	O
''	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Wade	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
dark	O
room	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
Welch	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
new	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
buy	O
any	O
new	O
linen	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
Welch	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
Martin	O
stepped	O
forward	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
had	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
some	O
new	O
linen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
call	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
asked	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
twenty-pence	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refusing	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no-body	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
;	O
to	O
lump	O
it	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
;	O
Welch	O
told	O
him	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
Martin	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
do	O
you	O
put	O
this	O
in	O
your	O
apron	O
and	O
go	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
wants	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
take	O
the	O
four	O
shillings	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
above	O
twelve	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
mistresses	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
man	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Shields	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
.	O
Grubb	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
very	O
unfair	O
practices	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
justice	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
this	O
girl	O
last	O
night	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
carried	O
off	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
friends	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
cloaths	O
she	O
has	O
on	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
that	O
hat	O
and	O
gown	O
?	O
Shields	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Martin	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
A	O
witness	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
houshold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
office	O
?	O
A.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Marshalsea	O
court	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
general	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
deals	O
in	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
furniture	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gun-maker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
small	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
Mark	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
reflection	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
9	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
-	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
about	O
eight	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
an	O
Irishman	O
)	O
had	O
some	O
cloth	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
remnants	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
twenty-pence	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
Ireland	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
fair	O
price	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
cloth	O
lay	O
in	O
her	O
open	O
shop	O
.	O
That	O
girl	O
has	O
been	O
bribed	O
upon	O
several	O
occasions	O
,	O
her	O
mistress	O
is	O
an	O
infamous	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
receiving	O
these	O
things	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
more	O
things	O
;	O
since	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
turned	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
indicted	O
last	O
Monday	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
is	O
an	O
infamous	O
man	O
and	O
the	O
justices	O
are	O
not	O
too	O
good	O
.	O
Guilty	O
T.	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARTMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13th	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
night	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Morton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Bishopgate	O
Ward	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
this	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
hand	O
near	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
133	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
LAZARUS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
