TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1775	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
Taken	O
in	O
SHORT-HAND	O
by	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
BELL	O
,	O
at	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
)	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKES	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
*	O
.	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
ASHHURST	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench+	O
.	O
The	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer||	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant~	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
tried	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heatley	I-pers
George	B-pers
Resdale	I-pers
James	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smalman	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Leadbetter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Sampson	B-pers
Rainforth	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
William	B-pers
Gyblett	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
George	B-pers
Coupland	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Darne	I-pers
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Kershaw	I-pers
Dodd	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
William	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Musson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
James	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
George	B-pers
Soward	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Bramble	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
John	B-pers
Stears	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sarflen	I-pers
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
William	B-pers
Frisby	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Stregent	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
578	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOSLING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Grave	I-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmden	I-pers
,	O
August	O
24	O
||	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
box	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
at	O
Mortlock	B-place
in	I-place
Surry	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23	O
l	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Madan	O
,	O
a	O
salesman	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
Madan	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
that	O
too	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
box	O
coat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Holmden	O
.	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Mc.Carty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
horses	O
,	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Holmden	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
box	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
for	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Madan	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
coat	O
for	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
for	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Madan	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
box	O
coat	O
of	O
Mc.Carty	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
579	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
chesnut-coloured	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thoman	B-pers
Hillson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
24	O
+	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hillson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
two	O
mile	O
stone	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Bow	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
a	O
Brewer	O
at	O
Stratford	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
Rye	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
another	O
horse	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
son	O
and	O
one	O
Stevens	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Rye	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
whose	O
possession	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
other	O
horse	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
line	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
soon	O
after	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Hillson	O
's	O
horse	O
in	O
Fair-Street	O
,	O
Horslydown	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
I	O
rode	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
near	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
with	O
orders	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hillson	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
horse	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hillson	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
horse	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
Hillson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Stevens	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
being	O
on	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
horse	O
at	O
Rye	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
580	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
DYMOND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
garnet	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
French	O
bead	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
a	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
;	O
one	O
hundred	O
French	O
beads	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
a	O
two	O
foot	O
rule	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
two	O
womens	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
stone	O
hairpins	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Spilsbury	I-pers
,	O
September	O
4th	O
.	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Spilsbury	I-pers
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
warehouse-man	O
in	O
Tavistock-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
.	O
I	O
sell	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
womens	O
apparel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
eight	O
months	O
.	O
Having	O
had	O
several	O
losses	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
Sunday	O
se'night	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
hamper	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
coal	O
cellar	O
,	O
containing	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
different	O
articles	O
.	O
This	O
alarmed	O
me	O
exceedingly	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
boxes	O
.	O
She	O
shewed	O
them	O
very	O
readily	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
such	O
as	O
were	O
locked	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
boxes	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
servant	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Turton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
boxes	O
were	O
searched	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
unlocked	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
I	O
demanded	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
boxes	O
.	O
She	O
delivered	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
womens	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
necklace	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
the	O
boxes	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Spilsbury	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
that	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
The	O
rule	O
and	O
the	O
French	O
beads	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
necklace	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
small	O
necklace	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
nobleman	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
masquerade	O
dresses	O
.	O
The	O
gold	O
locket	O
was	O
a	O
present	O
from	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Ancaster	O
to	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
The	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
are	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
``	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
were	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
``	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Spilsbury	O
.	O
''	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
old	O
linen	O
,	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Spilsbury	O
's	O
sister	O
.	O
found	O
the	O
locket	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
beads	O
I	O
swept	O
up	O
from	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
floor	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Spilsbury	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
child-bed	O
linen	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
581	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
corded	O
dimity	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
fifty-five	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
:	O
a	O
size	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rowley	B-pers
Lascelles	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
August	O
26th	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
582	O
,	O
583	O
,	O
584	O
,	O
585	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
EAST	I-pers
,	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CUTHBERT	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
FAGAN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leather	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
embroidered	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
embroidered	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
silk	O
coat	O
,	O
embroidered	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
;	O
another	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
trimmed	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
trimed	O
with	O
silver	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
gingham	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
linen	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
sixteen	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
;	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
;	O
twelve	O
cambrick	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
;	O
twelve	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
lace	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
five	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
nankeen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mares	I-pers
,	O
August	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
:	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Captain	O
Talbot	B-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
trunk	O
.	O
It	O
contained	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
chaise	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
town	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
set-out	O
for	O
Ellington	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
without	O
any	O
servant	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Ellington	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
trunk	O
was	O
not	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
then	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
the	O
fourth	O
mile	O
stone	O
,	O
in	O
Acton	B-place
bottom	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
lost	O
upon	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
trunk	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
things	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
likewise	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
putting	O
the	O
trunk	O
upon	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
strapped	O
it	O
across	O
with	O
two	O
straps	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
end	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
halter	O
,	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
fall	O
off	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ellerton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
tie	O
the	O
trunk	O
upon	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
to	O
Ellington	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
between	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
,	O
Bush	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
East	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
East	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
ride	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
turn	O
of	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Captain	O
Talbot	B-pers
's	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
information	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
trunk	O
from	O
behind	O
his	O
chaise	O
,	O
between	O
London	O
and	O
Ellington	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
immediately	O
sent	O
some	O
men	O
to	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
,	O
some	O
to	O
Pimblico	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
turnpikes	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
if	O
the	O
men	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stationed	O
at	O
Hyde-Park-Gate	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
four	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
,	O
all	O
loaded	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Fagan	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
double	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
immediately	O
set	O
off	O
towards	O
the	O
Lock	O
Hospital	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
bundles	O
from	O
Fagan	O
,	O
containing	O
several	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
kept	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
nankeen	O
breeches	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
were	O
given	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
Eyres	O
.	O
The	O
silk	O
stockings	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
breeches	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
trunk	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
strap	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
so	O
myself	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
with	O
a	O
cord	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
strap	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
stollen	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
four	O
mile	O
stone	O
.	O
(	O
``	O
The	O
straps	O
were	O
inspected	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
and	O
clearly	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
``	O
been	O
cut	O
.	O
''	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
after	O
Barnard	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Barnard	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
run	O
down	O
towards	O
the	O
Lock	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
East	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
rails	O
facing	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
garden	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
this	O
shirt	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
``	O
Eyres	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
``	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
contained	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
were	O
delivered	O
up	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
``	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
``	O
lost	O
.	O
''	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Jealous	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
Barnard	O
at	O
the	O
turnpike	O
.	O
Barnard	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Fagan	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopped	O
Cuthbert	O
and	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
tied	O
their	O
hands	O
together	O
.	O
Upon	O
Cook	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
Eyre	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Upon	O
East	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
Cook	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
a	O
blue	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
;	O
in	O
it	O
were	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
Eyre	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
an	O
outcry	O
I	O
stopped	O
Cuthbert	O
and	O
Cook	O
,	O
Cuthbert	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
;	O
amongst	O
other	O
things	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
Eyre	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Cuthbert	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Brentford	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
waterman	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
cricket-match	O
at	O
Kew	O
Green	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
just	O
by	O
Walham	O
Green	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
going	O
near	O
some	O
logs	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
bundle	O
lay	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
bundle	O
up	O
:	O
East	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
lifted	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
Cook	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
better	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
different	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
towards	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
Fagan	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
by	O
the	O
dead	O
wall	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
nearest	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
would	O
keep	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
.	O
Jealous	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
bundle	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
.	O
Another	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Jealous	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
Jennings	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
stand	O
to	O
reason	O
that	O
this	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
hardly	O
run	O
,	O
could	O
have	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
chose	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
escape	O
.	O
All	O
four	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
586	O
.	O
587	O
.	O
588	O
.	O
589	O
.	O
590	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILLIS	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TOMKINS	I-pers
,	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
BERRIDGE	I-pers
,	O
and	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
EDWARD	I-pers
ORNSBY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
copper	O
half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
August	O
26	O
*	O
.	O
All	O
five	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
591	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
ounces	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
1st	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
592	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
August	O
26th	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
seized	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
rummaged	O
my	O
coat	O
pockets	O
and	O
they	O
turned	O
my	O
breeches	O
pockets	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
wiped	O
my	O
face	O
with	O
it	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
there	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
Owen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
pocket	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
Brooks	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
kicked	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
before	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
593	O
.	O
594	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
and	O
WRIGHT	B-pers
STAGG	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
silver	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
September	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-case-maker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
desk	O
,	O
which	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
mark	O
several	O
pieces	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
silver	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
accused	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
)	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
silver	O
was	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
errand-boy	O
there	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
having	O
missed	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
marked	O
eleven	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
crying	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wright	B-pers
Stagg	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
a	O
green-stall	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
,	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Stagg	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
-	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Bryant	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
Stagg	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Bryant	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Stagg	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Bryant	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
two-pence	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Bryant	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Stagg	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
;	O
among	O
whom	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Bryant	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Stagg	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
595	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
James	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
covered	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
forty-shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
,	O
August	O
13th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
596	O
.	O
597	O
.	O
598	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
THOMAS	B-pers
BATH	I-pers
and	O
HENRY	B-pers
GRAY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
;	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
Russia	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
||	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
New	O
Broad	O
street	O
buildings	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Oxford-Road	O
to	O
Phenix-Yard	B-place
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
opposite	O
the	O
hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cavendish	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Bath	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
Bath	O
tripped	O
me	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
and	O
Johnson	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
on	O
my	O
hip	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Russia	O
cloth	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
That	O
expression	O
struck	O
me	O
rather	O
in	O
a	O
flurry	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
,	O
having	O
friends	O
not	O
above	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
held	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
like	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
palsy	O
or	O
an	O
ague	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
:	O
they	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
noise	O
!	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gate-way	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
right-hand	O
side	O
of	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
towards	O
Swallow-Street	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gate-way	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
``	O
Stop	O
robber	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right-hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
''	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
your	O
cloth	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Gray	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
Gray	O
carried	O
it	O
off	O
:	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
ran	O
off	O
together	O
;	O
Gray	O
was	O
behind	O
,	O
Path	O
and	O
Johnson	O
were	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
before	O
him	O
:	O
on	O
my	O
making	O
the	O
outcry	O
,	O
Gray	O
dropped	O
the	O
cloth	O
by	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Swallow-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Gray	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
cloth	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
caught	O
Gray	O
by	O
the	O
breast	O
;	O
Bath	O
and	O
Johnson	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Johnson	O
by	O
fight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
positively	O
say	O
that	O
Bath	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
opinion	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
now	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
Bath	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
really	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
Bath	O
.	O
Whether	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
sufficient	O
light	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
us	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
Adelphi	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
state	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
Bath	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
Gray	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
throat	O
and	O
almost	O
throttle	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
Germain	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
caught	O
Gray	B-pers
I	O
certainly	O
griped	O
him	O
unmercifully	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
any	O
thief	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
minutes	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
Gray	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
cloth	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
and	O
Still	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Phenix	O
Yard	O
,	O
three	O
fellows	O
came	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Not	O
so	O
dark	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
their	O
persons	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
running	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
why	O
three	O
men	O
should	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
Germain	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
hollowing	O
,	O
``	O
A	O
robbery	O
!	O
a	O
``	O
robbery	O
!	O
a	O
robbery	O
!	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand-side	O
``	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
(	O
Gray	O
)	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
bundle	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
when	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
tall	O
thin	O
man	O
made	O
a	O
catch	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
big	O
ones	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
about	O
four	O
paces	O
before	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
big	O
ones	O
say	O
to	O
Gray	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
``	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
make	O
``	O
haste	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
''	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
Bath	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
by	O
your	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
sharp	O
cocked	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Germain	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
by	O
your	O
dress	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
now	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
loose	O
bodied	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
colour	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
Gray	O
was	O
in	O
Marybone	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Bath	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
that	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Johnson	O
;	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Johnson	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Dusty	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Duck-lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
Bath	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
his	O
information	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnfather	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
favour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
discovered	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
justices	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
party	O
concerned	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
mention	O
him	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
all	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
would	O
use	O
my	O
utmost	O
endeavours	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
cleared	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
''	O
Johnson	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Bath	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Gray	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
596	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
MACKINTOSH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighty-one	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
gunpowder	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
;	O
a	O
hempen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
salt	O
prunella	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
salt	O
petre	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
one	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
black	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
ivory	O
black	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Plomer	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Phillip	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15th	O
.	O
++	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Plomet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
servant	O
.	O
We	O
observed	O
our	O
gunpowder	O
decreasing	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
justices	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
,	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
particularly	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
property	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Plomer	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
gunpowder	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justices	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
secured	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
gunpowder	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Barber	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
closet	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
powder	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
salt	O
prunella	O
,	O
salt	O
petre	O
,	O
black	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
ivory	O
black	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
gunpowder	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
sometime	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
of	O
whom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
cousin	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Mackintosh	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
steward	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
597	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
SILAS	B-pers
SHEERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
;	O
another	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
twopence	O
;	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
August	O
13th	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Five	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
seals	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch-key	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
chain	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
watch	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stopped	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
now	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
public-house	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
soldier	O
you	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
public-house	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
across	O
the	O
Ambury	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Williamson	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
had	O
some	O
seals	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
Five	O
Fields	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
the	O
soldier	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
seals	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
``	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
``	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
''	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
take	O
the	O
seals	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
prisoner	O
's	O
breeches	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Williamson	O
.	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
pursuer	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
Williamson	O
as	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
soldier	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
neckcloth	O
and	O
face	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
them	O
both	O
up	O
in	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Loams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Five	O
Fields	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
dressed	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
detain	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
peppermint	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Williamson	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
They	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
There	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
glass	O
of	O
peppermint	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Becket	O
and	O
my	O
maid	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
looks	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
women	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
followed	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
one	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Foster	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
talked	O
of	O
going	O
further	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
beer	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
towards	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
houses	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
just	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
were	O
they	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Williamson	O
.	O
Above	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
Williamson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
the	O
man	O
badly	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
robbed	O
by	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
?	O
Williamson	O
.	O
One	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
?	O
Williamson	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
speak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
down	O
?	O
Williamson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
knocked	O
down	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
fall	O
down	O
.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
little	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
nose	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
bleed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
these	O
seals	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
598	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CHILDES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
6th	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
;	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
field	O
from	O
Tottenham-Court	B-place
turnpike	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Childes	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
attacked	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
pistols	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
attacked	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
patience	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
be	O
quick	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
attacked	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
broke	O
my	O
shin	O
with	O
his	O
pistol	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Moon	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
now	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
positively	O
undertake	O
that	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
instantly	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
we	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
something	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
:	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
``	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
``	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
``	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
``	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
immediately	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
sight	O
,	O
but	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
``	O
taken	O
:	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
``	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
``	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
nobody	O
``	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
no	O
weapons	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
''	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
.	I-pers
Coming	I-pers
towards	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
field	O
from	O
Tottenham-Court	O
turnpike	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
breast	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
take	O
your	O
pistol	O
away	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
pistol	O
at	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Holmes	O
had	O
a	O
scuffle	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
,	O
in	O
Tottenham-Court-Road	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
constable	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
eight-pence	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
the	O
pistol	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Saw	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
Saw	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
footpad	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
handcuffed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
your	O
worst	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
but	O
tuck	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
eight-pence	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drank	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
field	O
from	O
the	O
turnpike	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pistol	O
in	O
a	O
water-gutter	O
cut	O
for	O
the	O
draining	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
eighty	O
or	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
foot-path	O
,	O
towards	O
Primrose	O
Hill	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
four	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
thousand	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
pistol	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
``	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
``	O
Holmes	O
was	O
attacked	O
and	O
robbed	O
by	O
another	O
``	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
``	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
not	O
robbed	O
at	O
``	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
from	O
``	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
``	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
``	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
``	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
pistol	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
``	O
was	O
the	O
pistol	O
the	O
prisoner	O
held	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
size	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
rust	O
``	O
there	O
was	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
another	O
``	O
pistol	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
water-track	O
``	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
was	O
quite	O
dry	O
.	O
''	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Saw	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
handcuffs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
handcuffed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
used	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
ill	O
,	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
his	O
trial	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
599	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
JEAN	B-pers
DANIEL	I-pers
SOLAR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beauchamp	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26th	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
600	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M	O
)	O
HENRY	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
July	O
25th	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
601	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
RUSSELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
mahogany	O
tea-chests	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Watman	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
September	O
8th	O
||	O
Robert	B-pers
Watman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
instant	O
,	O
ar	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
chests	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
one	O
Lyon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
released	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
:	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
second-hand	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
:	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
Middlesex	O
Court	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
chests	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
throw	O
them	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
goods	O
or	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Smithers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lyon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
off	O
a	O
table	O
that	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Watman	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
lives	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
five	O
small	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
husband	O
quite	O
blind	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
very	O
hard	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
chips	O
,	O
it	O
rained	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
602	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ISAAC	B-pers
SHEERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted-stockings	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
29th	O
.	O
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
comes	O
into	O
Strand-lane	O
,	O
the	O
fore-part	O
is	O
in	O
Surry-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
bundle	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
was	O
true	O
;	O
because	O
a	O
few	O
weeks	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
in	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
redeem	O
some	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
office	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thin	O
stockings	O
that	O
were	O
made	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Isle	O
of	O
Jersey	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
wore	O
them	O
above	O
once	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
curious	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
presume	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
thing	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
was	O
the	O
coat	O
I	O
now	O
have	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
coat	O
washed	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
coat	O
?	O
Eyres	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
about	O
to	O
discharge	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Eyres	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
things	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
his	O
wages	O
?	O
Eyres	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
his	O
wages	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
before	O
this	O
another	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
exceeded	O
his	O
wages	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
washing	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
now	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
603	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M.	O
)	O
HYDER	B-pers
CAMPION	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
flannel	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
women	O
's	O
silk	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
shalloon	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
checque	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
two	O
white	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
:	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gledhill	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Gledhill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swan	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
White	I-place
Chapel	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
next	O
morning	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
mentioned	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
men	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
bundles	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
lads	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
these	O
bundles	O
?	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
better	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
they	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
them	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
passed	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
they	O
began	O
,	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
,	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
up	O
Lambeth-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
men	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
alley	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
Rupert-Square	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
can	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gledhill	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
(	O
pointing	O
out	O
those	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
summer-house	O
;	O
the	O
shalloon	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
the	O
quantity	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
piece	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
hat	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mistresses	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
have	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
work	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
;	O
some	O
boys	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
wrangling	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
followed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
604	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
;	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
605	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
MARGARET	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
HENRY	I-pers
SPENCER	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	O
Adshead	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
.	O
Against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adshead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wardour-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
as	O
for	O
a	O
widow	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
her	O
to	O
continue	O
any	O
longer	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
widow	O
did	O
not	O
behave	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
herself	O
;	O
then	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
divers	O
times	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
continued	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
furniture	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
furniture	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
half	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
was	O
near	O
new	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
and	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
table-cloth	O
were	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Brotherton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
advanced	O
her	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
three-pence	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Priestman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
custom-house	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
accidently	O
in	O
court	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
this	O
situation	O
;	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
an	O
inn	O
in	O
Cambridgeshire	O
,	O
near	O
lord	O
Montford	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
business	O
often	O
with	O
his	O
lordship	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
that	O
inn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
606	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
PHILLIP	B-pers
ROWLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
and	O
Adam	B-pers
Dunford	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
in	O
Newport-Street	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Adam	O
Dunford	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
often	O
missed	O
shoes	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
that	O
were	O
made	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rested	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
shoes	O
mentioned	O
in	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Duperry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jarvis	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
he	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
D.	O
A.	O
besides	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
from	O
the	O
make	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Ten-pence	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
607	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
608	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
ANDREW	B-pers
HYSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
cutting	O
,	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
six	O
leaden	O
sash	O
weights	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
weights	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
building	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
masters	B-pers
and	I-pers
wardens	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
company	I-pers
of	I-pers
merchant-taylors	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
fraternity	I-pers
of	I-pers
St	I-pers
John	I-pers
Baptist	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29th	O
.	O
++	O
Walter	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
Wood	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
separately	O
;	O
they	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
leaden	O
weights	O
and	O
some	O
brass	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Wood	O
went	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Hughes	O
,	O
for	O
seven-pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
use	O
any	O
arts	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
confession	O
from	O
them	O
?	O
Prosser	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
an	O
uninhabited	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
merchant	O
taylors	O
;	O
they	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
they	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
four	O
other	O
leaden	O
weights	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sound	O
upon	O
Wood	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Sun-street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Sun	O
ale-house	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
weights	O
and	O
brass	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
sash	O
weights	O
upon	O
Wood	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
Hyson	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
three	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
ale	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Sun	O
ale-house	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
four	O
weights	O
upon	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
weights	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
just	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
weights	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
merchant-taylors	O
'	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
stile	O
and	O
title	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
set	O
forth	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
merchant-taylors	O
'	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
some	O
weights	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
premisses	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
weights	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
through	O
Sun-street	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
I	O
daresay	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
some	O
money	O
dropped	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boards	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
broke	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
leads	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
daresay	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
down	O
the	O
boards	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
down	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
another	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
hearth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
the	O
leads	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
609	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
MACDANIEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Kenrick	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3d	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Edward	I-pers
Kenrick	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
up	O
Holborn-hill	B-place
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
immediately	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
turn	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
fellows	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
witness	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
more	O
ragged	O
than	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
610	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
August	O
12th	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King's-head	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Fore-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pot	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
pot	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sixty-three	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
611	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
GWILLAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
velveret	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Else	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1st	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Else	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
for	O
being	O
addicted	O
to	O
drinking	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Else	O
and	O
Mr.	O
James	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
old	O
choaths	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Chick-lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
promised	O
to	O
forgive	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
Else	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
any	O
accomplices	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
612	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
DOVE	B-pers
ASH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
date	O
,	O
Bridgenorth	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
1775	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hastlewood	I-pers
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Alderson	O
and	O
Sandland	O
,	O
Cateaton-street	O
,	O
London	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
seven	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
to	O
Cobbe	B-pers
Pittman	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Plestow	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Aug.	O
3d	O
.	O
General	O
Plestow	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Vauxhall	O
upon	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
notes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
either	O
in	O
Vauxhall	B-place
gardens	I-place
,	O
or	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
garden	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
notes	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
places	O
where	O
the	O
notes	O
were	O
payable	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
caveat	O
against	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
particularly	O
to	O
Anderson	O
and	O
Sandland	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
;	O
a	O
notice	O
came	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
stop	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
;	O
being	O
ask	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
gentleman	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
the	O
gentleman's-name	O
that	O
employed	O
him	O
upon	O
an	O
errand	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lancoln	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
note	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
note	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
613	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
M.	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
SLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
shoe	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mattocks	I-pers
,	O
September	O
1st	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
614	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
COOLING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
three-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
August	O
19th	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
615	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOWMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
an	O
onyx	O
stone	O
set	O
therein	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen-shillings	O
;	O
another	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
breast	O
buckle	O
with	O
garnets	O
set	O
therein	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18th	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
shirt	O
buckle	O
with	O
garnets	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
minories	B-place
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
shirt	O
buckle	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
stone	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
payment	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
by	O
weight	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
stone	O
gold	O
ring	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
returned	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
:	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
shirt-buckle	O
set	O
with	O
garnets	O
:	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
shirt	O
buckle	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
gold	O
ring	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
half-pence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
he	O
might	O
change	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
it	O
weighed	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
twenty-nine	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
mend	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
for	O
my	O
sleeve-buttons	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
stole	O
a	O
ring	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
kept	O
it	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
ring	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
616	O
,	O
617	O
.	O
(	O
2d	O
.	O
M	O
)	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
IVES	I-pers
and	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty-one	O
guineas	O
and	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hanna	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
5th	O
||	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hanna	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
arrived	O
here	O
from	O
North	O
America	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
sale	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
effects	O
I	O
brought	O
over	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
curious	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
having	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
to	O
pass	O
through	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Salt-petre	B-place
Bank	I-place
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Ives	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
beckoned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
room	O
above	O
stairs	O
or	O
below	O
stairs	O
?	O
Hanna	O
.	O
Below	O
stairs	O
,	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
sat	O
down	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
out	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
returned	O
immediately	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Brown	O
;	O
Brown	O
returned	O
me	O
the	O
shilling	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
gold	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
observed	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
beside	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
use	O
some	O
freedoms	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
one	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
Ives	O
sat	O
down	O
close	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
shammy	O
pocket	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
fifty-one	O
guineas	O
and	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
:	O
on	O
my	O
discovering	O
that	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
immediately	O
fled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
said	O
something	O
.	O
Hanna	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
buttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
women	O
that	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
girl	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
lied	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
lose	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
lied	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
struck	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
girl	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Hanna	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
they	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
during	O
the	O
hurry	O
,	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
came	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
wrested	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
obliged	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
advised	O
to	O
inform	O
justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
runners	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Farrell	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
pretended	O
husband	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Brown	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
several	O
people	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
right	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
had	O
sled	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
M	O
'	O
Carty	O
at	O
Deptford	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
one	O
of	O
justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
runners	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
Deptford	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
taken	O
?	O
Hanna	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
by	O
one	O
Weston	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
complained	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
watch	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
thirty-two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
found	O
upon	O
Brown	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
``	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
``	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
when	O
he	O
``	O
went	O
to	O
Salt-petre	O
Bank	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
``	O
be	O
particular	O
to	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
``	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
``	O
be	O
six	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
``	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
justice	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
``	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
``	O
take	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
women	O
``	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
and	O
committed	O
``	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threatened	O
them	O
``	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
acquainted	O
``	O
with	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
``	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
to	O
one	O
woman	O
in	O
``	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
``	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
``	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
``	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
robbed	O
``	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
``	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
the	O
``	O
money	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
``	O
thing	O
he	O
observed	O
was	O
his	O
pocket	O
turned	O
inside	O
``	O
side	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
positively	O
``	O
do	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
''	O
George	B-pers
Waston	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
complained	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
one	O
he	O
said	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
that	O
the	O
one	O
was	O
tall	O
,	O
and	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
small-pox	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
short	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
wore	O
a	O
gold	O
necklace	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
and	O
received	O
some	O
information	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
lower	O
Water-gate	O
,	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
watched	O
the	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
thirty-two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Jack	B-pers
Farrell	I-pers
's	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
forty	O
guineas	O
from	O
Farrell	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
Farrell	O
came	O
by	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
received	O
some	O
blood-money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
Farrell	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
bring	O
my	O
name	O
in	O
question	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
to	O
lose	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
nutmeg-grater	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
small	O
box	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
necklace	O
and	O
locket	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Naria	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Palmer	O
,	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Mc	O
.	O
Carty	O
,	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
guineas	O
;	O
they	O
weighed	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
and	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
taken	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
prison	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
guinea	O
lighter	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
peppermint	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
guinea	O
back	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Brown	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
all	O
the	O
light	O
ones	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Palmer	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
herself	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
cloth	O
for	O
bed-gowns	O
and	O
shirts	O
.	O
Upon	O
an	O
alarm	O
given	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
near	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Ives	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Ives	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
met	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
this	O
empty	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
s	O
you	O
are	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
empty	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
blew	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
b	O
-	O
s	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Palmer	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
some	O
watchmen	O
came	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
