TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
1776	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SIXTH-SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAWBRIDGE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
REVISED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
BY	O
JOHN	B-pers
GLYNN	I-pers
,	O
SERJEANT	O
AT	O
LAW	O
,	O
AND	O
RECORDER	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
;	O
AND	O
SOLD	O
BY	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX	O
PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
SAWBRIDGE	O
,	O
MAYOR	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
Common	O
Council	O
holden	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
Guildhall	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
1775	O
,	O
A	O
MOTION	O
was	O
made	O
and	O
QUESTION	O
put	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
whole	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
be	O
regularly	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
after	O
every	O
Session	O
,	O
published	O
by	O
the	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
authenticated	O
with	O
his	O
Name	O
:	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
resolved	O
in	O
the	O
Affirmative	O
.	O
RIX	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAWBRIDGE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flude	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wallace	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Finley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Paley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Coggan	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Witham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lever	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
[	O
David	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coggan	I-pers
.	O
]	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
Stone	B-pers
Tuppen	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Barraston	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hastie	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mule	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bocquet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stoughton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Redshaw	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
501.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
containing	O
five	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowl	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JENKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowl	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
;	O
we	O
are	O
linen-drapers	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Coventry-street	B-place
:	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
gown	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
concealed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
concealed	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
502.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
covered	O
with	O
green	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
June	O
2d	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
charge	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
unconfirmed	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
testimony	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
Peach	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
June	O
2d	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
defect	O
in	O
the	O
evidence	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
503.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nineteen	O
bars	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Jewkins	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Holmer	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7th	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
Lays	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Diana	B-pers
Wooldridge	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
iron	O
missing	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
mark	O
thereon	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
identified	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
504.	O
MARY	B-pers
READING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coupland	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11th	O
.	O
'The	O
prosecutor	O
suffered	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
'picked	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
'with	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
'missed	O
his	O
bed-fellow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
'mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
'	O
A	O
witness	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
'deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
'he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
'could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
'the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
'had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
lodging	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
'the	O
fact	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
505.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GOSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
containing	O
thirty	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
June	O
12th	O
.	O
JOSIAH	B-pers
LISTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Andrews	O
and	O
Fisher	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
our	O
warehouse	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
shalloon	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
further	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
shalloon	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Lister	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
506.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pharez	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PHAREZ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	B-place
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
near	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
tug	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
snatched	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
down	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
507.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wether	O
lamb	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3d	O
.	O
'	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
two	O
'material	O
witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
were	O
'called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
'their	O
recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
'	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
508.	O
ANN	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
PATRICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
;	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
shifts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bed-gown	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
dining	O
room	O
on	O
Saturday	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
done	O
needle	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
times	O
for	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
-	O
CROCKFORD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
shirt	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
bed-gown	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
afternoon	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
shirt	O
and	O
bed-gown	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
shirts	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
509.	O
MORRIS	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
hogshead	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
510	O
,	O
511.	O
MARY	B-pers
MONK	I-pers
and	O
ROSE	B-pers
CAREY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
June	O
27th	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
charge	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
unconfirmed	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
testimony	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
512.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOVERIDGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
June	O
12th	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SALMON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
Fish-street-hill	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
Monument	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
DICKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BRUCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Salmon	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
might	O
search	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
513.	O
MARY	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
containing	O
nine	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
printed	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rose	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
12th	O
.	O
ROSE	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Union-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Middlesex-hospital	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
light	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
some	O
excuse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
candle	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
I	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
raised	O
some	O
suspicion	O
in	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
silk	O
and	O
my	O
clouded	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
silk	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
gown	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Westminster-bridge	O
,	O
walking	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
she	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
[	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
petticoat	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosetrix	O
.	O
]	O
EBENEZER	B-pers
STOKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
gown	O
from	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Mitchel	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
petticoat	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
on	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
on	O
the	O
petticoat	O
.	O
-	O
SWIFT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
shifts	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GATTY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
the	O
silk	O
gown	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
514.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BEAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
22d	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
my	O
watch	O
hung	O
over	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
:	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
serve	O
them	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TRUTTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Wells	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
dropped	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
called	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
dropped	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
515.	O
MARY	B-pers
ELIZABETH	I-pers
CHARLOTTE	I-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
a	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sheet	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
:	O
upon	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
Mary	O
Hall	O
,	O
bring	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
discharge	O
her	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
box	O
upon	O
discharging	O
her	O
I	O
should	O
discover	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Upon	O
searching	O
her	O
my	O
housekeeper	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
sheet	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
and	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
(	O
the	O
sheet	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
housekeeper	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Nicolls	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
sheet	O
in	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
:	O
upon	O
receiving	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
not	O
move	O
it	O
upon	O
any	O
account	O
,	O
but	O
watch	O
and	O
see	O
who	O
comes	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
those	O
that	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
certainly	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
afterwards	O
acquainted	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
fetched	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
informed	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parlour-door	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
sheet	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
sheet	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
beds	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
confessed	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
discovered	O
by	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
:	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
but	O
we	O
missed	O
something	O
or	O
other	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash.	O
[	O
The	O
neckcloths	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
EDWARD	B-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
being	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
date	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
brought	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
GRIFFIAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
HALL	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
spoon	O
so	O
marked	O
.	O
PROSECUTOR	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
spoon	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
missed	O
one	O
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
NICOLLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
discovered	O
a	O
sheet	O
in	O
the	O
ceiling	O
of	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
watch	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
person	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
through	O
the	O
garden	O
towards	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Hall	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
when	O
she	O
discovered	O
these	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GODERD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
NICOLLS	O
.	O
A	O
message	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
somebody	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
where	O
this	O
spoon	O
was	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Griffian	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
and	O
replace	O
them	O
.	O
'The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
'known	O
her	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
'good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
516.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SHRIMPTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
hand	O
garden-glasses	O
leaded	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
27th	O
.	O
'The	O
witnesses	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
the	O
'prisoner	O
carrying	O
six	O
glasses	O
,	O
four	O
upon	O
a	O
'stick	O
over	O
his	O
shoulder	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
'about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Lady	O
Cook	O
's	O
'garden	O
;	O
they	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
'he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Lady	O
Cook	O
's	O
garden	O
.	O
'The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
'them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
witnesses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
517.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DOVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
July	O
3d	O
.	O
'It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
'there	O
were	O
any	O
such	O
threats	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
or	O
'	O
a	O
putting	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
as	O
are	O
necessary	O
to	O
constitute	O
'	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
518.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ELLAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scales	O
and	O
weights	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
twelve	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Gersham	B-pers
Widdop	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gersham	O
,	O
May	O
23d	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
519.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bigger	I-pers
,	O
December	O
11th	O
.	O
'There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
'prisoner	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
'not	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
fairly	O
obtained	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
520.	O
MARY	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
]	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRIEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
pint	O
pots	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
breakfast	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
Webb	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
pots	O
:	O
we	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
within	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
a	O
little	O
bag	O
with	O
three	O
pots	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
as	O
she	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Webb	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WEBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Priest	O
's	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Priest	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
pursued	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
dropped	O
two	O
pots	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
one	O
pot	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pots	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pots	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
they	O
lugged	O
me	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
521.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SPENCER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
dimity	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Buggin	I-pers
;	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
tin	O
canisters	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
;	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plated	O
shoebuckles	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
copper	O
half-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Abbots	I-pers
;	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cheque	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Buggin	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3d	O
.	O
'	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
'prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
'robbery	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cheque	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Tenton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
5th	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
TENTON	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
a	O
widow	O
lady	O
,	O
No	B-place
53	I-place
,	I-place
Hatton-street	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
person	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
morning	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
I	O
him	O
:	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
repairing	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
desired	O
the	O
master	O
plaisterer	O
to	O
send	O
another	O
man	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
flurried	O
I	O
hesitated	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
watching	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
's	O
fork	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
us	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
cook	O
immediately	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
painters	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
unloading	O
the	O
paint	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
breakfast	O
and	O
would	O
return	O
presently	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
painter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
plaisterer	O
had	O
sent	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
believed	O
came	O
on	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
painter	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
painter	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
cloth	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
over	O
a	O
cabinet	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
dust	O
,	O
removed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cabinet	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
gone	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
pawned	O
at	O
five	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
painter	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
in	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
he	O
gave	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
met	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
CORNELIUS	B-pers
M'MENUS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
good	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
cloaths	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
white	O
apron	O
in	O
imitation	O
of	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
tucked	O
up	O
partly	O
as	O
mine	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
unloading	O
the	O
cart	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MATTAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Low	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
petticoat	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
six-shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Martha	B-pers
Tenton	I-pers
.	O
]	O
DENNIS	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
shift	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister-in-law	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Martha	B-pers
Tenton	I-pers
.	O
]	O
CHARLES	B-pers
MURTHWAITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
cloak	O
and	O
apron	O
that	O
were	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
seven	O
shillings	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
apron	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
the	O
cloak	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
shillings	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
he	O
pawned	O
something	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
petticoat	O
and	O
apron	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
PROSECUTRIX	O
.	O
His	O
brother	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
favourable	O
than	O
the	O
law	O
would	O
admit	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
522.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SPENCER	I-pers
junior	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27th	O
.	O
'	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
were	O
'called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
their	O
recognizances	O
'were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
523.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLIFTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Plunkett	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22d	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
PLUNKETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High	B-place
Holborn	I-place
:	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
my	O
shop	O
I	O
saw	O
somebody	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
great	O
speed	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
he	O
was	O
likely	O
to	O
outrun	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
people	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
:	O
Mulcaster	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
private	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
inner	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
not	O
only	O
promised	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
even	O
proposed	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
past	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
FRANKLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
cards	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Garling	O
's	O
door	O
in	O
King-street	O
(	O
Producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
PROSECUTOR	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
are	O
my	O
handwriting	O
:	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
twenty	O
yards	O
beyond	O
Mr.	O
Garling	O
's	O
.	O
FRANKLAND	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
:	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
more	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
down	O
our	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Garling	O
's	O
.	O
[	O
Five	O
other	O
cards	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
MARGARET	B-pers
MYHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Garling	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
black	O
lace	O
in	O
our	O
area	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Frankland	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
not	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
Mary	B-pers
Frankland	I-pers
found	O
the	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
PROSECUTOR	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
shutter	O
down	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MULCASTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
with	O
great	O
speed	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
Plunkett	O
was	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
behind	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
PLUNKETT	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
proposed	O
shewing	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
another	O
person	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
MULCASTER	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
running	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
CAPPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Plunkett	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
another	O
box	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
back	O
was	O
turned	O
.	O
MYHAM	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
CAPPER	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
lace	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RANSMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
this	O
Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
lace	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
box	O
down	O
an	O
area	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
run	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
pursued	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
myself	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
lace	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
that	O
lad	O
will	O
swear	O
against	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
.	O
'The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
mother	O
and	O
another	O
'other	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
'	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
524.	O
JOHN	B-pers
VOZEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
laced	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Bursell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6th	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
BURSELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
Jolly	B-place
Coopers	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Short	I-place
's	I-place
Buildings	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
Close	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
first	O
week	O
in	O
March	O
for	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
lodge	O
to	O
treat	O
Mr.	O
Sheldon	B-pers
the	O
turnkey	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
's	O
time	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
hot	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
send	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
lodge	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
for	O
a	O
second	O
pint	O
of	O
hot	O
wine	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
linen	O
we	O
were	O
ironing	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
dry	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
wetting	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
measured	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
to	O
warm	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
by	O
me	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
warm	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
backwards	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
wine	O
was	O
hot	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
wine	O
to	O
the	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
linen	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
Sheldon	O
brought	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
Sheldon	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
ale	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Sheldon	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
man	O
about	O
my	O
robbery	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
drunk	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Sheldon	O
say	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
no	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
answer	O
I	O
made	O
was	O
,	O
this	O
looks	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
wet	O
linen	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
no	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
Sheldon	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
told	O
you	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
wine	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
What	O
did	O
Sheldon	O
say	O
more	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
wine	O
mentioned	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
linen	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SHELDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
turnkey	O
at	O
Clerkenwell-bridewell	O
:	O
one	O
night	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
or	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
gaol	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
used	O
him	O
well	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
fetched	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
drank	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
insist	O
upon	O
my	O
having	O
something	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
red	O
port	O
mulled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
after	O
he	O
drank	O
that	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
pint	O
was	O
out	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
second	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
wish	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
brought	O
the	O
second	O
pint	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
full	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
this	O
day	O
fortnight	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
whenever	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mrs.	O
Bursell	O
say	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Repeat	O
the	O
conversation	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
Mrs.	O
Bursell	O
and	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bursell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bursell	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
gentleman	O
?	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
very	O
stedfastly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
remember	O
being	O
robbed	O
?	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
wine	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
law	O
!	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
recollect	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
nothing	O
else	O
was	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
To	O
BURSELL	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
pint	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
order	O
the	O
second	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
late	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
wished	O
him	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
high	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
waiter	O
at	O
a	O
tavern	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
525	O
,	O
526.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
jam	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ruston	I-pers
,	O
June	O
19th	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
was	O
bleaching	O
on	O
a	O
bush	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
it	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JANE	B-pers
GIBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
hung	O
this	O
jam	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
EDWARD	B-pers
M'CARTY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
near	O
Colbrooke-row	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
thieves	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
gardens	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
lean	O
over	O
into	O
a	O
garden	O
and	O
take	O
some	O
linen	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
jam	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
rag	O
in	O
Wright	O
's	O
apron	O
;	O
Jones	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
JONES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Wright	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
some	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
bundle	O
lie	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
'The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
'	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
527.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Flowers	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
22d	O
.	O
'There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
528.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Francis	B-pers
Lowndes	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
June	O
9th	O
.	O
'There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
'prisoner	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
529	O
,	O
530	O
,	O
531	O
,	O
532.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CONNOR	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
JAMES	I-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	O
MAJOR	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDRIAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
EDERYN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
CORBET	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
HILL	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
containing	O
384	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
110	O
l.	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
pea-green	O
silk	O
barred	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
warrant	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
signed	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
and	O
purporting	O
to	O
bear	O
date	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
1776	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
did	O
authorize	O
and	O
warrant	O
Messrs.	O
Boldero	O
,	O
Barnston	O
,	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
Snaith	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Caron	O
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
warrant	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
committing	O
the	O
felony	O
aforesaid	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
sum	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
payable	O
and	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
warrant	O
being	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
the	O
proprietor	O
thereof	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
2d	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
three	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
,	O
containing	O
384	O
yards	O
,	O
being	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Raven-row	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
:	O
upon	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
whole	O
pieces	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
?	O
-	O
Generally	O
about	O
70	O
yards	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
piece	O
;	O
the	O
six	O
pieces	O
contained	O
380	O
odd	O
yards	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
peagreen	O
silk	O
barred	O
with	O
silver	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
silk	O
died	O
black	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
draught	O
upon	O
my	O
banker	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
banker	O
?	O
-	O
Boldero	O
,	O
Barnston	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
No	O
5	O
,	O
Mansionhouse-street	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
2	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
certain	O
of	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
them	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
foreman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
six	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
,	O
Hanway-yard	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
nothing	O
else	O
but	O
the	O
draught	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
draught	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Connor	O
;	O
the	O
silk	O
has	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Stellings	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
head	O
man	O
is	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
draught	O
produced	O
by	O
Heley	O
;	O
)	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
draught	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
The	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
produced	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
so	O
positively	O
to	O
as	O
my	O
man	O
can	O
;	O
these	O
answer	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
measure	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
where	O
your	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
through	O
the	O
yard	O
into	O
a	O
lobby	O
where	O
the	O
work-people	O
are	O
served	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
broke	O
through	O
another	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
two	O
holes	O
through	O
each	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
one	O
was	O
large	O
enough	O
to	O
get	O
their	O
arm	O
through	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
over	O
where	O
the	O
bolts	O
were	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
BREDELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
;	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
sister	O
was	O
up	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knows	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
after	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
the	O
warehouse	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
formerly	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
that	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
fastened	O
up	O
the	O
lobby	O
where	O
they	O
broke	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
fastened	O
that	O
up	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
at	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
discovered	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
lock	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
off	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
whole	O
and	O
locked	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
entered	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
all	O
in	O
confusion	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
the	O
lobby	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
holes	O
cut	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
two	O
bolts	O
and	O
a	O
lock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
over	O
the	O
lock	O
that	O
commands	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
cut	O
in	O
like	O
manner	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
whole	O
when	O
you	O
locked	O
it	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
next	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
till	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
draught	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
lay	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
left	O
I	O
should	O
want	O
cash	O
in	O
his	O
absence	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
draught	O
,	O
I	O
recollect	O
it	O
perfectly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
silks	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
well	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
with	O
a	O
black-lead	O
pencil	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
20	O
lb	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
silk	O
died	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
pea-green	O
silk	O
,	O
barred	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
two	O
pounds	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
cash	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
over	O
night	O
:	O
the	O
silks	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
,	O
the	O
draught	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
advertisements	O
and	O
handbills	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ELAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk-mercer	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
information	O
of	O
these	O
silks	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
evening	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
tabbies	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
tabbies	O
very	O
often	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
these	O
black	O
silks	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
open	O
,	O
not	O
rolled	O
;	O
these	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
them	O
me	O
a	O
Jobb	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
all	O
together	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
before	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
struck	O
me	O
that	O
these	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
had	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Stellings	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
silks	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
ELAM	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Stellings	O
what	O
goods	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
buy	O
silks	O
cheaper	O
than	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
them	O
,	O
joking	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
goods	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
happy	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
blamed	O
myself	O
then	O
for	O
not	O
having	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
silks	O
till	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
JACOB	B-pers
WORTHY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
silks	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Edrian	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
ribband	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
weaver	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Major	O
Baker	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Still	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Corbet	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Still	O
then	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Or	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
produced	O
]	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Still	O
and	O
Baker	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
That	O
you	O
had	O
from	O
Edrian	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
is	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
then	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
was	O
not	O
delivered	O
till	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
paid	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
it	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
till	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edrian	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elam	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
loose	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
measured	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
folded	O
,	O
not	O
upon	O
rolls	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
silks	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
silks	O
worth	O
to	O
a	O
wholesale	O
dealer	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
ready	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
Major	O
Baker	O
and	O
Still	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
surprized	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
his	O
buying	O
these	O
silks	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
low	O
price	O
;	O
but	O
knowing	O
him	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WORTHY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Edrian	O
and	O
Baker	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Still	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Did	O
Baker	O
come	O
with	O
Edrian	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Edrian	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
Baker	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
is	O
85	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
not	O
that	O
a	O
mistake	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Still	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
his	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Still	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Edrian	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Edrian	O
,	O
Baker	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
Still	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
Baker	O
and	O
Edrian	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
passed	O
that	O
gave	O
you	O
to	O
understand	O
what	O
Baker	O
and	O
Still	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
wrote	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
CROSS	O
EXAMINATION	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Worthy	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
call	O
Still	O
tell	O
you	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Corbet	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Corbet	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Still	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
sold	O
Edrian	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
shewing	O
him	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
act	O
as	O
clerk	O
to	O
justice	O
Clark	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
magistrate	O
for	O
this	O
county	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
name	O
,	O
Major	O
Baker	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
write	O
Still	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
receipt	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
7	O
,	O
Holywell-row	O
,	O
Moorfields	O
:	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
somebody	O
threw	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Corbet	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Still	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
narrow	O
branch	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
bind	O
a	O
boy	O
apprentice	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Corbet	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
strip	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
jobb	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
write	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
mantua	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
on	O
to	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
wrong	O
,	O
it	O
contained	O
380	O
odd	O
yards	O
,	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
tore	O
that	O
off	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
indite	O
the	O
bill	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
Edrian	O
bought	O
of	O
Still	O
,	O
word	O
for	O
word	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
lent	O
a	O
person	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cast	O
up	O
the	O
contents	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
cast	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
it	O
up	O
myself	O
.	O
You	O
wrote	O
all	O
but	O
Major	O
Baker	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
write	O
Major	O
Baker	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Still	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
directed	O
to	O
put	O
Baker	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
understand	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
sellers	O
or	O
one	O
seller	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
seller	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
neither	O
buyer	O
nor	O
seller	O
could	O
write	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
Corbet	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
WORTHY	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Still	O
.	O
CROSS	O
EXAMINATION	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
Corbet	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
what	O
you	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
your	O
situation	O
as	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
high	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Smith	O
alias	O
Connor	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
fob	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
draught	O
.	O
You	O
found	O
nothing	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
that	O
draught	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
advertisement	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
exactly	O
tallied	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
Smith	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
answer	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
bill	O
was	O
produced	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
asked	O
who	O
could	O
prove	O
Still	O
's	O
hand-writiting	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
Corbet	O
did	O
not	O
write	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
he	O
can	O
write	O
only	O
a	O
mere	O
scrawl	O
.	O
CONNOR	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
note	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
Fields	O
.	O
For	O
CONNOR	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wells-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Connor	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
tall	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
brown	O
cloaths	O
with	O
the	O
white	O
buttons	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
inn	O
Fields	O
any	O
time	O
in	O
June	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
pick	O
up	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
draught	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
about	O
Wednesday	O
fortnight	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
name	O
was	O
Boldero	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
drawn	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
read	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
CROSS	O
EXAMINATION	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
surprized	O
at	O
his	O
good	O
fo	O
rtune	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
advise	O
him	O
to	O
restore	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
drop	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
upon	O
my	O
conscience	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
coming	O
from	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Wells-street	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
by	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
You	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
walked	O
through	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
Fields	O
;	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
Fields	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
Duke's-street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
the	O
Holborn-row	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
draught	O
printed	O
or	O
wrote	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
it	O
was	O
copper-plate	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
very	O
well	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
copper-plate	O
and	O
soiled	O
.	O
You	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
to	O
partake	O
of	O
his	O
good	O
luck	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
payable	O
,	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
or	O
order	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
bearer	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
mentioned	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
the	O
good	O
luck	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
home	O
about	O
his	O
good	O
luck	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
read	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
write	O
very	O
well	O
?	O
-	O
Legible	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
understood	O
.	O
(	O
Writes	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
draught	O
payable	O
to	O
bearer	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
I	O
remember	O
right	O
to	O
some	O
particular	O
person	O
or	O
bearer	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
this	O
good	O
luck	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gaol	O
of	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
mentioned	O
this	O
good	O
luck	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
nor	O
talked	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
halves	O
sometimes	O
claimed	O
in	O
such	O
cases	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
claim	O
no	O
share	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
day	O
did	O
he	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
or	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
lodger	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
let	O
lodgings	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
EDRIAN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
goods	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
two	O
people	O
in	O
Spittalfields	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
broker	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
often	O
employed	O
me	O
before	O
.	O
FOR	O
EDRIAN	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WHITEWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Edrian	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
formerly	O
kept	O
an	O
inn	O
at	O
Coventry	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
sell	O
narrow	O
ribbond	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
employed	O
by	O
several	O
people	O
to	O
sell	O
goods	O
for	O
them	O
as	O
a	O
broker	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
goods	O
by	O
commission	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
five	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
and	O
sometimes	O
seven	O
and	O
half	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
exceeded	O
that	O
.	O
Edrian	O
called	O
six	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BAKER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
Phillips	O
in	O
Spittalfields	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gibraltar	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
silks	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
whom	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
Lipe	O
Lyons	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
71	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
lot	O
of	O
damaged	O
goods	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
damaged	O
goods	O
;	O
they	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
trod	O
upon	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
65	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
a	O
40	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
Corbet	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Gibraltar	O
to	O
bargain	O
for	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
bring	O
them	O
away	O
:	O
my	O
brother	O
did	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
any	O
thing	O
nigh	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
.	O
FOR	O
BAKER	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
yesterday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
bargain	O
for	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
help	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Gibraltar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
one	O
Phillips	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
him	O
Lipe	O
Lyons	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
punch	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
brother	O
pay	O
a	O
30	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
punch	O
,	O
and	O
Phillips	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
receipt	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Phillips	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
CORBET	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
Baker	O
14	O
guineas	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
some	O
goods	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
Worthy	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
without	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
;	O
Baker	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
bill	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
write	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
it	O
wrote	O
,	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hobbs	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
;	O
when	O
Worthy	O
came	O
and	O
presented	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
interest	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Corbet	O
called	O
eight	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
To	O
John	B-pers
Worthy	I-pers
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Still	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
writing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Still	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
those	O
goods	O
to	O
Edrian	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
For	O
CONNOR	O
otherwise	O
SMITH	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
FINCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
lodges	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lie	O
at	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lie	O
at	O
home	O
the	O
24th	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
six	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
eight	O
nights	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sickly	O
man	O
;	O
nobody	O
can	O
go	O
out	O
without	O
my	O
knowing	O
:	O
I	O
generally	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
tea	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
tea	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
smuggler	O
.	O
CONNOR	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
BAKER	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
receiving	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
EDRIAN	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
CORBET	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
receiving	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
533	O
,	O
534.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GILHAM	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
containing	O
30	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
June	O
28th	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
Persian	O
silk	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
silk	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
missed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
found	O
his	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
535.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OLIVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
of	O
paint	O
,	O
called	O
Persian	O
blue	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
pounds	O
of	O
paint	O
called	O
king	O
's	O
yellow	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Topping	I-pers
,	O
June	O
24th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TOPPING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
manufacturer	O
of	O
colours	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
some	O
colours	O
;	O
I	O
weighed	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
yellow	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
six	O
pounds	O
wanting	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JERMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Eyre-street-hill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
any	O
colour	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
one	O
Parker	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
appointed	O
him	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
in	O
Angel-alley	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
paint	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
Parker	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
paint	O
was	O
blue	O
and	O
yellow	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
of	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
of	O
yellow	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
for	O
selling	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
I	O
:	O
thought	O
from	O
his	O
giving	O
us	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
piece	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Topping	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MANWARING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Topping	O
came	O
to	O
justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
Rider	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Topping	O
asked	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
wicked	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
farther	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
of	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
pounds	O
of	O
yellow	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
promises	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
confession	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
536.	O
JANE	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
callico	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3d	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
537.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WICKSPEAR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
riband	O
containing	O
14	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8th	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
riband	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
several	O
drawers	O
of	O
riband	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
at	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
her	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
broad	O
green	O
riband	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
riband	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PEARSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
Jane	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
about	O
ten	O
doors	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
lift	O
up	O
her	O
arm	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
riband	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
riband	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
538.	O
MARY	B-pers
CROSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heathfield	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATHFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tinplate-worker	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bed-curtain	O
off	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
;	O
the	O
breeches	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Lee	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
proof	O
;	O
she	O
afterwards	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
breeches	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
promise	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
'	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brodie	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
'the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
'in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
'for	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
'	O
SARAH	B-pers
SCALLOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
found	O
the	O
breeches	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
confessed	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
Mr.	O
Heathfield	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
confessed	O
taking	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
this	O
promise	O
.	O
'She	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
'the	O
prosecutor	O
promised	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
her	O
.	O
'	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
539.	O
JAMES	B-pers
QUICK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
white	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
stone	O
bottle	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarts	O
of	O
linseed	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
10th	O
.	O
'The	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
'not	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
colours	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
540	O
,	O
541.	O
JOHN	B-pers
M'COUL	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
June	O
9th	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
at	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Hampstead-road	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
single-horse	O
chaise	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
myself	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
near	O
Fig-lane	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
distance	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
apprehend	O
any	O
danger	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
foot	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
they	O
divided	O
,	O
two	O
came	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
stopped	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
some	O
words	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
the	O
chaise	O
curtain	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
was	O
drawn	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
a	O
baddish	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
vapoured	O
their	O
cutlasses	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
hat	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
those	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
clear	O
view	O
of	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
curtain	O
was	O
drawn	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
20	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
horse	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
had	O
cutlasses	O
.	O
What	O
light	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
light	O
that	O
I	O
distinguished	O
them	O
at	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
a	O
face	O
at	O
that	O
distance	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
Davis	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
face	O
the	O
light	O
might	O
deceive	O
me	O
.	O
Might	O
it	O
not	O
deceive	O
you	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
Davis	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
it	O
might	O
deceive	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
deceive	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
exceedingly	O
like	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
Davis	O
's	O
voice	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
You	O
bloody	O
dog	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
voice	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
might	O
be	O
deceived	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
might	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
two	O
people	O
that	O
stopped	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
one	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
horse	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
on	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
's	O
side	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
