TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
1776	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAWBRIDGE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
REVISED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
BY	O
JOHN	B-pers
GLYNN	I-pers
,	O
SERJEANT	O
AT	O
LAW	O
,	O
AND	O
RECORDER	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
;	O
FOR	O
EDWARD	O
AND	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DILLY	I-pers
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
SAWBRIDGE	O
,	O
MAYOR	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
Common	O
Council	O
holden	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
Guildhall	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
1775	O
,	O
A	O
MOTION	O
was	O
made	O
and	O
QUESTION	O
put	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
whole	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
be	O
regularly	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
after	O
every	O
Session	O
,	O
published	O
by	O
the	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
authenticated	O
with	O
his	O
Name	O
:	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
resolved	O
in	O
the	O
Affirmative	O
.	O
RIX	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAWBRIDGE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKSTONE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
1st	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Archibald	B-pers
Innes	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Sankson	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pargitter	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodyer	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Badcox	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Stanler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
1st	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
,	O
Packer	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Villers	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Amblin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Britton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Wallin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cambden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Nibbett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shrimpton	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elbro	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Barding	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
]	O
.	O
290.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
STALKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
Burbridge-street	B-place
:	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
which	O
stunned	O
me	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
recollection	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
that	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
knock	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
Burbridge-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
arm	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
and	O
forcible	O
way	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
decoying	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
bad	O
company	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
condition	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
that	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
291.	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hammer-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TOWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
:	O
this	O
hammer-cloth	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
chariot	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
coach-house	O
in	O
Temple-mews	B-place
upon	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
missing	O
till	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
chariot	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BURGESS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
this	O
Saturday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Holborn	O
enquiring	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
coach	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
first	O
for	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
afterwards	O
for	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
therefore	O
suspecting	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
I	O
there	O
put	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
hammer-cloth	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
there	O
now.	O
``	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PANTIN	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
and	O
confirmed	O
``	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
``	O
offering	O
the	O
hammer-cloth	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
''	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
now	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
292.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JEFFERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ragsdale	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
February	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
RAGSDALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
Bond-street	B-place
:	O
upon	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
masquerade	O
at	O
the	O
Pantheon	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
dressed	O
very	O
genteel	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sword	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
borrowing	O
some	O
jewels	O
for	O
the	O
masquerade	O
;	O
he	O
fixed	O
upon	O
a	O
diamond	O
button	O
to	O
be	O
borrowed	O
for	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
ring	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
button	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
large	O
house	O
,	O
No	O
16	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
:	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Hanover-square	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
houses	O
were	O
not	O
numbered	O
in	O
Hanover-square	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
:	O
my	O
daughter	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
missed	O
this	O
ring	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
had	O
bespoke	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
black	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
sword	O
on	O
.	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
upon	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
dressed	O
in	O
black	O
with	O
a	O
sword	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
advanced	O
him	O
nine	O
guineas	O
upon	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
ring	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
]	O
.	O
HARRIOT	O
RAGSDALE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
ring	O
in	O
the	O
show-box	O
upon	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
:	O
the	O
box	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
was	O
usually	O
kept	O
locked	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
One	O
Captain	O
Mansell	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
ring	O
on	O
that	O
evening	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
complaining	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
money	O
;	O
Captain	O
Mansell	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
way	O
of	O
supplying	O
me	O
but	O
letting	O
me	O
have	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
raise	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
has	O
said	O
:	O
Captain	O
Mansell	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
regiment	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
I	O
believe	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kingdom	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
witness	O
is	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
293.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Bath	O
beaver	O
scarlet	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clinkard	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLINKARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
box	O
in	O
which	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
paper-stainer	O
by	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
Day	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
accused	O
of	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
]	O
:	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
294.	O
EMANUEL	B-pers
COWEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sardonyx	O
stone	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cameo	O
stone	O
unset	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jenkin	O
,	O
February	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
JENKIN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
toyman	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James's-street	I-place
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
cornelian	O
stones	O
unset	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
tumbled	O
them	O
over	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
lad	O
could	O
not	O
fix	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
no	O
good	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
purchasing	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
nine	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
my	O
master	O
missed	O
the	O
seals	O
.	O
JENKIN	O
JONES	O
.	O
A	O
week	O
or	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
this	O
fifteenth	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
rights	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
seals	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
sardonyx	O
with	O
the	O
figure	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
another	O
a	O
white	O
cornelian	O
;	O
I	O
advertized	O
these	O
two	O
rings	O
;	O
hearing	O
the	O
account	O
my	O
lad	O
gave	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
effect	O
from	O
that	O
advertisement	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
Monday	O
my	O
lad	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
toyshops	O
about	O
;	O
going	O
through	O
Russell-court	O
I	O
obseryed	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Spicer	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
seal	O
engraver	O
,	O
the	O
sardonyx	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
immediately	O
charged	O
these	O
seals	O
as	O
being	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Spicer	O
's	O
lad	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
seal	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
gave	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
father	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
NEHEMIAH	O
SPICER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seal	O
engraver	O
in	O
Russell-court	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
offered	O
two	O
seals	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
a	O
white	O
cornelian	O
and	O
a	O
double	O
seal	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
sardonyx	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
little	O
onyx	O
that	O
was	O
unset	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
only	O
the	O
sardonyx	O
and	O
the	O
onyx	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
sardonyx	O
,	O
four	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
onyx	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
much	O
under	O
the	O
mark	O
;	O
the	O
sardonyx	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
forty	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
onyx	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
two	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
the	O
sardonyx	O
as	O
set	O
.	O
Mr.	O
SPICER	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
window	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
challenged	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
:	O
my	O
lad	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bond-street	O
upon	O
some	O
other	O
affair	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
295	O
,	O
296.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COCKIN	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MILES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LAKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
then	O
through	O
the	O
Green	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Constitution-hill	B-place
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
in	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
country	O
dialect	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
compliment	O
and	O
wished	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
several	O
distinct	O
voices	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
came	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
mended	O
my	O
pace	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
perceived	O
two	O
men	O
walking	O
before	O
me	O
very	O
slow	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
hearing	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
nudged	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
his	O
elbow	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
made	O
an	O
opening	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
walk	O
between	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
between	O
them	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
hit	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
breast	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
a	O
hard	O
blow	O
that	O
frighten	O
'd	O
me	O
pretty	O
much	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Stop	O
``	O
and	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
God	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
``	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
''	O
that	O
man	O
produced	O
a	O
horse	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
held	O
a	O
bayonet	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
who	O
wished	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
Miles	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
stature	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hat	O
flapp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
not	O
taken	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
while	O
this	O
conversation	O
was	O
going	O
forwards	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
``	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
strip	O
him	O
:	O
''	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
coat	O
(	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
off	O
they	O
tore	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sleeves	O
almost	O
off	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
brown	O
surtout	O
coat	O
;	O
Miles	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
that	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
perceived	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
which	O
was	O
tucked	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
by	O
``	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
''	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
thus	O
struggling	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
dropped	O
a	O
bundle	O
which	O
contained	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
drab-colour	O
'd	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
and	O
stock	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
breeches	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
home	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
Miles	O
staid	O
behind	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
``	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
``	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
protested	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
``	O
D	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
:	O
''	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Heley	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
attend	O
that	O
office	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
another	O
:	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Miles	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
over	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
shoulder	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
money	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
charged	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
Heley	O
immediately	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
breast	O
pocket	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
horse	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
his	O
fob	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
drew	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
charged	O
very	O
high	O
with	O
five	O
slugs	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Cockin	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Stokes	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Tothil-street	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Steele	O
's	O
,	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
Lake	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Steele	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stokes	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
coat	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Stokes	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
parlor	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
Miles	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
breeches	O
and	O
asked	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
Lake	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
immediately	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
breast	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
slugs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
breeches	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
frivolous	O
excuses	O
:	O
in	O
searching	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
slugs	O
and	O
some	O
powder	O
and	O
ball	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Ambery	O
I	O
met	O
Cockin	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
coat	O
which	O
Lake	O
had	O
described	O
;	O
Cockin	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
bayonets	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
each	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
powder	O
,	O
a	O
musket	O
ball	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
slugs	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ball	O
.	O
LAKE	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Cockin	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
passed	O
me	O
on	O
Constitution-hill	O
and	O
wished	O
me	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
but	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
COCKIN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
possession	O
of	O
that	O
bayonet	O
and	O
coat	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
appeared	O
upon	O
inspection	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
marked	O
]	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
this	O
bundle	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
were	O
all	O
bound	O
up	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
FOR	O
MILES	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
Miles	O
quartered	O
with	O
me	O
several	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
and	O
never	O
laid	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
quarters	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
Cockin	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
regiment	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
COCKIN	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
MILES	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
297.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
and	O
procuring	O
to	O
be	O
falsely	O
made	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
note	O
called	O
a	O
promisory	O
note	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
Henry	B-pers
M'Annully	I-pers
,	O
which	O
note	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
20th	O
Jan.	O
1775	O
,	O
four	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Arthur	B-pers
McAnnully	I-pers
or	O
order	O
133	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
May	O
23d	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
note	O
a	O
forgery	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
298.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
capt	O
and	O
jewell	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
seven	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
studs	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
ear	O
rings	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Bristol	O
stone	O
stay	O
hook	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
eighteen	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
white	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
gauze	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
linen	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
children	O
's	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
linen	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cheque	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
lawn	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
salted	O
leg	O
of	O
pork	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
undertaker	O
in	O
Chiswel-street	B-place
,	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
:	O
upon	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
about	O
eight	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
near	O
my	O
door	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
he	O
blew	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
pork	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
candle	O
run	O
the	O
candle	O
into	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
disconcerted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
who	O
promised	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
held	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
lock	O
tied	O
back	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
spring	O
lock	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
double	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
crow	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hook	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
hinge	O
hung	O
had	O
been	O
forced	O
out	O
and	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
staple	O
it	O
locks	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
examine	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
were	O
laid	O
empty	O
upon	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
my	O
bureau	O
up	O
stairs	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
cash	O
and	O
cloaths	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
cloaths	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Reynolds	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
the	O
leg	O
of	O
pork	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
bundle	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
inventory	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
bundle	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
back	O
to	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
The	O
witness	O
read	O
the	O
inventory	O
,	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
and	O
linen	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
REYNOLDS	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
bundle	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
looked	O
it	O
over	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
satisfied	O
it	O
contains	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
now	O
as	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
it	O
was	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
dark	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
dark	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
sun	O
went	O
down	O
then	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
-	O
REYNOLDS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
drawers	O
at	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
safe	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
is	O
mistaken	O
in	O
saying	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
299	O
,	O
300.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RUSSELL	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixty-three	O
guineas	O
,	O
ten	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
crowns	O
,	O
forty	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
two	O
French	O
crowns	O
,	O
value	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
French	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gabert	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
``	O
was	O
a	O
confession	O
deposed	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
``	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
justices	O
of	O
the	O
``	O
peace	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
witness	O
``	O
who	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
swore	O
he	O
``	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
heard	O
:	O
but	O
another	O
``	O
witness	O
swore	O
that	O
was	O
totally	O
false	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
``	O
he	O
only	O
carried	O
a	O
candle	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
``	O
came	O
out	O
immediately	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
301.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LONG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
committing	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
302.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LAWTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noble	O
Augustus	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Grafton	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
BENEDICT	B-pers
SCALLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Grafton	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
's	O
in	O
Half	B-place
Moon-street	I-place
that	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
copper	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
put	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Half	O
Moon-street	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
some	O
one	O
was	O
breaking	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
of	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Grafton	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
copper	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hole	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
brickwork	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
there	O
to	O
lie	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
squabble	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
303.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FARLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mare	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
``	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
``	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
``	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
mare	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fetched	O
``	O
the	O
mare	O
from	O
the	O
stable	O
agreeable	O
to	O
that	O
``	O
man	O
's	O
directions	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
evidence	O
that	O
another	O
man	O
left	O
the	O
mare	O
``	O
at	O
that	O
stable	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
further	O
,	O
that	O
``	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
his	O
fellow	O
``	O
servant	O
had	O
hanged	O
himself	O
.	O
''	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
304.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
KNOWLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
coach	O
hammer-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
NORTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach	O
maker	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
hammer-cloth	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
a	O
coach	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
skulking	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
steal	O
something	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlor	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
the	O
hammer-cloth	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Holland-street	O
with	O
the	O
hammer-cloth	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
DAKIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shop	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
cross	O
Oxford-street	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Holland-street	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
hammer-cloth	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
]	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
two	O
young	O
fellows	O
pushed	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
nearly	O
have	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
they	O
shoved	O
down	O
this	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
305	O
,	O
306.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
FINISS	I-pers
and	O
BRIDGET	B-pers
SHERIFF	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
eleven	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
truss	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
``	O
According	O
to	O
the	O
evidence	O
upon	O
the	O
trial	O
``	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
a	O
truss	O
``	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
another	O
in	O
``	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
and	O
replaced	O
it	O
.	O
''	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
307.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BALDWIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
till	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
lock	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
492	O
half	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
255	O
farthings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Burrows	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BURROWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hoxton-market-place	B-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
my	O
till	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
contained	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
half	O
pence	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BURROWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
lie	O
over	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
got	O
the	O
till	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
directly	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
till	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
people	O
were	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
-	O
SPENCE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
bringing	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
ran	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
they	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
308.	O
SARAH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goldwell	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
``	O
A	O
witness	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
``	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
only	O
``	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
stuff	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
``	O
but	O
rather	O
than	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
should	O
``	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
309.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MORAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Luke	B-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
oil	O
and	O
colourman	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
porter	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
money	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
my	O
master	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
mark	O
a	O
guinea	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
marked	O
six	O
pence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
counted	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
marked	O
ones	O
that	O
were	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
White	O
.	O
]	O
ANN	B-pers
HOW	I-pers
,	O
fellow	O
servant	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
confirmed	O
his	O
evidence	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
RAYNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
picked	O
out	O
three	O
marked	O
shillings	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
kitchen	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
owner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
difference	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
marked	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
310	O
,	O
311.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAGUE	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BURR	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
Prigmore	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
three	O
plain	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-one	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
garnet	O
stone	O
rings	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
stone	O
mourning	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-one	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
laced	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
stone	O
fluted	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
proof	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
depended	O
wholly	O
``	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
:	O
to	O
invalidate	O
``	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
the	O
headborough	O
of	O
``	O
Whitechapel	O
parish	O
who	O
knew	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
``	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
drunk	O
``	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
``	O
and	O
was	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
``	O
opinion	O
that	O
she	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
believed	O
``	O
upon	O
her	O
oath	O
.	O
''	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
312.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
BOWDEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gascoigne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
HOGGARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gascoigne	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
fetched	O
the	O
tea	O
tongs	O
from	O
the	O
silversmith	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gascoigne	O
:	O
the	O
tea	O
tongs	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
dressing	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
besides	O
him	O
except	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
and	O
I.	O
JOHN	O
SALKELD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
tea	O
tongs	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Hoggard	O
and	O
Morgan	O
.	O
]	O
HOGGARD	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
313.	O
SARAH	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cheque	O
chair	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cushion	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
round	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
thread	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
three	O
fillets	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
crowns	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
one	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
one	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOODMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
,	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
are	O
in	O
court	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
by	O
such	O
employment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
tied	O
up	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
in	O
Gouge-street	O
,	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
till	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
fire	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
master	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bundle	O
opened	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
inventory	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
,	O
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
tied	O
up	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
beadle	O
:	O
a	O
fire	O
happened	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
places	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
;	O
the	O
floor	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
was	O
burnt	O
quite	O
through	O
to	O
the	O
joists	O
,	O
the	O
bed	O
post	O
up	O
stairs	O
was	O
burnt	O
almost	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
mattrass	O
was	O
burnt	O
away	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
Goodman	O
brought	O
the	O
bundle	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
's	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
it	O
contained	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
inventory	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
inventory	O
myself	O
and	O
gave	O
another	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
a	O
thread	O
purse	O
containing	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
crowns	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
a	O
medal	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
six	O
pences	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
three	O
pence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
young	O
,	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
fair	O
and	O
open	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
mention	O
it	O
in	O
court	O
in	O
her	O
favour	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WEAVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Lambeth	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
gardener	O
's	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
mistress	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
leave	O
a	O
bed	O
there	O
till	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Goodman	O
she	O
said	O
should	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
bed	O
out	O
of	O
Bond-street	O
who	O
was	O
dead	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
cousin	O
who	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
Wales	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
helped	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
fetched	O
Goodman	O
,	O
and	O
engaged	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
,	O
Gouge-street	O
,	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Goodman	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SIMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
lining	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet	O
maker	O
,	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
succeeded	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
coachmaker	O
's	O
stock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
lining	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SALTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
the	O
table	O
linen	O
and	O
counterpane	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
working	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hatch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
maliciously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
314.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
JOHN	I-pers
MURRELL	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
child	O
's	O
silk	O
bonnets	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
tippet	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SANDFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
;	O
my	O
husband	O
lives	O
in	O
Roll's-buildings	B-place
,	I-place
Fetter-lane	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
carry	O
my	O
husband	O
his	O
supper	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cradle	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
afterwards	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
bundle	O
opened	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
opened	O
and	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
upon	O
my	O
asking	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DANIEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sandford	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
word	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Sandford	O
came	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
cloak	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
meant	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
when	O
I	O
could	O
redeem	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
315	O
,	O
316.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FERRELL	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STEPHENS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
SHERMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
school	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
a	O
servant	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
three	O
children	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
ajar	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
within	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Stephens	O
take	O
a	O
bundle	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
ran	O
towards	O
Kingsland	O
road	O
with	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
Stephens	O
ran	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
with	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
but	O
lost	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
girl	O
who	O
was	O
gathering	O
in	O
pots	O
hearing	O
me	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
secured	O
Ferrell	O
who	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
boys	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
gentleman	O
brought	O
in	O
Stephens	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
directly	O
;	O
an	O
officer	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
Stephens	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
notice	O
enough	O
of	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
bundle	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
bundle	O
down	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
stockings	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
STEPHENS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
garters	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PROSECUTION	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Stephens	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Stephens	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
FERRELL	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
STEPHENS	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
317	O
,	O
318.	O
SARAH	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
VAUGHAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allanson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ALLANSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
mercer	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Church-yard	I-place
:	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
missed	O
silks	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
for	O
eighteen	O
months	O
past	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
detected	O
the	O
thief	O
till	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Reid	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
that	O
particular	O
piece	O
then	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
REID	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
silk	O
to	O
pledge	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
DAVID	B-pers
JARVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
of	O
Armstrong	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
one	O
piece	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
appeared	O
very	O
genteel	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
being	O
winter	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
till	O
the	O
summer	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
near	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
this	O
other	O
piece	O
of	O
garnet	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Allanson	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
garnet	O
;	O
looking	O
for	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Allanson	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
then	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Allanson	O
.	O
]	O
``	O
GEORGE	B-pers
COLLEY	I-pers
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
``	O
Coney	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
some	O
silk	O
``	O
he	O
received	O
of	O
Armstrong	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PURSE	I-pers
,	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
``	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BANNISTER	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
``	O
apprentice	O
,	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
``	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
``	O
prisoner	O
Armstrong	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
lent	O
her	O
two	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
No	O
2	O
,	O
Craven-court	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
was	O
at	O
sea	O
;	O
that	O
afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Allanson	O
``	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
``	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
''	O
[	O
The	O
several	O
pieces	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
ELIZABETH	O
FEAR	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
these	O
two	O
gowns	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Armstrong	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
tabby	O
and	O
a	O
flowered	O
silk	O
)	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
Christmas	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
brown	O
tabby	O
was	O
some	O
silk	O
a	O
relation	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
ALLANSON	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
flowered	O
silk	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
two	O
gowns	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
dirty	O
linen	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Allanson	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Allanson	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
ARMSTRONG	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
is	O
innocent	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
entirely	O
myself	O
.	O
VAUGHAN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
gowns	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
her	O
transactions	O
.	O
ALLANSON	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
servant	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
ARMSTRONG	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
VAUGHAN	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
319.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Broad-street	B-place
,	I-place
Old	I-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
lay	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
only	O
lain	O
there	O
one	O
night	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
apartment	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
was	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
entering	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
amends.	O
``	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MANWARRING	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	O
``	O
OLDHAM	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
``	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
found	O
the	O
cloaths	O
in	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
''	O
[	O
The	O
cloaths	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
recommend	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
320.	O
MARY	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
OUGHTON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BUCKLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
sheets	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
trunk	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
at	O
length	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
cabin	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
BANNISTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
sheets	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
had	O
Buckley	O
's	O
name	O
at	O
length	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
my	O
own	O
bed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
321.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BANGAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
by	O
New-crane	B-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
which	O
were	O
kept	O
behind	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
concealed	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
four	O
pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
322	O
,	O
323.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STENNY	I-pers
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WHARFE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Belson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
``	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
chimney	O
sweepers	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
chimney	O
had	O
been	O
swept	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
ring	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
``	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
that	O
``	O
swept	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
with	O
``	O
the	O
ring	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
went	O
``	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
``	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
''	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
324.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
against	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
nature	O
)	O
had	O
a	O
certain	O
venereal	O
affair	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
beast	O
called	O
a	O
cow	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
and	O
wickedly	O
against	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
nature	O
did	O
carnally	O
know	O
the	O
said	O
beast	O
called	O
a	O
cow	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
beast	O
called	O
a	O
cow	O
did	O
feloniously	O
and	O
wickedly	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
nature	O
commit	O
and	O
perpetrate	O
the	O
detestable	O
and	O
abominable	O
crime	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
among	O
Christians	O
,	O
called	O
Buggery	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
DENNING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
cook	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
at	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Blue	I-place
Anchor	I-place
,	I-place
Limehouse-marsh	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cow-house	O
serving	O
the	O
cows	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
hayloft	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
a	O
cow	O
we	O
expected	O
to	O
calve	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cow	O
move	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
barn	O
adjoining	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
boarded	O
barn	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
chinks	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
stroking	O
the	O
cow	O
and	O
patting	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
stroking	O
and	O
patting	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
barn	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
tub	O
to	O
put	O
behind	O
the	O
cow	O
,	O
it	O
stood	O
up	O
edgeways	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
tub	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unbutton	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
his	O
trowsers	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
motions	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
motions	O
towards	O
the	O
cow	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
speak	O
out	O
more	O
plain	O
what	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
motions	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hands	O
upon	O
the	O
cow	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
wriggle	O
himself	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
in	O
that	O
posture	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
cow	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hayloft	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
in	O
doors	O
to	O
get	O
somebody	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stand	O
watching	O
him	O
ten	O
minutes	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
John	B-pers
Tumey	I-pers
to	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
again	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
down	O
off	O
the	O
tub	O
and	O
stood	O
behind	O
the	O
cow	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
I	O
could	O
back	O
.	O
What	O
posture	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
His	O
trowsers	O
were	O
down	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
up	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
he	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
came	O
and	O
assisted	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TUMEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
immediately	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
cow	O
hustling	O
his	O
breeches	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
up	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Denning	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Denning	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
cow	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
breeches	O
up	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
to	O
assist	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
LEONARD	B-pers
BOOTH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
and	O
Buckland	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struggling	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
Denning	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
a	O
cow	O
;	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
within	O
doors	O
;	O
when	O
within	O
doors	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
Buckland	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
close	O
together	O
when	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BUCKLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
assist	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
struggling	O
with	O
Denning	O
and	O
Tumey	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
within	O
doors	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
Tumey	O
and	O
I	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Denning	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
confess	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
wrongfully	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
nor	O
charged	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
To	O
BUCKLAND	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
doing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
To	O
BOOTH	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
trowsers	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
ALICE	B-pers
HEADLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
always	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sailor	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BROOKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twelve	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
mates	O
:	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
five	O
children	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
250	O
miles	O
from	O
hence	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
at	O
Shields	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
Griffiths	O
an	O
attorney	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hearing	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
falsely	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
325.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
PENTICROSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-three	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chisholm	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHISHOLM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cow-cross	B-place
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
upon	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
my	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
baker	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
wood	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
helping	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
above	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
twenty-three	O
shillings	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
off	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
money	O
chink	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
wood	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Noble-street	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
by	O
his	O
schoolmaster	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
an	O
halfpenny	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
LANGSTAFF	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
an	O
halfpenny	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
;	O
he	O
accused	O
his	O
mother	O
with	O
having	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
all	O
but	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
he	O
retracted	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
another	O
boy	O
,	O
that	O
proved	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
a	O
rag	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
by	O
the	O
pavement	O
where	O
his	O
father	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
boys	O
carrying	O
in	O
wood	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
terribly	O
frightened	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
326.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BALLETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
accomplice	O
unconnected	O
with	O
any	O
corroborating	O
circumstances	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
327.	O
MARY	B-pers
DOYLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Whelan	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WHELAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Jermyn-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
sadler	O
:	O
last	O
November	O
was	O
twelve-month	O
a	O
fire	O
broke	O
out	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
moving	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
passed	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
and	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
permitted	O
them	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
and	O
confusion	O
many	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
about	O
till	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
constables	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
their	O
directions	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Artz	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ARTZ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
spoon	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Whelan	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
spoon	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
328.	O
VALENTINE	B-pers
FULLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hogs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HARGRAVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Wanstead	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
hogs	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
over	O
night	O
in	O
a	O
coop	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
missing	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
upon	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
before	O
me	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hog	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
stuck	O
but	O
not	O
skinned	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
the	O
hog	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
hog	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
from	O
circumstances	O
I	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
fellow	O
of	O
that	O
hog	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
up	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
it	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
RYDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hog	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
covered	O
with	O
boards	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Hargrave	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
that	O
hog	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
found	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
forth	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hargrave	O
owned	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
entrails	O
of	O
the	O
hog	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
higher	O
by	O
a	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
concealed	O
another	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
hog	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
hogs	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
when	O
taken	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
329.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DRAKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mordaunt	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Whitby	O
,	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
not	O
having	O
separate	O
beds	O
we	O
slept	O
together	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
who	O
missed	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
shoes	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
DEODALUS	O
DEAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
:	O
these	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
evening	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
they	O
weighed	O
an	O
ounce	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
SPENCE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
331.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
GREENWOOD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
180	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
April	O
4th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WHITEHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
great	O
eating-house	O
there	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
1775	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
manner	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
180	O
guineas	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
glove	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
chest	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
bed-chamber	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
safe	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
found	O
my	O
chamber	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
last	O
September	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
means	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
prevail	O
with	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
forthcoming	O
since	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
information	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
by	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
;	O
the	O
chest	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
floor	O
upon	O
the	O
side	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
dined	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
victuals	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
these	O
persons	O
,	O
having	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
till	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
justices	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
induced	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
information	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
against	O
his	O
accomplices	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
accomplice	O
he	O
accused	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
witness	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
here	O
for	O
trial	O
at	O
the	O
September	O
sessions	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
trial	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
absence	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
only	O
took	O
his	O
security	O
for	O
his	O
appearance	O
;	O
the	O
trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
the	O
October	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
but	O
these	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
:	O
the	O
chest	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
talked	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
the	O
particulars	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
exact	O
quantity	O
of	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
chest	O
,	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
glove	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
other	O
particular	O
relating	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WYAT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
dined	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
last	O
April	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
dine	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
company	O
there	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
thus	O
called	O
for	O
their	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
together	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
staid	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
constant	O
customers	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
another	O
fellow-servant	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
was	O
Molly	O
,	O
discovered	O
it	O
first	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
appearance	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
went	O
voluntarily	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
recognizance	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
332.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
eleven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Upsdale	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brickmaker	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Oxford	B-place
