TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
1776	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SECOND	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAWBRIDGE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
REVISED	O
AND	O
PUBLISHED	O
BY	O
JOHN	B-pers
GLYNN	I-pers
,	O
SERJEANT	O
AT	O
LAW	O
,	O
AND	O
RECORDER	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
;	O
FOR	O
EDWARD	O
AND	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DILLY	I-pers
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX	O
PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
SAWBRIDGE	O
,	O
MAYOR	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
Common	O
Council	O
holden	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
Guildhall	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
1775	O
,	O
A	O
MOTION	O
was	O
made	O
and	O
QUESTION	O
put	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
whole	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
be	O
regularly	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
after	O
every	O
Session	O
,	O
published	O
by	O
the	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
authenticated	O
with	O
his	O
Name	O
:	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
resolved	O
in	O
the	O
Affirmative	O
.	O
RIX	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAWBRIDGE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	O
STAFFORD	O
SMYTHE	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Guy	B-pers
Wilbourne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cloak	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Mackerill	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
1st	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hett	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ayriss	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dover	I-pers
,	O
Caesar	O
Hoar	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Almon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
2d	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Tabois	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Figgins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Golton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Angeli	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grinnard	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Capell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ayriss	I-pers
.	O
]	O
112.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
covered	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trent	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
September	O
30th	O
.	O
``	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TRENT	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
``	O
the	O
watches	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
into	O
``	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
``	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
that	O
``	O
upon	O
his	O
return	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
four	O
months	O
afterwards	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
watches	O
were	O
wanting	O
.	O
''	O
[	O
The	O
watches	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Matthew	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
``	O
SWIFT	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
watches	O
were	O
``	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
care	O
at	O
the	O
justices	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
``	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
``	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
advertisement	O
inserted	O
``	O
in	O
the	O
news-paper	O
.	O
''	O
DAVID	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
113.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LEWINGTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
December	O
4th	O
.	O
-	O
KING	O
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
woollen-draper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
draper	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
's	O
Servant	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
.	O
114	O
,	O
115.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRANT	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
BEAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Desormeaux	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
25	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lewis	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
``	O
LEWIS	B-pers
DESORMEAUX	I-pers
,	O
a	O
dyer	O
,	O
in	O
Pearl-street	B-place
,	O
``	O
Spitalfields	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
house	O
``	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
``	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silk	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
indictment	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
''	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
an	O
accomplice	O
unconnected	O
with	O
any	O
corroborating	O
circumstances	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
therefore	O
found	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
.	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Lamb	O
Smith	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
for	O
the	O
same	O
burglary	O
,	O
Number	O
54	O
,	O
55	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Session	O
.	O
116.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HYAM	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
an	O
embroidered	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
mens	O
hats	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
ten-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
``	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHANDLER	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
``	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
``	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
-	O
MANWARING	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
``	O
found	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
``	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
``	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
''	O
It	O
appeared	O
in	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shirt	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
lodging	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
tried	O
for	O
another	O
offence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
.	O
117	O
,	O
118.	O
ISABELLA	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
CROSS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Corson	I-pers
,	O
December	O
5th	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
119.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BARNARD	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
December	O
18th	O
.	O
``	O
MARY	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
(	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
)	O
``	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
lodging	O
``	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
``	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
linen	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
``	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apartments	O
the	O
next	O
``	O
morning	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
PENELOPE	B-pers
GODDARD	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
the	O
``	O
shirts	O
;	O
that	O
suspecting	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
``	O
fairly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
stopt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
``	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
to	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
``	O
peace	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
-	O
CONNOLLY	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
``	O
prisoner	O
voluntarily	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
``	O
justice	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
``	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
120	O
,	O
121.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
M'KENSIE	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
M'KENSIE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13th	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
122.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
GARTHWAITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18th	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recoguizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
123.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OLIVER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
two-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
November	O
20th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LOVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Black	O
Man	O
and	O
Woolpack	O
in	O
Pimlico	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
the	O
prisoner	O
addressed	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
bring	O
to	O
the	O
Queen's-row	O
coffee	O
house	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
beer	O
and	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
very	O
angry	O
for	O
my	O
staying	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
change	O
and	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
another	O
pot	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
two-pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
that	O
pot	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
Friday	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
then	O
Love	O
picked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
amongst	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
people	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
124.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
bags	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
thirty-seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
shoebuckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
59	O
l.	O
twenty-seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
fifteen	O
stone	O
stock-buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
twenty-five	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
garnets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
eight	O
pearl	O
foil-stone	O
rings	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
six	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
garnets	O
and	O
paste	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
cluster	O
rings	O
,	O
paste	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
topaz	O
garnet	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
coloured	O
paste	O
rings	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
sixteen	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
forty-seven	O
metal	O
chains	O
,	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
pebble	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
gold	O
edges	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
sprig	O
mocoa	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
sprig	O
mocoa	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
setin	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
twelve	O
pearl	O
and	O
soil-stone	O
lockets	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
four	O
garnet	O
pearl	O
lockets	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
small	O
garnet	O
lockets	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
thirty-four	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
plain	O
gold	O
lockets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
paste	O
stay	O
hooks	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
,	O
fifteen	O
pair	O
of	O
garnet	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
twenty-one	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
and	O
foil-stone	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
two	O
garnet	O
crosses	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
fancy	O
garnet	O
pearl	O
and	O
foil-stone	O
shirt-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
thirty-eight	O
garnet	O
and	O
paste	O
shirt-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
ninety-five	O
silver	O
thimbles	O
,	O
with	O
steel	O
tops	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
fifty-five	O
foil	O
and	O
paste	O
hair	O
pins	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
forty-two	O
paste	O
shirt-buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
twenty-seven	O
silver	O
tooth	O
pick	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
ear	O
picks	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
dozen	O
of	O
Tasse	O
's	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
forty-two	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
six	O
dozen	O
gold	O
wire	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
twelve	O
plain	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
nineteen	O
fancy	O
lockets	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
nineteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
thirty-two	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
twelve	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
dozen	O
gold	O
hoop	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
twenty	O
eight	O
plain	O
gold	O
shirt-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
forty-two	O
plain	O
silver	O
shirt-buckles	O
.	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
twenty-one	O
morocco	O
pocket-books	O
,	O
with	O
silver	O
locks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
thirty-four	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
oz	O
.	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l	O
11	O
s.	O
one	O
vellum	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Topham	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TOPHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
saddle	O
bags	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
myself	O
in	O
Basing-lane	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
coach	O
from	O
Oxford	O
.	O
The	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
coach	O
would	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
arrive	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Cross	O
,	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
to	O
the	O
Golden-Cross	O
for	O
the	O
bags	O
;	O
the	O
messenger	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
parcel	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
though	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
entered	O
in	O
the	O
way-bill	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
bags	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
some	O
workmen	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
:	O
the	O
bags	O
were	O
cut	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
cards	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
bags	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
bags	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
Goldsmiths-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hand-bills	O
delivered	O
about	O
,	O
offering	O
20	O
l.	O
reward	O
for	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
post	O
to	O
Oxford	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
parcel	O
booked	O
there	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
my	O
pocket	O
ledger	O
,	O
containing	O
some	O
bills	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
on	O
Smallberry-Green	O
.	O
The	O
saddle-bags	O
contained	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
372	O
l.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STILES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
driver	O
of	O
the	O
Oxford	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
outside	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Hats	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
cold	O
wet	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
inside	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
consented	O
to	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Golden-Cross	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
unloaded	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
coach	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
parcel	O
,	O
pointing	O
out	O
a	O
bulky	O
parcel	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
brown	O
paper	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
parcel	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
money	O
upon	O
a	O
hoop	O
ring	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
asking	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
seached	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
claimed	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
hoop	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
trinkets	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
'S	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Burnt	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
125	O
,	O
126.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
RANDALL	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREENWOOD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Peter	B-pers
Planch	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
,	O
December	O
5th	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
PLANCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
play	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
and	O
I	O
accompanying	O
the	O
young	O
lady	O
home	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
were	O
overtaken	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
when	O
Randall	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
Greenwood	O
stood	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
Randall	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
and	O
demanded	O
more	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
pocket	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
:	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
Randall	O
turn	O
and	O
hold	O
the	O
money	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
moon	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
now	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Planch	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
moonlight	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
their	O
persons	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
LEVY	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
RANDALL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
GREENWOOD	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
particular	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
topaz	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
green-silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
December	O
10th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
WALSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
lighting	O
and	O
leading	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
from	O
Tottenham-court-road	B-place
to	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
is	O
almost	O
blind	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
stopt	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
presented	O
a	O
sword	O
,	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
bid	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
deliver	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
containing	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
gave	O
them	O
his	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
had	O
something	O
bulky	O
tucked	O
in	O
at	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
``	O
LEVIMOSES	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
``	O
the	O
bar	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
``	O
had	O
them	O
secured	O
.	O
''	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
127.	O
EMANUEL	B-pers
POLOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
topaz	O
and	O
eight	O
other	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
another	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
mocoa	O
stone	O
and	O
thirteen	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
and	O
silversmith	O
in	O
the	B-place
Minories	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
ring	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
shew-glass	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
case	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
taking	O
out	O
that	O
ring	O
,	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
two	O
rings	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
rings	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
any	O
truth	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
128.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
December	O
21st	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
pull	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
or	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SPENCERFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
before	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
129.	O
MARY	B-pers
READ	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
sattin	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
three	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
fourteen	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
nine	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
muslin	O
peckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buckles	O
;	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
nine	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty-seven	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mathias	B-pers
Hamburg	I-pers
,	O
December	O
25th	O
.	O
MATHIAS	B-pers
HAMBURG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
10.	I-place
in	I-place
Salisbury-court	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
delivered	O
into	O
her	O
care	O
:	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
theft	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
involved	O
in	O
debt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
mercy	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
hang	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
deprive	O
me	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FLEMING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hair-pin	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
QUINCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
here	O
are	O
three	O
gowns	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
sheets	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
in	O
November	O
and	O
December	O
1774	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
in	O
February	O
1775	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
likewise	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
130.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
COLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
December	O
27th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
belonging	O
to	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
tied	O
round	O
her	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GATES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pots	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pots	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
131.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
December	O
28th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
NEWSOM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
upon	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
cheapened	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
having	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
Edward	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
coat	O
that	O
hung	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
ran	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
fell	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
132.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shingley	I-pers
,	O
December	O
30th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHINGLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
Saturday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
threw	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
companion	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
missed	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
133.	O
HENRY	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
love	O
riband	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty	O
six	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty-one	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-four	O
shillings	O
,	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
mittens	O
,	O
value	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
velvet	O
riband	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
gross	O
of	O
shirt	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
,	O
Jervis	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
,	O
December	O
18th	O
.	O
JARVIS	B-pers
CHAMBERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
co-partnership	O
with	O
Stephen	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
porter	O
:	O
having	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
a	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
person	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
goods	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
our	O
goods	O
.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
INGRAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
there	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
CHAMBERS	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
our	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOLYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Messrs	O
.	O
Chambers	O
and	O
Langston	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
the	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
now	O
produced	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
134	O
,	O
135.	O
MAXWELL	B-pers
BLACKMORE	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Eggleton	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
,	O
December	O
24th	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
EGGLETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
glass-house	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Saltpetre	B-place
Bank	I-place
on	O
the	O
24th	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
pistols	O
about	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
Hall	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
me	O
;	O
Blackmore	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe-buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
very	O
plain	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
them	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
people	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
thought	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
whispered	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
to	O
another	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
Prussian	O
Hero	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
Blackmore	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
steaks	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
more	O
help	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
Blackmore	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
Blackmore	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
Hall	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
we	O
took	O
Blackmore	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Prussian	O
Hero	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
Blackmore	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
of	O
justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
men	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
Blackmore	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
saw	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
Blackmore	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
light	O
near	O
when	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Hall	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
close	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
cut	O
in	O
his	O
eye	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
justice	O
Camper	O
's	O
men	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
Hall	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
twenty	O
yards	O
distance	O
from	O
any	O
lamp	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
136.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Mary	O
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ship	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
stuff	O
poplin	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
December	O
20th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SHIP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
May-fair	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
in	O
service	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Queen-street	B-place
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
stooped	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
together	O
they	O
forced	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
my	O
lord	O
Verney	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
by	O
his	O
Maker	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
resistance	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
a	O
third	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
dead	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
might	O
help	O
myself	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
that	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
woman	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
poplin	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
demanded	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
moon	O
did	O
not	O
shine	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
neighbours	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
again	O
whether	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
consequences	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
worse	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
leaving	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
opened	O
the	O
paper	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
lord	O
Essex	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
paper	O
was	O
there	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
dated	O
that	O
day	O
week	O
:	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
the	O
chairmen	O
about	O
lord	O
Essex	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coward	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
poplin	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
,	O
a	O
publichouse	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
and	O
rather	O
than	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
trouble	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
satisfaction	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Coward	O
advised	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
for	O
compounding	O
of	O
felony	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
down	O
two	O
guineas	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
offer	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
very	O
poor	O
woman	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
in	O
service	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
lucky	O
thing	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
receipt	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
receipt	O
was	O
not	O
produced	O
,	O
nor	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
watchmen	O
at	O
the	O
ends	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
nor	O
alarm	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
threatened	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
dead	O
wall	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lord	O
Essex	O
's	O
and	O
shewed	O
the	O
receipt	O
and	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coward	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
then	O
with	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
an	O
orange-coloured	O
piece	O
of	O
poplin	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
pocket	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
receipt	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
papers	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
receipt	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
paper	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
confession	O
made	O
?	O
-	O
Before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
upon	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
:	O
the	O
chairmen	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
Mrs.	O
Ship	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
:	O
while	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
Mrs.	O
Ship	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
in	O
lieu	O
of	O
the	O
poplin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
the	O
poplin	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
leave	O
that	O
guinea	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
set	O
him	O
at	O
liberty	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
immediately	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
then	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
strangers	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
directly	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
poplin	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
he	O
afterwards	O
offered	O
her	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
poor	O
woman	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
persuaded	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
she	O
might	O
herself	O
be	O
indicted	O
for	O
compounding	O
felony	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
mention	O
being	O
robbed	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
forced	O
a	O
ring	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
does	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
bear	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
where	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
there	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
groom	O
to	O
lord	O
Orwell	O
;	O
she	O
takes	O
in	O
washing	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
woman	O
.	O
The	O
chairmen	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
presence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
them	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
Hay-hill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
:	O
my	O
lord	O
Antrim	O
's	O
chairman	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
,	O
that	O
dropped	O
the	O
rings	O
:	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
Williams	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
Mount-street	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
Williams	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
BROWN	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Coward	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
the	O
poplin	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
Hay-hill	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
treat	O
us	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
company	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
towards	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
had	O
mentioned	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
towards	O
New	O
Bond-street	O
:	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HAWKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Berkeley-square	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Dover-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
convince	O
us	O
by	O
the	O
company	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
goi	O
ng	O
through	O
Berkeley-square	O
to	O
Dover-street	O
,	O
upon	O
Hay-hill	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
down	O
towards	O
Grafton-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
offered	O
to	O
treat	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
us	O
a	O
guinea	O
each	O
;	O
indeed	O
he	O
afterwards	O
offered	O
to	O
double	O
it	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
refused	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coward	O
's	O
in	O
Curzon-street	O
,	O
May-fair	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Ship	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
ten	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
pitched	O
upon	O
him	O
directly	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
poplin	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
likewise	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
half	O
pence	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
decoyed	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Whether	O
she	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
name	O
in	O
Coward	O
's	O
parlour	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
:	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
.	O
What	O
description	O
did	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
lord	O
Antrim	O
's	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
Lord	O
Antrim	O
's	O
servants	O
said	O
the	O
ring-droppers	O
were	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mrs.	O
Ship	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
both	O
expressions	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
not	O
wish	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Coming	O
down	O
Curzon-street	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Ship	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
looking	O
at	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Ship	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
the	O
contents	O
I	O
think	O
were	O
,	O
``	O
Bought	O
of	O
``	O
John	O
Brown	B-pers
an	O
enamelled	O
mourning	O
ring	O
,	O
``	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
''	O
Mrs.	O
Ship	O
insisted	O
upon	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
without	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
it	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
consented	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
without	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
tomorrow	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
ring	O
till	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
wished	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
with	O
her	O
half	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
favour	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Mount-street	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
137	O
,	O
138.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SHEPPARD	I-pers
and	O
PATRICK	B-pers
CROCKHALL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
December	O
18th	O
.	O
``	O
JOHN	B-pers
BRYAN	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
``	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
of	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
``	O
penknife	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
leading	O
from	O
Ratcliffe	B-place
``	O
Cross	O
to	O
Mile-end	B-place
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
star-light	O
night	O
,	O
``	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
``	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
``	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
WALKINGTON	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
``	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
``	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
committed	O
``	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
called	O
witnesses	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
an	O
alibi	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
139	O
,	O
140.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRANT	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
BEAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Moseley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
forty-eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
another	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
thirty-six	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
accomplice	O
unaccompanied	O
with	O
any	O
corroborating	O
circumstances	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
141.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
BUTLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
November	O
20th	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
.	O
142.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Stubbins	I-pers
,	O
October	O
15th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
VINCENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Silver-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
.	I-place
Upon	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
with	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Vincent	O
and	O
I	O
concluded	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
frequently	O
have	O
had	O
these	O
alarms	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
engaged	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
taller	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
standing	O
upon	O
their	O
feet	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
engaged	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
watch	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
watch	O
appeared	O
:	O
the	O
men	O
had	O
both	O
light	O
coloured	O
coats	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
tall	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
lighter	O
coloured	O
coat	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
tall	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
under	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
short	O
man	O
under	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
calling	O
watch	O
incessantly	O
:	O
the	O
undermost	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Mistress	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
``	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
has	O
murdered	O
me	O
;	O
''	O
he	O
spoke	O
it	O
so	O
short	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
down	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Stubbins	O
?	O
-	O
Extremely	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
dark	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
distinguish	O
faces	O
;	O
his	O
coach-house	O
was	O
adjoining	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
tallest	O
man	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
disentangled	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
down	O
Bloomsbury-court	O
towards	O
Holborn	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
and	O
then	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
and	O
ran	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
again	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
alarmed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ealand	I-pers
the	O
butcher	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
as	O
he	O
reeled	O
and	O
fell	O
twice	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
on	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stabbed	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
take	O
up	O
an	O
instrument	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
coachman	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
fetch	O
Mr.	O
Younge	O
the	O
surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
Great-Russel-street	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
had	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
engaged	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
without	O
either	O
when	O
he	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
remarkably	O
clean	O
shaved	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
died	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
-	O
TUTAL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
looks	O
right	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
coach-house	O
is	O
;	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
scuffling	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
biggest	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
gave	O
the	O
shortest	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
dragging	O
him	O
further	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
got	O
loose	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
on	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
have	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Before	O
six	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
you	O
heard	O
was	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Your	O
house	O
is	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
Southampton-street	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
corner	O
of	O
Silver-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
stables	O
are	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pretty	O
night	O
the	O
wall	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
stables	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
his	O
stables	O
are	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
stables	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
biggest	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
.	O
And	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
either	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
fall	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
falls	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hat	O
first	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SMALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
alarm	O
of	O
murder	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
:	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
window	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
scuffling	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
distance	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
drunken	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
deceased	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
murdered	O
him	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
and	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
fell	O
just	O
opposite	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
``	O
Oh	O
dear	O
!	O
he	O
has	O
killed	O
``	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
:	O
''	O
a	O
gentleman	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Blinkow	O
's	O
one-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
window	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
down	O
Bloomsbury-court	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
head	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
clean	O
shaved	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
were	O
they	O
from	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
imagine	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
pretty	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
light	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
beginning	O
to	O
be	O
break	O
of	O
day	O
.	O
-	O
BLINKOW	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
with	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
I	O
sleep	O
in	O
a	O
two-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
scuffling	O
together	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
drunken	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
no	O
regard	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
they	O
came	O
nearer	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
undermost	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
then	O
disengaged	O
himself	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
leaving	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
serious	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Bloomsbury-market	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
running	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
attempted	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
short	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Bloomsbury-court	O
by	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
ask	O
the	O
deceased	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bloomsbury-court	O
:	O
the	O
deceased	O
died	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
first	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
stable	O
is	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
.	O
Did	O
,	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
on	O
when	O
first	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
first	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
break	O
of	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
distance	O
I	O
could	O
but	O
just	O
discern	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
came	O
ten	O
yards	O
nearer	O
me	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARRENER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
together	O
,	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
coach-house	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
stables	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
they	O
both	O
got	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
stables	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
first	O
?	O
-	O
Pretty	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
another	O
fall	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
some	O
time	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
murderer	O
got	O
loose	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bloomsbury-court	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
looked	O
after	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
murderer	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
murderer	O
set	O
off	O
down	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
with	O
his	O
rattle	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
assisting	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
in	O
picking	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
an	O
instrument	O
which	O
we	O
supposed	O
the	O
murder	O
was	O
committed	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
carried	O
away	O
on	O
a	O
shutter	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOLLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
by	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
watch	O
and	O
murder	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
for	O
some	O
minutes	O
,	O
but	O
groaned	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
``	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
``	O
murdered	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
murdered	O
me	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
sprung	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
staggered	O
and	O
run	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
kerb-stone	O
of	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
lean	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
``	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
``	O
has	O
murdered	O
me	O
.	O
''	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
what	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
doing	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
some	O
people	O
were	O
assembled	O
round	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
person	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
wound	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
belly	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
shirt	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
congealed	O
blood	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
shutter	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Southampton-street	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
VINCENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
(	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
)	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
coachman	O
was	O
murdered	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
to	O
my	O
right-hand	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
leaning	O
on	O
Holland	O
's	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
eye	O
to	O
my	O
left-hand	O
and	O
saw	O
Israel	O
Dearing	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
stable	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
two	O
hats	O
and	O
the	O
wig	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
lying	O
?	O
-	O
Against	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
coach-house	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
murdered	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
both	O
very	O
strictly	O
:	O
I	O
dressed	O
myself	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
his	O
shirt	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
likewise	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
blood	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
above	O
his	O
left	O
pap	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wound	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
blood	O
gushed	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
into	O
Great	O
Russel	O
street	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Younge	O
the	O
surgeon	O
,	O
I	O
stayed	O
there	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
minutes	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
shutter	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Younge	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
shutter	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
he	O
examined	O
the	O
wound	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
mortal	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
the	O
deceased	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
hartshorn	O
and	O
water	O
given	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
refreshed	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
so	O
;	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
In	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stables	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
brought	O
in	O
this	O
instrument	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
small	O
bayonet	O
bent	O
at	O
the	O
point	O
,	O
made	O
to	O
fix	O
upon	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
stick	O
)	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
instrument	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
bent	O
by	O
his	O
fall	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Younge	O
wrote	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
into	O
St.	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
Hospital	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
weak	O
through	O
the	O
effusion	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
he	O
died	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
instrument	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
boy	O
is	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
person	O
here	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
condition	O
was	O
the	O
instrument	O
in	O
when	O
given	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
watchman	O
had	O
wiped	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
tip	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
finger	O
to	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
blood	O
.	O
ISRAEL	O
DEERING	O
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
Bloomsbury-court	O
and	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
murder	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Silver-street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
i	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
runing	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
gateway	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
pick	O
up	O
that	O
weapon	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
it	O
where	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
were	O
lying	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
stable	O
door	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
deceased	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
probed	O
the	O
wound	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
weapon	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
wound	O
went	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
the	O
weapon	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
somebody	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
and	O
departed	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
boy	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
weapon	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
offered	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
hats	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
weapon	O
close	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Hum	O
,	O
hum	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sutton	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
terrible	O
noise	O
,	O
rather	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
coach-yard	O
over	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
I	O
slipt	O
my	O
cloaths	O
on	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Vincent	O
said	O
,	O
Sutton	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
coachman	O
is	O
murdered	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
slag	O
stones	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
open	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
gore	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
running	O
off	O
the	O
slag	O
stones	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
poor	O
fellow	O
lie	O
here	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Holborn	O
to	O
seek	O
a	O
surgeon	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
one	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
probed	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
plaister	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
shewed	O
the	O
weapon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
thing	O
that	O
stabbed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
faintly	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Younge	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
sit	O
still	O
,	O
his	O
agony	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
reeling	O
about	O
he	O
knocked	O
his	O
head	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
to	O
his	O
wound	O
:	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
surgeon	O
at	O
the	O
hospital	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
ward	O
where	O
the	O
coachman	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
expired	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Being	O
ind	O
icted	O
for	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
people	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
speak	O
hereafter	O
:	O
when	O
this	O
murder	O
was	O
committed	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
description	O
in	O
the	O
news-papers	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
had	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
suspect	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
news-papers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
confirmed	O
in	O
my	O
suspicion	O
by	O
the	O
girl	O
he	O
cohabited	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Sir	O
John	O
that	O
the	O
javelin	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
javelin	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
information	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
girl	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
instrument	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
blade	O
was	O
not	O
bent	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
ground	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
sixes	O
upon	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
particular	O
mark	O
besides	O
its	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
six	O
upon	O
a	O
stick	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
came	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
(	O
we	O
keep	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sheath	O
to	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
gave	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
dead	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
hair	O
or	O
a	O
wig	O
that	O
he	O
wears	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
false	O
curls	O
;	O
he	O
wore	O
a	O
wig	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
the	O
newspapers	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
committed	O
the	O
murder	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
had	O
white	O
thickset	O
cloaths	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wore	O
white	O
thickset	O
cloaths	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
washed	O
almost	O
white	O
by	O
being	O
often	O
cleaned	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
VINCENT	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
I	O
saw	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
ISRAEL	O
DEERING	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
To	O
HOPKINS	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
who	O
that	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
Both	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
distinguish	O
it	O
by	O
in	O
particular	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
hat	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
coarse	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
out	O
once	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
a	O
shilling	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
wig	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
hat	O
is	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
gave	O
information	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
New-prison	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
clerk	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
near	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
Bolton-street	O
,	O
Long-acre	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
engraver	O
.	O
You	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
hat	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
so	O
coarse	O
that	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
a	O
shilling	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
that	O
black	O
piece	O
round	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
white	O
cord	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
To	O
DEERING	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pick	O
up	O
the	O
two	O
hats	O
and	O
the	O
wig	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
hat	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
servant	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
bit	O
of	O
cord	O
that	O
was	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coarseness	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
lining	O
;	O
the	O
wig	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
hat	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
servant	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
To	O
VINCENT	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
the	O
hat	O
is	O
tore	O
inside	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Who	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Deering	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
Deering	O
.	O
What	O
marks	O
do	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
lining	O
is	O
unsown	O
or	O
torn	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
coarse	O
whipcord	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
coarse	O
thread	O
or	O
tape	O
round	O
it	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
hat	O
delivered	O
to	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
into	O
his	O
servant	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
ROSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
undertaker	O
,	O
I	O
buried	O
the	O
deceased	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
's	O
servant	O
delivered	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
morning	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
murdered	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
clerk	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
both	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
at	O
Sir	O
John-Fielding	O
's	O
with	O
an	O
R	O
in	O
ink	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
wig	O
upon	O
the	O
red	O
riband	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witness	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
marks	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
Jury	O
.	O
]	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
LAWRENCE	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
fourth	O
or	O
fifth	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
wig	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
alteration	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
deep	O
enough	O
in	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
wig	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
alter	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
alteration	O
in	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
shaved	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
time	O
since	O
the	O
alteration	O
of	O
his	O
wig	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
following	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
you	O
shaved	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shave	O
the	O
hair	O
all	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
some	O
hair	O
on	O
each	O
temple	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
neck	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Craven-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
or	O
Hog-lane	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
by	O
both	O
names	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
wig	O
to	O
alter	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
fourth	O
or	O
fifth	O
of	O
October	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
days	O
,	O
by	O
day	O
light	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
left	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
made	O
longer	O
from	O
the	O
forehead	O
to	O
the	O
neck	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wear	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
His	O
own	O
hair	O
,	O
with	O
curls	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
wig	O
fetched	O
back	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
cut	O
his	O
hair	O
off	O
.	O
That	O
wig	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
wore	O
with	O
the	O
hair	O
?	O
-	O
With	O
the	O
hair	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
might	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
fearful	O
of	O
catching	O
cold	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
shaved	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shave	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
generally	O
do	O
,	O
when	O
people	O
are	O
afraid	O
of	O
catching	O
cold	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
it	O
pretty	O
close	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
affair	O
happening	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
answer	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
-	O
CONYER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Newtoner's-street	O
,	O
Holborn	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
wig	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
wore	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
dressed	O
it	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
combed	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
riband	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
particular	O
thing	O
in	O
a	O
wig	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
more	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
Newtoner's-street	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
No	O
8	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
mother	O
and	O
sister	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
this	O
murder	O
happened	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
or	O
the	O
Monday	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
note	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagine	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
contained	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
a	O
little	O
shop	O
there	O
.	O
Who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Mrs.	O
Lilly	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
.	O
You	O
dressed	O
the	O
wig	O
twice	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
days	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
rabbits	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
generally	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
note	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
note	O
came	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
my	O
stand	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Seven-dials	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
upon	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
listening	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
clock	O
strike	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
running	O
up	O
Queen-street	O
very	O
fast	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
thickset	O
coat	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
leather	O
breeches	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Watchman	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
ever	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
up	O
``	O
this	O
street	O
?	O
''	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
madman	O
to	O
run	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
without	O
your	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
cold	O
frosty	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
into	O
Great	O
St.	O
Andrew's-street	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
cross	O
'd	O
over	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
cross-street	O
;	O
then	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
looked	O
round	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
last	O
Friday	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
written	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
person	O
:	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
running	O
by	O
me	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
met	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Near	O
enough	O
to	O
touch	O
him	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
countenance	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
is	O
this	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
from	O
Silver-street	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
or	O
rather	O
better	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ROUT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
:	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
wig	O
he	O
wore	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
wears	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
or	O
a	O
wig	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
:	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
at	O
all	O
hours	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
this	O
man	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
nights	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
taken	O
ill	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
recover	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
since	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
again	O
.	O
A	O
SURGEON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
hospital	O
:	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
deceased	O
Stubbins	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
breast	O
,	O
which	O
passed	O
between	O
the	O
third	O
and	O
fourth	O
rib	O
,	O
and	O
perforated	O
the	O
upper	O
lobe	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
lungs	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
entered	O
the	O
cavity	O
of	O
the	O
heart	O
;	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
what	O
that	O
wound	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
wool-comber	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
mother	O
and	O
sister	O
upon	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
promised	O
him	O
a	O
room	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
honest	O
and	O
civil	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
to	O
feed	O
his	O
rabbits	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
rabbits	O
?	O
-	O
Fourteen	O
breeding	O
does	O
;	O
he	O
bred	O
them	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KNIBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-market	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
his	O
person	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
very	O
well	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
rabbits	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
just	O
man	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GROVES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
curiosity	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
lord	O
Mansfield	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
second	O
coachman	O
to	O
my	O
lord	O
eight	O
years	O
ago	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
prejudice	O
;	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
service	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
asked	O
one	O
another	O
how	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
nothing	O
farther	O
passed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
Friday	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
body	O
to	O
be	O
afterwards	O
dissected	O
and	O
anatomized	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
directions	O
in	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
143	O
,	O
144.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
Bamfylde	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
December	O
11th	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
lady	O
Bamfylde	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
my	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
admit	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
hospital	O
;	O
she	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
my	O
lady	O
sent	O
Martin	B-pers
the	O
butler	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
message	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
:	O
my	O
lady	O
Bamfylde	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
her	O
any	O
letter	O
of	O
recommendation	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
looked	O
ill	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
charity	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
her	O
to	O
another	O
lady	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
recommendation	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
:	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cupboard	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
found	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
there	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
stopped	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
again	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
men	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
?	O
she	O
seemed	O
confused	O
,	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
