TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
1776	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIRST	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALLIFAX	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
;	O
AND	O
SOLD	O
BY	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALLIFAX	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Form	I-pers
,	O
Sidalance	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Emmott	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Butts	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
Silvester	B-pers
Lowden	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Quidington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Berrisford	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Elisha	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Showell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vardy	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Segar	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edmondson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hurd	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Elliott	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kerry	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Irwin	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Clempson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Huie	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rodes	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brown	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
;	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bridget	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FITZPATRICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Bridget	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Clarges-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
back-door	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
two	O
young	O
masters	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hemmings	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Davies	O
keeps	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
from	O
a	O
house	O
adjoining	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back-door	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
quite	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
girl	O
who	O
was	O
within	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
wanted	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
six	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
DAVIES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
fastened	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
spot	O
of	O
dirt	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
judged	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
foot	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
buckles	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAVIES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
being	O
shut	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
stock-buckle	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
the	O
watch	O
over	O
the	O
chimney-piece	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
ANN	B-pers
DUFFIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
doors	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
in	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
bolt	O
was	O
put	O
back	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
through	O
which	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
and	O
push	O
it	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
fastened	O
it	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
foot	O
on	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HIDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
offering	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
and	O
silver	O
buckles	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Davies	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
in	O
Clarges-street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Davies	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bunker	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
large	O
gates	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
going	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
where	O
James	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
'	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
2.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BURROWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
feloniously	O
,	O
diabolically	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
nature	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
venereal	O
affair	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
carnally	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
commit	O
and	O
perpetrate	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
that	O
detestable	O
and	O
abominable	O
crime	O
(	O
among	O
Christians	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
)	O
called	O
buggary	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
LOAME	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
cabinet	O
and	O
chair-maker	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
action	O
.	O
Begin	O
regularly	O
?	O
-	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Harlequin	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
coming	O
up	O
time	O
after	O
time	O
bothering	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
knew	O
him	O
personally	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
tap-room	O
at	O
the	O
Harlequin	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
rightly	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
eat	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
turkey	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
goose	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
to	O
eat	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head-court	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
his	O
carriage	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
gentlemen	O
there	O
besides	O
him	O
.	O
What	O
all	O
to	O
sup	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
washes	O
and	O
irons	O
and	O
cooks	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
for	O
these	O
sodomites	O
;	O
and	O
picks	O
up	O
young	O
fellows	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
of	O
no	O
particular	O
trade	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
were	O
drank	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
act	O
any	O
indecency	O
then	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Come	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
Thursday	O
night	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
action	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
quarters	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
concerning	O
some	O
business	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
servants	O
together	O
;	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
rug	O
hung	O
up	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire-place	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
rug	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
Brooks	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
behind	O
it	O
;	O
Brooks	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
connections	O
together	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
saw	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
rug	O
continue	O
hanging	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
might	O
see	O
at	O
one	O
corner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
against	O
the	O
fire-place	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
rug	O
quite	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
wainscoat	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
side	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
opening	O
that	O
one	O
might	O
see	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
hung	O
over	O
a	O
line	O
at	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
particular	O
in	O
describing	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
Brooks	O
leaning	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
their	O
breeches	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
-	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
Brooks	O
's	O
-	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
behind	O
this	O
rug	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
above	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
continue	O
behind	O
the	O
rug	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
farther	O
than	O
from	O
that	O
gentleman	O
(	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
)	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
nastiness	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Burrows	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
corner	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
just	O
behind	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
began	O
kissing	O
and	O
slavering	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
kissing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
offered	O
me	O
three	O
guineas	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
inn	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
ten	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Fourteen	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
locked	O
out	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
,	O
said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
seeing	O
so	O
much	O
clandestineness	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
or	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
me	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
positively	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
-	O
was	O
in	O
Brooks	O
's	O
-	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
Burrows	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
their	O
shirts	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
tucked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Where	O
you	O
sat	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
behind	O
the	O
rug	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
this	O
for	O
ten	O
minutes	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
ten	O
minutes	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
guess	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
quietly	O
upon	O
your	O
chair	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
transaction	O
made	O
me	O
sick	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
What	O
position	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
side-ways	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Every	O
word	O
he	O
says	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
quite	O
a	O
reverse	O
story	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
:	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
story	O
as	O
true	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
man	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
Loame	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sixty	O
pounds	O
lying	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Townsend	O
's	O
in	O
Prescot	O
street	O
now	O
for	O
my	O
discharge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
fellow	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
buttock	O
of	O
beef	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
eat	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
one	O
day	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sentry	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
longed	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
long	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
had	O
dashed	O
her	O
through	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
arm	O
almost	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
sleep	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
pressed	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
tender	O
from	O
Saturday	O
to	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
this	O
accusation	O
against	O
me	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchcase	O
maker	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
upon	O
Puddle-dock	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
harrassed	O
about	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
quite	O
a	O
different	O
story	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
now	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
3.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CATHERALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
an	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
outside	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
August	O
25th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HAMMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Agent's-office	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Ranelagh-walk	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
three	O
fellows	O
,	O
one	O
held	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
another	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
sight	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
happen	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
any	O
house	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BULL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chandler	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Compasses	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
;	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
Lyon	O
a	O
constable	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
while	O
Lyon	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
three	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Ephraim	O
,	O
whose	O
character	O
I	O
suspected	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
Heckstall	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
people	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
buy	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
just	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Heckstall	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
me	O
some	O
plate	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
anoth	O
er	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
advanced	O
money	O
without	O
having	O
goods	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
that	O
moment	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
Lyon	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
NATHAN	B-pers
LYON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Bull	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
Heckstall	O
and	O
Catherall	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
positive	O
to	O
Catherall	O
's	O
person	O
as	O
to	O
Heckstall	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
candles	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Heckstall	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
Office	O
upon	O
another	O
account	O
,	O
nobody	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Catherall	O
and	O
one	O
Dover	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
in	O
Ranelagh-walk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
some	O
Jews	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Catherall	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
his	O
room	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HECKSTALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Catherall	O
in	O
the	O
Walk	O
at	O
Mary-le-bone	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bathe	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
New-river	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
again	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Nag's-head	O
in	O
Hedge-lane	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Westminster	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
bathe	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
transport	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
returned	O
back	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
London-bridge	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
walked	O
to	O
Hedge-lane	O
again	O
;	O
Catherall	O
then	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pick	O
pockets	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
consented	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
to	O
stop	O
somebody	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
walked	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
in	O
Ranelagh-walk	O
we	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
,	O
Catherall	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
walk	O
;	O
he	O
struggled	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
Catherall	O
was	O
stronger	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
Dover	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
Catherall	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
knife	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
.	O
HAMMOND	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
.	O
HECKSTALL	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
White-horse	O
in	O
Picadilly	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
head	O
again	O
in	O
Hedge-lane	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bull	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
seized	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
being	O
seized	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
Catherall	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
dropped	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Oxford	O
road	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seventeen	O
years	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
saw	O
him	O
industrious	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
the	O
witness	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRAWFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
the	O
witness	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
man	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
DEATH	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
4.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
CALCOTT	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
COCKET	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
October	O
20th	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
JENNINGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
town	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
behind	O
an	O
empty	O
cart	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
thieves	O
and	O
murder	O
twice	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
throwing	O
me	O
down	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
come	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
tore	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
directly	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
cut	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
whether	O
designedly	O
or	O
accidentally	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
two	O
boys	O
,	O
Hatfield	O
and	O
Ross	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
sooner	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
moon-light	O
;	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
Hughes	O
is	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
hearing	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
another	O
occasion	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
has	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
often	O
go	O
there	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HATFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
Did	O
both	O
swear	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Calcott	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Calcott	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
Calcott	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
Calcott	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
Calcott	O
threw	O
me	O
against	O
a	O
cow-house	O
or	O
barn	O
that	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
men	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
black	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
Calcott	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Hatfield	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
playing	O
in	O
Islington	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
murder	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Hatfield	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
close	O
at	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
he	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
Calcott	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Calcott	O
pushed	O
Hatfield	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
her	O
legs	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
barn	O
;	O
Hughes	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
across	O
her	O
throat	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
Hughes	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
cut	O
your	O
throat	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
us	O
your	O
money	O
or	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
two	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
pulling	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
pulled	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
black	O
with	O
a	O
cane	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
her	O
ear	O
was	O
cut	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
perfectly	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
Hughes	O
pulled	O
off	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Calcott	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
their	O
faces	O
by	O
the	O
lamp	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
:	O
Hughes	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
and	O
slapped	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
colour	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
threatened	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
throat	O
.	O
LEONARD	B-pers
STAPLES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Spotted-dog	O
,	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
complained	O
of	O
her	O
door	O
being	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
things	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
ill	O
by	O
these	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Calcott	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Calcott	O
throw	O
the	O
cloak	O
over	O
the	O
pallisadoes	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
immediately	O
got	O
over	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
;	O
Calcott	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
cloak	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
Calcott	O
ran	O
some	O
yards	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
Evans	O
that	O
stopped	O
Hughes	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Staples	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Black-dog	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
they	O
called	O
Scampin	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wished	O
we	O
had	O
come	O
up	O
sooner	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
fellows	O
had	O
been	O
breaking	O
her	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Hughes	O
and	O
Calcott	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
George	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Hughes	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
complaint	O
;	O
Calcott	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
rather	O
drunkish	O
,	O
he	O
shoved	O
up	O
against	O
us	O
;	O
Staples	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Calcott	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
Staples	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
held	O
Hughes	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
woman	O
Scampin	O
,	O
whether	O
this	O
was	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
Calcott	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
knife	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
clasp	O
knife	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
below	O
the	O
Spotted-dog	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
complaint	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
her	O
door	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
things	O
cut	O
;	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
whom	O
she	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
in	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
:	O
while	O
Staples	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
Hughes	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
Calcott	O
lean	O
towards	O
an	O
area	O
and	O
take	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
'The	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
'charge	O
.	O
'	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONERS	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Calcott	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
never-heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
and	O
jobber	O
;	O
he	O
often	O
moves	O
lodgers	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JEFFERYS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
Calcott	O
is	O
a	O
porter	O
and	O
made	O
shoes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hughes	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
goods	O
by	O
tenants	O
at	O
their	O
request	O
when	O
they	O
distrained	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Calcott	O
seven	O
,	O
eight	O
,	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
bad	O
of	O
Hughes	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
FERGUSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
and	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
Calcott	O
's	O
father	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
Calcott	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
entrusted	O
him	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
Warren-street	O
;	O
Calcott	O
was	O
esteemed	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Hughes	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
5.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BRENT	I-pers
and	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
EYRES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Cammerell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
soop	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Frederick	O
;	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Betty	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
BETTY	B-pers
OLDFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cammerell	O
at	O
Hanwell	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
's	O
room	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
sash	O
thrown	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
one	O
window	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
inside	O
shutters	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
put	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
locks	O
to	O
two	O
cupboard	O
doors	O
and	O
the	O
locks	O
on	O
two	O
drawers	O
.	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
shirts	O
which	O
the	O
young	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
window	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
family	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
after	O
twelve	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
sleep	O
below	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
dirty	O
feet	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
window	O
high	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
a	O
sugar	O
chopper	O
and	O
a	O
dirty	O
stick	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
these	O
cupboards	O
and	O
drawers	O
were	O
fast	O
then	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
locks	O
were	O
quite	O
tore	O
off	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
the	O
wood	O
broke	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
shirts	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
cloak	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Betty	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
.	O
]	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
cause	O
to	O
suspect	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
as	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
burglary	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
first	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
backs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
shirts	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
black	O
worsted	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
has	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wristbands	O
that	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
those	O
marks	O
and	O
the	O
work	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
no	O
name	O
marked	O
on	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
them	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
shut	O
down	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
GRAPES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
shut	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
October	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
shut	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
shut	O
the	O
shutters	O
to	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
wire	O
lattice	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
hung	O
on	O
with	O
hooks	O
,	O
that	O
lattice	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
hooks	O
and	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
grass	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
shut	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
shutters	O
and	O
was	O
called	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
next	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
after	O
my	O
fellow	O
serservant	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
drawers	O
and	O
the	O
cupboard	O
shut	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
locks	O
broke	O
off	O
and	O
the	O
drawers	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
shoved	O
quite	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wire	O
lattice	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
This	O
room	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
for	O
suspecting	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Brent	I-pers
:	O
upon	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Hound	O
and	O
Hare	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
on	O
Hanwell-heath	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
directly	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
;	O
several	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
old	O
neighbour	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
stick	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
walk	O
home	O
with	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
it	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
cut	O
off	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
stick	O
this	O
belongs	O
to	O
walk	O
home	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
off	O
this	O
piece	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
and	O
Brent	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
they	O
leave	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
stick	O
produced	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
home	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seems	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
some	O
where	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
brewing	O
;	O
Betty	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
in	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
romance	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
brewing	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
it	O
should	O
happen	O
;	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
How	O
large	O
is	O
this	O
yard	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
15	O
yards	O
wide	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
see	O
that	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
between	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
and	O
that	O
window	O
;	O
one	O
stands	O
opposite	O
the	O
South	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
opposite	O
the	O
North	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Betty	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
into	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lattice	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
taken	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
cupboards	O
and	O
the	O
locks	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sugar	O
chopper	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
business	O
again	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
stick	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
match	O
with	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
burnt	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
candle	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
sticks	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Hare	O
and	O
Hounds	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
public-house	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
Richard	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
Brent	O
over-night	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
Parker	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
that	O
stick	O
to	O
Brent	O
over-night	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
to	O
Brent	O
's	O
lodging	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
together	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
yard	O
secured	O
by	O
a	O
wall	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
the	O
coach-house	O
,	O
is	O
between	O
that	O
yard	O
and	O
the	O
yard	O
where	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
is	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
on	O
Eyre	O
's	O
back	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shirts	O
from	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
of	O
Watson	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
fix	O
your	O
suspicion	O
on	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
stick	O
belonged	O
to	O
Parker	O
?	O
-	O
Parker	O
cleared	O
himself	O
by	O
swearing	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
stick	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
all	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
MITCHEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoners	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Lamb	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Which	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
Eyre	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
bundle	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
different	O
way	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
these	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
:	O
the	O
cloak	O
I	O
have	O
produced	O
was	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
WRIGHT	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
.	O
FOR	O
EYRE	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KNOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Horse-grenadier	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eyre	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
an	O
excellent	O
character	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NAIL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eyre	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Brent	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
bear	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SIMMONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eyre	O
upwards	O
of	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
stain	O
his	O
character	O
till	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
early	O
and	O
late	O
.	O
GILBERT	B-pers
MITCHEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eyre	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
discredit	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
his	O
getting	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
EWER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eyre	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MACINTOSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eyre	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
good	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
NAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eyre	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
6.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
asses-skin	O
pocket-books	O
in	O
leather	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shenton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
26th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
]	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
7.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
FENNELSON	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
LYONS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-seven	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
-	O
WILLIAMS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Walter	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
who	O
is	O
a	O
sugar-refiner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
12	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
acquire	O
a	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
manufacture	O
;	O
Fennelson	O
is	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
miller	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
conveyed	O
some	O
sugar	O
away	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
us	O
should	O
watch	O
:	O
several	O
men	O
sat	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
John	B-pers
Eck	I-pers
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Fennelson	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
looked	O
for	O
some	O
body	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
lump	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
Lyons	O
then	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
sugar	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
.	O
Fennelson	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Lyons	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
sign	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
conceal	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
Fennelson	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Fennelson	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
lived	O
there	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
employment	O
of	O
a	O
miller	O
in	O
a	O
sugar-house	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
the	O
greatest	O
trust	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
distinction	O
,	O
the	O
servants	O
are	O
all	O
intrusted	O
alike	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
general	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
employed	O
in	O
sugar-houses	O
are	O
foreigners	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
foreigners	O
in	O
sugar-houses	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
majority	O
are	O
not	O
foreigners	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
majority	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
foreigners	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
Irishmen	O
and	O
Dutchmen	O
.	O
Pray	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
yard	O
from	O
which	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
sugar	O
conveyed	O
a	O
common	O
yard	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
yard	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
,	O
other	O
people	O
have	O
across	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
way	O
through	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
Lyons	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
the	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
Fennelson	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ECK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
appointed	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
watched	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Lyons	O
come	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
we	O
stood	O
and	O
watched	O
,	O
till	O
Fennelson	O
came	O
down	O
from	O
his	O
bed-room	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
shewed	O
his	O
face	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
Fennelson	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
sugar	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
while	O
Lyons	O
held	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
Lyons	O
then	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
catched	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
sugar	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
sugar	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
weigh	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
years	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
German	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
greater	O
number	O
of	O
Germans	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blunt	O
's	O
than	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
nation	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
most	O
of	O
us	O
are	O
Germans	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
Germans	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
offended	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
people	O
of	O
another	O
nation	O
are	O
employed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
miller	O
in	O
a	O
sugar-house	O
the	O
head	O
servant	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
common	O
servant	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
his	O
work	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
grind	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
other	O
servants	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
not	O
much	O
more	O
trusted	O
than	O
the	O
common	O
men	O
ordinarily	O
are	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
any	O
more	O
trusted	O
than	O
another	O
is	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
ever	O
any	O
quarrel	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Germans	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
bring	O
out	O
the	O
sugar	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
.	O
'	O
Philip	B-pers
Boyson	I-pers
,	O
another	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
'Blunt	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
'witnesses	O
.	O
'	O
EDWARD	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
sugar	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
FENNELSON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
LYONS	O
'	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
yard-door	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
parish	O
pump	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Fennelson	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COLLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
sleeve-buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
MOSES	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
November	O
10th	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Crutched-fryars	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drew	O
beer	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
one-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
Who	O
slept	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
buckles	O
and	O
buttons	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
Mr.	O
Marshall	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
mother	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
9.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HULSE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
ounces	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Anstie	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Worstead	I-pers
,	O
November	O
16th	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
ANSTIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Worstead	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
tea	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
suspected	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
perpetually	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
particularly	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
in	O
goods	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Worstead	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
change	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Worstie	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cannister	O
;	O
we	O
fetched	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
loose	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
an	O
Indiaman	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
it	O
loose	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Grasshopper	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Anstie	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pri-prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
chest	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
tea	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Anstie	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
tea	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
touched	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
tea	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
MARY	B-pers
BASSING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gandy	I-pers
,	O
November	O
12th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GANDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine-cooper	O
in	O
Houndsditch	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LAYTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
two	O
table-spoons	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
16	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
heard	O
some	O
plate	O
rattle	O
somewhere	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Gandy	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
some	O
cloaths	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
on	O
further	O
pressing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mrs.	O
Gandy	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
pepper	O
castor	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
containing	O
sixty	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dyke	I-pers
Edgar	I-pers
,	O
November	O
29th	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
DYKE	I-pers
EDGAR	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
factor	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
flannel	O
from	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
10	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
call	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
stepped	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
flannel	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
flannel	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
flannel	O
from	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
flannel	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Ash	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
some	O
bad	O
design	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Edgar	O
's	O
warehouse	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edgar	O
's	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
bloody	O
bouger	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
peaceably	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
run	O
a	O
knife	O
into	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
china	O
flower-pots	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
September	O
6th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
13.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KELLY	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LATHAM	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
metal	O
case	O
chased	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
eighty	O
wrought	O
silk	O
patterns	O
for	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
japanned	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
nippers	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pen-knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
cork-screw	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pencil	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
top	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
tweezers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
tambour	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colcomb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
October	O
25th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COLCOMB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tambour	O
warehouse	O
in	O
Cecil-court	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
:	O
upon	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
stripped	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
ten	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shop-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bureau	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
drawers	O
opened	O
and	O
stripped	O
;	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
was	O
about	O
40	O
l.	O
Latham	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
observed	O
at	O
my	O
shop-window	O
,	O
looking	O
under	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
women	O
who	O
were	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop-door	O
,	O
Latham	O
always	O
walked	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
often	O
saw	O
Kelly	O
with	O
Latham	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Latham	O
that	O
particular	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Kelly	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
challenged	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
as	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Latham	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
what	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
affect	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
recollected	O
his	O
face	O
instantly	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
often	O
seen	O
about	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
Kelly	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
lodgings	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
precise	O
as	O
to	O
whose	O
lodgings	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
understood	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
,	O
other	O
trinkets	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
,	O
a	O
lock	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
's	O
hair	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
lose	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
SWIFT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
Kelly	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pen-knife	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Winchester-street	O
;	O
in	O
Kelly	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
nippers	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
a	O
lock	O
of	O
hair	O
in	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
behind	O
the	O
grate	O
in	O
Kelly	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PERCIVAL	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
cork-screw	O
upon	O
Latham	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
dropped	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
pick-locks	O
.	O
LATHAM	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
KELLY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
lodging	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
sometimes	O
went	O
;	O
other	O
people	O
might	O
have	O
left	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
me	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONERS	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
ISAAC	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Colcomb	O
:	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
fact	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
suspected	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
lodgers	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
a	O
little	O
thin	O
,	O
short	O
,	O
shabby	O
,	O
ill-looking	O
fellow	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
his	O
window	O
:	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Colcomb	O
has	O
sworn	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
80	O
pieces	O
of	O
tambour	O
embroidery	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
either	O
have	O
sworn	O
falsely	O
now	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Conscience	O
,	O
because	O
upon	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
this	O
embroidery	O
,	O
I	O
summoned	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Conscience	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
ever	O
received	O
this	O
tambour	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
done	O
by	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
for	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
done	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
DEATH	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
14.	O
MARY	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
printed	O
book	O
,	O
intitled	O
Hervey	O
's	O
Meditations	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
printed	O
book	O
,	O
intitled	O
The	O
Practical	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Floyer	I-pers
jun	O
.	O
October	O
30th	O
.	O
'There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
'home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
15.	O
ANN	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
quilted	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
scarlet	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dadford	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29th	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
DADFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
17	I-place
in	I-place
Gray	I-place
's	I-place
Buildings	I-place
:	O
upon	O
Michaelmas-day	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
case	O
I	O
should	O
want	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
trunk	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
eleven	O
days	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
pounds	O
;	O
the	O
most	O
valuable	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
recovered	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
upon	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
pillow	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
beds	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
her	O
mother	O
gave	O
up	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
or	O
had	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
lodgers	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
table	O
clock	O
in	O
a	O
mahogany	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramble	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Nov.	O
21st	O
.	O
'The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
the	O
clock	O
the	O
'morning	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
'Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
watched	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
'shop	O
where	O
he	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
'he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
'had	O
kept	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
'clock	O
from	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
'and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
enquire	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
'he	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
'character	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
17.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
DOYLE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
live	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
21st	O
.	O
'It	O
appeared	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
hens	O
'were	O
found	O
dead	O
upon	O
the	O
stall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
'were	O
present	O
.	O
'	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
18.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
HANDREQUAS	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
STEWARD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
180	O
yards	O
of	O
callimanco	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28th	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
FREEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hewitt	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
my	O
whitener	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
callimanco	O
upon	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STREET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
service	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
deliver	O
out	O
the	O
callimancoes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bufoys	O
to	O
whiten	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bufoys	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
callimanco	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
callimanco	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bufoys	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
where	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DIGNAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
meet	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
custody	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Hill	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
a	O
house	O
for	O
that	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
doors	O
off	O
that	O
I	O
well	O
knew	O
;	O
my	O
curiosity	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
perhaps	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
this	O
callimanco	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Steward	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Handrequas	O
;	O
Steward	O
seeing	O
me	O
dropped	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
secured	O
them	O
both	O
and	O
the	O
callimanco	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
all	O
the	O
pieces	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
FREEMAN	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
out	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
seal	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
upon	O
each	O
piece	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
DIGNAM	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
landing-place	O
of	O
the	O
one-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
one-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
a	O
table	O
opposite	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
Handrequas	O
gave	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
Steward	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Steward	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
HANDREQUAS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
work	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
George	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
supper	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
violent	O
noise	O
below	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
press-gang	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
shoemaker	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
two-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
press-gang	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Dignam	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
handcuffed	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
STEWARD	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
We	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
press-gang	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
long	O
dark	O
entry	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
'Steward	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
'	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
'	O
'Handrequas	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
'he	O
knew	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
he	O
'bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
'	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
19.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
31st	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LAYTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
several	O
gowns	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
to	O
suit	O
her	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
'	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
'	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
tenpence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
20.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
CONNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
'	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
'	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
shift-sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
eight-pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hopkinson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Oct.	O
18th	O
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
HOPKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Steele	O
in	O
Great	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
in	O
Dyot-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
'The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
'	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
tenpence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
21.	O
MARY	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Kershaw	I-pers
,	O
October	O
29th	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
KERSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
wet	O
night	O
she	O
dried	O
herself	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
pour	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
into	O
the	O
ashes	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
her	O
beer	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
was	O
missed	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
'The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
pleaded	O
poverty	O
'and	O
great	O
distress	O
.	O
'	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
distressed	O
situation	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
tenpence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
22.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CLAYTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
'	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
White-cross-street	B-place
:	O
upon	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
childrens	O
Morocco	O
pumps	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
keep	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
warmth	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
such	O
as	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
in	O
just	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
believed	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
mine	O
there	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SADLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	B-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
some	O
objections	O
to	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
SILVANUS	B-pers
HENLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
some	O
stockings	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
on	O
no	O
good	O
errand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
buy	O
something	O
at	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
watched	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
while	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
backwards	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
glass-case	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
tenpence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
23.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRIGGS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GROVE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
pocket	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pounds	O
nine	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stogden	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
November	O
15th	O
.	O
'The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
'his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
'estreated	O
.	O
'	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
24.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goode	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
a-silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
brass	O
watch	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	O
,	O
November	O
17th	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
GOODE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
at	O
Shoreditch	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Willow	B-place
Walk	I-place
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
drew	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
or	O
stirred	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
collar	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
snatched	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
poker	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
manner	O
;	O
one	O
blow	O
fell	O
on	O
my	O
stock	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
stock-buckle	O
;	O
he	O
hit	O
me	O
another	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
pistol	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
back	O
beating	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
down	O
and	O
wrested	O
the	O
poker	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
from	O
under	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
draw	O
my	O
cutlass	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
''	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
cutlass	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
head	O
off	O
I	O
loosed	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
under	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
just	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
got	O
clear	O
off	O
.	O
You	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
this	O
moment	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
next	O
morning	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
where	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
mistake	O
one	O
man	O
for	O
another	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HODGETTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goode	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
by	O
two	O
footpads	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
for	O
a	O
pistol	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
pistol	O
is	O
deficient	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
officer	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
knot	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
they	O
say	O
just	O
fits	O
that	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
box	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
24.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gelder	I-pers
,	O
October	O
7th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GELDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
wife	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
waked	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Edwards	O
must	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
and	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
another	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
that	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
often	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
watch	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
over	O
the	O
fire-place	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
GELDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
lay	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
gaming	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
any	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
order	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
waked	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
FOX	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
18	O
s.	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
has	O
swore	O
,	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
ANN	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1st	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BEACH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
when	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea	O
spoon	O
at	O
the	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
SARAH	B-pers
BEACH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
expected	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
her	O
father	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
meant	O
to	O
bilk	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
stripped	O
the	O
room	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
stays	O
were	O
not	O
gone	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
some	O
she	O
owed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Charing	O
cross	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
staying	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
fits	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
them	O
till	O
