TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
1777	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALLIFAX	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
;	O
AND	O
SOLD	O
BY	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
248.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
lutestring	O
,	O
containing	O
sixty-six	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
March	O
27th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LILLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
entering	O
the	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
looking	O
stedfastly	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
reply	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
a	O
penny	O
to	O
a	O
beggar	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lutestring	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lutestring	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
silk	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
counter	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
confused	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
motion	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
conceal	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
suspicious	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
shopman	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lutestring	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
To	O
SMITH	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
besides	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Another	O
shop-man	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
249.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COSBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
riband	O
,	O
containing	O
100	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
TOMLINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
haberdasher	O
in	O
Cranborne-alley	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
having	O
missed	O
ribands	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
riband	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
riband	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
marked	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
possession	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
served	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
to	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
seize	O
him	O
immediately	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
pieces	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
an	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
's	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
every	O
time	O
the	O
servant	O
turned	O
her	O
back	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
FATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tomlinson	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
ribands	O
piece	O
by	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
myself	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Tomlinson	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
opposite	O
shop	O
watching	O
him	O
.	O
JURY	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
all	O
these	O
pieces	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
counted	O
all	O
the	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
eight	O
missing	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
ribands	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
a	O
nosegay	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
joking	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
ribands	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
joke	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
250.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BLACKWELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Kersimere	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ostliff	I-pers
;	O
four	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
OSTLIFF	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Kent-court	B-place
,	I-place
Berwick-street	I-place
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
landlady	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
our	O
lodgings	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
is	O
my	O
bed-fellow	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
REED	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
Saturday	O
fortnight	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
,	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Corby	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Corby	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
doors	O
down	O
Berwick-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
cloaths	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
drop	O
the	O
cloaths	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
that	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
chissel	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
four	O
keys	O
for	O
door	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
pawnbrokers	O
duplicates	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
CORBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
apartment	O
on	O
Saturday	O
afternoon	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
along	O
the	O
passage	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
four	O
and	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pass	O
by	O
with	O
the	O
cloaths	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ostliff	O
and	O
Reed	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
's	O
window	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
six	O
coats	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Bull	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
when	O
somebody	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
being	O
frightened	O
I	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
these	O
keys	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
I	O
kept	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
accidentally	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
CORBY	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
staple	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
251.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
lappets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
GIFFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
millener	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
church-yard	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
laid	O
some	O
lace	O
lappets	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
advertized	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ARTZ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
this	O
lace	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
one	O
Christian	B-pers
M'Cloud	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
millener	O
in	O
Earl-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
advertized	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
lace	O
she	O
lost	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
lace	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
PATRICK	B-pers
McDANIEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
in	O
Earle-street	O
,	O
Seven-dials	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
pawned	O
the	O
lace	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
particular	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
warming	O
the	O
purl	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
some	O
lace	O
and	O
ribands	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
brags	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
good	O
booties	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
purl	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
CHRISTIAN	B-pers
McCLOUD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
some	O
lace	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Artz	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
at	O
Mr.	O
McDaniel	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
good	O
booties	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Artz	O
and	O
asked	O
18	O
d.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
McDaniel	O
's	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
252.	O
MARY	B-pers
DRAPER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
lawn	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
26th	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CURTIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-lane	B-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Walley	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
left	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gone	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
at	O
a	O
puppet-show	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
and	O
apron	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
surprized	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
accuse	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
cloaths	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
talked	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
puppet-show	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Curtis	O
to	O
the	O
puppet-show	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
stripped	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
that	O
takes	O
in	O
girls	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
253.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COYLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
feloniously	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
iron	O
poker	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
upon	O
the	O
right-side	O
of	O
her	O
head	O
feloniously	O
did	O
strike	O
,	O
giving	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
such	O
striking	O
with	O
the	O
iron	O
poker	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
bruise	O
and	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
right-side	O
of	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
bruise	O
and	O
wound	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
until	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
languish	O
and	O
languishing	O
did	O
live	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
said	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
of	O
the	O
mortal	O
bruise	O
and	O
wound	O
aforesaid	O
died	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
]	O
ANN	B-pers
ERRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
wife	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
they	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Robinhood	B-place
and	I-place
Little	I-place
John	I-place
in	O
Mary	B-place
le	I-place
bone-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
chairman	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
with	O
his	O
chair	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
his	O
wife	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
;	O
they	O
sat	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
drinking	O
gin	O
and	O
purl	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
deceased	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
husband	O
and	O
wife	O
upon	O
very	O
good	O
terms	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
us	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
quarrel	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
soberer	O
than	O
she	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
soberer	O
than	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Up	O
how	O
many	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
was	O
her	O
lodging	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
I	O
laid	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
helpless	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
mistress	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
screaming	O
from	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
garret	O
door	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
blood	O
running	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
right-side	O
of	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
posture	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
only	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
'Help	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
murdered	O
me	O
;	O
'	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
woman	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
for	O
any	O
further	O
assistance	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
mistress	O
came	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
frightened	O
and	O
went	O
d	O
own	O
again	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
the	O
lodger	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
deceased	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
surgeon	O
came	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
surgeon	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
a	O
lodger	O
fetched	O
him	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
surgeon	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
surgeon	O
came	O
we	O
cut	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
hair	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
wound	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
deep	O
wound	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
surgeon	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
in	O
thus	O
deep	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
(	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
)	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
continue	O
to	O
bleed	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
surgeon	O
desired	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
had	O
to	O
an	O
hospital	O
;	O
a	O
coach	O
was	O
called	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
further	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
you	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
further	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
any	O
subsequent	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
stupid	O
dozing	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
talking	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
?	O
-	O
Three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
the	O
preceding	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
chair-work	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
tap-room	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
gin	O
and	O
beer	O
from	O
nine	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
very	O
friendly	O
terms	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
He	O
helped	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
talk	O
about	O
or	O
desire	O
that	O
a	O
surgeon	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
POPE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Robinhood	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
two-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
they	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
story	O
above	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
sociable	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
purl	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
at	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
up	O
stairs	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
went	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
fright	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
she	O
was	O
leaning	O
against	O
the	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
blood	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
up	O
her	O
hands	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
their	O
acquaintance	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Lavendar	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
Lavendar	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
conversation	O
between	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
Lavender	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Her	O
husband	O
had	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
poker	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
it	O
happened	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
To	O
ERRIDGE	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
poker	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
poker	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
of	O
POPE	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
injury	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
was	O
not	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
dangerous	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
that	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
custody	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
after	O
this	O
time	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
voluntarily	O
upon	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
deceased	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
the	O
quarrel	O
happened	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
any	O
questions	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
only	O
just	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
herself	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
in	O
my	O
tap-room	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
employed	O
about	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
they	O
drinking	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
sat	O
up	O
late	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
screaming	O
or	O
calling	O
out	O
above	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
nor	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
chairman	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
appeared	O
very	O
sober	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
sat	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
purl	O
with	O
gin	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
Ann	B-pers
Erridge	I-pers
to	O
see	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
laid	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
screaming	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
I	O
followed	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
leaning	O
against	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
head	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Nor	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
deceased	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
that	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CHARTERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surgeon	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
deceased	O
Mary	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
It	O
fell	O
to	O
your	O
share	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
did	O
.	O
Upon	O
examining	O
her	O
what	O
situation	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
right-side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
A	O
cut	O
or	O
contused	O
wound	O
?	O
-	O
Partly	O
cut	O
and	O
partly	O
contused	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
in	O
length	O
.	O
What	O
depth	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
or	O
hardly	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
With	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
an	O
instrument	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
occasioned	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
blunt	O
instrument	O
with	O
a	O
coarse	O
edge	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
skull	O
affected	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
bare	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
fractured	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
fracture	O
upon	O
examination	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
it	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
rather	O
stupid	O
.	O
Did	O
that	O
stupor	O
appear	O
to	O
proceed	O
from	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
liquor	O
or	O
any	O
concussion	O
of	O
the	O
brain	O
?	O
-	O
More	O
from	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
liquor	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Three	O
weeks	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
at	O
first	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
then	O
some	O
bad	O
symptoms	O
came	O
on	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
necessary	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
trapaned	O
,	O
and	O
matter	O
was	O
found	O
formed	O
under	O
the	O
skull	O
;	O
she	O
continued	O
going	O
on	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
wound	O
and	O
the	O
matter	O
formed	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
your	O
attendance	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
her	O
express	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
wound	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
declaration	O
made	O
from	O
the	O
hospital	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
application	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
word	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
well	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
message	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
fancy	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Pope	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
grudge	O
for	O
demanding	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
demanded	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
gowns	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
let	O
out	O
upon	O
bail	O
from	O
Tothillfields	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
turning	O
about	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
slip	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
slipped	O
against	O
the	O
bedstead	O
or	O
whether	O
against	O
the	O
sender	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
moon	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
we	O
kept	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
an	O
angry	O
word	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
days	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
the	O
accident	O
happened	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
sender	O
or	O
the	O
grate	O
.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
FOY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
asked	O
the	O
surgeon	O
how	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
confinement	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
no	O
offence	O
against	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
surprising	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
the	O
accident	O
happened	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
CHARTER	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
such	O
declaration	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
such	O
enquiry	O
;	O
Patrick	B-pers
Foy	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BYRNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
years	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
married	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
they	O
lived	O
happy	O
together	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
18	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
quiet	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
LANGLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
14	O
years	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
endeavouring	O
man	O
.	O
Did	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
him	O
live	O
happily	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
have	O
him	O
cleared	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
right	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
through	O
a	O
fall	O
she	O
got	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
TIPPIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
inclinable	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
show	O
any	O
violence	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
What	O
occupation	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
publican	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
COLVILE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
this	O
misdemeanor	O
.	O
Did	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
he	O
live	O
quite	O
happily	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
quite	O
agreeable	O
,	O
and	O
loving	O
and	O
good-natured	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
murder	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
254	O
,	O
255.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GILPHIN	I-pers
and	O
GRIFFITH	B-pers
BUCKLEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
theft	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Rose	O
Richardson	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Twaits	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Twaits	I-pers
,	O
February	O
26th	O
.	O
'The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
given	O
them	O
'to	O
execute	O
upon	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
'upon	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
'she	O
afterwards	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
'having	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
'they	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
'make	O
any	O
complaint	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
the	O
first	O
'time	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
'according	O
to	O
her	O
account	O
,	O
was	O
immediately	O
'after	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
'the	O
charge	O
was	O
without	O
foundation	O
.	O
'	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
256.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EADES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
19th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
her	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
]	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
257	O
,	O
258.	O
SARAH	B-pers
CRADDOCK	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
259.	O
ISABELLA	B-pers
COMYNS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
watch	O
riband	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
March	O
1st	O
.	O
'The	O
prosecutor	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
'so	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
when	O
he	O
'lost	O
his	O
watch	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
recollect	O
'what	O
passed	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
260.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COOLEDGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
till	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
hundred	O
and	O
eighty	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
hundred	O
and	O
eighty	O
farthings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cuthforth	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
261	O
,	O
262.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KING	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
embezzle	O
,	O
and	O
purloin	O
a	O
linen-sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
February	O
7th	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
263.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JAMES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
seven	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
eighteen	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
thirty	O
china	O
tea-cups	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
thirty	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
toilet	O
china-cup	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
china-man	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
church-yard	I-place
:	O
upon	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
my	O
clerk	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
shop	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Ransford	O
's	O
,	O
Green-street	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALLAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
putting	O
into	O
the	O
basket	O
a	O
complete	O
set	O
of	O
china	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
must	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
finished	O
packing	O
up	O
the	O
china	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
forward	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
rattle	O
some	O
more	O
china	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
accomplished	O
his	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
basket	O
forward	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
aside	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
added	O
13	O
plates	O
to	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
I	O
requested	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
carry	O
those	O
plates	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
what	O
had	O
passed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
from	O
his	O
staying	O
out	O
and	O
neglecting	O
his	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
bad	O
connections	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
confession	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ransford	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
RANSFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
earthen-ware	O
and	O
china	O
shop	O
in	O
Green-street	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
china	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Deptford	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
several	O
things	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
;	O
eight	O
dozen	O
of	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
dozen	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
china	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
Halliburton	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALLIBURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
china	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Ransford	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BEWLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
china	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ransford	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
china	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
customer	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
RANSFORD	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
basons	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
by	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
264	O
,	O
265.	O
PIERCE	B-pers
DONNOVAN	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KERWIN	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
KERNON	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
KERVAN	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
KERONS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Olivia	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
one	O
mahogany	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch-chain	O
set	O
with	O
mocha	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
diamond	O
button	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
repeating	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
gold	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
five	O
trinkets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
lockets	O
set	O
with	O
garnets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
locket	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
and	O
rubies	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
earrings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
six	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
diamond	O
hoop	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
diamond	O
pin	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
eleven	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
medals	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
gold	O
coin	O
called	O
a	O
three	O
moidore	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
another	O
gold	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Olivia	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
promissory	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
governor	O
and	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
another	O
promissory	O
note	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
promissory	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
governor	O
and	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
promissory	O
note	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
promissory	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
governor	O
and	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
another	O
promis	O
sory	O
note	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
promissory	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
governor	O
and	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
(	O
the	O
said	O
notes	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
committing	O
the	O
felony	O
asoresaid	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Olivia	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
20	O
l.	O
15	O
l.	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
payable	O
and	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
promissory	O
notes	O
,	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Olivia	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
the	O
proprietor	O
thereof	O
)	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
15th	O
.	O
OLIVIA	B-pers
HARRINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
Haddock	O
's	O
bagnio	O
at	O
Charing-cross	B-place
:	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
doctor	O
's	O
hands	O
for	O
a	O
cancer	O
in	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
hot	O
bath	O
three	O
times	O
a-week	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
bath	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bath	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
maids	O
was	O
dressing	O
my	O
breast	O
with	O
a	O
plaister	O
of	O
hemlock	O
;	O
Donnovan	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
waiter	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
cordial	O
wanting	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
keys	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
seven	O
guineas	O
loose	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
inside	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
iron	O
chest	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
mahogany	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
bank	O
notes	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
Breslau	O
's	O
exhibition	O
bills	O
;	O
Donnovan	O
and	O
Molly	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
iron	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
chest	O
very	O
carefully	O
;	O
the	O
mahogany	O
box	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
keys	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
night	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justamond	O
who	O
attended	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
iron	O
chest	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
keys	O
were	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
possession	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
iron	O
chest	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bunch	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
cordials	O
;	O
the	O
cordials	O
and	O
iron	O
chest	O
are	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
where	O
I	O
generally	O
sit	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
my	O
watches	O
and	O
money	O
and	O
rings	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Charing-cross	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
Haddock	O
's	O
bagnio	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
great	O
resort	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
was	O
this	O
iron	O
chest	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
parlour	O
.	O
All	O
your	O
servants	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
are	O
there	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
-	O
Twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
keys	O
upon	O
that	O
bunch	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
often	O
part	O
with	O
this	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
when	O
things	O
are	O
wanted	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
generally	O
serve	O
them	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
suspected	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
servants	O
besides	O
Donnovan	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
but	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
found	O
upon	O
Kerwin	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
silver	O
clasp	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
suspect	O
a	O
maid-servant	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
and	O
send	O
after	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
her	O
stealing	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
know	O
something	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MARDELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pocket-book	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
on	O
Kerwin	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
papers	O
in	O
it	O
and	O
lottery	O
tickets	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
HARRINGTON	O
.	O
That	O
pocket-book	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
seventeen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
paper	O
my	O
notes	O
were	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
of	O
Donnovan	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
lottery	O
tickets	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
as	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
as	O
you	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
the	O
papers	O
?	O
-	O
More	O
so	O
.	O
You	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
papers	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
Breslau	O
's	O
paper	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
produced	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
day	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
you	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
positively	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
particular	O
marks	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
seventeen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
being	O
tore	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
it	O
so	O
long	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
no	O
marks	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
losses	O
were	O
so	O
great	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
recollect	O
all	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
Kerwin	O
said	O
Donnovan	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
six	O
months	O
and	O
then	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Kerwin	O
before	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
JOLLIFFE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
my	O
mistress	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
Donnovan	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
cordial	O
for	O
some	O
company	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
the	O
keys	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
poultice	O
for	O
her	O
breast	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
pain	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
ill.	O
She	O
was	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
keys	O
again	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
the	O
evening	O
she	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
14th	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
St.	O
Patrick	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
person	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Donnovan	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
detained	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
pocket-book	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Nor	O
Kerwin	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
by	O
seeing	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
eleven	O
years	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
is	O
cordial	O
wanted	O
?	O
-	O
Every	O
day	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
often	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
except	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
suspected	O
Captain	O
Evans	B-pers
about	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Evans	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
REDGRAVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
Kerwin	O
,	O
Mardell	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
that	O
is	O
produced	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Kerwin	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
altered	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DILLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Donnovan	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
particular	O
matters	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
or	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
shillings	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
and	O
bring	O
him	O
a	O
duplicate	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
duplicate	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
14th	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
passed	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
or	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
boy	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
his	O
cloaths	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
some	O
bills	O
he	O
owed	O
his	O
mistress	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
discovered	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
barber	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
he	O
slipped	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
room	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GAHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Harrington	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
make	O
application	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
cloaths	O
were	O
in	O
pawn	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
release	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
for	O
money	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
things	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
cloak	O
or	O
any	O
things	O
being	O
bought	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
say	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
DILLY	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Kerwin	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DOBBINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Harrington	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Kerwin	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Kerwin	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
Donnovan	O
.	O
DONNOVAN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
keys	O
from	O
her	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
present	O
herself	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Ireland	O
.	O
KERWIN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
such	O
a	O
paper	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Donnovan	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
trust	O
the	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
possession	O
but	O
that	O
once	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
FOR	O
DONNOVAN	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
DEERING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Donnovan	O
two	O
years	O
or	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
pocket	O
book	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
like	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Donnovan	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
last	O
Whitsuntide	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
repeatedly	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
instruments	O
in	O
your	O
pocket-book	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
tweezers	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
To	O
DEERING	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Open	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
torn	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
dirty	O
round	O
here	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
lock	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
peremptorily	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Donnovan	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
years	O
last	O
October	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
in	O
Ireland	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
why	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
?	O
-	O
Some	O
dispute	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
injure	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
jewels	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
OBRYAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Donnovan	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
pocket-book	O
about	O
ten	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
plain	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
pocketbook	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
letter	O
out	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
reading	O
it	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
up	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
the	O
clasp	O
being	O
loose	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MOULTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Donnovan	O
nine	O
years	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
pocketbook	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
frequently	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
past	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
book	O
;	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
possibility	O
of	O
swearing	O
to	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
under	O
a	O
prosecution	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
insured	O
some	O
tickets	O
at	O
a	O
lottery	O
office	O
and	O
they	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
having	O
been	O
beforehand	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
and	O
knowing	O
they	O
were	O
drawn	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
I	O
bailed	O
it	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
action	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
attorney	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
nothing	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
DONNOVAN	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
KERWIN	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
266	O
,	O
267.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BANGEY	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BANGEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Dagley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Catherine	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
error	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
268	O
,	O
269	O
,	O
270.	O
DAVID	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BALDWIN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
George	I-pers
Mohringk	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
six	O
china	O
tea-cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
boy	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
George	I-pers
Mohringk	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
iron	O
chissels	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heakens	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
MOHRINGK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
country	O
house	O
in	O
Phillips	B-place
's	I-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
Tottenham	I-place
;	O
I	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
am	O
an	O
agent	O
to	O
two	O
officers	O
in	O
the	O
navy	O
:	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
a	O
bar	O
had	O
been	O
wrenched	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
kitchen	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
casement	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
by	O
taking	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
likewise	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
made	O
an	O
entrance	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
hung	O
by	O
one	O
screw	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
had	O
been	O
also	O
opened	O
by	O
some	O
small	O
instrument	O
,	O
the	O
top-part	O
of	O
the	O
wood	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
flap	O
pulled	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
turned	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
list	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoners	O
acknowledge	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
list	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
account	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
servants	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
recollect	O
was	O
missing	O
without	O
referring	O
to	O
that	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
punch-ladle	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
very	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEAKENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Edmonton	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mohringk	O
's	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
tools	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
my	O
tools	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
broad	O
chissels	O
,	O
two	O
inches	O
in	O
space	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
three	O
quarter	O
chissel	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
at	O
Mr.	O
George	O
Marshall	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
Easter	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
down	O
Green-lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
drive	O
a	O
mare	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
off	O
the	O
common	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Mohringk	O
's	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
drove	O
the	O
mare	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
of	O
pasture	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
off	O
the	O
mare	O
and	O
a	O
chissel	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
chissel	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Heakens	O
.	O
]	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MARKHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
little	O
work	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
brick	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
place	O
like	O
a	O
pantry	O
by	O
pulling	O
a	O
bar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
town	O
or	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
before	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
first	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
we	O
went	O
towards	O
Tottenham	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
miles	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
London	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
house	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
Tottenham	O
way	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Tottenham	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
or	O
lane	O
or	O
what	O
you	O
may	O
call	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
backwards	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
pantry	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
a	O
pantry	O
or	O
a	O
kitchen	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
pantry	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
a	O
carpenter	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
bar	O
that	O
went	O
right	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
casement	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
necessary	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
broke	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
casement	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
got	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
afterwards	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
opened	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
another	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
chissels	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
brought	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
some	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
could	O
join	O
them	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
some	O
plate	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
chissels	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Three	O
chissels	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
chissels	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
there	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
chissels	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
hedge	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
last	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
had	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
punch	O
ladle	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
punch	O
ladle	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
up	O
and	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
near	O
Stoney-lane	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
linen	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Any	O
silver	O
spoons	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
more	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
justly	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
silver	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
it	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
us	O
took	O
the	O
punch	O
ladle	O
?	O
-	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
apron	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Who	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
all	O
sold	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Which	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
?	O
-	O
David	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
they	O
break	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
that	O
was	O
only	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
?	O
What	O
did	O
Baldwin	O
do	O
?	O
-	O
Went	O
in	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
found	O
upon	O
that	O
is	O
produced	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
half	O
dozen	O
of	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
chissels	O
found	O
upon	O
?	O
-	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
chissels	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
to	O
WRIGHT	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
chissels	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
searched	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
near	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
evidence	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
chissel	O
that	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
by	O
a	O
white	O
vein	O
it	O
has	O
runs	O
along	O
the	O
handle	O
(	O
points	O
it	O
out	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
.	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
COURT	O
to	O
WRIGHT	O
.	O
Which	O
was	O
the	O
chissel	O
th	O
at	O
dropped	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
pulled	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
mare	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
with	O
the	O
white	O
raye	O
round	O
the	O
handle	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
in	O
the	O
handle	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
other	O
chissel	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
HEAKENS	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
chissels	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
READ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
parish	O
officer	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
when	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
to	O
join	O
some	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
and	O
Baldwin	O
;	O
David	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
ran	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
afterwards	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
chissel	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
chissels	O
to	O
town	O
to-day	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Heakens	O
to	O
bring	O
into	O
court	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
trial	O
began	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
chissel	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
where	O
the	O
scuffle	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
scuffle	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
shewn	O
where	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
chissel	O
there	O
.	O
Who	O
shewed	O
you	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
scuffle	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HANCOCK	I-pers
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
spot	O
where	O
the	O
scuffle	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
John	O
Hill	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
To	O
JOHN	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
Hancock	O
told	O
you	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
another	O
John	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HANCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
took	O
another	O
;	O
Wright	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
chissel	O
directly	O
almost	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
chissel	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
chissel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
scuffle	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
two	O
horses	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
tied	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
rail	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
town	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
horses	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
his	O
ground	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
pound	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
drive	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
these	O
men	O
coming	O
up	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
BALDWIN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
these	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
hired	O
us	O
to	O
ride	O
the	O
horses	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
271.	O
MARY	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
did	O
forge	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
a	O
certain	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
drawn	O
by	O
one	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
,	O
one	O
month	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
did	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
or	O
her	O
order	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
so	O
falsely	O
made	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
is	O
as	O
followeth	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
1	O
March	O
,	O
1777	O
.	O
50	O
``	O
One	O
month	O
after	O
date	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
``	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
or	O
her	O
order	O
50	O
l.	O
value	O
received	O
.	O
FRENCIS	O
TUTTE	O
.	O
''	O
With	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blades	I-pers
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
2d	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
as	O
true	O
the	O
said	O
note	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
3d	O
Count	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
only	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
4th	O
Count	O
.	O
Same	O
as	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
only	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BLADES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
An	O
upholder	O
and	O
cabinet-maker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Margaret-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
receive	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
owed	O
me	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
for	O
houshold	O
furniture	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
money	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
delivered	O
the	O
furniture	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
,	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
discount	O
it	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
10	O
l.	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
knowing	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
forgeries	O
about	O
I	O
rather	O
suspected	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
cash	O
enough	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
discount	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
my	O
neighbour	O
that	O
lived	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
neighbour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
forged	O
note	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
if	O
she	O
presented	O
that	O
note	O
as	O
a	O
true	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
again	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
rather	O
suspected	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
signature	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
clergyman	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
refused	O
the	O
note	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
note	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
about	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Kensington-gore	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
proceeded	O
to	O
ask	O
several	O
other	O
questions	O
;	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
chuse	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
enquire	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
concerning	O
this	O
note	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
discount	O
the	O
note	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
discount	O
the	O
note	O
without	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
well	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
upon	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
said	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
was	O
at	O
Oxford	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
that	O
that	O
should	O
be	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
was	O
at	O
Oxford	O
that	O
the	O
signature	O
should	O
be	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
another	O
?	O
her	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
town	O
and	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
decline	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
Barnarda	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
name	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
confectioner	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Barnarda	O
would	O
give	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
real	O
note	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
her	O
in	O
suspense	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
enquire	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Barnarda	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
such	O
a	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Strong	O
who	O
is	O
attorney	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
know	O
the	O
signature	O
as	O
he	O
does	O
business	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
for	O
the	O
note	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
elsewhere	O
to	O
get	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Strong	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
produces	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
about	O
between	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
's	O
house	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
;	O
after	O
receiving	O
the	O
note	O
myself	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
said	O
knew	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
the	O
note	O
last	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
I	O
then	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
BLADES	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
you	O
delivered	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
the	O
note	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
offered	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
is	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
of	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BLADES	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
is	O
a	O
foreigner	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
She	O
speaks	O
but	O
indifferent	O
English	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
always	O
understand	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
speaks	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
native	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
note	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
you	O
she	O
remained	O
with	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
enquiries	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
attempt	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Whose	O
note	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
rather	O
suspected	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
tendered	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
the	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
Christian	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
of	O
Kensington-gore	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
lives	O
at	O
Kensington-gore	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
does	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
such	O
man	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
connection	O
between	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
relations	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
advance	O
any	O
money	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
this	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
told	O
you	O
where	O
you	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
off	O
while	O
you	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
enquiry	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
pleased	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
she	O
stay	O
with	O
your	O
wife	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
and	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
enquiry	O
?	O
-	O
Above	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
three	O
hours	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
former	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
real	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
debt	O
contracted	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
present	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
true	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
present	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
true	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
?	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
name	O
Francis	O
was	O
not	O
rightly	O
spelt	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
you	O
know	O
frequently	O
write	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
in	O
haste	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
pardon	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
care	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
writer	O
;	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Ma'am	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
ask	O
,	O
how	O
had	O
you	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
hands	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
not	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
hands	O
;	O
how	O
then	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
sent	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
note	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
walk	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
this	O
evening	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
acknowledges	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
true	O
note	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
upon	O
my	O
honor	O
have	O
cast	O
for	O
it	O
to-morrow	O
morning	O
;	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
by	O
no	O
means	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Oxford	O
;	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
Madam	O
?	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
;	O
how	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
note	O
then	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
note	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
one	O
hand	O
writing	O
,	O
the	O
signature	O
of	O
another	O
;	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
account	O
for	O
that	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
note	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
post	O
to	O
me	O
signed	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
objected	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
indifference	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
or	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
give	O
cash	O
for	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Barnarda	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
an	O
'Italian	O
warehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
perfectly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
and	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
cash	O
for	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
;	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
suspicious	O
thing	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
my	O
friend	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
10	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
advantage	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
true	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
wished	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
evening	O
and	O
walked	O
through	O
the	O
parlour	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
exceeding	O
glad	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
step	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnarda	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnarda	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
story	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
neither	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
or	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
seeing	O
it	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
knowing	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
could	O
acquaint	O
me	O
of	O
every	O
circumstance	O
;	O
he	O
referred	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Strong	O
;	O
happening	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Strong	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Strong	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
all	O
these	O
suspicions	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
that	O
you	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
forgery	O
?	O
-	O
Indirectly	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
her	O
so	O
.	O
Enough	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
understand	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Sufficiently	O
so	O
.	O
She	O
directed	O
you	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Barnarda	O
who	O
had	O
discounted	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
my	O
reasons	O
for	O
saying	O
that	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
your	O
reason	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
staid	O
there	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
while	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
you	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
this	O
note	O
from	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SMART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
of	O
Kensington-gore	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
name	O
subscribed	O
to	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
writing	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
your	O
reasons	O
for	O
not	O
believing	O
it	O
is	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
his	O
usual	O
way	O
of	O
writing	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
usual	O
way	O
of	O
writing	O
,	O
how	O
does	O
he	O
spell	O
his	O
Christian	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
Francis	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
spelt	O
Frencis	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Independent	O
of	O
that	O
circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
spelling	O
being	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
spelling	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
character	O
like	O
his	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Then	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
do	O
you	O
or	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
has	O
sometimes	O
given	O
notes	O
to	O
this	O
lady	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
them	O
sometimes	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Have	O
these	O
declarations	O
of	O
his	O
been	O
since	O
this	O
affair	O
or	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Since	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
is	O
a	O
student	O
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
,	O
Oxford	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
chiefly	O
resides	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
now	O
resides	O
at	O
Kensington-gore	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
appointed	O
committee	O
of	O
a	O
lunatic	O
.	O
But	O
still	O
is	O
a	O
student	O
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
There	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
connections	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
within	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
other	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
,	O
do	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Francis	B-pers
Tutte	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
forged	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
back	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
leave	O
every	O
thing	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
witnesses	O
who	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
JURY	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
note	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
's	O
of	O
Kensington-gore	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blades	O
says	O
they	O
asked	O
the	O
question	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
say	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tutte	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
upon	O
the	O
2d	O
Count	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
note	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
272.	O
ANN	B-pers
FRANKS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Daulton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
7th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
273.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GULLICK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Timothy	I-pers
Dowling	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Timothy	O
,	O
February	O
21st	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
274	O
,	O
275.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WYNER	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ASBERRY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
stuff	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
laced	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
;	O
a	O
worsted	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
6th	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CLARKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
King's-street	B-place
,	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
lodgers	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
those	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
are	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
are	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
Easter	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
Asberry	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
any	O
mercy	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
on	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
SWIFT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
EVERITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
some	O
things	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Clarkson	O
says	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
herself	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
gowns	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Clarkson	O
.	O
]	O
JAMES	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
an	O
apron	O
which	O
was	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
two	O
gowns	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wyner	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
;	O
whether	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
duplicate	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
an	O
apron	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Asberry	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicates	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
Wyner	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
WYNER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Asberry	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
whom	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
.	O
ASBERRY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
through	O
necessity	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
coining	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
supply	O
me	O
with	O
necessaries	O
.	O
WYNER	O
