TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
:	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
1777	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALLIFAX	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
;	O
AND	O
SOLD	O
BY	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
.	O
HALLIFAX	O
,	O
MAYOR	O
.	O
A	O
Common	O
Council	O
holden	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
of	O
the	O
Guildhall	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
First	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
1777	O
.	O
A	O
MOTION	O
being	O
made	O
and	O
QUESTION	O
put	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
beginning	O
with	O
the	O
present	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
every	O
Member	O
of	O
this	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
City	O
Officers	O
who	O
have	O
usually	O
received	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
City	O
's	O
Expence	O
:	O
The	O
same	O
was	O
resolved	O
in	O
the	O
Affirmative	O
.	O
ORDERED	O
,	O
That	O
Messrs.	O
EDWARD	O
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DILLY	I-pers
,	O
Proprieters	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
do	O
deliver	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Serjeants	O
of	O
the	O
Chamber	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Number	O
of	O
Copies	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
of	O
each	O
Session	O
,	O
beginning	O
with	O
the	O
present	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
RIX	O
.	O
GEO	O
.	O
RHODES	O
,	O
Clk	O
.	O
Co	O
,	O
Co	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALLIFAX	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Buxton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carvick	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Benwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burrill	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Couthurst	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Causton	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Churchman	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holroyd	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonnell	I-pers
,	O
Robie	B-pers
Sherwin	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Berresford	I-pers
.	O
[	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
instead	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
]	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pinner	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
Pulham	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
.	O
347.	O
SARAH	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mourning	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
crystal	O
stone	O
and	O
six	O
brilliant	O
diamonds	O
set	O
therein	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
10th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shoe-warehouse	O
in	O
Postern-row	B-place
,	I-place
Tower-hill	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
family	O
mourning	O
ring	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
SMITH	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
ring	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
charity	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
estate	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ring	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
Sunday	O
afternoon	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
FOX	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
ring	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
ring	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
fatherly	O
and	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
little	O
dependence	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
righted	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
will	O
and	O
power	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
lawyer	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
deprive	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
ring	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
;	O
I	O
wore	O
the	O
ring	O
till	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
then	O
being	O
in	O
distress	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs.	O
SMITH	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
ring	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
delivered	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
possession	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
to	O
her	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
had	O
shewn	O
her	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
into	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
missing	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
opened	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
diamond	O
ear-rings	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
ring	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
bought	O
some	O
asparagus	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
348.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
April	O
12th	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
coat	O
to	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
EDMUNDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
coat	O
from	O
his	O
porter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
cart	O
in	O
an	O
inn	O
yard	O
by	O
the	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
frock	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
under	O
his	O
frock	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
coat	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
Taylor	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
fact	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
coat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
as	O
a	O
drover	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
allmost	O
starving	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
349.	O
JANE	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
short	O
quarter	O
of	O
mutton	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
3d	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
350.	O
SARAH	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BLACKBURN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Helmer	I-pers
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Matthew	O
,	O
May	O
5th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERCIVAL	I-pers
sworn	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Helmer	O
,	O
a	O
linen-dradraper	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
up	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
conceal	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
;	O
she	O
afterwards	O
bought	O
some	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Percival	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
counsel	O
,	O
will	O
your	O
lordship	O
please	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
a	O
lady	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
cotton	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
thought	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
do	O
me	O
any	O
harm	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
his	O
pardon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
suspicious	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
my	O
apartments	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
can	O
tell	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
PEAKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
ten	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
rooms	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
drawers	O
unlocked	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
beds	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
things	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
examined	O
every	O
thing	O
since	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
keep	O
any	O
bad	O
company	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
any	O
bad	O
hours	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
extravagant	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
many	O
times	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
upon	O
a	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
potatoes	O
;	O
I	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
did	O
it	O
very	O
honestly	O
and	O
well	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
bought	O
that	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
.	O
PROSECUTOR	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
.	O
-	O
PEAKE	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
and	O
hair-dresser	O
in	O
Little	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
kept	O
house	O
there	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Charles	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
.	O
JURY	O
.	O
What	O
rent	O
do	O
you	O
pay	O
?	O
-	O
Fourteen	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
lease	O
for	O
twenty-one	O
years	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
has	O
taken	O
in	O
washing	O
and	O
plain-work	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
cooper	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
bad	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten	O
pence	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
351.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREENHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Corpe	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
352	O
,	O
353.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assualt	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
seven	O
shilling	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Islington	O
in	O
the	O
Islington	O
stage	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopped	O
upon	O
the	O
City	B-place
road	I-place
near	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Shepherdess	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
their	O
persons	O
;	O
they	O
first	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
Stop	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
;	O
Harris	O
opened	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
;	O
he	O
robbed	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
two	O
ladies	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Suttle	O
and	O
myself	O
;	O
Lucas	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Harris	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
Harris	O
was	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
withdrew	O
from	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
his	O
box	O
and	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
(	O
the	O
coachman	O
came	O
after	O
us	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
acquainted	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
run	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
and	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
just	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
their	O
assistance	O
;	O
they	O
complied	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
ran	O
together	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
's	O
Vinegar-yard	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
opposite	O
the	O
Lying-in	O
Hospital	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
separated	O
;	O
Harris	O
took	O
towards	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
and	O
Lucas	O
towards	O
Old-street	O
road	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
pursued	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
Lucas	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
Lucas	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
persons	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
fire-arms	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
Lucas	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
there	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
brought	O
in	O
Harris	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
this	O
pursuit	O
take	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
Lucas	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
pistols	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
dressed	O
the	O
same	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
much	O
better	O
dressed	O
now	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MERRIT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
last	O
April	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
in	O
the	O
City-road	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
taking	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
directly	O
:	O
I	O
stopped	O
opposite	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
seeing	O
them	O
come	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
Harris	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
Hoxton-square	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
dropped	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
fired	O
the	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
nobody	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
try	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
but	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
then	O
Thomas	O
Brumsdell	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
run	O
or	O
walk	O
when	O
you	O
followed	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
ran	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
his	O
legs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
throwed	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
his	O
pistols	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
cut	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
fingers	O
with	O
his	O
hanger	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
hanger	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
afterwards	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
picked	O
up	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
pistol	O
(	O
a	O
small	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
)	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brumsdell	I-pers
came	O
up	O
;	O
Harris	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
Brumsdell	O
and	O
I	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
Half	O
after	O
eight	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
later	O
than	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
Harris	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
HARRIS	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
has	O
been	O
advised	O
by	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
thief-catchers	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
cast	O
for	O
death	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
40	O
l.	O
all	O
the	O
court	O
laughed	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
falsely	O
;	O
the	O
thief-catcher	O
took	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
cast	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
-	O
MERRIT	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
false	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tussel	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
ball	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRUMSDELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Whitefield	O
's	O
tabernacle	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
coach	O
stop	O
at	O
about	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
or	O
hardly	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
either	O
a	O
hackney	O
or	O
a	O
stage	O
coach	O
;	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
bright	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Merrit	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
some	O
villians	O
have	O
stopped	O
that	O
c	O
oach	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
rob	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
somebody	O
has	O
rode	O
so	O
far	O
and	O
wants	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
and	O
walk	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
almost	O
opposite	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Shepherdess	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
road	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
seemed	O
to	O
step	O
down	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
seeing	O
us	O
stand	O
there	O
,	O
asked	O
us	O
whether	O
we	O
would	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
set	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
ran	O
towards	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
the	O
Hoxton	O
way	O
;	O
Merrit	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
Harris	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
rise	O
of	O
a	O
hill	O
,	O
Merrit	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Harris	O
outran	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Merrit	O
had	O
got	O
Harris	O
down	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Merrit	O
was	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pistol	O
lie	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
tussling	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
tie	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
garter	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bind	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
his	O
hands	O
bound	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
objection	O
I	O
would	O
run	O
him	O
through	O
with	O
the	O
hanger	O
;	O
I	O
bound	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
set	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
Merrit	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
cutlass	O
myself	O
;	O
one	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
we	O
led	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
into	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Hughes	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
you	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
small	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
did	O
you	O
perceive	O
either	O
Harris	O
or	O
Merrit	O
wounded	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
perceived	O
Merrit	O
's	O
hand	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
over	O
bloody	O
.	O
Which	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
pistol	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
charged	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Merrit	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
Lucas	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
road	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
with	O
a	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
candle	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
two	O
straight	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
gave	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Hughes	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
those	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
spent	O
them	O
long	O
ago	O
.	O
HARRIS	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
,	O
now	O
they	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
.	O
BRUMSDELL	O
.	O
The	O
moon	O
was	O
near	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
full	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Almanack	O
was	O
referred	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
moon	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
full	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
]	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
LATIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
work	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
the	O
vinegar-merchant	O
's	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Lucas	O
running	O
along-side	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
scabbard	O
of	O
a	O
cutlass	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
loaded	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
powder	O
and	O
ball	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
sheath	O
of	O
a	O
cutlass	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
(	O
cutlass	O
fitted	O
the	O
sheath	O
exactly	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Cloudy	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
plainly	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
shining	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
moon-light	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
pocket	O
one	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
Crocker	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
]	O
To	O
BRUMSDELL	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
distant	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
Merrit	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
fifty	O
yards	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
fifty	O
yards	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
moon-light	O
then	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
the	O
moon	O
rise	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
rather	O
a	O
dullish	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
moon	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
its	O
appearance	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
:	O
Lucas	O
,	O
Latis	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
run	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
tumbled	O
down	O
;	O
Latis	O
caught	O
Lucas	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
Lucas	O
was	O
running	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
for	O
?	O
Lucas	O
turned	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
because	O
other	O
people	O
ran	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Latis	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
shine	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
HARRIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
people	O
near	O
by	O
the	O
City	O
Lying-inn	O
Hospital	O
holla	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
towards	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
and	O
Shepherdess	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
before	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
cutlass	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
fighting	O
with	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
directly	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
one	O
jumped	O
over	O
some	O
rails	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
immediately	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
thieves	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
cutlass	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
LUCAS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
holiday	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Old-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
men	O
running	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
these	O
men	O
are	O
all	O
connected	O
together	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
blood	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
is	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
swore	O
I	O
cut	O
him	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
blood-money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
justices	O
and	O
they	O
laughed	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
BRUMSDELL	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
assist	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
these	O
thieves	O
?	O
we	O
replied	O
we	O
would	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
Mowbrey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
their	O
recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
]	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Suttle	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SUTTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
the	O
Islington-stage	B-place
;	O
the	O
stage	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
two	O
people	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
very	O
positively	O
to	O
Harris	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
belief	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
Lucas	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
persons	O
behave	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
swore	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
;	O
Harris	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
give	O
me	O
all	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
arms	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
presented	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
;	O
Harris	O
was	O
much	O
confused	O
;	O
first	O
he	O
waved	O
his	O
pistol	O
all	O
round	O
and	O
then	O
presented	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
all	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Behind	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
did	O
he	O
attack	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
rapp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
down	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
guinea	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
day	O
was	O
hardly	O
gone	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
their	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
dress	O
,	O
which	O
rather	O
confused	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
not	O
positive	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Harris	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
said	O
to	O
three	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
pathway	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
assistance	O
?	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
coach	O
stand	O
still	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
Hughes	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
coachman	O
for	O
his	O
assistance	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
came	O
down	O
immediately	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
MOWBREY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Islington	O
stage	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
HARRIS	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
LUCAS	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
354.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
TODD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
jam	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
silk	O
riband	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
1st	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
355.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ELLIOT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
live	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
live	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27th	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
356	O
,	O
357.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MORTIMER	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
covered	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Craig	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
her	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
]	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
358.	O
ANN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	I-pers
indicted	I-pers
by	I-pers
the	I-pers
name	I-pers
of	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
at	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
entering	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
BOWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
;	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
herself	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Smith	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
magistrate	O
called	O
her	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
answered	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Smith	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
359.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MARKS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Spiller	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
360.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CUMMINGS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Augston	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
Mr.	O
Augston	O
:	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
April	O
his	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
my	O
assistance	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
property	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
At	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
his	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
pictures	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Fuller	O
's	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
draught	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
at	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
draughts	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
400	O
l.	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drew	O
this	O
sword	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
some	O
assistance	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
twice	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRESSEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
delivered	O
up	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
from	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
say	O
particularly	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
361.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HAWKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Laforest	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bladen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Caridge	I-pers
,	O
April	O
29th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLADEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
London	O
Tavern	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Laforest	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Caridge	I-pers
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
industrious	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
dishes	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
victuals	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
carry	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
hurry	O
being	O
over	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
to	O
count	O
up	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
bowl	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
bowl	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
words	O
The	O
London	O
Tavern	O
engraved	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
-	O
EDWARDS	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
old	O
plate	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
The	O
London	O
Tavern	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
ruins	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
burnt	O
down	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
questions	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Tavern	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
defaced	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
house	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
362.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
covered	O
with	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLOUGHBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bishop	O
a	O
proctor	O
in	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
Christ	O
's	O
Church	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
crowd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
shoved	O
by	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
moment	O
they	O
shoved	O
me	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
ISAAC	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
soldier	O
Turner	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
dropping	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
case	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
from	O
the	O
church	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
NOAH	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
having	O
strong	O
suspicious	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
soon	O
after	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
the	O
same	O
ground	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUNCASTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
quietly	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Newgate-street	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Ivy-lane	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
somebody	O
calling	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
ran	O
on	O
this	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
running	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
people	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
soldier	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
363.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAMBURY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
April	O
17th	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ROWLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stage-coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mould	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
,	O
having	O
a	O
parcel	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mould	O
in	O
my	O
boot	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
wheel	O
of	O
my	O
coach	O
taking	O
a	O
parcel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Hallow	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
at	O
?	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
between	O
the	O
wheel	O
and	O
the	O
splinter-bar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
bundle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
wheel	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
bundle	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
364	O
,	O
365.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LYNCH	I-pers
and	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
GOODMAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
'There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
'home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
'unconnected	O
with	O
any	O
corroborating	O
'circumstances	O
.	O
'	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
366.	O
ANN	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robson	I-pers
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
April	O
8th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
367.	O
ANN	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
riband	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
week	O
after	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
apartment	O
except	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
but	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
pettycoat	O
,	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
hat	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
birth	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
ANN	B-pers
HETTLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
silly	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
an	O
alarm	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
daughter	O
were	O
selling	O
radishes	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prison	O
Rogers	O
with	O
some	O
money	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
chinking	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
exceedingly	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Mrs.	O
Kettle	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
immediately	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Rogers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
cardinal	O
,	O
hat	O
,	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
riband	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
back	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
home	O
by	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
speaks	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
tried	O
herself	O
twice	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
for	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
368.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
Morocco	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pencil	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
top	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
nippers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
corkscrew	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
April	O
19th	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
369.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BURKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
half-crowns	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
similitude	O
of	O
a	O
half-crown	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wick	I-pers
,	O
May	O
1st	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
WICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wick	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Worcester-street	O
,	O
Old-gravel-lane	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
prison	O
on	O
some	O
business	O
;	O
the	O
children	O
were	O
walking	O
in	O
procession	O
to	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
sermon	O
;	O
the	O
crowd	O
was	O
very	O
great	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
steps	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
or	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
half-crowns	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
half-crown	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
bad	O
half-crown	O
,	O
the	O
head	O
stands	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
the	O
new	O
halfpence	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Old-gravel-lane	O
when	O
the	O
children	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
A	O
pick-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
likewise	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
while	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
half-crowns	O
amongst	O
it	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
church	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
her	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
pocket	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
yours	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
370.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRASIER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
371.	O
MARTIN	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
live	O
lambs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
372	O
,	O
373.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
pompadore	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shepherdson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3d	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
374	O
,	O
375	O
,	O
376.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FRANTER	I-pers
,	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PAGGOTT	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARGARET	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
HARTLEY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
fifty-six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
scrapings	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bewley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
,	O
well-knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
7th	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
377.	O
MARY	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
patent	O
net-caul	O
for	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
,	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LANGSTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Jarvis	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Langston	I-pers
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
last	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
patent	O
cauls	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
tea	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
her	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
caul	O
while	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
reaching	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
back	O
by	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
net-caul	O
between	O
her	O
petticoats	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
missed	O
several	O
things	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
five	O
cauls	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
reach	O
some	O
lace	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
four	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
directly	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
four	O
cauls	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
lappets	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
378.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PAUL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hoole	I-pers
,	O
May	O
1st	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
HOOLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
undertaker	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
WOODWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
Clarke	B-place
's	I-place
buildings	I-place
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
he	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
which	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
beaufet	O
;	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
beaufet	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tongs	O
and	O
spoons	O
through	O
necessity	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
by	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
379.	O
BARNARD	B-pers
RILEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
linen	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOVEGROVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	O
in	O
the	O
meat	O
way	O
:	O
my	O
man	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
cloaths	O
in	O
his	O
basket	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
with	O
meat	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
accountable	O
for	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
lost	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lovegrove	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
opposite	O
the	O
stall	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
step	O
down	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
cloths	O
in	O
his	O
basket	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
straw	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
cloths	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stall	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
these	O
cloths	O
?	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
hired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
excuse	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
misfortunes	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
380.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BRITAIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
killing	O
and	O
slaying	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
by	O
divers	O
times	O
striking	O
,	O
beating	O
and	O
casting	O
and	O
throwing	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
divers	O
mortal	O
bruises	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
breast	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
bruises	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
April	O
16th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JOYCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
pass	O
between	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
the	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
DAVID	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
man	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
off	O
his	O
cattle	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
symptoms	O
of	O
an	O
oppressed	O
brain	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
vomitting	O
and	O
purging	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
raised	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
external	O
mark	O
of	O
any	O
injury	O
;	O
I	O
dissected	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
died	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
assign	O
as	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
that	O
you	O
suppose	O
the	O
man	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
death	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
brain	O
had	O
received	O
some	O
contusion	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
him	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
die	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
of	O
a	O
fall	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BUXTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
public	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
London	I-place
Apprentice	I-place
;	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
free	O
together	O
,	O
some	O
other	O
persons	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Britain	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Lewis	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
an	O
interloper	O
himself	O
;	O
Britain	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
other	O
;	O
so	O
one	O
word	O
brought	O
up	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
fight	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
directly	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
fight	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
exactly	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
several	O
blows	O
and	O
falls	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
stirred	O
nor	O
moved	O
hardly	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
set	O
on	O
a	O
seat	O
and	O
his	O
hand	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
at	O
all	O
afterwards	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
damage	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fair	O
battle	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
foul	O
blows	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
watering-time	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
challenged	O
one	O
another	O
to	O
fight	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
fought	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
fall	O
which	O
occasioned	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
death	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROOKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stay-maker	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
my	O
board	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
fighting	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
both	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
neck	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
joint	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
any	O
body	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
doctor	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
supposed	O
his	O
neck	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
381.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
clover-seed	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Fillingham	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
and	O
sell	O
saloop	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
many	O
years	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
my	O
faloop	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
some	O
clover-seed	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fill	O
his	O
side-pockets	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
seed	O
was	O
in	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
was	O
cut	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
cut	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
people	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
but	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clarkson	O
who	O
had	O
landed	O
the	O
seed	O
,	O
the	O
seed	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fillingham	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
bag	O
of	O
this	O
clover-seed	O
cut	O
open	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
receiving	O
information	O
from	O
Griffiths	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
seed	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
seed	O
sticking	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
seed	O
had	O
been	O
emptied	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
REEVES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
;	O
being	O
the	O
watchman	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
losses	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
382.	O
SARAH	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
fenders	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clapham	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
15th	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WORSOP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
tap	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
with	I-place
Two-necks	I-place
in	I-place
Lad-lane	I-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
kept	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clapham	I-pers
:	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
something	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
fender	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
brass	O
fenders	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
tap	O
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
witness	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
two	O
fenders	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
stairs	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Clapham	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
fenders	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
383.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
11th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
her	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
]	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
384.	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
GARDINER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PHIPPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Bull	I-place
in	I-place
Cow-lane	I-place
,	I-place
West	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Grinley	O
the	O
constable	O
saw	O
me	O
stop	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
other	O
pots	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pot	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
gentleman	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
385.	O
MARY	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
MITCHELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
May	O
2d	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HAYWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
9	B-place
,	I-place
Snowhill	I-place
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
linen	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JAMES	B-pers
HAYWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pothecary	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
linen	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cloak	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
;	O
one	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
who	O
bought	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
customer	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
conversation	O
pass	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
Pothecary	O
?	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
linen	O
her	O
sister	O
had	O
bought	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
cleaved	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
POTHECARY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
which	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
sister	O
bought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
;	O
on	O
observing	O
them	O
turn	O
the	O
things	O
over	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
especially	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
meant	O
to	O
steal	O
something	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
several	O
things	O
:	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
patern	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
on	O
turning	O
round	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shook	O
vastly	O
and	O
turned	O
pale	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
kept	O
her	O
arm	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
side	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
linen	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
base	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
stuck	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
mistake	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
my	O
sister	O
had	O
bought	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
it	O
cleaved	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
die	O
this	O
minute	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
386	O
,	O
387.	O
ANN	B-pers
ELLIOTT	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
brown	O
camblet	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
mourning	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Alloway	I-pers
,	O
April	O
10th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ALLOWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Liquor	B-place
Pond-street	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
last	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
gowns	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
lay	O
dead	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
and	O
was	O
buried	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
of	O
cloaths	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
publican	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
go	O
by	O
wit	O
h	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
drop	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Laystall-street	O
;	O
something	O
rattled	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bundle	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
black	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GOODMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Laystall-street	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
black	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HORTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
burial	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
mother-in-law	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
apartment	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pulled	O
off	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
and	O
the	O
undertaker	O
put	O
the	O
cloak	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
undertaker	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
us	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
us	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
funeral	O
;	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
deceased	O
some	O
years	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
388	O
,	O
389.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BANGAY	I-pers
and	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
May	O
7th	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
BOX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Bethnall-green	B-place
in	I-place
a	I-place
tenter-ground	I-place
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
shirts	O
which	O
were	O
hung	O
out	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
shirts	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
directly	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
about	O
the	O
place	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
neighbours	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
immediately	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
marked	O
;	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Paternoster-row	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Batson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
tenter-ground	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Hall	O
had	O
the	O
shirts	O
loose	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
Bangay	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
apron	O
to	O
wrap	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
they	O
wrapped	O
the	O
shirts	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
apron	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Coming	O
down	O
the	O
walk	O
on	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
see	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
linen	O
?	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Who	O
made	O
that	O
answer	O
?	O
-	O
Hall	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
both	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
apron	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
at	O
the	O
buildings	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
scaffold	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Hall	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
wanted	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bald	O
Stag	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
Manwarring	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
HALL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
BANGAY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
>	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
Woman	O
lay	O
side	O
by	O
side	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
;	O
the	O
bundle	O
lay	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
bundle	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
390.	O
ANN	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25th	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Seven-dials	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
printed	O
linens	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
different	O
patterns	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
buy	O
what	O
they	O
liked	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
,	O
containing	O
24	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
rod	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cloth	O
concealed	O
in	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
stoop	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
You	O
seized	O
her	O
immediately	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
the	O
gentleman	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
woman	O
dropped	O
it	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
391.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
callico	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joshua	O
,	O
May	O
5th	O
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
MEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-court	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
muslin	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
muslin	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mead	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
some	O
ladies	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
by	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
ladies	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
come	O
back	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ladies	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pattern	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
cut	O
off	O
a	O
pattern	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
ladies	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
Mr.	O
Ball	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
two	O
girls	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
muslin	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
ours	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
by	O
the	O
cut	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BELCHIER	I-pers
BALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
Newport-alley	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
girls	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
shop-lifters	O
by	O
their	O
having	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
their	O
arms	O
and	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
kept	O
looking	O
behind	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
observed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
several	O
shops	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
cloth	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
woman	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
come	O
towards	O
us	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
at	O
my	O
feet	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
392.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BURNE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Southey	I-pers
,	O
April	O
29th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SOUTHEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
public-house	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Mullings	O
's	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
her	O
head	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Young	O
man	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
Dyot-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
my	O
things	O
off	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
you	O
found	O
your	O
things	O
gone	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
you	O
besides	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
one	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
we	O
laid	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
wake	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
twelve	O
or	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
recovered	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
with	O
my	O
stockings	O
on	O
her	O
legs	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
round-house	O
:	O
this	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
change	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
sitting	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
his	O
stockings	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
magistrate	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
stockings	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
unfortunately	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
doing	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
harbour	O
nothing	O
but	O
such	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
these	O
stockings	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
young	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
To	O
SOUTHEY	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
stockings	O
left	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
her	O
stockings	O
were	O
,	O
her	O
shoes	O
were	O
left	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
liquor	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Who	O
proposed	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
you	O
or	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
bed	O
myself	O
.	O
Who	O
proposed	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
herself	O
;	O
she	O
knows	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
my	O
God	O
!	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
or	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
393.	O
SARAH	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
HALSEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
check	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lilwell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20th	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
goods	O
she	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
child	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
394.	O
MARY	B-pers
M'CARTY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cotton	O
jam	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14th	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
my	O
apartment	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
table	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
M'Carty	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
disown	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
who	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
395.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COX	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
the	O
kingdom	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
term	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
conviction	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
examined	O
that	O
copy	O
with	O
the	O
original	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Follett	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
copy	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
assize	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
tried	O
at	O
Salisbury	O
in	O
the	O
Summer	O
assize	O
1773	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
forgery	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
then	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELEY	I-pers
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
Chandos-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
trial	O
at	O
Salisbury	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
for	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
America	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
returning	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Thompson	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
America	O
at	O
Baltimore	O
:	O
one	O
Captain	O
Grice	B-pers
,	O
captain	O
of	O
a	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
Provincials	O
,	O
entreated	O
and	O
almost	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
company	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
force	O
him	O
into	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
forced	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
employment	O
or	O
livelihood	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
failed	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
he	O
failed	O
;	O
they	O
threaten	O
there	O
if	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
companies	O
to	O
tar	O
and	O
feather	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
settled	O
there	O
in	O
business	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
trade	O
was	O
stopped	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
business	O
for	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
I	O
failed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sailed	O
for	O
Lisbon	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bound	O
for	O
Lisbon	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
ship	O
was	O
bound	O
for	O
Lisbon	O
;	O
he	O
entered	O
as	O
a	O
sailor	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
in	O
at	O
Norfolk	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
having	O
sprung	O
a	O
leak	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
;	O
to	O
my	O
certain	O
knowledge	O
he	O
shipped	O
himself	O
for	O
Lisbon	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
396.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HATTELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
ells	O
of	O
yard-wide	O
black	O
alamode	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Hattell	I-pers
,	O
April	O
21st	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
397.	O
JAMES	B-pers
NEWBERY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
knowing	O
that	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
had	O
lately	O
served	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
frigate	O
or	O
ship	O
of	O
war	O
called	O
the	O
Acteon	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
respect	O
of	O
his	O
service	O
,	O
did	O
personate	O
and	O
assume	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
with	O
intent	O
to	O
demand	O
and	O
receive	O
the	O
wages	O
then	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15th	O
.	O
ADAM	B-pers
JELLICOE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
treasurer	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
navy	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
applied	O
