TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1777	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIRST	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
31	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
M.DCC.LXXVII	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
Kn	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ASTON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bch	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAHMONT	O
HOTHAM	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Sherbone	I-pers
,	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Emery	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cover	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Viven	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mace	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edmondson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Gimbert	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Thorncastle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Venables	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tetlow	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Whiteside	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jover	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stennell	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Brownell	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STORER	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BLAKEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
(	O
Ann	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
white	O
linnen	O
bed-quilt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
time-piece	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
tobacco-box	O
set	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shagreen	O
knife-case	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
mode	O
cloak	O
trimmed	O
with	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
NEWBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
merchant	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tokenhouse	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
likewise	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
the	O
preceding	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
PENNY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newby	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
went	O
accidentally	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Storer	O
at	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
two	O
men	O
sent	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
looks	O
towards	O
a	O
field	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
cloth	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
napkin	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
upon	O
Storer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
knife-case	O
hid	O
under	O
some	O
rubbish	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Blakey	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
ages	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
understand	O
Storer	O
is	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
Blakey	O
twelve	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
recovered	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HATFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
Storer	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
ge	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
Blakey	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
connected	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
Blakey	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Blakey	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
Storer	O
had	O
had	O
this	O
tobacco-box	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
some	O
rubbish	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Newby	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tobacco-box	O
.	O
STORER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
BLAKEY	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
STORER	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s	O
.	O
BLAKEY	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STORER	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BLAKEY	I-pers
were	O
(	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
)	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
September	O
20th	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
at	O
about	O
twelve	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
Storer	O
.	O
)	O
STORER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
.	O
BLAKEY	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
STORER	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
BLAKEY	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
SEBASTIAN	B-pers
BISHOP	I-pers
LAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Janetta	B-pers
Nettleton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
September	O
12th	O
.	O
JANETTA	O
NETTLETON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
my	O
sister	O
in	O
Charles-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Portland-Square	I-place
;	O
she	O
lets	O
lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
apron	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
among	O
the	O
dirty	O
linnen	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CHURCHMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
this	O
apron	O
and	O
these	O
ruffles	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
seven	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
,	O
Thompson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
customer	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
questions	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FREE	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BEAUMONT	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
small	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
360	O
halfpence	O
and	O
1056	O
farthings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
then	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Cow-Lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
standing	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
bar	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
hand	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
put	O
through	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
halfpence	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
there	O
the	O
preceding	O
day	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
exactly	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
forty	O
shillings	O
worth	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
barred	O
and	O
locked	O
both	O
the	O
doors	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
boy	O
's	O
having	O
been	O
stopped	O
with	O
some	O
half-pence	O
;	O
that	O
led	O
to	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
this	O
basket	O
and	O
the	O
halfpence	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
halfpence	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
basket	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
halfpence	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
paper	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
likewise	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
it	O
contains	O
farthings	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HALLIDAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
James	O
Hall	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
a	O
link	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
basket	O
hid	O
under	O
some	O
stones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GAHAGAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
ELIZABETH	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
M'Donald	I-pers
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
money	O
payable	O
and	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
bank	O
note	O
being	O
then	O
duo	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
to	O
James	B-pers
M'Donald	I-pers
the	O
proprietor	O
thereof	O
.	O
-	O
Against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
picture	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
garnet	O
stones	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
stone	O
rings	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
enamel	O
'd	O
mourning	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
box	O
made	O
of	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
and	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
box	O
made	O
of	O
ivory	O
and	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
soup	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
eight	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
M'Donald	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
M'Donald	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
Lord	I-place
Tyrawley's-head	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
High-street	I-place
,	I-place
Marybone	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
twenty-pound	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
in	O
change	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
into	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
drawer	O
were	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
eight	O
half	O
guineas	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
it	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
to	O
weigh	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
changed	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
;	O
the	O
twenty	O
pound	O
Bank	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
money	O
and	O
rings	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Lord	O
Tyrawley's-head	O
:	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
my	O
wife	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
weigh	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
;	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
nick	O
in	O
the	O
eye	O
,	O
likewise	O
in	O
the	O
G	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
line	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
constable	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
these	O
marks	O
upon	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Gahagan	O
's	O
:	O
to	O
my	O
recollection	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
particular	O
half	O
guinea	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
count	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-four	O
guineas	O
and	O
eight	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Bank	O
Note	O
was	O
changed	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
money	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witness	O
inspected	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
MACDONALD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Lord	O
Tyrawley's-head	O
,	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
to	O
have	O
stole	O
this	O
money	O
;	O
accordingly	O
myself	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
Gahagan	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
only	O
Gahagan	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
search	O
t	O
he	O
cupboard	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Gahagan	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
contained	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
sewed	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
which	O
together	O
made	O
nine	O
guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Macdonald	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
guineas	O
was	O
very	O
remarkable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
in	O
Gahagan	O
's	O
passage	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
trial	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Gahagan	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
money	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
What	O
she	O
said	O
is	O
not	O
evidence	O
.	O
-	O
Her	O
husband	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
GAHAGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
Gahagan	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
work	O
again	O
till	O
after	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
M'Donald	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
M'Donald	O
's	O
house	O
I	O
saw	O
Gahagan	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
pass	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
their	O
legs	O
through	O
the	O
rails	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
YORK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Gahagan	I-pers
;	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
two	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
hammer	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
use	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
this	O
chamber	O
a-jar	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
that	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
of	O
Gahagan	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Gahagan	O
himself	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Gahagan	O
's	O
wife	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
the	O
tin	O
box	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
.	O
Gahagan	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
McDonald	O
had	O
not	O
exposed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
hit	O
,	O
or	O
right	O
way	O
of	O
getting	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GAHAGAN	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
got	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
labour	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GAHAGAN	I-pers
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
THORNTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Gahagan	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gahagan	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
wife	O
then	O
lay	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gahagan	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
emptied	O
several	O
guineas	O
and	O
half	O
guineas	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
She	O
offered	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
so	O
much	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
only	O
took	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
YORKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
-	O
York	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
examined	O
.	O
Gahagan	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
took	O
task	O
work	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
these	O
last	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
sometimes	O
30	O
,	O
sometimes	O
27	O
or	O
25	O
s.	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
Mr.	O
M'Donald	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
along	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GAHAGAN	I-pers
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GAHAGAN	I-pers
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
6.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
POPE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
Japan	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
-	O
pieces	O
of	O
christal	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
seventeen	O
pieces	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
enameled	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
forty	O
pieces	O
of	O
paste	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
Mocoa	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
ear-ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
mounted	O
with	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Usener	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
FREDERICK	B-pers
USENER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
being	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
abroad	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
USENER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
upon	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
parlour	O
window	O
in	O
Albemarle-street	B-place
wide	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
shutters	O
not	O
shut	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
jumped	O
in	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
hat	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
tried	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
satisfied	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sexton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Murrell	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
also	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sexton	O
seized	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
stones	O
and	O
paste	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
box	O
and	O
its	O
contents	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Usener	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MURRELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Sexton	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
containing	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
immediately	O
claimed	O
the	O
box	O
as	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
bureau	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
easy	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
area	O
into	O
this	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
is	O
very	O
narrow	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SEXTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Murrell	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
mud	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
wiping	O
myself	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
at	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
lives	O
;	O
seeing	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
men	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
beat	O
me	O
for	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
then	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
square	O
,	O
two	O
towards	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
,	O
they	O
throwed	O
my	O
hat	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NORTH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bey	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CLEMENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
at	O
Isleworth	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
or	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
grass	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
eight	O
mile	O
stone	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
preceding	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Furning	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
horse	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FURNING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
sent	O
Downing	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
at	O
the	O
turnpikes	O
after	O
North	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
intelligence	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
Colbrooke	O
turnpike	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
at	O
another	O
turnpike	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
through	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
farther	O
intelligence	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
wrote	O
letters	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
friends	O
near	O
Marlborough	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Marlborough	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
mother-in-law	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
John	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
his	O
mother	O
hesitated	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
stairs	O
of	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
we	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
horse	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
horse	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
poney	O
his	O
master	O
rode	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sack	O
and	O
halter	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sack	O
and	O
halter	O
missing	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
together	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
again	O
where	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
begged	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Inn	O
,	O
near	O
Hungerford	O
and	O
Newberry	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
inn-keeper	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
received	O
one	O
pound	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DOWNING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
between	O
Brentford	O
and	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
smoaking	O
a	O
pipe	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
boy	O
for	O
his	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
said	O
,	O
North	O
had	O
gone	O
away	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
supposed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
Furning	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
at	O
several	O
turnpikes	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
intelligence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Marlborough	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
his	O
mother-in-law	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
when	O
we	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
us	O
and	O
hesitated	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
who	O
wanted	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
enough	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
Furning	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
what	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
stealing	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
horse	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
they	O
would	O
set	O
me	O
free	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
you	O
promise	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
confessed	O
where	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
him	O
free	O
.	O
DOWNING	O
and	O
FURNING	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
made	O
him	O
any	O
such	O
promise	O
,	O
Question	O
to	O
Downing	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
lodge	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
8.	O
EMANUEL	B-pers
SIMON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	I-pers
privily	I-pers
and	I-pers
secretly	I-pers
from	I-pers
the	I-pers
person	I-pers
of	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
November	O
10th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
9	O
,	O
10	O
,	O
11.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
,	O
HARRIETT	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
WARE	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
broken	O
silver	O
lamp	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Kandler	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
FREDERICK	B-pers
KANDLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
Jermin	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gold	O
heart	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
shew	O
them	O
any	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
the	O
tallest	O
(	O
Ware	O
)	O
advanced	O
further	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
only	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
one	O
(	O
Harriett	O
Davis	O
)	O
catched	O
up	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
immediately	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
this	O
silver	O
cup	O
and	O
broken	O
lamp	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
just	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
A	O
carter	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
yard	O
in	O
York-street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
were	O
secured	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
searched	O
their	O
lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
mine	O
found	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carter	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lamp	O
and	O
cup	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COLWELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
Nassau	O
skin	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
,	O
October	O
19th	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
they	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Or	O
did	O
you	O
pick	O
them	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
twice	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
woman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
her	O
hands	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Near	O
Charing	B-place
Cross	I-place
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
any	O
one	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
nobody	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
last	O
Monday	O
from	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Waters	O
the	O
watchman	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
WATERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
call	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
gentleman	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
mentioned	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASTON	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
SIDNEY	B-pers
MACDONALD	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
diaper	O
clouting	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
sheeting	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
clear	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHIELDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
stopping	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
linen	O
under	O
their	O
feet	O
.	O
-	O
SHIELDS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
shed	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
this	O
linen	O
which	O
was	O
making	O
up	O
against	O
my	O
lying-in	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
shut	O
it	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
making	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
latched	O
the	O
door	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
twelve	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GARLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
more	O
footpads	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
between	O
Stepney	B-place
and	O
Mile-End	B-place
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
accomplice	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
uncorroborated	O
.	O
]	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
STEVENSON	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAVEN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
glass	O
lamps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
tin	O
heads	O
for	O
lamps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
tin	O
burners	O
for	O
lamps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Collison	I-pers
,	O
November	O
25	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
COLLISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tin-plate	O
worker	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
upon	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
alm-houses	O
at	O
Shoreditch	B-place
and	O
Kingsland	B-place
turnpike	I-place
.	O
They	O
were	O
lamps	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
contract	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ARMSTRONG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
lamps	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
Kingsland-Road	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
light	O
the	O
lamps	O
on	O
the	O
Kingsland-Road	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
lamp	O
(	O
pointing	O
it	O
out	O
)	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
.	O
I	O
placed	O
it	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
just	O
by	O
Shoreditch	O
workhouse	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
safe	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
at	O
twelve-o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WALTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrole	O
on	O
Kingsland-Road	O
:	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
from	O
Kingsland	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
right	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
KIDGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
two	O
lamps	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
one	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
first	O
said	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Savage	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Kingsland	O
;	O
afterwards	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Kingsland-Road	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
lamps	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
lamps	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDMUNDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
these	O
lamps	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
hard-working	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
lamps	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
drink	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
patrole	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
watchmen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
liquor	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Question	O
to	O
Walton	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
this	O
pass	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
Kingsland	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BORDEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
hundred	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
ten	O
pards	O
of	O
plain	O
gauze	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
six	O
hundred	O
and	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
blond	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
four	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
twelve	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
five	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
white	O
thread	O
edging	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
Persian	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
alamode	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
COLLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
milliner	O
's	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
95	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
my	O
shop-woman	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
all	O
my	O
doors	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
shopwoman	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
returned	O
instantly	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
marks	O
of	O
dirty	O
feet	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
with	O
a	O
crow	O
;	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
more	O
goods	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
counter	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
where	O
the	O
valuable	O
things	O
were	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
thence	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
case	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
reading	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
all	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
padlock	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
Miss	O
Jennings	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
likewise	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
goods	O
in	O
Holland	O
's	O
house	O
which	O
she	O
thought	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Miss	O
Jennings	O
to	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
bundles	O
containing	O
some	O
goods	O
of	O
mine	O
intermixed	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
Miss	O
Jennings	O
's	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
the	O
headborough	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HOLLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
That	O
bundle	O
my	O
wife	O
bought	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
screw	O
in	O
the	O
shutter	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
square	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
out	O
.	O
Somebody	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
got	O
through	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
unfastened	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
alarmed	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
down	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
one	O
Harris	O
;	O
but	O
Harris	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
This	O
witness	O
deposed	O
that	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
were	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
BENJAMIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Little	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
,	O
Spital	O
Fields	O
;	O
I	O
sell	O
linnens	O
,	O
ribbons	O
and	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
this	O
bundle	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
lot	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
another	O
lot	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Confine	O
your	O
evidence	O
to	O
what	O
you	O
bought	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
others	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
a	O
dozen	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
as	O
old	O
shop-keepers	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
only	O
bought	O
these	O
two	O
lots	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
pedlars	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
wife	O
once	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Fair	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
bought	O
by	O
this	O
witness	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
fitting	O
by	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
with	O
this	O
bundle	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
goods	O
hid	O
under	O
some	O
cloaths	O
and	O
some	O
baskets	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
gave	O
forty	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Harris	O
.	O
[	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ELBEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
at	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Forrester	O
at	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
goods	O
.	O
[	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BANT	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
innocent	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Drummond	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
DRUMMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
)	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
on	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Drummond	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Forrester	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
herself	O
his	O
wife	O
at	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
passed	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
among	O
all	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
She	O
offered	O
me	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
prisoner	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
COURT	O
to	O
Drummond	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
only	O
day	O
upon	O
which	O
you	O
ever	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Harris	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
O	O
yes	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
November	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
that	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
any	O
goods	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
but	O
that	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
at	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
and	O
half	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
was	O
there	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
days	O
?	O
-	O
Three	O
days	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
Harris	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
house-keeper	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
parrot	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
debt	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
shop-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
goods	O
on	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
had	O
lain	O
by	O
him	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
because	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
are	O
here	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tillings	O
a	O
shopkeeper	O
in	O
Cloth	O
Fair	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
Harris	O
is	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
since	O
.	O
Harris	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
us	O
before	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
LOCKYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Cow-Cross	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Harris	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
have	O
carried	O
purl	O
and	O
such	O
liquors	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
these	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
when	O
Harris	O
has	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
Mrs.	O
Borden	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
a	O
payment	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
likewise	O
,	O
called	O
Edward	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
-	O
Croker	O
,	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
-	O
Drake	O
,	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Idingslon	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
18.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
AVERY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
cutting	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chopping	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
lead	O
being	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
called	O
a	O
stable	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
CHOPPING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Chopping	I-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
keeps	O
livery	O
stables	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
these	O
stables	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
dog	O
bark	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ripping	O
the	O
lead	O
off	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
The	O
prisoner	O
heard	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
off	O
the	O
building	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
.	O
He	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
He	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
large	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
ripped	O
,	O
and	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
tinder	O
and	O
matches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
slint	O
and	O
steel	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
.	O
Another	O
witness	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
off	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
quartered	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
quarters	O
at	O
near	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
past	O
Hyde-Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
collared	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
rip	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
easily	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
alone	O
.	O
He	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
19.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
STARR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
men	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
GREENHILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hat-maker	O
at	O
Brentford	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
hats	O
on	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
work-shop	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
Hanwell	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
hats	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
serve	O
his	O
time	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
prosecuting	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
riotously	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
hats	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
testimony	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LAWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
scythe	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
of	O
potatoes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
farmer	O
at	O
Poplar	B-place
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
potatoe-field	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
potatoes	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
dug	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
scytbe	O
of	O
his	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
field	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
wrong	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
potatoes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
scythe	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
21.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ALKIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
engine	O
screws	O
made	O
of	O
mixed	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
,	O
October	O
23d	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HADLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
engine-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live-in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Pockham	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
took	O
these	O
screws	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hadley	O
's	O
men	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
screws	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
screws	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bagg	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13th	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BAGG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Friday	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
at	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
against	O
me	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
turned	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
caught	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
immediately	O
cried	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
something	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
drew	O
my	O
pocket	O
almost	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
My	O
money	O
was	O
lose	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
women	O
.	O
She	O
shoved	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
their	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
one	O
else	O
near	O
when	O
her	O
hand	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
so	O
near	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
they	O
come	O
up	O
and	O
blasted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
christening	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drank	O
rather	O
more	O
than	O
did	O
me	O
good	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
;	O
two	O
women	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
both	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
a	O
thimble	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
loosed	O
my	O
hands	O
till	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
,	O
24.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MINSHER	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLOAK	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventy	O
yards	O
of	O
raw-silk	O
,	O
value	O
60	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
hempen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Streeton	I-pers
,	O
Bryant	B-pers
Trotton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STREETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Bryant	B-pers
Trotton	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
dined	O
abroad	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
misfortune	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
with	O
some	O
silk	O
to	O
an	O
inn	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Streeton	O
and	O
Company	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
some	O
silk	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
on	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
hamper	O
and	O
a	O
truss	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
hamper	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
truss	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
on	O
any	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
immediately	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LEVI	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
the	O
rotation-office	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
three	O
suspicious	O
persons	O
were	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Bull	O
with	O
three	O
bundles	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Hawes	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
man	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
one	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Minsher	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
with	O
three	O
bundles	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
them	O
.	O
Hawes	O
asked	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
in	O
New-Court	O
,	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
silk	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
silk	O
advertised	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HAWES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
Minsher	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
a	O
coachman	O
take	O
a	O
hamper	O
down	O
the	O
inn-yard	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
coachman	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
Minsher	O
opened	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
truss	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
in	O
New-Court	O
,	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
afterwards	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
were	O
secured	O
.	O
MINSHER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
Hawes	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
m	O
e.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
New-Court	O
,	O
Fleet-Market	O
.	O
He	O
tied	O
some	O
silk	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handerchief	O
of	O
Cloak	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
silk	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
.	O
CLOAK	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Hawes	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bull's-Head	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Minsher	O
:	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Cloak	O
:	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
,	O
26.	O
ANN	B-pers
HAWKINS	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SUMMERS	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
October	O
30	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRUNSELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
mehere	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
informed	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
have	O
a	O
cloak	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
overtook	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
cloak	O
under	O
Summers	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
cloak	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
Brunsell	O
deposed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
HAWKINS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
SUMMER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
cloak	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
HAWKINS	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
SUMMERS	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
JANE	B-pers
BRISTOW	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plain	O
gold	O
earrings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
stone	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Bazier	I-pers
,	O
October	O
22d	O
.	O
JACOB	B-pers
BAZIER	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Negro	O
)	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
for	O
a	O
seal	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
change	O
,	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
earrings	O
and	O
ring	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
that	O
box	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
you	O
can	O
see	O
them	O
here	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
snatched	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
the	O
rings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
by	O
sight	O
.	O
-	O
SWEETMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
share	O
when	O
you	O
stole	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
ear-rings	O
from	O
the	O
black	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
black	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Justices	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
Sweetman	O
company	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
left	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
grudge	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
HAMMOND	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
nephew	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
coach-master	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
an	O
old	O
cloth	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
upon	O
a	O
coach-box	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
out	O
till	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FULLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
three	O
tuns	O
,	O
seeing	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
;	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
from	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
hammer	O
cloth	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
EVAN	B-pers
STEPHENS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
October	O
21st	O
.	O
MACDONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-court	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-first	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
waiting	O
on	O
two	O
ladies	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
my	O
young	O
woman	O
ran	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
our	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
windows	O
are	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-two	O
piles	O
of	O
cloths	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
afterwards	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Macdonald	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
,	O
minutes	O
in	O
White	O
Hart-yard	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
fell	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
groud	O
in	O
Russel-court	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
stumbled	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
wrapped	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eighteen	O
or	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
cloth	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cloth	O
in	O
motion	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
from	O
Russel	O
Court	O
to	O
White	O
Hart	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
WILSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-first	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
twenty-two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
at	O
night	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
dropp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
green	O
cloaths	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
green	O
cloaths	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
mistres	O
's	O
cloth	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
denied	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
.	O
31.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
on	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
featherbed	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
bolsters	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
dressing-glass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
mattrass	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
window	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
night	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
oval	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
Wilton	O
carpets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
paper	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Geneva	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
country-house	O
near	O
Marybone	B-place
fields	I-place
,	O
where	O
my	O
family	O
are	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Summer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
received	O
intelligence	O
that	O
my	O
country-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
safe	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
On	O
receiving	O
intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
cross	O
a	O
field	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
Anderson	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
a	O
publichouse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Blackborough	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
most	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bostick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
watch-house	O
keeper	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
rooms	O
below	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Had	O
that	O
window	O
been	O
secured	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
staircase	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
casement	O
which	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
button	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
bed	O
room	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
together	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BOSTICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
by	O
three	O
watchmen	O
who	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Islington-Road	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
escaped	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
my	O
partner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
stop	O
three	O
men	O
he	O
suspected	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Between	O
us	O
we	O
stopped	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
near	O
the	O
Angel	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
three	O
large	O
bundles	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
their	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
running	O
away	O
from	O
their	O
landlord	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
owed	O
rent	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
coming	O
loaded	O
with	O
three	O
bundles	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
by	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
stopped	O
them	O
near	O
the	O
Angel	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bundles	O
opened	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
bundles	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
person	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
cloud	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
these	O
things	O
off	O
for	O
fear	O
his	O
landlord	O
should	O
seize	O
them	O
.	O
TURNER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
.	O
Turner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
FOR	O
ANDERSON	O
.	O
-	O
REDGRAVE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
justices	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
mercy	O
made	O
to	O
Anderson	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
discovery	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
by	O
Justice	O
Blackborough	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
very	O
honestly	O
give	O
the	O
best	O
information	O
he	O
could	O
respecting	O
his	O
Confederates	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
discovery	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
every	O
information	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
true	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
successful	O
enough	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
persons	O
.	O
Anderson	O
seemed	O
very	O
affected	O
and	O
sensible	O
of	O
his	O
faults	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
promised	O
him	O
mercy	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
all	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
accomplices	O
to	O
justice	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
has	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
ill.	O
TURNER	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
ANDERSON	B-pers
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Hubert	B-pers
Pent	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cheque	O
mattrasses	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hubert	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
HUBERT	B-pers
PENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-James-Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
country-house	O
near	O
the	O
country-house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
a	O
neighbour	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
windows	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
on	O
one	O
floor	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
bottom	O
parts	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
mattrasses	O
,	O
two	O
window	O
curtains	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
The	O
waistcoat	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
who	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
need	O
only	O
produce	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
here	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
DAVID	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bundles	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
TURNER	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
ANDERSON	B-pers
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
MERCIER	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
LOUIS	I-pers
LE	I-pers
BUTTE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Mondrey	I-pers
,	O
October	O
12	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charged	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
arraigned	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
mute	O
;	O
therefore	O
the	O
Court	O
directed	O
the	O
sheriff	O
to	O
return	O
a	O
jury	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
be	O
stood	O
mute	O
through	O
obstinacy	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
visitation	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
A	O
jury	O
was	O
accordingly	O
returned	O
by	O
the	O
sheriff	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
following	O
oath	O
tendered	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
``	O
You	O
shall	O
diligently	O
enquire	O
and	O
true	O
presentment	O
``	O
make	O
for	O
and	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
``	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
whether	O
Francis	B-pers
Mercier	I-pers
,	O
``	O
otherwise	O
Louis	O
Le	O
Butte	O
,	O
the	O
now	O
prisoner	O
at	O
``	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
being	O
now	O
here	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
wilful	O
``	O
murder	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Mondrey	I-pers
,	O
stands	O
``	O
mute	O
fraudulently	O
,	O
wilfully	O
and	O
obstinately	O
,	O
``	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
providence	O
and	O
act	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
according	O
``	O
to	O
your	O
evidence	O
and	O
knowledge	O
.	O
``	O
So	O
help	O
you	O
GOD	O
.	O
''	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRETTON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
examined	O
this	O
man	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
charge	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
now	O
stands	O
indicted	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
,	O
upon	O
such	O
examination	O
,	O
understand	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
language	O
?	O
and	O
has	O
he	O
himself	O
spoke	O
English	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
language	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
language	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
many	O
letters	O
wrote	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
language	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
apprehend	O
him	O
to	O
understand	O
it	O
nearly	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
does	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
French	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GOODMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Akerman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
attended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
speak	O
?	O
-	O
Coming	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
when	O
below	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
had	O
better	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
ca	O
n't	O
stand	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
sit	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
has	O
this	O
man	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
past	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
sick	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HATCHMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ward-man	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
wards	O
in	O
the	O
gaol	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
in	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
him	O
talk	O
either	O
to-day	O
or	O
yesterday	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
talking	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Redshaw	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
the	O
trial	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
wine	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
muttered	O
and	O
mumbled	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
these	O
four	O
days	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
morning	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
understand	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
understand	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
this	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
obliged	O
to	O
lift	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
mumbled	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Redshaw	O
and	O
he	O
together	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Redshaw	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
REDSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
night	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
talked	O
as	O
hearty	O
as	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
conversed	O
with	O
him	O
upon	O
some	O
business	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
.	O
He	O
talked	O
very	O
hearty	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
spirit	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
understands	O
English	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
to-day	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
here	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
conversation	O
you	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
or	O
not	O
plead	O
this	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
health	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
all	O
the	O
evidence	O
without	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
any	O
counsel	O
whatever	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
or	O
would	O
not	O
plead	O
this	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
or	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
ASTON	O
.	O
'Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Mercier	I-pers
,	O
'alias	O
Louis	O
Le	O
Butte	O
,	O
stand	O
indicted	O
of	O
the	O
'wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Mondrey	I-pers
.	O
'He	O
has	O
been	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
and	O
'makes	O
no	O
answer	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
,	O
'stands	O
mute	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
impannelled	O
to	O
try	O
'whether	O
he	O
stands	O
mute	O
wilfully	O
,	O
fraudulently	O
,	O
'and	O
obstinately	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
visitation	O
'of	O
God	O
.	O
'	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
some	O
medical	O
gentleman	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
some	O
medicine	O
that	O
might	O
have	O
produced	O
the	O
effect	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
speech	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Ogle	O
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
was	O
requested	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OGLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
you	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
questions	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
answer	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
shook	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
breast	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
form	O
a	O
judgment	O
whether	O
this	O
man	O
is	O
or	O
is	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
speaking	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
impossible	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
pulse	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
exceeding	O
languid	O
,	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
quick	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
swelling	O
upon	O
the	O
pit	O
of	O
his	O
stomach	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
belly	O
;	O
his	O
tongue	O
is	O
rather	O
moist	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
,	O
after	O
consulting	O
together	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
found	O
that	O
be	O
stood	O
mute	O
fraudulently	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
obstinately	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
providence	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Aston	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
the	O
Recorder	O
)	O
immediately	O
passed	O
sentence	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
'	O
That	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
executed	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
December	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
body	O
be	O
afterwards	O
dissected	O
and	O
anatomized	O
.	O
'-	O
Which	O
sentence	O
was	O
accordingly	O
executed	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
33.	O
MARY	B-pers
RIPPON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
September	O
5th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
up	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
in	O
Castle-court	B-place
,	I-place
Poppins-court	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
I	O
missed	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
the	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
pawned	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
sorvant	O
produced	O
a	O
shirt	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
ROSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
shirt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pawn	O
the	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
cleared	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MORTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
covered	O
with	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
forty	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Seddon	I-pers
,	O
October	O
18th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SEDDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
and	O
apothecary	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
last	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
the	B-place
Mitre	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Mitre-court	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
coachman	O
put	O
the	O
trunk	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
in	O
Mitre-court	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Jewry-street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
and	O
some	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
trunk	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
ACORN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
coach	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
gateway	O
to	O
Mitre-court	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
gateaway	O
with	O
a	O
trunk	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
Just	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
,	O
gone	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
trunk	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
along	O
White	O
Chapel	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
way	O
the	O
man	O
took	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
up	O
Jewry-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
past	O
me	O
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
GRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
before	O
nine	O
,	O
as	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Jewry-street	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
trunk	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
run	O
past	O
me	O
towards	O
White	O
Chapel	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
pursuing	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
George-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
asked	O
a	O
