TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
1777	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SECOND	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALLIFAX	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
PRINTED	O
BY	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
;	O
AND	O
SOLD	O
BY	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
in	O
PATER-NOSTER	O
ROW	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALLIFAX	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SIDNEY	B-pers
STAFFORD	I-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NARES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Pudner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Osburn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Standard	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
,	O
Silver	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
d'Rippe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Johannott	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
Norton	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
.	O
66.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
KENT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Augustus	B-pers
Levage	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
5th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PETER	I-pers
ESTEINNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Augustus	B-pers
Levage	I-pers
,	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Suffolk-street	B-place
,	I-place
Charing-cross	I-place
:	O
upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
case	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
more	O
;	O
on	O
examination	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
broke	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
the	O
preceding	O
day	O
.	O
[	O
Two	O
pair	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Grubb	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
by	O
Lloyd	B-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
CHARLES	B-pers
GRUBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Decem	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Ann	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
offering	O
these	O
buckles	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
of	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
bring	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
scrape	O
,	O
by	O
sending	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
buckles	O
that	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
she	O
came	O
afterwards	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
Grubb	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
BOLTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
Lloyd	B-pers
the	O
shopman	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
buckles	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cloaths-shop	O
in	O
King-street	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
Long	O
Acre	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
buckles	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
rolled	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
67	O
,	O
68.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
OLDGATE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
ten	O
muslin	O
neck-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Theed	I-pers
,	O
December	O
13th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
THEED	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grafton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
Oldgate	O
;	O
a	O
shirt	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Oldgate	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
?	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
as	O
a	O
wife	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
shirt	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
PEACHY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
neck-cloths	O
and	O
things	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Oldgate	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
landlord	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
Lane	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tubbs	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
lodged	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
backwards	O
:	O
Oldgate	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
at	O
Lane	O
's	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
Eleven	O
neck-cloths	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
Mr.	O
Theed	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Theed	O
?	O
-	O
O	O
yes	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
marked	O
and	O
figured	O
;	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
neck-cloths	O
are	O
marked	O
T	O
T	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
are	O
marked	O
Theed	O
at	O
full	O
length	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
cloth	O
that	O
covered	O
his	O
linen	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
particular	O
to	O
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
loaf	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
Oldgate	O
in	O
our	O
passage	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Theed	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Oldgate	O
who	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
lodgers	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Theed	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
breaking	O
open	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
light-coloured	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
Richard	B-pers
Oldgate	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LANE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
Oldgate	O
brought	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
two	O
shirts	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Oldgate	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
since	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Oldgate	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
son	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
secure	O
Oldgate	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
AINGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Green-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Oldgate	O
rented	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
a	O
Mr.	O
or	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
Oldgate	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Richard	B-pers
Oldgate	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
searched	O
his	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Oldgate	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
pick-locks	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
Davis	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
and	O
some	O
matches	O
and	O
tinder	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Tubbs	O
went	O
up	O
first	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
Oldgate	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TUBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
Mr.	O
Theed	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
a	O
complaint	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
gentleman	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
different	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
a	O
widow	O
woman	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
she	O
directed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
:	O
Lane	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
Davis	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Oldgate	O
's	O
wife	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
neck-cloth	O
to	O
wash	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
shirt	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
staying	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
Oldgate	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
room	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Mr.	O
or	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
opened	O
a	O
trunk	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
OLDGATE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
by	O
a	O
Mrs.	O
Watson	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
OLDGATE	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
fringed	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
five	O
muslin	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
mangle-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cotton	O
night-cap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
night-gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
night-gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
mittens	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
seven	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
five	O
dimity	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
diaper	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
18th	O
.	O
CHARITY	B-pers
FINCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
at	O
Wandsworth	B-place
in	I-place
Surry	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
we	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
reading	O
a	O
lift	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
Tubbs	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
laundry	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
out-house	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
and	O
left	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
BRESON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
nurse	O
to	O
the	O
children	O
:	O
seven	O
childrens	O
frocks	O
,	O
seven	O
petticoats	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
flannel	O
one	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
laundry	O
.	O
[	O
Three	O
frocks	O
,	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
MARTHA	B-pers
PITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
:	O
I	O
washed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TUBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
Oldgate	O
's	O
lodging	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
produced	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Theed	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
M'Daniel	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
upon	O
Davis	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
THORNTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
chissels	O
among	O
some	O
brickbats	O
by	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PITTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
laundry	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
M'DANIEL	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
key	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Davis	O
's	O
pocket	O
that	O
fits	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
some	O
matches	O
and	O
tinder	O
and	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Oldgate	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
Davis	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
small	O
key	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
69	O
,	O
70.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BURDETT	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Arthur	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
an	O
half-crown	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Arthur	O
,	O
October	O
15th	O
.	O
ARTHUR	B-pers
HANCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Newington-green	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Canonbury-house	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
Newington-green	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
;	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
Jones	O
)	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
an	O
half-crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
be	O
quiet	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
:	O
Hall	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
or	O
bludgeon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
ran	O
back	O
towards	O
Canonbury-house	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
Canonbury-house	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
several	O
people	O
afterwards	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
never	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
their	O
faces	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
NATHAN	B-pers
JEFFRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
on	O
a	O
quarrel	O
at	O
Newington-green	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
Hall	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
justice	O
Blackbury	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
he	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
blasted	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
hardened	O
wretch	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Mr.	O
Hancock	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Hancock	O
give	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
then	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
Exactly	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
80	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
:	O
Hall	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
behind	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Paradise-row	O
;	O
we	O
watched	O
them	O
because	O
we	O
thought	O
they	O
meant	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Jones	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DEAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
garden	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
beckon	O
Hall	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
lifted	O
Hall	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
.	O
'Another	O
witness	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
'Edward	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
'	O
JONES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
HALL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
SMYTHE	O
.	O
71.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FREELAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
upon	O
Peter	B-pers
Burnett	I-pers
wilfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
demand	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
with	O
a	O
feloniously	O
intent	O
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
'There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
SMYTHE	O
.	O
72	O
,	O
73	O
,	O
74.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
GOSWELL	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
LIFE	I-pers
,	O
and	O
VALENTINE	B-pers
FULLER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
gold	O
watch-string	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
white	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
another	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Bartholomew	O
,	O
December	O
25th	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
BARTHOLOMEW	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
upon	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
December	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Gunnersbury-lane	B-place
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
moon-light	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
one-horse	O
chaise	O
;	O
Goswell	O
and	O
Fuller	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
Fuller	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
person	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
moon	O
was	O
bright	O
and	O
shone	O
in	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
because	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
moon	O
:	O
Goswell	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
likewise	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
and	O
another	O
seal	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
set	O
in	O
metal	O
;	O
the	O
string	O
was	O
green	O
and	O
gold	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
these	O
two	O
persons	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
next	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
notice	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Bow-street	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
fright	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
their	O
faces	O
then	O
;	O
Goswell	O
's	O
voice	O
struck	O
me	O
exceedingly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BRYANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Goswell	O
's	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
further	O
in	O
his	O
great-coat	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
some	O
powder	O
;	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
four	O
pebbles	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
cypher	O
upon	O
it	O
and	O
my	O
crest	O
;	O
Goswell	O
rode	O
a	O
sorrel	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
horses	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
:	O
between	O
Turnham-green	O
and	O
Gunnersbury-lane	O
Goswell	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
watches	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
both	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
moon-light	O
,	O
very	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
one	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
their	O
persons	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
brother	O
then	O
that	O
I	O
recollected	O
Goswell	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
declined	O
swearing	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
both	O
his	O
voice	O
and	O
person	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
now	O
produced	O
is	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
Goswell	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
sorrel	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BARNARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
garter	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Fuller	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
booted	O
and	O
spurred	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Goswell	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
immediately	O
upon	O
some	O
capital	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Goswell	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Blackman-street	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
exactly	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Fuller	O
went	O
for	O
Goswell	O
,	O
Goswell	O
came	O
:	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
discount	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
for	O
325	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
me	O
150	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
10	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
shall	O
I	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
to-morrow	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
either	O
call	O
or	O
send	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Baker	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
newspaper	O
,	O
whether	O
this	O
bill	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
discovery	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
upon	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
24th	O
I	O
examined	O
again	O
;	O
Goswell	O
neither	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
sent	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
Christmas-day	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
together	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
;	O
Goswell	O
leaned	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
cheek	O
and	O
whispered	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
done	O
the	O
bill	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
tried	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
stay	O
till	O
Friday	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
10	O
guineas	O
for	O
your	O
trouble	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
on	O
Friday	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
papers	O
about	O
this	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
as	O
having	O
been	O
stolen	O
upon	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
particular	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
great	O
notice	O
of	O
all	O
their	O
horses	O
;	O
Goswell	O
's	O
was	O
a	O
sorrel	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
,	O
Fuller	O
's	O
a	O
dark	O
coloured	O
chesnut	O
gelding	O
,	O
Life	O
's	O
a	O
chesnut	O
mare	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
as	O
Fuller	O
's	O
;	O
having	O
made	O
this	O
discovery	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
bill	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
discovered	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
then	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
returned	O
Fuller	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
booted	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
we	O
do	O
no	O
more	O
business	O
than	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
came	O
upon	O
other	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
watches	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
come	O
and	O
dine	O
with	O
my	O
partners	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
something	O
dressing	O
for	O
dinner	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
some	O
watches	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Primrose	O
Street	O
;	O
Goswell	O
and	O
Life	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
Goswell	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
watches	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
these	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
pretty	O
ones	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
all	O
;	O
Life	O
shew	O
yours	O
;	O
then	O
Life	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
pocket	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
any	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
talk	O
of	O
business	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Goswell	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
that	O
bill	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
20	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Asher	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
directly	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
notice	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
Asher	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
all	O
their	O
watches	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
Life	O
then	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
strings	O
and	O
seals	O
;	O
Goswell	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
them	O
all	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
Life	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
the	O
seals	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
all	O
go	O
together	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Life	O
returned	O
the	O
seals	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
watches	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
:	O
the	O
watch	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
Life	O
cut	O
the	O
seals	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
directed	O
my	O
servant	O
maid	O
to	O
watch	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
give	O
information	O
when	O
the	O
messenger	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
15	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
whispered	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
Goswell	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Life	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
all	O
the	O
property	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
leave	O
Fuller	O
here	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
the	O
bill	O
's	O
coming	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
9	O
gold	O
watches	O
more	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
bought	O
these	O
;	O
then	O
Fuller	O
gave	O
the	O
two	O
watches	O
to	O
Goswell	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
likewise	O
a	O
pistol	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
rather	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
saw	O
where	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
not	O
above	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
gone	O
5	O
or	O
600	O
yards	O
about	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
conceal	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
if	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
direct	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
where	O
she	O
saw	O
us	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
came	O
;	O
Fuller	O
was	O
secured	O
immediately	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
secured	O
:	O
Life	O
was	O
leaning	O
his	O
head	O
upon	O
his	O
hands	O
asleep	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
chain	O
out	O
of	O
Life	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
loaded	O
pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
gunpowder	O
,	O
a	O
crape	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wig	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
seals	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
string	O
was	O
fastened	O
to	O
my	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
CLARKE	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Goswell	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
your	O
horses	O
?	O
Goswell	O
said	O
,	O
loose	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
the	O
horses	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
loosened	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
he	O
wrote	O
this	O
note	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
Barnard	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Barnard	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
horses	O
that	O
each	O
person	O
rode	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
specify	O
each	O
particular	O
horse	O
immediately	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
Goswell	O
's	O
horse	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
with	O
the	O
white	O
face	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ABELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
ostler	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lion	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Life	O
and	O
Fuller	O
perfectly	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
Thursday	O
afternoon	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
leading	O
the	O
third	O
horse	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
horse	O
was	O
the	O
sorrel	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
face	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
after	O
dark	O
.	O
GOSWELL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
has	O
spoke	O
very	O
false	O
in	O
his	O
evidence	O
concerning	O
the	O
Bill	O
.	O
LIFE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
prepare	O
for	O
my	O
trial	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
my	O
trial	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
.	O
FULLER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
on	O
a	O
message	O
as	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
might	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
any	O
robbery	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
in	O
Chiswel-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
busy	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
75.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DRAKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
December	O
11th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Half-moon	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
Cheapside	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
mutton	O
chops	O
for	O
dinner	O
and	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
eating	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
some	O
marks	O
on	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
anchor	O
and	O
73.	O
after	O
dinner	O
he	O
ordered	O
another	O
mug	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
waiter	O
a	O
charge	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
shew	O
a	O
gentleman	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
bell	O
rang	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
waiter	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
waiter	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
smoked	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Boots	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Tavern	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
yesterday	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
mug	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
'	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CUTTINGDON	I-pers
,	O
the	O
waiter	O
,	O
'confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
testimony	O
,	O
and	O
'added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
mug	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
'table	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
2	O
minutes	O
'before	O
he	O
missed	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
'there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
'	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
76.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOWETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Luke	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
December	O
6th	O
.	O
LUKE	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
Friday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
pull	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
immediately	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
throw	O
down	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
boy	O
who	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
77.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
SWIFT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
January	O
6th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
near	O
Holborn	B-place
Bars	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
4	O
half-dozen	O
of	O
tea-spoons	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'ennight	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
3	O
men	O
,	O
handcuffed	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
past	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
shew-glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
half-dozen	O
of	O
tea-spoons	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
weighing	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
glass	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
spoons	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
Dinmore	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
DINMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
handcuffed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
his	O
handcuff	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shew-glass	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
it	O
so	O
openly	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
escape	O
detection	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
other	O
officers	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
house-breaking	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
cleared	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
frosty	O
weather	O
,	O
my	O
foot	O
slipt	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hand	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spoons	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
78.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STEWARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen-sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
December	O
25th	O
.	O
'The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
'were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
'by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
'house	O
by	O
a	O
girl	O
who	O
was	O
gathering	O
in	O
alehouse	O
'pots	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
'to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
men	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
'upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
'that	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
'	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
79.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
RICHARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holston	I-pers
,	O
December	O
10th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOLSTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Skinners-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
theatre	I-place
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
fell	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
off	O
the	O
pavement	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
outer	O
case	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
recovered	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
very	O
distinctly	O
,	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
chain	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
after	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
being	O
the	O
poorest	O
person	O
near	O
him	O
he	O
challenged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
80.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
SNARBON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bath-beaver	O
surtout-coat	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
stocks	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PAXTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	B-place
Posts	I-place
,	I-place
Bennet-street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
surtout-coat	O
,	O
some	O
shirts	O
,	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
:	O
about	O
10	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
coat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EDMUNDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Having	O
heard	O
that	O
this	O
coat	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Ponder	O
's	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LIBERTY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
borrowed	O
the	O
coat	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
FREDERICK	B-pers
RAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
6	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
borrow	O
the	O
coat	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
of	O
one	O
Christian	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
;	O
Lamb	O
worked	O
then	O
at	O
a	O
sugar-house	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
To	O
LIBERTY	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Six	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
honest	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
regularly	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
81.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
LEBURT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Priestman	I-pers
,	O
November	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
and	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PRIESTMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Princes-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
rings	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
several	O
;	O
this	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
ring	O
from	O
his	O
finger	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LESSLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
sincerely	O
confessed	O
his	O
error	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
speak	O
English	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
French	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
little	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
very	O
broken	O
English	O
:	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
82.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BARRINGTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
studs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
an	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dudman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
December	O
18th	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
DUDMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
in	O
the	O
pit	O
of	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
playhouse	I-place
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
containing	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
playhouse	O
very	O
full	O
the	O
night	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
king	O
and	O
queen	O
were	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
play-house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
theatre	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
pit	O
did	O
you	O
fit	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Near	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
crowded	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
detect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
your	O
purse	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
detect	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
with	O
my	O
purse	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
side	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stand	O
?	O
-	O
First	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
,	O
then	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
immensity	O
of	O
that	O
crowd	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
assert	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
hand	O
you	O
felt	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
his	O
crowding	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
peremptory	O
in	O
swearing	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
under	O
all	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
crowd	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
purse	O
dropped	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
means	O
was	O
he	O
secured	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
called	O
out	O
did	O
you	O
point	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
to	O
whom	O
you	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
-	O
MARSHALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pit	O
of	O
the	O
play-house	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Mr.	O
Barrington	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
this	O
Lady	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Barrington	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
purse	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
fortune	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Pallmall	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
character	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
express	O
any	O
doubt	O
about	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
instant	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
purse	O
,	O
she	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
purse	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
his	O
hand	O
away	O
across	O
his	O
breast	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
theatre	O
much	O
crouded	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
lady	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sit	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
first	O
falling	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
of	O
the	O
purse	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
Miss	O
Dudman	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
come	O
athwart	O
his	O
own	O
breast	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
she	O
declared	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
picked	O
her	O
pocket	O
of	O
her	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
I	O
.	O
Was	O
no	O
different	O
relation	O
given	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
to	O
what	O
is	O
now	O
given	O
before	O
the	O
court	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
that	O
he	O
crowded	O
Miss	O
Dudman	O
before	O
that	O
she	O
complained	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
civil	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
civility	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expected	O
at	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
accompany	O
the	O
lady	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
as	O
peremptory	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
as	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
and	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
The	O
evidence	O
which	O
has	O
come	O
before	O
your	O
lordship	O
and	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
think	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
of	O
felony	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
relate	O
the	O
transaction	O
as	O
briefly	O
as	O
possible	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
play-house	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
pit	O
which	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
standing	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
crowded	O
that	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
screwed	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
push	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
seats	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
standing	O
part	O
were	O
endeavouring	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
procure	O
seats	O
;	O
the	O
crowd	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
that	O
they	O
hurt	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
this	O
lady	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
making	O
towards	O
a	O
seat	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
every	O
person	O
then	O
present	O
,	O
was	O
doing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
that	O
some	O
person	O
had	O
their	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
round	O
immediately	O
and	O
fixed	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
many	O
people	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
minute	O
at	O
least	O
before	O
she	O
could	O
turn	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
professed	O
my	O
innocence	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
company	O
to	O
declare	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
transaction	O
to	O
happen	O
without	O
some	O
person	O
being	O
privy	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
were	O
assembled	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
every	O
gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
opinion	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
unanimous	O
in	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
certain	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
and	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
upwards	O
of	O
5	O
minutes	O
had	O
passed	O
in	O
this	O
altercation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
noise	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
had	O
subsided	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
their	O
property	O
at	O
the	O
play-house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
rumour	O
,	O
came	O
immediately	O
and	O
declared	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
suspected	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
necessary	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
satisfaction	O
and	O
clear	O
himself	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
retire	O
to	O
some	O
place	O
and	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
I	O
assented	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
retiring	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
with	O
several	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
detained	O
for	O
8	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
,	O
because	O
no	O
person	O
could	O
claim	O
a	O
single	O
article	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
evidence	O
this	O
lady	O
has	O
given	O
is	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
life	O
or	O
liberty	O
of	O
any	O
person	O
whatsoever	O
;	O
such	O
a	O
crime	O
as	O
this	O
could	O
never	O
happen	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
without	O
some	O
person	O
being	O
witness	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
might	O
have	O
found	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
fear	O
might	O
make	O
her	O
believe	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
her	O
purse	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
crowd	O
was	O
so	O
exceeding	O
great	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
turn	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
crying	O
out	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
excessively	O
squeezed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
weight	O
with	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
just	O
now	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
exceedingly	O
crowded	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
transaction	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
impossible	O
to	O
fix	O
upon	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
mean	O
to	O
reflect	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
every	O
circumstance	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
extricate	O
myself	O
,	O
the	O
lady	O
is	O
blind	O
of	O
one	O
eye	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
conceive	O
adds	O
to	O
the	O
impossibility	O
of	O
fixing	O
upon	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
lady	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
acquainted	O
with	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Groves	O
?	O
DUDMAN	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
:	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
handwriting	O
?	O
DUDMAN	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
admit	O
that	O
letter	O
came	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
Tothill-fields	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
gaol	O
,	O
natural	O
curiosity	O
prompted	O
him	O
to	O
ask	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
perfectly	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
often	O
heard	O
her	O
express	O
her	O
regret	O
for	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
treated	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
address	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
few	O
lines	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
disagreeable	O
thing	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
bill	O
would	O
be	O
thrown	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
trouble	O
;	O
this	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
letter	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
(	O
Looks	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
'Madam	O
,	O
'	O
I	O
am	O
happy	O
to	O
embrace	O
the	O
opportunity	O
'which	O
presents	O
itself	O
of	O
addressing	O
to	O
you	O
a	O
'few	O
lines	O
relative	O
to	O
a	O
prosecution	O
which	O
'you	O
have	O
lately	O
commenced	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
,	O
'Madam	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
possessed	O
of	O
'humanity	O
,	O
therefore	O
hope	O
that	O
you	O
will	O
feel	O
'for	O
my	O
unhappy	O
situation	O
;	O
deplorable	O
as	O
it	O
'is	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
power	O
to	O
extricate	O
'me	O
from	O
it	O
without	O
sustaining	O
the	O
smallest	O
'injury	O
;	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
are	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
bills	O
'to-morrow	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
depends	O
'upon	O
your	O
evidence	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
bill	O
found	O
'or	O
rejected	O
;	O
what	O
shall	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
what	O
'words	O
shall	O
I	O
address	O
you	O
?	O
innocent	O
or	O
'guilty	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
suffered	O
severely	O
,	O
suffered	O
'more	O
than	O
you	O
can	O
think	O
or	O
suppose	O
;	O
my	O
'character	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
totally	O
lost	O
,	O
is	O
injured	O
in	O
'the	O
highest	O
degree	O
;	O
my	O
confinement	O
and	O
'the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
exposed	O
'	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
mention	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
'they	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
greatest	O
weight	O
in	O
an	O
'humane	O
and	O
feeling	O
mind	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
such	O
'would	O
be	O
considered	O
as	O
a	O
sufficient	O
punishment	O
'even	O
for	O
a	O
guilty	O
person	O
;	O
may	O
this	O
'consideration	O
animate	O
your	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
induce	O
'you	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
a	O
prosecution	O
which	O
'	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
attended	O
by	O
any	O
agreeable	O
reflection	O
;	O
'though	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
every	O
'assurance	O
of	O
safety	O
from	O
those	O
who	O
are	O
versed	O
'in	O
affairs	O
of	O
this	O
nature	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
thought	O
of	O
'appearing	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
of	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
'greatest	O
innocence	O
is	O
sometimes	O
ineffectual	O
,	O
'compels	O
me	O
to	O
address	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
'and	O
to	O
intrude	O
upon	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
,	O
'is	O
acquainted	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
this	O
letter	O
,	O
'and	O
to	O
use	O
his	O
good	O
offices	O
,	O
hoping	O
they	O
'will	O
be	O
effectual	O
,	O
convinced	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
'superior	O
to	O
interest	O
,	O
or	O
being	O
made	O
an	O
instrument	O
,	O
'and	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
reliance	O
'upon	O
your	O
feeling	O
and	O
sensibility	O
;	O
I	O
remain	O
'with	O
the	O
greatest	O
respect	O
your	O
obedient	O
'humble	O
servant	O
,	O
G	O
.	O
BARRINGTON	O
.	O
''	O
Tothillfields	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
Directed	O
to	O
Miss	O
Dudman	O
.	O
FOR	O
THE	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
FINCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perukemaker	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
dressed	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Cross	O
,	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
16	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Barrington	O
frequently	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Deadcraft	O
's	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Deadcraft	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
did	O
too	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
such	O
a	O
lodger	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
civil	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
among	O
the	O
officers	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
honor	O
to	O
attend	O
;	O
his	O
conduct	O
was	O
very	O
regular	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
after	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
his	O
trades	O
people	O
very	O
genteelly	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
83	O
,	O
84.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
CHARLES	I-pers
PARSONS	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
James	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
December	O
1st	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DUNBAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Charles	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
half-pence	O
;	O
he	O
demanded	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
search	O
to	O
satisfy	O
himself	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
Davis	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
Mary	B-pers
Spratley	I-pers
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
presented	O
his	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
moon-light	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
star-light	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
star-light	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
their	O
faces	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
they	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
9	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
dressed	O
as	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
observation	O
upon	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
voice	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
resembled	O
Parsons	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
SPRATLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Davis	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Parsons	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
observed	O
sufficiently	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
Davis	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
he	O
turned	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Dunbar	O
.	O
'	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tapsell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
'	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
'prisoners	O
under	O
suspicious	O
circumstances	O
;	O
'that	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
they	O
found	O
a	O
'loaded	O
pistol	O
.	O
'	O
PARSONS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
a-bed	O
.	O
FOR	O
DAVIS	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
CLASS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-engraver	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Davis	O
rather	O
above	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
different	O
bills	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
refuse	O
now	O
to	O
intrust	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
I	O
have	O
before	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FELBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
musick-engraver	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
,	O
Westminster	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Davis	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
tractable	O
good	O
boy	O
,	O
industrious	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
workman	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TABER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Davis	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BRIGGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-engraver	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Davis	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
hard-working	O
industrious	O
lad	O
.	O
-	O
BARNARD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Davis	O
3	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
FOR	O
PARSONS	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PEARSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Parsons	O
about	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
every	O
thing	O
right	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SEDGWICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
joiner	O
and	O
house	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Parsons	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Parsons	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
years	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
by	O
profession	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
say	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
get	O
his	O
living	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
often	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
very	O
busy	O
and	O
industrious	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
surveyor	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
85.	O
ANN	B-pers
BUCKLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
callico	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
black	O
silk	O
clocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
printed	O
cotton	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
head	O
cloth	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
tester	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
cotton	O
vallens	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
an	O
accomplice	O
unattended	O
with	O
any	O
corroborating	O
circumstances	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
86.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BRYAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
wrought	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
chased	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
coral	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
with	O
seven	O
silver	O
bells	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FORTESCUE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
:	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
year	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
ISABELLA	O
FORTESCUE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
4	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
injury	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
thieves	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
concealed	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
snuff-box	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PHENIX	O
FLETCHER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
Mrs.	O
Fortescue	O
;	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
startled	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
a	O
man	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
candle	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
stand	O
clear	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
fright	O
seized	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
do	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Fortescue	O
's	O
house	O
is	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
snuff-box	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
87	O
,	O
88.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WICKSTEAD	I-pers
and	O
EPIPHANY	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
and	O
instrument	O
called	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
upon	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
December	O
31st	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Messrs	O
.	O
Rains	O
and	O
Barker	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tree	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Gains	O
,	O
up	O
Park-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
yards	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
Parker	O
put	O
a	O
drawn	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
Wickstead	O
clap	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
rather	O
pushed	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Parker	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
resistance	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
the	O
knife	O
into	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
putting	O
their	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Gains	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tree	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
Parker	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Tree	I-pers
secured	O
him	O
;	O
Wickstead	O
ran	O
down	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
Gains	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
Gains	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
Wickstead	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gains	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
both	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
together	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
Gains	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
fired	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
air	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
loaded	O
and	O
cocked	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Tree	O
brought	O
Parker	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
From	O
PARKER	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
up	O
against	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GAINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Park-lane	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tree	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
was	O
about	O
30	O
yards	O
before	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
stopped	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
footpath	O
under	O
the	O
dead	O
wall	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
Bell	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
replied	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tree	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
secured	O
Parker	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
Wickstead	O
down	O
Park-lane	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
come	O
any	O
farther	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
discharged	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TREE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
the	O
last	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
old	O
year	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
Park-lane	O
;	O
Bell	O
was	O
about	O
30	O
yards	O
before	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
stop	O
him	O
and	O
demand	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
dead	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
resign	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gains	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
;	O
Wickstead	O
jumped	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
Parker	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Bell	O
,	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
Bell	O
immediately	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
then	O
Bell	O
and	O
Gains	O
followed	O
Wickstead	O
down	O
Park-lane	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
Parker	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
WICKSTEAD	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Parker	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Uxbridge	O
coach	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
Park-lane	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
postchaise	O
stop	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
threw	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
we	O
thought	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
postboy	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
lucky	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
or	O
else	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
robbed	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Parker	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
resign	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
PARKER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Uxbridge	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Wickstead	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Park-lane	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
postchaise	O
stop	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
on	O
our	O
coming	O
up	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
we	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
GAINS	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
stopped	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
coach	O
had	O
just	O
passed	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
our	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
that	O
,	O
alluding	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
that	O
had	O
just	O
passed	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Gains	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
that	O
they	O
had	O
laid	O
this	O
plot	O
against	O
us	O
.	O
GAINS	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
footpads	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
passed	O
them	O
before	O
and	O
apprehended	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
run	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
89.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Penson	I-pers
,	O
November	O
25th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PENSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Twickenham	B-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
punctual	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
which	O
I	O
keep	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
man	O
wearing	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
breeches	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
.	O
To	O
PENSON	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
new	O
breeches	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
I	O
gave	O
five	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Davis	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
breeches	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Taylor	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
REID	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Davis	O
buy	O
the	O
breeches	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
five	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pay	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
breeches	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
bread	O
for	O
my	O
family	O
for	O
three	O
days	O
and	O
three	O
nights	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
NARES	O
.	O
90	O
,	O
91	O
,	O
92	O
,	O
93.	O
HENRY	B-pers
DIPNALL	I-pers
senior	O
,	O
HENRY	B-pers
DIPNALL	I-pers
junior	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
560	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
December	O
13th	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
ALL	O
FOUR	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
94.	O
JAMES	B-pers
M'DORMOT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
ham	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
84.	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
January	O
6th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRIFFITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
near	O
Clare-market	B-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
rabbits	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
his	O
rabbits	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
ill-natured	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
stand	O
there	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
compassion	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
decent	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
sell	O
his	O
rabbits	O
at	O
my	O
bulk	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
bacon	O
afterwards	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bacon	O
and	O
a	O
ham	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
;	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
bacon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
that	O
would	O
suit	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
saw	O
three-quarters	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
bacon	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
ham	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
CHRISTIAN	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Compasses	O
in	O
Little	O
Wild-Street	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
bacon	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
flat	O
basket	O
which	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
pole	O
they	O
hang	O
their	O
rabbits	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
with	O
another	O
piece	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
back-room	O
table	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
basket	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
basket	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
dirty	O
my	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
fourth	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
taylors	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
then	O
that	O
bid	O
money	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
bacon	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
bacon	O
or	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
butt	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
another	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
largest	O
piece	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
that	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
troublesome	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
to	O
fetch	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
related	O
the	O
story	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
's	O
losing	O
some	O
bacon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
bacon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
bacon	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
twelfth-day	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
the	O
customers	O
he	O
walked	O
out	O
and	O
in	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
presently	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unhook	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
unhooked	O
it	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
drop	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
lie	O
best	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
biggest	O
piece	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
bacon	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
chastised	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
moved	O
the	O
bacon	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
move	O
vessels	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
To	O
BURTON	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
bacon	O
hang	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
hung	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
ham	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
one	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
his	O
bacon	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
SMYTHE	O
.	O
95	O
,	O
96	O
,	O
97	O
,	O
98.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
,	O
HENRY	B-pers
HASLAM	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOLLEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
HOLLIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hair	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
twelve	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
an	O
onyx	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
mock	O
sardonyx	O
ring	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
covered	O
with	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
six	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
toupee-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
December	O
18th	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Nottingham	O
,	O
I	O
entrusted	O
a	O
trunk	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
town	O
before	O
a	O
postchaise	O
,	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
stolen	O
between	O
May-fair	B-place
and	O
Golden-square	B-place
;	O
upon	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
office	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
trunk	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
trunk	O
been	O
opened	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
acquainted	O
me	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
situation	O
it	O
was	O
packed	O
up	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
trunk	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
postchaise	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
ILLI	B-pers
ROWLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
postchaise	O
,	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
tied	O
before	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
last	O
from	O
Barnet	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
trunk	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
did	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
trunk	O
there	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
to	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
?	O
-	O
Ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
With	O
a	O
strap	O
before	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
by	O
the	O
ostler	O
at	O
Barnet	O
.	O
EDMUND	B-pers
INGRAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
postchaise	O
driver	O
:	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
from	O
Barnet	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
fastened	O
on	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Barnet-hill	O
,	O
with	O
leather	O
straps	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
at	O
Tottenham-road-gate	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
street	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
straps	O
were	O
cut	O
and	O
were	O
hanging	O
down	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
straps	O
were	O
not	O
wore	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
COURT	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
at	O
the	O
turnpikes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
stopped	O
from	O
May-fair	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
straps	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
White-Bear	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
From	O
HASLAM	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
many	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
straps	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
straps	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
trunk	O
with	O
three	O
men	O
down	O
to	O
Cold-bath	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
;	O
accordingly	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
his	O
coach	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Eyre-street	O
I	O
think	O
;	O
we	O
walked	O
down	O
Warner-street	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
took	O
the	O
trunk	O
in	O
at	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
trunk	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
linen	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
papers	O
strewed	O
about	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Tolley	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
side-pocket	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
tongs	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
side-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
large	O
clasp-knife	O
;	O
I	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
else	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
the	O
trunk	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
information	O
brought	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
trunk	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
before	O
we	O
knew	O
a	O
trunk	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
.	O
To	O
ROWLAND	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
irons	O
,	O
are	O
these	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
called	O
a	O
coach	O
up	O
St.	O
Alban's-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
call	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
standing	O
with	O
this	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
coach-door	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
trunk	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
third	O
man	O
to	O
get	O
behind	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Leather-lane	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Leather-lane	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Purpool-lane	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
up	O
as	O
much	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
as	O
I	O
possibly	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
W	O
upon	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
A	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
what	O
my	O
fare	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
18	O
d.	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
five-shilling	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
half-crown	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
my	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
down	O
Eyre-street-hill	O
;	O
they	O
pitched	O
the	O
trunk	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Warner-street	O
;	O
I	O
placed	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
went	O
up	O
Warner-street	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
it	O
was	O
pitched	O
on	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
Warner-street	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
facing	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
up	O
the	O
stair-case	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutters	O
put	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
my	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
clerk	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
information	O
of	O
a	O
trunk	O
being	O
stole	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
carrying	O
a	O
trunk	O
with	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
suspicion	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
clerk	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
men	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
one	O
was	O
like	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
assistance	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
coach	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Leather-lane	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
