TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1778	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
THIRD	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
M.	O
DCC	O
.	O
LXXVIII	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vanes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Humphery	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
Ivon	B-pers
Lemain	I-pers
,	O
Ricchard	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goujon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cubbitt	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Orgill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hanbury	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hayler	I-pers
,	O
Southerton	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Richmond	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Joice	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Drawwater	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bedell	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
M'Donall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Utterton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
George	I-pers
Snowden	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nourse	I-pers
.	O
207.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Glocester-court	B-place
,	I-place
Whitecross-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
parlour	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
sheet	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moulton	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
lad	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
sheet	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
sheet	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
who	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
sheet	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MOULTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pull	O
the	O
sheet	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Moulton	I-pers
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
15	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
208.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leather	O
cloak-bag	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Mr.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
cloaths	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Faden	O
's	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
before	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Faden	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
straps	O
were	O
cut	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
near	O
the	O
Whitehorse-cellar	O
with	O
this	O
cloak-bag	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
presently	O
surrounded	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
sight	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
cloak-bag	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
surrounded	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
cloak-bag	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
or	O
walking	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
walking	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
it	O
drop	O
from	O
the	O
carriage	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
fastened	O
with	O
cords	O
;	O
the	O
cords	O
and	O
straps	O
were	O
apparently	O
cut	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
portmanteau	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
gently	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Whitehorse-cellar	O
;	O
there	O
this	O
gentleman	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
portmanteau	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
run	O
away	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
cutting	O
or	O
stealing	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
that	O
lenity	O
may	O
be	O
shewn	O
him	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
209.	O
JUDITH	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
gallon	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Abbott	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ABBOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Buffalo	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Newman-street	I-place
,	I-place
Oxford-road	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
beer	O
slop	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
we	O
kept	O
a	O
gallon	O
pot	O
to	O
put	O
waste	O
beer	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
gallon	O
pot	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
excuse	O
she	O
made	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
fetch	O
water	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
that	O
is	O
unborn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
210	O
,	O
211.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FINCK	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAKE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
February	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bowry	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
returned	O
chaise	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
stopped	O
upon	O
Hillindon-heath	B-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lake	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bowry	O
's	O
side	O
;	O
my	O
window	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
Lake	O
said	O
,	O
halloa	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
-	O
Lake	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
.	O
Then	O
Lake	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
which	O
he	O
presented	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
Lake	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
this	O
will	O
do	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
never	O
wore	O
one	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
demanded	O
Mr.	O
Bowry	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bowry	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bowry	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
Lake	O
bid	O
him	O
hand	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Bowry	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Lake	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
both	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
baker	O
at	O
Pimlico	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
served	O
with	O
flour	O
;	O
I	O
recollected	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
pistol	O
and	O
presented	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
his	O
face	O
to	O
disguise	O
him	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BOWRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
two	O
highwaymen	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
was	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
only	O
stood	O
as	O
a	O
guard	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
single	O
word	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JEALOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
.	O
Information	O
was	O
laid	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
getting	O
off	O
their	O
horses	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins-street	O
,	O
near	O
Hedge-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
informed	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Prince	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
;	O
we	O
immediately	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Lake	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Francis	B-pers
Bowry	I-pers
.	O
]	O
Lake	O
was	O
in	O
boots	O
and	O
spurs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
exceedingly	O
dirty	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Finck	O
hired	O
a	O
chesnut-coloured	O
horse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
,	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
another	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
home	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
both	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
cool	O
.	O
-	O
BARRET	O
sworn	O
.	O
Finck	O
hired	O
a	O
mare	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Brentford	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
relation	O
.	O
As	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
Finck	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
LAKE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
:	O
that	O
watch	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
to	O
get	O
cleaned	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friends	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
FINCK	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
LAKE	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FINCK	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAKE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Francis	B-pers
Bowry	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
,	O
February	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
upon	O
the	O
last	O
trial	O
.	O
FINCK	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
LAKE	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FINCK	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LAKE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
at	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
11th	O
and	O
12th	O
mile	O
stone	O
on	O
the	O
Uxbridge	B-place
road	I-place
:	O
they	O
bid	O
us	O
stop	O
;	O
they	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
our	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
Lake	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
money	O
not	O
to	O
Lake	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
handful	O
.	O
Lake	O
threatened	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
dusk	O
and	O
candle	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lake	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
From	O
Lake	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
cloaths	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
Lake	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Lake	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
PRIOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cock	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
Finck	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JEALOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
From	O
Lake	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
cloaths	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
when	O
you	O
apprehended	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
Brown	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
with	O
brass	O
buttons	O
,	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
first	O
stopped	O
at	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
Hanwell	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
coloured	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
dress	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
inside	O
coat	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
pompadour	O
colour	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
Lake	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
pompadour	O
coloured	O
coat	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
trial	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
Finck	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
.	O
-	O
BARRET	O
sworn	O
.	O
Finck	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
of	O
me	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
mane	O
and	O
tail	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
-	O
Lake	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
chesnut	O
horse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
face	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
rode	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Finck	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
LAKE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
ever	O
before	O
a	O
court	O
.	O
FINCK	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
LAKE	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
212.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
;	O
containing	O
20	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shrigley	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHRIGLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk-mercer	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
cry	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
20	O
rods	O
beyond	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
people	O
say	O
the	O
mercer	O
's	O
shop	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
pursued	O
him	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
recollect	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
my	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
recollected	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
recovered	O
my	O
property	O
again	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GODDARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
doorway	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
lads	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
stood	O
ajar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stoop	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drag	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brown	O
stuff	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
off	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
stuff	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
213	O
,	O
214.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
containing	O
20	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
215.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
PASCAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bacon	O
ham	O
,	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
ham	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
some	O
ladies	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
stealing	O
a	O
ham	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
ham	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
ham	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
the	O
ham	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
40	O
l.	O
reward	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
14	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
lift	O
it	O
.	O
Day	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
18	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
216.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Moffett	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MOFFETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
changing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
and	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
wrapped	O
another	O
pair	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
parcels	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
parcel	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
217.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HANCOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scafford	I-pers
;	O
three	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
half-pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sandy	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
218.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
containing	O
70	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butlin	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
219.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
feloniously	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ASHTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
Orange-court	B-place
,	I-place
Swallow-street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
apartment	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
apartments	O
to	O
different	O
lodgers	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Underwood	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
;	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
was	O
lighting	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
parlour	O
door	O
and	O
my	O
street	O
door	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
secure	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
letter	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
declared	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
smith	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
a	O
possibility	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
happen	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
smith	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
that	O
in	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
lock	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
key	O
could	O
be	O
turned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
door	O
must	O
be	O
locked	O
;	O
therefore	O
from	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
lighting	O
a	O
person	O
down	O
stairs	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
three	O
stairs	O
of	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ashton	O
's	O
parlour	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Ashton	O
immediately	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
pray	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Underwood	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
and	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
lighted	O
tinder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
turn-screw	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wax-taper	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
scutcheon	O
upon	O
the	O
key	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
this	O
parlour	O
was	O
removed	O
from	O
its	O
usual	O
place	O
as	O
if	O
done	O
by	O
violence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
much	O
resistance	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
forgiveness	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ashton	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
candle-light	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
several	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
,	O
a	O
tin-box	O
with	O
lighted	O
tinder	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
flint	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
a	O
screw-driver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dirty	O
bag	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
coals	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
UNDERWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
Sunday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
;	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
was	O
lighting	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ashton	O
,	O
your	O
parlour	O
door	O
is	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
here	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
:	O
a	O
laundress	O
;	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
lodge	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Underwood	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
empty	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
body	O
say	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	O
HOWELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Ashton	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Ashton	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
turn	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
lock	O
;	O
therefore	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Judgment	O
she	O
looked	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
bag	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
breeches	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
then	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
stair-foot	O
;	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Watts	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ashton	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
door	O
is	O
open	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
next	O
day	O
upon	O
bail	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
since	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Ashton	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
220.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BURLEIGH	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
2d	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
fine	O
gold	O
,	O
weighing	O
1	O
oz	O
.	O
3	O
penny	O
wts	O
.	O
and	O
18	O
grains	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gold-beater	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Long	B-place
Acre	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
hired	O
into	O
my	O
service	O
as	O
a	O
nurse	O
maid	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
she	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
afterwards	O
returned	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
(	O
the	O
24th	O
)	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
gold	O
(	O
contrary	O
to	O
my	O
usual	O
course	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
in	O
my	O
dining-room	O
;	O
the	O
parcel	O
contained	O
10	O
oz	O
.	O
in	O
different	O
pieces	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
piece	O
was	O
the	O
largest	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
;	O
with	O
great	O
difficulty	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
this	O
fact	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stopped	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
gold	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
directions	O
.	O
Several	O
pawnbrokers	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
giving	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
things	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
pawned	O
with	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
this	O
table	O
spoon	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
he	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
The	O
spoon	O
was	O
likewise	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
A	O
pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
table	O
spoon	O
in	O
pawn	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
request	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
221.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
OSBORNE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Teresia	B-pers
Barkham	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
dollars	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Teresia	O
,	O
February	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
TERESIA	B-pers
BARKHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
stopped	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Edgware	B-place
road	I-place
.	O
Two	O
highwaymen	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
came	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
and	O
watches	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
quick	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
dollars	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
chaise	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
coming	O
towards	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
chaise	O
,	O
suspecting	O
they	O
were	O
highwaymen	O
,	O
got	O
out	O
as	O
they	O
rode	O
towards	O
that	O
chaise	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Edgware	O
road	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
Miss	O
Barkham	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
first	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
where	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Miss	O
Barkham	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
across	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
stopped	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
highwaymen	O
when	O
they	O
passed	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
to	O
Miss	O
Barkham	O
;	O
I	O
recollected	O
his	O
face	O
when	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
recollected	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
with	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
suspected	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
enough	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
from	O
his	O
face	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
committing	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
rode	O
off	O
towards	O
a	O
returned	O
chaise	O
which	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
;	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
men	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
then	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
passed	O
our	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
towards	O
Edgware	O
.	O
The	O
post	O
boys	O
took	O
one	O
horse	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TOPHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
chaise	O
Miss	O
Barkham	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
two	O
highwaymen	O
passed	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
turned	O
about	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
mask	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
round	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
one	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
mask	O
on	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
out	O
my	O
brains	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
looked	O
back	O
;	O
a	O
returned	O
chaise	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
highwaymen	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
that	O
chaise	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
passed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
Edgware	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
post-boy	O
got	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
highwaymen	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
continued	O
to	O
pursue	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
particularly	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
in	O
Hendon	O
town	O
;	O
they	O
galloped	O
on	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
rode	O
amongst	O
the	O
country	O
people	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
pistols	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
threatening	O
to	O
shoot	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
side	O
with	O
his	O
pistol	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
further	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
horse	O
failed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
quitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
shot	O
at	O
me	O
his	O
face	O
was	O
uncovered	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
him	O
distinctly	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fight	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
.	O
ALDERIDGE	O
HAWKES	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
returned	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
other	O
chaise	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
both	O
their	O
faces	O
were	O
uncovered	O
;	O
I	O
plainly	O
then	O
discerned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
men	O
on	O
horseback	O
there	O
besides	O
those	O
two	O
persons	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
post-boy	O
and	O
I	O
rode	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
alighted	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
rode	O
on	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
coming	O
up	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
horses	O
,	O
I	O
mounted	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
fire	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
with	O
blue	O
buttons	O
on	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SADLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
countryman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hendon	O
;	O
hearing	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
highwaymen	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
furtout	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
saw	O
William	B-pers
Topham	I-pers
in	O
the	O
field	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
pistols	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
powder-horn	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DARWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
countryman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fire	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
the	O
post-chaiseman	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
pistols	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hendon	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
riding	O
a	O
horseback	O
;	O
one	O
threw	O
his	O
pistol	O
away	O
.	O
These	O
men	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
robbery	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
delivered	O
the	O
butt	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
pistol	O
into	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
222.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SHERWOOD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
falsely	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
and	O
procuring	O
to	O
be	O
falsely	O
made	O
,	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
and	O
willingly	O
acting	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
false	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
deed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
names	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
and	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
thereunto	O
subscribed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bear	O
date	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
1777	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
signed	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
and	O
one	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
sealed	O
and	O
delivered	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
;	O
the	O
tenor	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
deed	O
is	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
``	O
Know	O
all	O
men	O
,	O
by	O
these	O
presents	O
,	O
that	O
``	O
we	O
,	O
the	O
Reverend	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
,	O
``	O
of	O
Coney	O
Court	O
,	O
Gray's-Inn	O
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
of	O
``	O
Bow	O
,	O
do	O
make	O
,	O
constitute	O
and	O
appoint	O
,	O
``	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
``	O
draper	O
,	O
our	O
true	O
and	O
lawful	O
``	O
attorney	O
,	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
names	O
and	O
``	O
on	O
our	O
behalf	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
assign	O
and	O
``	O
transfer	O
,	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
part	O
,	O
of	O
seven	O
``	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
being	O
all	O
our	O
joint-interest	O
,	O
``	O
or	O
share	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
capital	O
,	O
or	O
``	O
joint-stock	O
,	O
of	O
3	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Annuities	O
,	O
``	O
erected	O
by	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
of	O
``	O
the	O
25th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
his	O
``	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	B-pers
II	I-pers
.	O
intitled	O
,	O
``	O
an	O
Act	O
for	O
converting	O
the	O
several	O
``	O
annuities	O
therein	O
mentioned	O
into	O
several	O
``	O
joint-stocks	O
of	O
annuities	O
,	O
transferable	O
``	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
to	O
``	O
be	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Sinking	O
Fund	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
by	O
several	O
subsequent	O
acts	O
;	O
also	O
to	O
``	O
receive	O
the	O
consideration	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
give	O
a	O
receipt	O
,	O
or	O
receipts	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
``	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
all	O
lawful	O
acts	O
``	O
requisite	O
for	O
effecting	O
the	O
premises	O
,	O
``	O
hereby	O
ratifying	O
and	O
confirming	O
all	O
``	O
that	O
our	O
said	O
attorney	O
shall	O
do	O
therein	O
``	O
by	O
virtue	O
hereof	O
.	O
In	O
witness	O
whereof	O
,	O
``	O
we	O
have	O
hereunto	O
set	O
our	O
hands	O
``	O
and	O
seals	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
``	O
the	O
year	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
,	O
one	O
thousand	O
``	O
seven	O
hundred	O
and	O
seventy	O
seven	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MYONNET	I-pers
,	O
D.D	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
L.S	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
,	O
(	O
L.S	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
Signed	O
,	O
sealed	O
and	O
delivered	O
(	O
the	O
``	O
paper	O
being	O
first	O
duly	O
stamped	O
)	O
``	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
us	O
``	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
,	O
Salesman	O
,	O
Houndsditch.	O
``	O
Francis	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
Salesman	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
''	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
2d	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
,	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
forged	O
deed	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
Count	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
only	O
laying	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
4th	O
Count	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
5th	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Count	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
6th	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
7th	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
third	O
and	O
fifth	O
Counts	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
8th	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
fourth	O
and	O
sixth	O
Counts	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
Counts	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
count	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
additional	O
words	O
over	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
``	O
Consolidated	O
``	O
3	O
l.	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Annuities	O
.	O
''	O
11th	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
the	O
same	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Dr.	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
assign	O
and	O
transfer	O
,	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
part	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
transferable	O
share	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
700	O
l.	O
transferable	O
share	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
of	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
capital	O
stock	O
of	O
annuities	O
,	O
established	O
by	O
certain	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
(	O
reciting	O
the	O
titles	O
and	O
dates	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
)	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
12th	O
Count	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
eleventh	O
,	O
only	O
calling	O
it	O
a	O
certain	O
share	O
,	O
omitting	O
the	O
word	O
transferable	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Silvester	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
WALLACE	O
,	O
MAY	O
it	O
please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
counsel	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
in	O
support	O
of	O
this	O
prosecution	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
stands	O
now	O
charged	O
before	O
you	O
with	O
forging	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
assisting	O
to	O
forge	O
and	O
publishing	O
,	O
a	O
false	O
deed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
to	O
enable	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
transfer	O
stock	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Dr.	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
other	O
charges	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
stating	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
different	O
persons	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
transaction	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
also	O
charged	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
special	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
,	O
relative	O
to	O
the	O
stocks	O
-	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
which	O
charges	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
pleaded	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
laid	O
before	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
determine	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
offence	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
shortly	O
state	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
this	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
the	O
better	O
apply	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
hear	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
woollen-draper	O
and	O
salesman	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
He	O
married	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lived	O
at	O
Westham	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
year	O
1768	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hewlett	O
having	O
agreed	O
upon	O
a	O
marriage	O
with	O
a	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Drathgate	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
possessed	O
of	O
Consolidated	O
Bank	O
3	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Annuities	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
some	O
property	O
in	O
other	O
stocks	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
,	O
previous	O
to	O
the	O
marriage	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
interest	O
in	O
these	O
stocks	O
should	O
be	O
settled	O
upon	O
certain	O
trusts	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
as	O
trustees	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
agreement	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Drathgate	O
,	O
previous	O
to	O
her	O
marriage	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hewlett	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
transferred	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
700	O
l.	O
Consolidated	O
Bank	O
3	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Annuities	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
700	O
l.	O
3	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Reduced	O
Annuities	O
.	O
This	O
proposed	O
marriage	O
took	O
effect	O
;	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
was	O
afterwards	O
made	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
trustees	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
to	O
enable	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
dividends	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
apply	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
trusts	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
vested	O
in	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hewlett	O
died	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hewlett	O
continuing	O
to	O
be	O
entitled	O
under	O
this	O
trust	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
the	O
dividends	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
accommodate	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
agree	O
to	O
sell	O
out	O
the	O
Reduced	O
Annuities	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
occasion	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
executed	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
enable	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Reduced	O
Annuities	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
became	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
suspicions	O
arising	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Consolidated	O
Bank	O
Annuities	O
had	O
also	O
been	O
transferred	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Reduced	O
Annuities	O
,	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
trustee	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
that	O
,	O
applied	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Consolidated	O
Bank	O
Annuities	O
had	O
been	O
transferred	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
given	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Reduced	O
Annuities	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
given	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
from	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
transferred	O
these	O
Consolidated	O
Annuities	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
the	O
attorney	O
for	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
authorized	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
transfer	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
nor	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
was	O
forged	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
doubt	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
concerned	O
in	O
that	O
forgery	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
publishing	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
state	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
this	O
forgery	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
applied	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Nesbitt	O
,	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
stock	O
under	O
this	O
forged	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
The	O
stock	O
was	O
accordingly	O
transferred	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
,	O
set	O
his	O
name	O
as	O
the	O
person	O
acting	O
and	O
authorized	O
by	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
are	O
described	O
to	O
be	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
,	O
salesman	O
,	O
of	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
salesman	O
,	O
of	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
for	O
such	O
persons	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
names	O
were	O
real	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
actually	O
subscribed	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
as	O
attesting	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
both	O
relations	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
proved	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
set	O
their	O
names	O
as	O
witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
saw	O
it	O
executed	O
by	O
either	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
or	O
by	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
folded	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
set	O
their	O
names	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
witnesses	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
witnesses	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
did	O
not	O
conceive	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
wrong	O
,	O
depending	O
upon	O
the	O
credit	O
and	O
integrity	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
a	O
thing	O
which	O
was	O
improper	O
,	O
or	O
desire	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
thing	O
which	O
was	O
improper	O
.	O
They	O
set	O
their	O
names	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
seeing	O
it	O
executed	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
truth	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
subscribed	O
their	O
names	O
to	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
alone	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
answered	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
stock	O
being	O
vested	O
in	O
two	O
trustees	O
,	O
jointly	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
must	O
concur	O
in	O
an	O
act	O
to	O
transfer	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
must	O
either	O
both	O
concur	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
act	O
of	O
transferring	O
,	O
personally	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
must	O
authorize	O
an	O
attorney	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
alone	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
sufficient	O
.	O
The	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
appears	O
with	O
a	O
seal	O
to	O
that	O
name	O
to	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
;	O
and	O
under	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
proved	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
applied	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
actually	O
did	O
sell	O
,	O
this	O
stock	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
lay	O
before	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
guilt	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
this	O
transaction	O
.	O
The	O
name	O
of	O
Doctor	O
Myonnet	B-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
resemblance	O
to	O
Doctor	O
Myonnet	B-pers
's	O
usual	O
manner	O
of	O
writing	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
does	O
not	O
resemble	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
call	O
the	O
witnesses	O
who	O
will	O
prove	O
these	O
facts	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
already	O
stated	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
proof	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
his	O
guilt	O
and	O
his	O
concern	O
in	O
this	O
transaction	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
judge	O
upon	O
that	O
evidence	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
satisfied	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
be	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
discharge	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
your	O
duty	O
in	O
pronouncing	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STONEHOUSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
accountant	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
book	O
here	O
containing	O
the	O
transfers	O
of	O
Consolidated	O
3	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Bank	O
Annuities	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Transfer	O
Book	O
.	O
Refer	O
to	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1768	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
transfer	O
of	O
stock	O
upon	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
French	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
transfer	O
of	O
700	O
l.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
,	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Divinity	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
signed	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Drathgate	I-pers
as	O
the	O
transferrer	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
entry	O
of	O
the	O
transfer	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
stock	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
were	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
NISBETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
stock-broker	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
applying	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
about	O
selling	O
some	O
3	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
annuities	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
700	O
l.	O
Bank	O
Consolidated	O
Annuities	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
acted	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
instructions	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
.	O
The	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
the	O
stock	O
stood	O
in	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Reverend	O
John	B-pers
Myonnet	I-pers
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
into	O
the	O
Rotunda	O
,	O
where	O
that	O
kind	O
of	O
business	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
broker	O
for	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
the	O
stock	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
usual	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
register	O
of	O
these	O
kind	O
of	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
stock	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
price	O
was	O
78	O
3/8	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
and	O
which	O
amounted	O
to	O
550	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
sum	O
I	O
paid	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
make	O
the	O
transfer	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
the	O
transfer	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
what	O
I	O
mean	O
by	O
make	O
the	O
transfer	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witness	O
read	O
the	O
transfer	O
from	O
the	O
transfer	O
book	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
this	O
,	O
Witness	O
my	O
hand	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	O
attorney	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
transfer	O
are	O
Robert	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
and	O
myself	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Nesbitt	I-pers
,	O
as	O
broker	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
produce	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
writing	O
in	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
fancy	O
it	O
is	O
filled	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
:	O
when	O
instructions	O
are	O
given	O
for	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
I	O
understand	O
that	O
the	O
date	O
is	O
inserted	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
execution	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
date	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
hand	O
as	O
the	O
filling	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
instrument	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
;	O
the	O
demand	O
to	O
act	O
under	O
that	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
is	O
signed	O
by	O
Sherwood	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PIGG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
subscribing	O
witness	O
to	O
something	O
written	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
witness	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
transferring	O
of	O
the	O
700	O
l.	O
stock	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
something	O
printed	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
demand	O
to	O
act	O
by	O
this	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
4th	O
April	O
,	O
1777	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
signed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
By	O
whom	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
gentleman	O
who	O
wrote	O
his	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
signed	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Nesbitt	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
broker	O
,	O
signified	O
his	O
knowledge	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
I	O
subscribed	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nesbitt	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
executed	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Nesbitt	O
.	O
Who	O
signed	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
personally	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
reputation	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Call	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
French	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
object	O
to	O
the	O
examination	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
interested	O
witness	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
We	O
will	O
prove	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Bank	O
have	O
replaced	O
the	O
stock	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
Mr.	O
French	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
interested	O
.	O
Mr.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LEWIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
I	O
believe	O
secretary	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
order	O
to	O
transfer	O
any	O
stock	O
to	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
French	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
minute-book	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Directors	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
read	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Court	O
pleases	O
.	O
``	O
At	O
a	O
Court	O
of	O
Directors	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
``	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1778	O
,	O
``	O
Mr	O
.	O
Governor	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
-	O
.	O
''	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
object	O
to	O
the	O
reading	O
of	O
that	O
minute	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
proposed	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
shewing	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
affixed	O
to	O
this	O
instruments	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
say	O
is	O
forged	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
disinterested	O
witness	O
and	O
capable	O
of	O
proving	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
render	O
him	O
a	O
disinterested	O
witness	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Directors	O
have	O
replaced	O
the	O
stock	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
indifferent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
French	O
whether	O
the	O
instrument	O
be	O
valid	O
or	O
a	O
forged	O
one	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Directors	O
have	O
done	O
so	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
placed	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bank	O
are	O
themselves	O
interested	O
in	O
proving	O
this	O
a	O
forged	O
instrument	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
be	O
true	O
or	O
forged	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
will	O
depend	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
or	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
demanding	O
a	O
repayment	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
by	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
person	O
whose	O
name	O
this	O
imports	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
Therefore	O
as	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Directors	O
are	O
themselves	O
interested	O
in	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
consequently	O
no	O
minute	O
made	O
by	O
them	O
will	O
be	O
proper	O
evidence	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
They	O
state	O
themselves	O
liable	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
to	O
Mr.	O
French	O
and	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
this	O
stock	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
improperly	O
transferred	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
make	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
direct	O
the	O
stock	O
to	O
be	O
transferred	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
act	O
against	O
their	O
interest	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
trying	O
for	O
forgery	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
offered	O
is	O
tending	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
forgery	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Bank	O
can	O
never	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
therefore	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
its	O
being	O
a	O
matter	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
are	O
interested	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
strongest	O
degree	O
proving	O
against	O
their	O
own	O
interest	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
order	O
read	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lewin	O
,	O
as	O
followeth	O
:	O
]	O
``	O
That	O
the	O
committee	O
of	O
Treasury	O
``	O
have	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
good	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Dr.	O
``	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
said	O
sum	O
of	O
700	O
l.	O
Consolidated	O
three	O
``	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Annuities	O
.	O
''	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
We	O
will	O
now	O
shew	O
that	O
that	O
transfer	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
this	O
transfer	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
made	O
by	O
Burgess	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
transfer	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
SUTTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
[	O
refers	O
to	O
the	O
book	O
]	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
accept	O
the	O
transfer	O
of	O
this	O
stock	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
both	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
now	O
examine	O
the	O
Reverend	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
French	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
have	O
proved	O
the	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
stock	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
;	O
Mr.	O
French	O
's	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
stock	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
conceive	O
,	O
a	O
sufficient	O
discharge	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
trustee	O
,	O
the	O
transfer	O
is	O
not	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
complete	O
.	O
Would	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
this	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
tranfers	O
by	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
supposing	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
had	O
not	O
accepted	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
have	O
entitled	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
dividend	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
signed	O
that	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
stock	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
personally	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
transfer	O
is	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
accepted	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
his	O
mental	O
faculties	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
talk	O
very	O
sensibly	O
,	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
confess	O
he	O
varied	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
really	O
of	O
found	O
understanding	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
accepted	O
that	O
stock	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
sensible	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
name	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
annexed	O
as	O
a	O
party	O
to	O
that	O
instrument	O
[	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
]	O
your	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
execute	O
,	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
that	O
instrument	O
as	O
your	O
deed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
presume	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
name	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
certainly	O
like	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
writing	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
better	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
than	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
But	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
rather	O
incline	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
by	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
shewn	O
this	O
instrument	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
opinion	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
's	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
thought	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
once	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
sufficient	O
judge	O
of	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
name	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
to	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
is	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
handwriting	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
similitude	O
to	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
STACY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
well	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
name	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
subscribed	O
to	O
that	O
letter	O
of	O
a	O
ttorney	O
,	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
name	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
to	O
the	O
transfer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
transfer	O
book	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
way	O
of	O
his	O
signing	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
usual	O
way	O
of	O
his	O
signing	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
Pray	O
what	O
character	O
does	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
bear	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
disrespectful	O
word	O
said	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
worthy	O
man	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HEWLETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
instrument	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
]	O
Is	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
your	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
,	O
or	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
execute	O
that	O
instrument	O
?	O
-	O
Neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
your	O
name	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
an	O
instrument	O
to	O
sign	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
either	O
an	O
injury	O
to	O
me	O
or	O
himself	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
bring	O
that	O
instrument	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
name	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
competent	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
subscribed	O
his	O
name	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
to	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
an	O
instrument	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
instrument	O
executed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
received	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Dodd	O
;	O
it	O
will	O
only	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
witness	O
's	O
credit	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
with	O
the	O
instrument	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
usually	O
did	O
,	O
Tommy	O
,	O
sign	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
punctual	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
;	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
write	O
,	O
salesman	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
name	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
to	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
signed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
seeing	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
French	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
Doctor	O
Myonnet	B-pers
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Reverend	O
Mr.	O
French	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
an	O
instance	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
reduced	O
annuities	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Doctor	O
Myonnet	B-pers
,	O
did	O
sign	O
the	O
like	O
authority	O
with	O
that	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
question	O
,	O
without	O
there	O
being	O
any	O
subscribing	O
witnesses	O
to	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
to	O
obtain	O
subscriptions	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
witnesses	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
Where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
design	O
of	O
fraud	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
subscribing	O
witnesses	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
positively	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
To	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlett	I-pers
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
long	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
frequently	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
date	O
to	O
that	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
3d	O
April	O
,	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
positively	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
SHERWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
name	O
Francis	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
to	O
this	O
instrument	O
(	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
)	O
your	O
handwriting	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
your	O
name	O
to	O
that	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
name	O
thereto	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
,	O
or	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
execute	O
that	O
instrument	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
writing	O
my	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
paper	O
but	O
writing	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
Were	O
either	O
Doctor	O
Myonnet	B-pers
,	O
or	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
counter	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
a	O
shopman	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
name	O
James	B-pers
French	I-pers
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
any	O
name	O
,	O
nor	O
nothing	O
,	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
writing	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
of	O
course	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
3d	O
April	O
upon	O
that	O
instrument	O
;	O
whose	O
hand-writing	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
3d	O
April	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
judgment	O
,	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
being	O
now	O
closed	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
wish	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
your	O
defence	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
understand	O
that	O
your	O
counsel	O
can	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
farther	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
than	O
call	O
your	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Therefore	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
refer	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
to	O
be	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
counsel	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
If	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
will	O
urge	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
furnishes	O
a	O
hint	O
for	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
pursue	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
for	O
selling	O
700	O
l.	O
Three	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
Reduced	O
Annuities	O
,	O
was	O
signed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
present	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
signed	O
that	O
;	O
upon	O
reading	O
it	O
over	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
this	O
``	O
should	O
be	O
witnessed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
signing	O
;	O
''	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
matter	O
of	O
form	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
signed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
departed	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
already	O
very	O
clearly	O
proved	O
;	O
namely	O
,	O
his	O
undoubted	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
are	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
;	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
proved	O
by	O
one	O
or	O
ten	O
thousand	O
witnesses	O
makes	O
no	O
difference	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
another	O
thing	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
shortly	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
some	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
,	O
the	O
counsel	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
are	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
in	O
an	O
infirm	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
very	O
infirm	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
the	O
counsel	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
whether	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
is	O
near	O
at	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
age	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
very	O
apt	O
to	O
forget	O
;	O
supposing	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
Mr.	O
French	O
's	O
deed	O
;	O
whether	O
this	O
being	O
described	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
as	O
the	O
deed	O
of	O
both	O
,	O
can	O
be	O
truly	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
deed	O
,	O
quoad	O
Mr.	O
French	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
deed	O
,	O
quoad	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
count	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
shaped	O
to	O
that	O
particular	O
case	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
count	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
to	O
answer	O
that	O
objection	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
witnesses	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
subscribed	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
too	O
common	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
subscribing	O
witness	O
after	O
the	O
party	O
has	O
signed	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
frequently	O
done	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
commonly	O
understood	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
witnesses	O
are	O
necessary	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
has	O
signed	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
stock	O
transferred	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
subscribed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
only	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
thinking	O
that	O
sufficient	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
the	O
broker	O
finding	O
two	O
necessary	O
,	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
care	O
who	O
signs	O
it	O
afterwards	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
common	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
improper	O
practice	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
less	O
his	O
deed	O
;	O
the	O
deed	O
is	O
complete	O
before	O
it	O
is	O
subscribed	O
by	O
any	O
witness	O
;	O
therefore	O
,	O
supposing	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
deed	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
,	O
the	O
question	O
is	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
deed	O
as	O
described	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
can	O
be	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
charge	O
is	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
this	O
warrant	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
warrant	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
and	O
Mr.	O
French	O
;	O
now	O
allowing	O
that	O
Dr.	O
Myonnet	O
did	O
execute	O
that	O
deed	O
,	O
yet	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
be	O
necessary	O
for	O
the	O
transferring	O
the	O
stock	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
French	O
should	O
likewise	O
have	O
signed	O
and	O
sealed	O
that	O
deed	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
deed	O
is	O
forged	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Ashhurst	O
summed	O
up	O
the	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
who	O
after	O
having	O
withdrawn	O
for	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
pronounced	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
223	O
,	O
224.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TICKNER	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
purpose	O
of	O
their	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
lying	O
in	O
wait	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Jacobb	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tickner	I-pers
with	O
a	O
bill-hook	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
wood	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
slit	O
the	O
nose	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Jacobb	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intention	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
to	O
maim	O
and	O
disfigure	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Jacobb	I-pers
in	O
the	O
manner	O
beforementioned	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
knowing	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
privy	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
felony	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tickner	I-pers
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
felony	O
.	O
2d	O
Count	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
only	O
charging	O
the	O
assault	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
with	O
a	O
weapon	O
and	O
instrument	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Jurors	O
,	O
as	O
yet	O
unknown	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JACOBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
at	O
Twickenham	B-place
;	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Whitham	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
turnep-field	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
pulling	O
the	O
turneps	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
turneps	O
had	O
been	O
stole	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
turnep-field	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Tickner	O
pulling	O
up	O
the	O
turneps	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Tickner	O
's	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
so	O
soon	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
strike	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
what	O
instrument	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
fixed	O
on	O
wood	O
which	O
cut	O
me	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
discern	O
whether	O
it	O
shone	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
judge	O
from	O
the	O
fling	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
fixed	O
into	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
it	O
hung	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
hard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
long	O
bill	O
,	O
but	O
something	O
loose	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
came	O
round	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
tied	O
to	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
flail	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
blow	O
fell	O
upon	O
my	O
nose	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
discover	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
received	O
the	O
second	O
blow	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sensible	O
of	O
having	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
I	O
lay	O
some	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
senseless	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
either	O
see	O
,	O
or	O
hear	O
,	O
any	O
person	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Tickner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
else	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
rightly	O
sensible	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
do	O
you	O
suppose	O
that	O
you	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
Tickner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
called	O
up	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
very	O
light	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Tickner	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
Tickner	O
was	O
a	O
hired	O
servant	O
to	O
Adams	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
REASON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Adams	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
Tickner	O
lived	O
there	O
too	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
Jacobb	O
's	O
having	O
been	O
hurt	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
master	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
call	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
that	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HUNTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
surgeons	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Hospital	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
Jacobb	O
:	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
superficial	O
wound	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
nose	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
wound	O
upon	O
his	O
neck	O
immediately	O
under	O
the	O
lower	O
jaw	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
eight	O
wounds	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
cuts	O
by	O
wounds	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
upon	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
also	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
brow	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
three	O
were	O
all	O
.	O
What	O
instruments	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
judgement	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
these	O
wounds	O
were	O
caused	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
by	O
a	O
sharp	O
instrument	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
wound	O
was	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
nose	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
slit	O
the	O
nose	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
divided	O
the	O
exteguments	O
of	O
the	O
nose	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
bones	O
of	O
the	O
nose	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
an	O
oblique	O
direction	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
it	O
penetrate	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
through	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
very	O
little	O
but	O
the	O
skin	O
covers	O
the	O
bones	O
of	O
the	O
nose	O
;	O
it	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bone	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
cut	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
scratch	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
cut	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
penetrate	O
through	O
the	O
skin	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
flesh	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
here	O
is	O
hardly	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
skin	O
;	O
it	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
skin	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
reach	O
the	O
bone	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
might	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
such	O
a	O
wound	O
as	O
will	O
leave	O
any	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
cicatrix	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
seen	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
cicatrix	O
is	O
scarcely	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
slit	O
of	O
the	O
nose	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lacerated	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
very	O
plainly	O
see	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
nose	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
do	O
you	O
suppose	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
before	O
that	O
wound	O
is	O
so	O
healed	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
visible	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
elapsed	O
last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
visible	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
well	O
say	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
will	O
take	O
to	O
obliterate	O
the	O
mark	O
.	O
Will	O
the	O
mark	O
ever	O
be	O
erased	O
during	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
;	O
there	O
may	O
be	O
some	O
little	O
mark	O
of	O
it	O
discovered	O
upon	O
a	O
close	O
examination	O
.	O
TICKNER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
my	O
mother	O
here	O
.	O
Adams	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
For	O
Tickner	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
TICKNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Tickner	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
lived	O
with	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
but	O
Adams	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
Adams	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
village	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
near	O
Riply	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
how	O
old	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
minister	O
for	O
the	O
register	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
something	O
turned	O
of	O
eighteen	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
farmer	O
at	O
Riply	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Adams	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
seldom	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
chairing	O
.	O
TICKNER	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
ADAMS	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
live	O
tame	O
fallow	O
deer	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
GEORGE	B-pers
COWSELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sixteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
,	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
tame	O
deer	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
up	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
another	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
barn-yard	O
;	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
bought	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
two	O
years	O
old	O
next	O
June	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
of	O
an	O
age	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
tame	O
.	O
The	O
buck	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
rub	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
the	O
doe	O
was	O
shy	O
to	O
strangers	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
left	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
barn-yard	O
on	O
Christmas-eve	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
buck	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
pails	O
round	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
that	O
evening	O
;	O
sometimes	O
we	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
buck	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
blood	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
barn-yard	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
hair	O
and	O
blood	O
upon	O
the	O
wall	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
over	O
.	O
Describe	O
the	O
buck	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
dumpty	O
horn	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
torn	O
his	O
car	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
shepherd	O
cut	O
it	O
half	O
off	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
colour	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
REASON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
Christmas-eve	O
Adams	O
and	O
Tickner	O
came	O
home	O
together	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
upon	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
dead	O
deer	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
stuck	O
;	O
its	O
throat	O
was	O
cut	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
horn	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
skinned	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
all	O
the	O
flesh	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
eating	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
haunch	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
mistress	O
carried	O
for	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
skin	O
and	O
the	O
head	O
(	O
except	O
a	O
bit	O
which	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
dog	O
)	O
were	O
buried	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
workman	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
dig	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
garden	O
for	O
the	O
skin	O
of	O
the	O
deer	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
dig	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
skin	O
,	O
four	O
legs	O
and	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
witness	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
skin	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
deer	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
This	O
deer	O
struck	O
my	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
ribbs	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deer	O
ran	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
kill	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
it	O
across	O
the	O
throat	O
with	O
my	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
lay	O
some	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
killed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Tickner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
servant	O
maid	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pity	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
lie	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
skinned	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
put	O
the	O
skin	O
under	O
ground	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
225.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
three	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BALLARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Chequers	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Duke-street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
I	O
sent	O
out	O
two	O
servants	O
to	O
collect	O
in	O
my	O
pots	O
;	O
the	O
pots	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
strap	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
pots	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
