TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1778	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
MDCCXXXVIII	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKSTONE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
.	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Caney	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blower	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Horsford	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Warcup	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hiching	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Beans	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jolland	I-pers
,	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martyn	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Leverick	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Willoughby	O
Brewer	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Hougham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Dunkley	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Broxup	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Renswick	I-pers
.	O
727.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
tape	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sewing	O
thread	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stockdale	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
19th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
STOCKDALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
button-shop	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stockdale	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
twice	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
something	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
stay-tapes	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marrow	I-pers
after	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
brough	O
;	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stay-tapes	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARROW	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
step	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
work	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
parcel	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
slipped	O
the	O
thread	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
bid	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
parcel	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
parcel	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
;	O
they	O
pursued	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
had	O
above	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
hank	O
or	O
two	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
:	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shape	O
or	O
size	O
of	O
this	O
bundle	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
such	O
a	O
mistake	O
should	O
happen	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
728	O
,	O
729.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ROSE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9th	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
decoyed	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Black-boy-alley	B-place
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
prevent	O
her	O
taking	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Barber	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
held	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
their	O
persons	O
;	O
Rose	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
Barber	O
and	O
one	O
Doyle	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
Barber	O
then	O
threw	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
another	O
indictment	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
speak	O
of	O
that	O
now	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
your	O
own	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
receive	O
5	O
l.	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
give	O
change	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
the	O
person	O
should	O
give	O
me	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Rose	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
nobody	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
secured	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
any	O
agreement	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
any	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Girdler	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
BARBER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
committed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
Doyle	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
raise	O
five	O
guineas	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
rigour	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
ROSE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
take	O
me	O
?	O
Both	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9th	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
decoyed	O
by	O
Hannah	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
into	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Doyle	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
indictment	O
)	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
;	O
Barber	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
herself	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
arm	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wrenched	O
my	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
5	O
l.	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Doyle	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
After	O
Doyle	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
she	O
kept	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pursue	O
Doyle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
fastened	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Doyle	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
so	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Doyle	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
return	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
us	O
;	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
expect	O
the	O
utmost	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
raise	O
five	O
guineas	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
apply	O
to	O
friends	O
to	O
lend	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
730.	O
SARAH	B-pers
LYNCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
17th	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Lovegrove	O
and	O
Hunter	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
salesmen	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-market	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
bill	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tons	O
,	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
an	O
alley	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
New-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
in	O
doors	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
they	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
up	O
their	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
unbuttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
resist	O
her	O
doing	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
resist	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
immediately	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
my	O
eyes	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
other	O
women	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
were	O
the	O
women	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
always	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
731	O
,	O
732.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOLLOWAY	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMALLCOMB	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Proffitt	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
steel	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
inkholder	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
October	O
17th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PROFFITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
under	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Knight's-bridge	B-place
.	O
On	O
yesterday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
pretty	O
near	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
Chelsea	B-place
on	O
foot	O
,	O
three	O
soldier	O
s	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
within	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
throw	O
of	O
the	O
high	O
road	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
two	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
my	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
inkhorn	O
,	O
and	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
again	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
weapons	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
only	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
fright	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
towards	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
I	O
durst	O
not	O
follow	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
knocked	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
Holloway	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dusk	O
,	O
the	O
moon	O
was	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
cloud	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Holloway	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
when	O
Holloway	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JEALOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
An	O
information	O
was	O
given	O
at	O
our	O
office	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
and	O
took	O
Holloway	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
opposite	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
PISS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
quarters	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
to	O
Brompton	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
soldiers	O
,	O
Holloway	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Holloway	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
quarters	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
about	O
some	O
robbery	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
two	O
sessions	O
to	O
live	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
sharp	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
lead	O
these	O
young	O
men	O
away	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
many	O
a	O
one	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
laugh	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
stick	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
the	O
errand	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
more	O
good	O
than	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
weak	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
supposed	O
we	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Twenty-one	O
if	O
I	O
live	O
till	O
next	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Holloway	O
is	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
a	O
deserter	O
;	O
Holloway	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
company	O
;	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
field	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
soldier	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
)	O
;	O
Holloway	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
before	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
throw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
off	O
when	O
they	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
overtook	O
them	O
again	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
from	O
where	O
they	O
robbed	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
short	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
were	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
then	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
complained	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
To	O
Proffitt	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
behind	O
.	O
HOLLOWAY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
Tothil-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
deserter	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Bailey	O
's	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
soldier	O
almost	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
twenty	O
one	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
SMALLCOMB	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
serjeant	O
is	O
not	O
come	O
yet	O
.	O
HOLLOWAY	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
SMALLCOMB	O
Not	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
733.	O
SARAH	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
September	O
19th	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
four	O
weeks	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
somebody	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
same	O
noise	O
repeated	O
,	O
turning	O
round	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
(	O
the	O
curtains	O
being	O
drawn	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
drew	O
back	O
the	O
curtains	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
with	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
and	O
petticoat	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
likewise	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
asked	O
my	O
husband	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
four	O
shillings	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
and	O
seised	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
think	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stays	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
dropped	O
and	O
extricated	O
herself	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
had	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
recollected	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
Timnall	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
two	O
shillings	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
she	O
afterwards	O
produced	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TIMNALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Scott	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
screaming	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
without	O
any	O
cap	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
being	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
that	O
stood	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
I	O
apprehend	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
two	O
shillings	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
secured	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Scott	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
shillings	O
she	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
upon	O
being	O
told	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
declare	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
shoe	O
and	O
stocking	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
girl	O
that	O
had	O
some	O
rags	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Spitalfields	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
bed-chamber	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
734.	O
MARY	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
treble	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
worked	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
double	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
worked	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
lawn	O
apron	O
worked	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
lawn	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
July	O
21st	O
-	O
SCOTT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
trunk	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
note	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
emptied	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
it	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
near	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
who	O
was	O
below	O
stairs	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
fetched	O
the	O
trunk	O
had	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
insisted	O
then	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
she	O
that	O
had	O
fetched	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
theft	O
upon	O
her	O
sister	O
;	O
her	O
sister	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
nothing	O
appeared	O
against	O
her	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
cap	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ALDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cordy	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Berwick-street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
and	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
Miss	O
Berry	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Well-street	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
RICHARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Newtoner's-lane	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
did	O
likewise	O
occasionally	O
pawn	O
goods	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Sarah	O
;	O
the	O
sister	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
Mary	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
REYNOLDS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
cap	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
(	O
pointing	O
them	O
out	O
)	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
justice	O
committed	O
for	O
stealing	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
she	O
drew	O
out	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
by	O
herself	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
sister	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
several	O
articles	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
sister	O
that	O
fetched	O
the	O
trunk	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
and	O
pawn	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Miss	O
Berry	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Miss	O
Berry	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Hopwood	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
confess	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
nor	O
see	O
her	O
go	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
to	O
beg	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
735.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbands	O
,	O
containing	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hollier	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3d	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HELLIER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
on	O
Holborn	B-place
Bridge	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
October	O
my	O
servant	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
containing	O
the	O
ribbands	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
recovered	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BROUGHTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
back	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
October	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
his	O
limbs	O
and	O
his	O
walk	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
wainscott	O
box	O
with	O
a	O
deal	O
front	O
,	O
painted	O
mahogany	O
colour	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
inches	O
square	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
IVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
HELLIER	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Hellier	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
ribbands	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
further	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
ribbands	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
twice	O
before	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BASKERVILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
October	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
hair	O
cut	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bundle	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rolls	O
of	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
without	O
having	O
his	O
hair	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
presently	O
;	O
one	O
Roach	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
contained	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
woman	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
bring	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Baskerville	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
;	O
Peg	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
736.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PRINGLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
hundred	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
gauze	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
26th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TREHERN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Worcester	O
stage	O
waggon	O
,	O
which	O
comes	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
Inn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Worcester	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
at	O
about	O
six	O
miles	O
from	O
High	O
Wycombe	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
afterwards	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
waggoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
nobody	O
can	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
gap	O
of	O
an	O
hedge	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
my	O
waggon	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
deal	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
737.	O
ANNE	B-pers
CORKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Botheroyd	I-pers
,	O
October	O
16th	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
738.	O
SARAH	B-pers
BRIGGS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Botheroyd	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
24th	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BOTHEROYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
my	O
pots	O
in	O
Beach-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
some	O
pots	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pot	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
water	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Towers	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
water	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
739.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BEANS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
loaves	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
28	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
October	O
19th	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
SKINNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
monday	O
evening	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Poor	B-place
Jury	I-place
Lane	I-place
with	O
two	O
baskets	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Goble	O
in	O
Church	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
loaves	O
of	O
sugar	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
partner	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
since	O
seen	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
dragged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
my	O
horse	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
Skinner	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
loaves	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty	O
loaves	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GUARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
five	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
just	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
should	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
nor	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
740.	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
LYNCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
an	O
infant	O
of	O
eight	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
did	O
wickedly	O
know	O
and	O
abuse	O
,	O
September	O
21st	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
741.	O
ANNE	B-pers
HAGGER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
October	O
5th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TOWERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
aunt	O
,	O
Anne	O
Green	O
,	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
and	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
club-night	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
off	O
the	O
upper	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
aunt	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
till	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
girl	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
myself	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
underneath	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
good	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pot	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Towers	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
his	O
aunt	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
pot	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
small	O
beer	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
742.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LESTRUCCI	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ryves	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
19th	O
Mr.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RYVES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
17	I-place
in	I-place
great	I-place
Titchfield-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
my	O
place	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
looking	O
over	O
,	O
it	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
frequented	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Hedge-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
directed	O
to	O
one	O
Lewis	B-pers
Rossi	I-pers
's	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Maid-Court	O
,	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
possession	O
of	O
some	O
duplicates	O
of	O
table	O
spoons	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
pledged	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
Rossi	O
very	O
honestly	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
LEWIS	B-pers
ROSSI	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
by	O
translating	O
from	O
foreign	O
languages	O
into	O
English	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
frequenting	O
Italian	O
houses	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
raise	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
duplicates	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
commissioned	O
to	O
sell	O
these	O
duplicates	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
paying	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
and	O
redeem	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
three	O
table	O
spoons	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
eight	O
shillings	O
on	O
each	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
duplicates	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
desposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
sister-in-law	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ryves	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ryves	O
;	O
perhaps	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
wanted	O
my	O
wages	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
raise	O
this	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
for	O
my	O
wages	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
743	O
,	O
744.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
GREENSLADE	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
AGAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steal	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wainyates	I-pers
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
October	O
13th	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
abovementioned	O
goods	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WAINYATES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Antigallican	O
and	O
Prize	O
in	O
Margaret-street	O
,	O
Cavendish-square	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Mary-le-Bonne	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
George-alley	B-place
,	O
which	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
Greenslade	O
crossed	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
followed	O
me	O
some	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
to	O
a	O
rather	O
light	O
place	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
liquor	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
rather	O
fumbling	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
chose	O
not	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
cast	O
my	O
eye	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
something	O
that	O
glittered	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
hinder-most	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
fob	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Greenslade	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
glittering	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
Rather	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
accosted	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
Swan	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
liquor	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
George-alley	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
Greenslade	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
some	O
bad	O
houses	O
in	O
the	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
intelligence	O
where	O
Agan	O
had	O
pawned	O
or	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
intelligence	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
was	O
Burkett	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
BURKETT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
boat-builder	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
on	O
the	O
Surry	O
side	O
of	O
Black-Friar	O
's	O
Bridge	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Agan	I-pers
seventeen	O
shillings	O
upon	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
eleventh	O
instant	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
How	O
happened	O
she	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
What	O
friend	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Chick-lane	O
:	O
another	O
woman	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
Sunday	O
night	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
market	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Nor	O
not	O
caring	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
born	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Agan	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
GREENSLADE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
our	O
place	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
my	O
supper	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
watch	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
nor	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
constable	O
charge	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
he	O
fetched	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
while	O
he	O
fetched	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
drive	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
nor	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
AGAN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
George-alley	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
trod	O
upon	O
something	O
;	O
it	O
rattled	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
halves	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
us	O
17	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
further	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
your	O
having	O
looked	O
at	O
your	O
watch	O
any	O
time	O
that	O
evening	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
going	O
over	O
Smithfield	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
then	O
wanted	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
to	O
nine	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
GREENSLADE	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
AGAN	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
Greenslade	O
,	O
Agan	O
:	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Greenslade	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
745	O
,	O
746	O
,	O
747.	O
PATRICK	B-pers
BURN	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONQUE	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
22	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
748.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
POWLETT	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
George	B-pers
Strahan	I-pers
,	O
clerk	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
May	O
17th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
749	O
,	O
750	O
,	O
751.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
,	O
MARY	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Kirkman	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
)	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
752.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GARDNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
linen	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lingham	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
23d	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
LINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
some	O
stockings	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
'pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
Harding	O
,	O
the	O
apprentice	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
HARDING	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
stomach-ache	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
her	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
stockings	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
linen	O
gloves	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
pair	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
has	O
Mr.	O
Lingham	O
's	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
put	O
fifteen	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
stockings	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
fourteen	O
pair	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
miss	O
the	O
gloves	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
pair	O
there	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Westminster	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
black	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
gloves	O
were	O
pushed	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
pushed	O
all	O
the	O
heap	O
in	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
step	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
knows	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nine	O
cock	O
's	O
heads	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
lives	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pin-maker	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
753.	O
MARY	B-pers
MOLLINEAUX	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
containing	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Emanuel	O
,	O
Oct.	O
8th	O
.	O
EMANUEL	B-pers
THORLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	B-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
gauze	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
common	O
sort	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
kind	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
wanted	O
silk	O
gauze	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
silk	O
gauze	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
milliners	O
and	O
haberdashers	O
goods	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sorry	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
them	O
within	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
arm	O
round	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
of	O
mine	O
under	O
your	O
cloak	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
slide	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropped	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
heel	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
boy	O
that	O
was	O
near	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
cloth	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
directly	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
has	O
my	O
own	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
this	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
red	O
cloak	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
three	O
women	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
near	O
his	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
lived	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
service	O
in	O
Lincolns-inn-fields	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
towards	O
Westminster	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
buy	O
some	O
gauze	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
a	O
cap	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
vast	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
turned	O
her	O
head	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
coming	O
;	O
that	O
rather	O
startled	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
;	O
she	O
dropped	O
something	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
no	O
cloak	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
cloak	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
this	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
red	O
cloak	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
persuaded	O
before	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
cloth	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
sliding	O
down	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
bid	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Whether	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
cloak	O
on	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
circumstance	O
that	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
cloak	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
swear	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
the	O
circumstance	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
When	O
that	O
woman	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
this	O
;	O
she	O
wished	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
trouble	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
evaded	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
questions	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
bind	O
her	O
over	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
754.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
19th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
some	O
pegs	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
another	O
account	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
stockings	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
frock	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
frock	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
sold	O
the	O
breeches	O
and	O
hat	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
again	O
afterwards	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
transpired	O
.	O
-	O
CORNFORTH	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
frock	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
coat	O
for	O
the	O
one	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
frock	O
and	O
coat	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
stockings	O
and	O
buckles	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mark	O
in	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
mark	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
and	O
buckles	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
stockings	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
755.	O
LETITIA	B-pers
GARDINER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21st	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
756.	O
MARY	B-pers
BUTLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
laced	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mildred	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MILDRED	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mildred	I-pers
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
wash	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
counted	O
out	O
the	O
linen	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
and	O
had	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
of	O
the	O
landlady	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
key	O
on	O
her	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
tub	O
and	O
some	O
water	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
soap	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
;	O
being	O
tired	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
drawers	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SADLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Mildred	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
to	O
surrender	O
herself	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
black	O
crape	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
were	O
Mrs.	O
Mildred	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
wrenched	O
open	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
laced	O
cap	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
flowered	O
linen	O
gown	O
at	O
one	O
Davidson	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
petticoat	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
again	O
;	O
Davidson	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
clothes	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
washed	O
for	O
this	O
woman	O
eight	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
a	O
thing	O
from	O
her	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
757.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
COCKED	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
diaper	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
huckerback	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
diaper	O
night	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
thirteen	O
table	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
table	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
carving	O
knife	O
and	O
fork	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
desert	O
knife	O
and	O
fork	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
China	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
account	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
proper	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clapham	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
18th	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
758.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARPENTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
moist	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
October	O
14th	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
759.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BURKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
760.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Disman	I-pers
,	O
October	O
17th	O
MARY	B-pers
DISMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Disman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
to	O
clean	O
our	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
selling	O
fruit	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
in	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
again	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
unlocked	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
near	O
Stepney	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
cloak	O
and	O
silk	O
hat	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
a	O
bushel	O
basket	O
covered	O
with	O
straw	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
hat	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SADLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Sword	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
bid	O
me	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
an	O
old	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
ribband	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Produce	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
forgot	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
cap	O
and	O
ribband	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
then	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
things	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
but	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
herself	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
this	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
ship-mate	O
's	O
wife	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
alehouse	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
her	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
and	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
761.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
SPONG	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hornsby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
762.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COX	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
women	O
's	O
cloth	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
September	O
13th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATKINS	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
fairs	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
makes	O
hats	O
and	O
bonnets	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
the	O
fairs	O
and	O
statutes	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coach	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
information	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
WATKINS	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
down	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
at	O
the	O
fair	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
privilege	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
any	O
other	O
passenger	O
he	O
might	O
meet	O
with	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
parcels	O
into	O
his	O
boot	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
petticoats	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bonnets	O
,	O
ribbands	O
,	O
and	O
hats	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
two	O
parcels	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
likewise	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
three	O
parcels	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
a	O
hat-box	O
,	O
bonnet-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
petticoats	O
,	O
the	O
cloaks	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
pack	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Edmonton	B-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
seek	O
a	O
lodging	O
which	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
and	O
sunk	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
raved	O
in	O
an	O
outrageous	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bell	O
to	O
change	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
off	O
with	O
this	O
other	O
parcel	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
hear	O
nothing	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
made	O
a	O
man	O
strip	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
two	O
miles	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
boot	O
and	O
coach	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Locke	O
took	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
we	O
came	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
the	O
coachmen	O
went	O
out	O
we	O
should	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
coach	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
we	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
changed	O
countenance	O
at	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
regard	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
known	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
hear	O
further	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
knows	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATKINS	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
took	O
this	O
man	O
under	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
warrant	O
?	O
Yes	O
:	O
Halliburton	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
shall	O
come	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
cared	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
drag	O
me	O
along	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
appear	O
like	O
a	O
blackguard	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
clean	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
that	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
woman	O
that	O
officiated	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
upon	O
what	O
account	O
,	O
I	O
there	O
mentioned	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
would	O
come	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
gentleman	O
have	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
tongue	O
out	O
,	O
signifying	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
some	O
gin	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
mother	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
thirteen	O
cloaks	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
My	O
pack	O
that	O
was	O
round	O
these	O
goods	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROFE	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother-in-law	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
cloak	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MILSON	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
a	O
cloak	O
was	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
by	O
Dinah	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
Who	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Dinah	B-pers
West	I-pers
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PAXTON	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
cloak	O
of	O
Dinah	B-pers
West	I-pers
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cloak	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
this	O
woman	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
drove	O
my	O
coach	O
away	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
horseswater	O
;	O
they	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
fare	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
every	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
miles	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
outside	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
followed	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
coachman	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
your	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
these	O
people	O
down	O
at	O
Bishopsgate	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
gentleman	O
at	O
Temple-bar	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
fares	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
seat	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
my	O
hammer	O
to	O
knock	O
the	O
pole	O
of	O
my	O
coach	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
mother-in	O
law	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
bundle	O
in	O
case	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
enquired	O
after	O
or	O
advertised	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
must	O
then	O
be	O
given	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
a	O
whole	O
week	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
never	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
safe	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
mother	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
twenty-six	O
years	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
a	O
misbehaviour	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
fault	O
in	O
the	O
days	O
of	O
my	O
breath	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
bread	O
all	O
my	O
life	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
but	O
God	O
and	O
your	O
lordship	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
coach	O
a	O
year	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
the	O
footman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
lordship	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
will	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
EYRE	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
763.	O
MARY	B-pers
BOW	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
valued	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Kenny	I-pers
,	O
September	O
24th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
764.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Caney	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
5th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
765.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BALE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Hume	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
in	O
8	O
vols	O
.	O
octavo	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
Hume	O
's	O
Essays	O
,	O
in	O
2	O
vols	O
.	O
octavo	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
August	O
8th	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
brother	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
barrister	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Scotland	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
detected	O
in	O
pawning	O
Hume	O
's	O
History	O
of	O
England	O
and	O
his	O
Essays	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
party	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
name	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
books	O
being	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
porter	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
.	O
HUGH	B-pers
DAVIDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
ten	O
books	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
History	O
of	O
England	O
by	O
Hume	O
and	O
Hume	O
's	O
Essays	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
porters	O
of	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
came	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pledge	O
such	O
books	O
,	O
I	O
particularized	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
name	O
Peter	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
in	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
particularly	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
library	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PULLAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
stair-case	O
with	O
some	O
books	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
brother	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Gone	O
the	O
Northern	O
circuit	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
these	O
books	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
your	O
brother	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
?	O
The	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
judges	O
went	O
the	O
Northern	O
circuit	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
has	O
been	O
laundress	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
this	O
year	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
nothing	O
ever	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chambers	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
meant	O
to	O
be	O
returned	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
imputation	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
766.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
October	O
17th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
her	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
767	O
,	O
768	O
,	O
769.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
PEARCE	I-pers
,	O
ANNE	B-pers
ARROGONY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
for	O
350	O
l.	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
for	O
150	O
l.	O
another	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
another	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
another	O
for	O
75	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
William	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
Peter	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
September	O
15th	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
KITCHEN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
near	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
by	O
three	O
women	O
;	O
they	O
surrounded	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
go	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
hands	O
held	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
secured	O
Pearce	O
directly	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
do	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
seemed	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
seem	O
before	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
surrounded	O
me	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
whether	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
surrounded	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
immediately	O
as	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
notes	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
14	O
or	O
1500	O
l.	O
and	O
many	O
memorandums	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
night	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
women	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
four	O
hands	O
held	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
one	O
must	O
have	O
held	O
two	O
hands	O
up	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
so	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
book	O
was	O
taken	O
four	O
hands	O
were	O
held	O
up	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
Arrogony	O
and	O
Davis	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
perfect	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
when	O
the	O
hands	O
were	O
held	O
up	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
seem	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
another	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
might	O
have	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
woman	O
besides	O
Pearce	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
other	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
's	O
being	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
yard	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Simpson	O
and	O
Arrogony	O
about	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
those	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
by	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Talbot	O
Gate	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
church	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
fat	O
one	O
(	O
Davis	O
)	O
ran	O
away	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
running	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
woman	O
near	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
women	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
you	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unhappy	O
woman	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
taken	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mills	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Griffiths	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Or	O
Price	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Or	O
Frisket	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Frisket	I-pers
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
they	O
might	O
call	O
me	O
Bet	B-pers
Frisket	I-pers
.	O
But	O
you	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Frisket	O
nor	O
Price	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Price	O
?	O
-	O
Price	O
the	O
bailiff	O
?	O
The	O
same	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
never	O
called	O
Price	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
connexion	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
these	O
women	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Kitchen	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
walked	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
talking	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
talking	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
talking	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
by	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Church-yard	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot-Inn	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
walking	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
all	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
women	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Simpson	B-pers
some	O
years	O
.	O
Were	O
did	O
they	O
first	O
salute	O
the	O
gentleman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
was	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
woman	O
near	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
off	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
before	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
Church-yard	O
before	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
women	O
standing	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
but	O
this	O
woman	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
how	O
many	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
before	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Pearce	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
together	O
.	O
AARON	B-pers
AARONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
bills	O
of	O
exchange	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
sums	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
bills	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
PEARCE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
SIMPSON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
ARROGONY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
For	O
Arrogony	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
woman	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Griffiths	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
Has	O
she	O
taken	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
by	O
your	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
have	O
not	O
called	O
her	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
woman	O
as	O
deserves	O
credit	O
upon	O
her	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
not	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HAYES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
several	O
names	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Griffiths	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
abandoned	O
woman	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
woman	O
as	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
believed	O
on	O
her	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
honour	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
she	O
ought	O
.	O
For	O
Pearce	O
.	O
AMELIA	B-pers
BURCHEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
woman	O
running	O
.	O
Was	O
Pearce	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
when	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
woman	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
staggered	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
Pearce	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
with	O
his	O
arms	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
escaped	O
from	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Pearce	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sheriff	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Pearce	O
immediately	O
?	O
-	O
Immediately	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
Holywell-passage	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
cried	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
Pearce	O
off	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Arrogony	O
and	O
that	O
lusty	O
woman	O
(	O
Davis	O
)	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
,	O
said	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
b	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
snitching	O
at	O
?	O
the	O
lusty	O
one	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Arrogony	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
four	O
yards	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Pearce	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
Bet	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
and	O
Bet	B-pers
Erisket	I-pers
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
PEARCE	O
GUILTY	O
Imp	O
.	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
ARROGONY	O
and	O
DAVIS	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
This	O
Jury	O
were	O
returned	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
770.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
dimitty	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
linen	O
night	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
with	O
broad	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
thirteen	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
twelve	O
muslin	O
hoods	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
twelve	O
fine	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
six	O
muslin	O
tippets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
with	O
pockets	O
and	O
bibs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
