TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1778	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
MDCCXXXVIII	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Higdens	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Pistor	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pallett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Arnell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bethell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whetherilt	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tibbs	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vardy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Seger	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Edmonson	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Marsh	O
,	O
*	O
Mark	B-pers
Warcup	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Warcup	I-pers
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Peasley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Slack	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dowle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
628.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DURHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11th	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Deptford	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
field	O
,	O
from	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
field	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
horse	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
Saunders	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopkins	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
;	O
Saunders	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Allen	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
brown	O
horse	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Allen	O
at	O
Rotherithe	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Hopkins	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
at	O
Tattersell	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Tattersell	O
's	O
at	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
expected	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Wildman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tattersell	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
-	O
WILDMAN	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tattersell	O
's	O
to	O
sell	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
;	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
bought	O
the	O
brown	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
in	O
Mint-street	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
bought	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
before	O
we	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
say	O
much	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
Is	O
neither	O
Allen	O
nor	O
Hopkins	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wildman	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
sold	O
at	O
Tattersell	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
black	O
horse	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
ears	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
booked	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Edmonds	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Watkins	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
ear	O
torn	O
off	O
by	O
rolling	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
bruised	O
with	O
the	O
gravel	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wildman	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
brought	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
sells	O
fish	O
;	O
he	O
comes	O
from	O
Kent	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
629.	O
AARON	B-pers
ABERDEEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burtost	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
September	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
:	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
630	O
,	O
631.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BUTT	I-pers
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Kayll	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
and	O
a	O
farthing	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
August	O
6th	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
632.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
cloth	O
containing	O
eighty	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Zenogle	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ZENOGLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Milk-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linens	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ERANKLIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Zenogle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
when	O
the	O
linens	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
pile	O
of	O
printed	O
linens	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
not	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
at	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
it	O
raised	O
my	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
some	O
linens	O
on	O
his	O
moulder	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
person	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
linen-immediately	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
man	O
but	O
went	O
a	O
wrong	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
with	O
the	O
linen	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
grey	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Mr.	O
DEPUTY	O
JONES	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Basinghall-street	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wyat	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
carrying	O
the	O
linen	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
seeing	O
himself	O
observed	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
some	O
lines	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
in	O
Moor-lane	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
passed	O
through	O
Moor-lane	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
account	O
so	O
trifling	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
constable	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
sour	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Fore-street	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wyatt	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Take	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
has	O
stole	O
that	O
linen	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
Moor-lane	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Moor-lane	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
sixpence	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deputy	O
Jones	O
gave	O
the	O
beadle	O
(	O
who	O
we	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
)	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Zenogle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
beadle	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
633.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15th	O
.	O
GABRIEL	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bell	B-place
in	I-place
Great	I-place
Carter-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Doctors	I-place
Commons	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
tankard	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HENNEKIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
proctor	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
Thursday	O
afternoon	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
drinking	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
clerks	O
in	O
the	O
Commons	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
understood	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
from	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
us	O
as	O
we	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
sitting	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
behind	O
us	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
tankard	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
supposed	O
that	O
ugly	O
fellow	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
Hennikin	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
Hennikin	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
delivered	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
634.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WOOLLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
steel	O
hand-saw	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22d	O
.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
on	O
a	O
new	O
building	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
second	O
story	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
saw	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
saw	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
saw	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
all	O
our	O
tools	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
NEWTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
if	O
any	O
carpenters	O
tools	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
saw	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Chippendale	O
produced	O
some	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Buckey	I-pers
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
for	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
635.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PEARCE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
leather	O
for	O
boot	O
legs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NICHOLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
currier	O
in	O
Jewin-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
boot	O
legs	O
at	O
Messrs.	O
Redford	O
and	O
Hollingsworth	O
,	O
stable-keepers	O
in	O
Little	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
by	O
one	O
Miles	O
,	O
who	O
transacts	O
business	O
for	O
Redford	O
and	O
Hollingsworth	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
leather	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
he	O
would	O
show	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
;	O
Miles	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
unmanufactured	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
information	O
.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
ELDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
four	O
unmanufactured	O
boot	O
legs	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
-	O
SMITH	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Redford	O
and	O
Hollingsworth	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
legs	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
these	O
legs	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
legs	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
Miles	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
son	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
him	O
these	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
discovery	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
Nichols	O
wanted	O
to	O
swear	O
the	O
robbery	O
agains	O
t	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
charged	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
636.	O
EPHRAIM	B-pers
EPHRAIMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Cushin	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
another	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
August	O
4th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
637.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HAROLD	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SALT	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
salt-cellar	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitefoot	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
September	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WHITEFOOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Hatton-garden	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nninght	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
before	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
table	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
having	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
weary	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
maid	O
came	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
cloth	O
;	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
the	O
salt-cellar	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
presently	O
called	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gone	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
the	O
salt-cellar	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
recovered	O
either	O
the	O
spoon	O
or	O
salt-cellar	O
.	O
Except	O
my	O
own	O
people	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
my	O
maid	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
off	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
in	O
much	O
confusion	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
salt	O
spoon	O
;	O
the	O
porter	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
boy	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
island	O
of	O
Dominica	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
638.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
DELILE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
hair	O
pins	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brilliant	O
diamond	O
earrings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
locket	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
bow-knot	O
set	O
with	O
brilliant	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
plain	O
gold	O
drop	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
hair	O
necklace	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
buckle	O
and	O
gold	O
end	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
Henry	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
and	O
not	O
perfectly	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
visit	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
's	O
in	O
Park-lane	B-place
,	O
near	O
Hyde-park-corner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
these	O
diamond	O
hair	O
pins	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
diamond	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
gold	O
locket	O
with	O
a	O
bow	O
knot	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plain	O
gold	O
drop	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
hair	O
neck-lace	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
buckle	O
and	O
gold	O
end	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
a	O
dressing-glass	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bed-room	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
a	O
visit	O
;	O
I	O
last	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
Whitsunday	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
:	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
this	O
room	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
's	O
valet	O
de	O
chambre	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
These	O
jewels	O
were	O
lost	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
reside	O
there	O
I	O
believe	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
an	O
accidental	O
visitor	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
reason	O
you	O
had	O
to	O
suspect	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
valet	O
de	O
chambre	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
particular	O
room	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
there	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
bed-rooom	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
bed-room	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
wait	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
maid	O
servants	O
waited	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
this	O
man	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
you	O
lay	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
access	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
's	O
bed-room	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
sleep	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
's	O
bedroom	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
wore	O
any	O
over	O
night	O
only	O
the	O
locket	O
and	O
ear-rings	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
servant	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
's	O
bed-room	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
sleep	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
WILKINSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
solicitor	O
.	O
Having	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
be	O
particularly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
consulted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
about	O
this	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
examined	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
him	O
contradict	O
himself	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
betwen	O
the	O
lining	O
and	O
the	O
crown	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
concealed	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
quession	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
tenacious	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
this	O
created	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
concealed	O
in	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
one	O
Sunday	O
,	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
baggage	O
ready	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
dressing-room	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
my	O
powder	O
sack	O
and	O
comb	O
as	O
customary	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
powder	O
and	O
the	O
combs	O
in	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
wrapped	O
up	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
wrapped	O
up	O
the	O
sack	O
of	O
powder	O
and	O
the	O
combs	O
in	O
that	O
table-cloth	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
that	O
table-cloth	O
to	O
wrapped	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
baggage	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
that	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
trunk	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
this	O
happened	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
attended	O
my	O
master	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
bed	O
as	O
customary	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
these	O
things	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
finding	O
these	O
things	O
put	O
there	O
by	O
mistake	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
thinking	O
that	O
the	O
lady	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
the	O
journey	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
delivering	O
them	O
again	O
which	O
I	O
intended	O
.	O
The	O
portmantua	O
was	O
put	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
The	O
lady	O
next	O
morning	O
took	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
lady	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
,	O
as	O
really	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
jewels	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nevill	O
,	O
who	O
wrote	O
one	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
effects	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
portmantua	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
master	O
wanted	O
to	O
examine	O
into	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
apart	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
them	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
coming	O
as	O
I	O
staid	O
upwards	O
of	O
six	O
weeks	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
threatened	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
about	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
on	O
my	O
arrival	O
at	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
conducted	O
immediately	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
interrogated	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
as	O
that	O
gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
French	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
conducted	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
understood	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
jewels	O
into	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
intending	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
639	O
,	O
640.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
GOODWIN	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Esther	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Esther	O
,	O
July	O
27th	O
.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
QUIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Five	B-place
Fields	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
foot-way	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
)	O
Goodwin	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Goodwin	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
bitch	O
!	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
money	O
,	O
run	O
her	O
through	O
!	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
three	O
halfpence	O
;	O
they	O
untied	O
my	O
silk	O
cloak	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
presented	O
a	O
brass	O
hanger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blade	O
rusty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
information	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
guardhouse	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
soldiers	O
dresses	O
when	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
SOLDIER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
guard-room	O
when	O
Esther	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
came	O
to	O
complain	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
came	O
and	O
talked	O
afterwards	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
guard-room	O
door	O
;	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
sword	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
cloak	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
twelve	O
.	O
The	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
sword	O
is	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blade	O
is	O
rusty	O
.	O
-	O
THORNTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
guard-room	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
Richmond	O
came	O
and	O
complained	O
too	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
:	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
arms	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
blade	O
of	O
a	O
sword	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
coats	O
:	O
the	O
serjeant	O
took	O
the	O
sword	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
guard-room	O
and	O
kept	O
them	O
till	O
nine	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
GOODWIN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
after	O
a	O
deserter	O
,	O
one	O
Stephen	B-pers
Blott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
hanger	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
guardroom	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
guard-room	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
kept	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
GREEN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
deserter	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
fact	O
sent	O
after	O
a	O
deserter	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
was	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
the	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
leave	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
to	O
miss	O
the	O
roll-call	O
.	O
)	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
641.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LARWILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
carnally	O
know	O
and	O
abuse	O
Jane	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
an	O
infant	O
under	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
ten	O
years	O
(	O
to	O
wit	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
nine	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
MARGARET	O
EAST	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
East	I-pers
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
to	O
nurse	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
service	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
this	O
complaint	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
is	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
private	O
parts	O
swelled	O
and	O
inflamed	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
one	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
that	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
feet	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
cried	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
mammy	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
her	O
unmercifully	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
directly	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
resused	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
without	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
subpoenaed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
faculty	O
examined	O
this	O
child	O
,	O
Dr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Andree	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Nine	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
purpose	O
you	O
are	O
brought	O
here	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
upon	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
an	O
oath	O
is	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
an	O
oath	O
is	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
God	O
that	O
governs	O
this	O
world	O
;	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
will	O
happen	O
to	O
people	O
that	O
are	O
wicked	O
,	O
that	O
tell	O
lies	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
bad	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
they	O
go	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
hell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sensible	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
wrong	O
thing	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
wrong	O
thing	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
still	O
worse	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
an	O
oath	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
therefore	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
JANE	O
EAST	O
sworn	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
you	O
must	O
tell	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
feet	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
bed-room	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
lick	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
any	O
thing	O
into	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
far	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
wet	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Sunday	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
lie	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Somebody	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
forwards	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
dine	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Mifflin	O
's	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
told	O
this	O
to	O
anybody	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
to	O
myself	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ramsey	O
,	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
seen	O
Mrs.	O
Ramsey	O
often	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
once	O
before	O
in	O
that	O
week	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Had	O
your	O
master	O
Larwell	O
and	O
you	O
any	O
quarrels	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
wicked	O
enough	O
to	O
whip	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
whipped	O
you	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
told	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
that	O
he	O
whipped	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
dined	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mifflin	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
whipped	O
you	O
for	O
doing	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
true	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
lie	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
whipped	O
me	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
done	O
what	O
he	O
whipped	O
you	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
Margaret	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Andree	O
examine	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Which	O
examined	O
her	O
first	O
?	O
-	O
Dr.	O
Dale	O
first	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
afterwards	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
-	O
KENNEDY	O
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
an	O
apothocary	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
girl	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
parts	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
inflamed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
swelling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
discharge	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
apprehend	O
from	O
the	O
vagina	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
cause	O
;	O
there	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
injury	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
parts	O
;	O
I	O
suggested	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
digitation	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
cause	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
hymen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
quite	O
perfect	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
sort	O
of	O
laceration	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
entered	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
impossible	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
laceration	O
of	O
the	O
hymen	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
in	O
this	O
child	O
do	O
you	O
suppose	O
the	O
hymen	O
to	O
be	O
up	O
the	O
vagina	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
understood	O
upon	O
former	O
occasions	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
various	O
in	O
different	O
subjects	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
sometimes	O
happens	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
course	O
of	O
things	O
there	O
is	O
little	O
deviation	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
do	O
you	O
suppose	O
the	O
hymen	O
to	O
lye	O
up	O
the	O
vagina	O
in	O
this	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
high	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
.	O
Whatever	O
then	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
this	O
injury	O
,	O
you	O
think	O
from	O
appearances	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
entered	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
so	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
necessary	O
to	O
observe	O
,	O
that	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
complaint	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
a	O
relaxation	O
of	O
the	O
bladder	O
;	O
her	O
urine	O
came	O
away	O
involuntary	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
cause	O
an	O
inflamation	O
of	O
the	O
parts	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
troubled	O
with	O
this	O
complaint	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
confident	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
troubled	O
with	O
that	O
complaint	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
examined	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Whether	O
in	O
your	O
knowledge	O
and	O
experience	O
that	O
disorder	O
,	O
occasioning	O
a	O
discharge	O
from	O
young	O
girls	O
,	O
which	O
produces	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
inflammation	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
extremely	O
common	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
common	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
this	O
girl	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
rancour	O
and	O
violence	O
in	O
the	O
women	O
and	O
friends	O
about	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
I	O
inspected	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
care	O
and	O
accuracy	O
possible	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
neither	O
laceration	O
,	O
ulceration	O
,	O
or	O
excoriation	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
observe	O
the	O
least	O
swelling	O
of	O
the	O
labia	O
or	O
the	O
lips	O
.	O
The	O
hymen	O
was	O
as	O
perfectly	O
complete	O
as	O
any	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
small	O
discharge	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
shift	O
;	O
the	O
mucous	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
upon	O
the	O
part	O
than	O
what	O
we	O
commonly	O
observe	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
degree	O
of	O
inflammation	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
urethra	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
vagina	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
urine	O
passes	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
did	O
observe	O
just	O
round	O
the	O
passage	O
a	O
very	O
slight	O
degree	O
of	O
inflammation	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
any	O
violence	O
had	O
lately	O
been	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
parts	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
clear	O
from	O
these	O
circumstances	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
entered	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
impossible	O
;	O
the	O
orifice	O
was	O
not	O
larger	O
than	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
quill	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
vagina	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
the	O
hymen	O
to	O
have	O
laid	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
hymen	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
examined	O
,	O
lies	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
enterance	O
of	O
the	O
vagina	O
,	O
not	O
within	O
the	O
vagina	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
called	O
the	O
vagina	O
till	O
you	O
pass	O
the	O
hymen	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
it	O
till	O
you	O
arrive	O
at	O
the	O
hymen	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
the	O
external	O
labia	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
labia	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
name	O
nymphae	O
;	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
external	O
parts	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
force	O
or	O
violence	O
used	O
to	O
her	O
so	O
recently	O
as	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
discovered	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
much	O
violence	O
used	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
recovered	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
short	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
more	O
marks	O
.	O
With	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
discharge	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
complaint	O
to	O
which	O
children	O
are	O
very	O
subject	O
?	O
-	O
Exceedingly	O
common	O
;	O
we	O
see	O
it	O
every	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
female	O
sex	O
of	O
all	O
ages	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
arise	O
from	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
causes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
it	O
was	O
exceeding	O
hot	O
weather	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
that	O
acrid	O
discharge	O
is	O
produced	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
always	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
degree	O
of	O
inflammation	O
?	O
-	O
Less	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
suppose	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
violence	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
which	O
the	O
child	O
mentioned	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
possible	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
more	O
appearances	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
different	O
appearances	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
days	O
may	O
do	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
little	O
violence	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
great	O
violence	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
impossible	O
;	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
introduction	O
,	O
there	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
other	O
appearances	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Dr.	O
COOPER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
child	O
very	O
attentively	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
redness	O
upon	O
the	O
external	O
parts	O
;	O
in	O
other	O
respects	O
the	O
appearances	O
were	O
quite	O
natural	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
swelling	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
no	O
excoriation	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
left	O
any	O
laceration	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
The	O
hymen	O
was	O
quite	O
complete	O
,	O
as	O
perfect	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
more	O
so	O
than	O
it	O
usually	O
is	O
in	O
children	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
redness	O
upon	O
the	O
passage	O
to	O
the	O
bladder	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
a	O
weakness	O
in	O
the	O
bladder	O
;	O
redness	O
is	O
universal	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
that	O
weakness	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
hymen	O
hath	O
once	O
been	O
penetrated	O
it	O
never	O
unites	O
afresh	O
;	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
it	O
forms	O
the	O
caruncula	O
myrtiformes	O
.	O
So	O
it	O
is	O
absolutely	O
impossible	O
that	O
there	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
least	O
penetration	O
,	O
nor	O
were	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
whatsoever	O
upon	O
the	O
parts	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
VERINDER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ramsden	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
grocer	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
;	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
foot	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
gown	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
top	O
of	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
mother	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
lick	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
running	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
looked	O
very	O
sore	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
RAMSDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
than	O
merely	O
the	O
account	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
given	O
us	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
else	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
nurse	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
further	O
than	O
her	O
coming	O
on	O
errands	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
till	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
through	O
the	O
entry	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
used	O
very	O
ill	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
nurse	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
in	O
what	O
respect	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
victuals	O
enough	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
they	O
beat	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
victuals	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
worse	O
than	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lick	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
hold	O
her	O
tongue	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
kept	O
it	O
to	O
herself	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
expected	O
her	O
mammy	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
tell	O
anybody	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
mammy	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
pain	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
for	O
three	O
days	O
sit	O
,	O
but	O
half	O
way	O
in	O
her	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
hurt	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
sending	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
till	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
came	O
immediately	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
washing	O
for	O
me	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
on	O
her	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
looked	O
reddish	O
and	O
sore	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
shift	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
washed	O
for	O
her	O
put	O
another	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
worse	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
642.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
RUFF	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
44	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
sixpence	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
September	O
8th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
44	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Crown-alley	B-place
.	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
apartments	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
formerly	O
rented	O
another	O
apartment	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
sometime	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
removed	O
to	O
this	O
apartment	O
where	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
removing	O
my	O
furniture	O
and	O
effects	O
from	O
the	O
former	O
apartment	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Purchase	I-pers
to	O
the	O
present	O
apartment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
assisted	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
in	O
moving	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
my	O
furniture	O
and	O
goods	O
were	O
removed	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
also	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
44	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
removed	O
;	O
the	O
44	O
l.	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
made	O
up	O
and	O
deposited	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
sum	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
knew	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
box	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
apartment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
assisted	O
in	O
placing	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
position	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
remain	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
apartment	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
bag	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
apartment	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
which	O
bag	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
among	O
this	O
44	O
l.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
sixpence	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
two	O
large	O
holes	O
drilled	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
enabled	O
to	O
distinguish	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
sixpence	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
made	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
daughter	O
;	O
she	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
this	O
box	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
money	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
employed	O
in	O
selling	O
salop	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
usual	O
custom	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
daughter	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
me	O
in	O
carrying	O
my	O
table	O
and	O
salop	O
into	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
my	O
daughter	O
returned	O
and	O
perceived	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
which	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
kept	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
bureau	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
clothes	O
and	O
other	O
effects	O
were	O
all	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
contained	O
in	O
them	O
were	O
thrown	O
about	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
gowns	O
wrapped	O
up	O
to	O
all	O
appearance	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
this	O
bag	O
lay	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
was	O
meant	O
to	O
put	O
these	O
clothes	O
and	O
gowns	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
was	O
disturbed	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
left	O
the	O
bag	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
bag	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
bag	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
for	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
offered	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
very	O
little	O
;	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
particular	O
observations	O
upon	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
more	O
holes	O
in	O
it	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
dirty-pillow	O
case	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
showed	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
such	O
observation	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
one	O
pound	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
six-pence	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
the	O
forty-four	O
pounds	O
was	O
not	O
made	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
removed	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
afterwards	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bag	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bag	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
observation	O
upon	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
that	O
my	O
mother	O
had	O
offered	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
dirty	O
pillow	O
case	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
identical	O
bag	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
had	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sixpence	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
is	O
the	O
identical	O
sixpence	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
another	O
reason	O
for	O
suspecting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
assisted	O
in	O
placing	O
the	O
box	O
where	O
it	O
stood	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MASON	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
,	O
Grub-street	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
pound	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
six-pence	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
daughter	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
fruit	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
eight	O
shillings	O
worth	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
six-pence	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
attend	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
appeared	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LASSELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
,	O
Grub-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
civil	O
,	O
and	O
sober	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
staid	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
sometimes	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
observation	O
was	O
made	O
that	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
six-pence	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
pocket	O
by	O
itself	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
inspected	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
643.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BEST	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
key	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
POOLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fourteen	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
chain	O
and	O
stone	O
seal	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
Artillery	B-place
ground	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
sham	O
fight	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
birth-day	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directly	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
UPHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
rescued	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
644	O
,	O
645.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRADLEY	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
WARE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Aug.	O
27th	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
646.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FLINT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Aaron	O
,	O
Aug.	O
16th	O
.	O
AARON	B-pers
COATS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oilman	O
,	O
in	O
Eastcheap	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
Nicholas-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
merely	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Lombard-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
croud	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
daily	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ADLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
MORANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Flint	O
,	O
two	O
boys	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
in	O
Flint	O
's	O
parlour	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
seal	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coats	O
's	O
watch	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
647	O
,	O
648.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RINKLE	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WABLE	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
649.	O
ANNE	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
bible	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
thread	O
edging	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
broad	O
blond	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
yds	O
.	O
of	O
plain	O
white	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worked	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
doyles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
egg	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rigacci	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
RIGACCI	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Prescot-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman	I-place
's	I-place
fields	I-place
.	O
Between	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
and	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
my	O
family	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
discharged	O
her	O
upon	O
a	O
regular	O
warning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intelligence	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
till	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
quitted	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
upon	O
an	O
application	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
to	O
what	O
place	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
quitted	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
use	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
particulars	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
discovered	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
by	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
accident	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Seddon	O
,	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
in	O
Salisbury-court	O
,	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
is	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
workman	O
for	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Seddon	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Seddon	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
on	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
was	O
three	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
as	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
up	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
promise	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rigacci	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
her	O
any	O
such	O
promise	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
650	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
double	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trim	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Eleanor	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
TRIM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
two-pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
ready	O
furnished	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
June	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
rent	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
workmen	O
she	O
employed	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
made	O
tents	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Howlit	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
sheet	O
and	O
blanket	O
;	O
the	O
sauce-pan	O
and	O
candlestick	O
were	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
place	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
651	O
,	O
652	O
,	O
653	O
,	O
654.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOSTON	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FLINT	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ELBURN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
GOODBURN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Benham	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
JENNINGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
chamber-maid	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Benham	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Catherine	B-place
Wheel	I-place
Inn	I-place
at	I-place
Colnbrook	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
dine	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
castor	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
they	O
paid	O
the	O
reckoning	O
.	O
Two	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
a	O
lady	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
stage	O
coach	O
dined	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
gentlewoman	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
removed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
sideboard	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
then	O
all	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
mistress	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
herself	O
much	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
sent	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Flint	O
,	O
Elburn	O
,	O
and	O
Goodburn	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Goodburn	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
hid	O
at	O
Windsor	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
WALKER	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Flint	O
,	O
Elburn	O
and	O
Goodburn	O
came	O
to	O
Colnbrook	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
which	O
wanted	O
some	O
repair	O
;	O
I	O
repaired	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Elburn	O
and	O
Goodburn	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Windsor	O
;	O
Flint	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
place	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Colnbrook	O
,	O
Flint	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
indemnification	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
Goodburn	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pepper	O
castor	O
and	O
silver	O
spoon	O
were	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
found	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
necessary	O
at	O
Windsor	O
;	O
the	O
spo	O
on	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
Flint	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
lads	O
,	O
Elburn	O
and	O
Goodburn	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbery	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
Goodburn	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
refused	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
a	O
felony	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
applied	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	O
promised	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
get	O
him	O
sent	O
to	O
sea	O
;	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
he	O
mentioned	O
a	O
robbery	O
at	O
Colnbrook	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
all	O
dined	O
at	O
the	O
Catherine	O
Wheel	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
can	O
not	O
admit	O
that	O
as	O
evidence	O
.	O
-	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Catherine-Wheel	O
at	O
Colnbrook	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
at	O
Windsor	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
a	O
necessary	O
,	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
behind	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
joists	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
Bolton	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
fight	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
Bolton	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
him	O
that	O
broke	O
the	O
spoon	O
it	O
was	O
Flint	O
that	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
Was	O
Flint	O
at	O
Windsor	O
when	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
London	O
upon	O
another	O
affair	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
]	O
BOLTON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
at	O
Windsor	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Colnbrook	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
dinner	O
myself	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
He	O
dined	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
she	O
reckoning	O
was	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Bolton	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
nine	O
at	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
or	O
whiskey	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
just	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Windsor	O
.	O
ELBURN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GOODBURN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
FLINT	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Wind	O
.	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
fire	O
works	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
and	O
dined	O
at	O
Colnbrook	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
knot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
put	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
her	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
accuse	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
blacksmith	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
indemnification	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
direction	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
lived	O
.	O
GOODBURN	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
three	O
aquitted	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
655.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29th	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
TURNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
near	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
behind	O
his	O
back	O
when	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
take	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
!	O
''	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
tumbled	O
down	O
behind	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
656.	O
MARY	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Blatchford	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BLATCHFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Duke-street	B-place
,	I-place
Portman-square	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
three	O
quart	O
and	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SPENCER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
a	O
person	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
stolen	O
some	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
quart	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
'	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
quart	O
pot	O
thrown	O
down	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
pint	O
pot	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
water	O
tub	O
at	O
the	O
necessary	O
door	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pots	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
pots	O
with	O
beer	O
when	O
he	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
water	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stoned	O
me	O
to	O
death	O
;	O
they	O
owe	O
me	O
a	O
spight	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
my	O
husband	O
spend	O
every	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
their	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
a	O
woman	O
since	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
657.	O
ANNE	B-pers
GILLIAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Virrier	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
August	O
14th	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
VIRRIER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	B-place
's	I-place
Lodge	I-place
,	I-place
Buckingham-gate	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
COX	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
in	O
Petty	O
France	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
next	O
day	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Virrier	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
]	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
658.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
in	O
April	O
1777	O
,	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
on	O
the	O
Thames	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
execution	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
sentence	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
overseer	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Plumstead	B-place
in	I-place
Kent	I-place
,	O
unlawfully	O
did	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
his	O
confinement	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
term	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
To	O
which	O
indictment	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
659.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BEACH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
general	O
Quarter	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
1776	O
,	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
petit	O
larceny	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
on	O
the	O
Thames	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
execution	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
order	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
overseer	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Plumstead	B-place
in	I-place
Kent	I-place
,	O
unlawfully	O
did	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
his	O
confinement	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
term	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
660.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
held	O
at	O
Justice	O
Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
Thames	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
execution	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
order	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
overseer	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Plumstead	B-place
in	I-place
Kent	I-place
,	O
unlawfully	O
did	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
of	O
his	O
confinement	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
term	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
661.	O
MARY	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
woman	O
's	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
boy	O
's	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
clouts	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
diaper	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
night-cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
barrow	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8th	O
.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
DELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
.	O
We	O
live	O
at	O
Battle	B-place
Bridge	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
at	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
son	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
any	O
old	O
clothes	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
eyes	O
on	O
the	O
woman	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
A	O
basket	O
which	O
contained	O
the	O
foul	O
clothes	O
was	O
emptied	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
bundle	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
she	O
let	O
loose	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
and	O
dropped	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
servant	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
LUCY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
servant	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
afterwards	O
into	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
so	O
when	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
sight	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
-	O
DELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
sent	O
me	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
mother	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
selling	O
any	O
old	O
clothes	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
bid	O
me	O
keep	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
stop	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
constantly	O
in	O
my	O
eye	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
662.	O
JANE	B-pers
WALLACE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rachael	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Caddle	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22d	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
CADDLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Henry	B-pers
Caddle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shift	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
at	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gown	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
shift	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Ferry	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
justice	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
RACHAEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Caddle	O
to	O
wash	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
KIRKPATRICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Terry	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
gown	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Caddle	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
shift	O
you	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
patch	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
663.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
ABRAHAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
printed	O
hebrew	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30th	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
locked	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
my	O
hebrew	O
grammar	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
lurking	O
about	O
my	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
drove	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
DAVIS	B-pers
WOLF	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Abraham	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
:	O
he	O
looked	O
much	O
confounded	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
that	O
book	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
book	O
to	O
Davis	O
,	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
664.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Timothy	I-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
August	O
3d	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
665.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
BURN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wainright	I-pers
,	O
August	O
2d	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
666.	O
JANE	B-pers
DARWIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sugar-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ashburn	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23d	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ASHBURN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
in	O
Hair-court	B-place
,	I-place
Aldgersgate-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
before	O
They	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
last	O
March	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
October	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
chest	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
confessed	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
with	O
one	O
Burrows	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
duplicates	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
no	O
promise	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COUCHTAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
mentioned	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
;	O
and	O
Burrows	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
BURROWS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
her	O
coming	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
buckle	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
the	O
tickets	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
in	O
seven	O
sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
will	O
show	O
me	O
the	O
duplicates	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
him	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Ashburn	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
alderman	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
on	O
what	O
account	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
some	O
stolen	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
articles	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
desired	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
that	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
dealt	O
so	O
unfairly	O
as	O
a	O
tradesman	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
tickets	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
duplicates	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Burrows	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
tickets	O
are	O
all	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
duplicate	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
buckle	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pawned	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
and	O
buckle	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
liberty	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
her	O
liberty	O
to	O
pawn	O
an	O
article	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
PRISONERS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
wrong	O
Mr.	O
Ashburn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
ever	O
so	O
many	O
witnesses	O
attending	O
for	O
me	O
till	O
to-day	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
any	O
attending	O
now	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
667	O
,	O
668.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
NOSIER	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
NOSEY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
carcase	O
of	O
lamb	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Fountain	I-pers
,	O
