TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1778	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
MDCCLXXVIII	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDING	O
'S	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JAMES	B-pers
ESDAILE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Haslam	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duperoy	I-pers
,	O
Almond	B-pers
Shroder	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Blyth	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Allen	O
Wall	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Maberley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carvel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Broomfield	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bakewell	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Tahourdin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nevett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hawkes	I-pers
,	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Treslove	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Birchall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reddish	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nesbett	I-pers
*	O
,	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Whitecombe	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nesbett	I-pers
.	O
Somerville	B-pers
Macqueen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greaves	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boodger	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
416.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
HERRING	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Talley	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
esterated	O
.	O
]	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
417.	O
CHARLOTTE	B-pers
SMEE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Roney	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
418.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENNIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
guineas	O
and	O
seven	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
March	O
8th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Hereford-shire	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
quarters	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
way	O
;	O
after	O
travelling	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
show	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
apiece	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
sixpence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
sixpence	O
being	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
change	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
glove	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
publican	O
could	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
paid	O
the	O
other	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
money	O
into	O
my	O
glove	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
countryman	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
Herefordshire	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
very	O
freely	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
glove	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
as	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
all	O
strangers	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
all	O
be	O
concerned	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
Williams	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Benjamin-street	B-place
,	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
sixpence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
change	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
children	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
glove	O
with	O
some	O
gold	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
publican	O
would	O
not	O
change	O
any	O
gold	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
other	O
penny	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
arm	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
within	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Was	O
Williams	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
but	O
was	O
properly	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Did	O
Williams	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
coming-to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
arm	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
wanted	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
money	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Edwards	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
arm	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Edwards	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
home	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
him	O
show	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
till	O
Monday	O
morning	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
not	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
pocket	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
money	O
into	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
Christopher	B-pers
Poul	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
]	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HASLING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
extreme	O
confusion	O
,	O
and	O
raved	O
like	O
a	O
madman	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
I	O
stripped	O
him	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
very	O
steady	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
to	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
black	O
glove	O
torn	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watchman	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
glove	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
money	O
into	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Edwards	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
the	O
watchmen	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
searched	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hearing	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
RICHMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
say	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
going	O
from	O
Jackson	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PARTRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HEELING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
just	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
419.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
16th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DARBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Wentworth-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spitalfields	I-place
.	O
The	O
plate	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
cleaned	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
(	O
who	O
lives	O
near	O
me	O
)	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
SOLOMON	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
Abraham	B-pers
Emanuel	I-pers
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
soldier	O
had	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
plate	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
showed	O
him	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
soldier	O
;	O
the	O
soldier	O
ran	O
up	O
George	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
before	O
his	O
Lordship	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Jew	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
plate	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
some	O
plate	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
EMANUEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
touched	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
tankard	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
worth	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Davis	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
tankard	O
he	O
showed	O
me	O
was	O
without	O
a	O
handle	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CHIVERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
Davis	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
run	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
a	O
stocking	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
to	O
pick	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
Jew	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
advertise	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
cleared	O
once	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
]	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
420.	O
DOROTHY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
traiterously	O
colour	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
colour	O
resembling	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
base	O
coin	O
resembling	O
the	O
silver	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
421.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HAYWARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
washed	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
,	O
March	O
26th	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
HAWES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Mitchell-street	B-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
watch	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
hung	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
fire-place	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
stopped	O
that	O
night	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHIVERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
offering	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Iron-gate	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Victualling	O
Office	O
;	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Hawes	O
's	O
fire-place	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
told	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
lies	O
:	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
422.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GLASS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Townsend	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25th	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
TOWNSEND	O
ANDREWS	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
into	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
,	O
a	O
person	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
pocket	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
picked	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
picked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
it	O
not	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
COVIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
boys	O
following	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Billiter-Lane	O
;	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
hung	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
turning	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
CAMPBELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
secure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breast	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
423.	O
ABIGAIL	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
silk	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cayley	I-pers
,	O
May	O
29th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CAYLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	I-place
High-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
gloves	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
showed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
gloves	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
CAYLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
black	O
silk	O
gloves	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
rich	O
enough	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
her	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
she	O
fixed	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
that	O
pattern	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
gloves	O
over	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
she	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
I	O
watched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
offered	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
the	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
brother	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gloves	O
found	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
behind	O
the	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
gloves	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
gloves	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
called	O
seven	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
424.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
leaden	O
sash	O
weights	O
,	O
22	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
14th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
watched	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
these	O
weights	O
were	O
stolen	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MONTAGUE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
legs	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
weights	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
weights	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
That	O
gentleman	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
twenty-five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
me	O
wrong	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
four	O
children	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
425	O
,	O
426.	O
MARY	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
at	O
a	O
gin	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
Half	B-place
Moon	I-place
in	I-place
Duke-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHEATLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hughes	O
pawned	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
apron	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
by	O
Arnold	B-pers
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
HUGHES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
a	O
pin	O
's	O
worth	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
[	O
Saunders	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
]	O
HUGHES	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
SAUHDERS	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
427	O
,	O
428.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
PENTECROSS	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
PENTECROSS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
429	O
,	O
430.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EDDISON	I-pers
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
EDDISON	I-pers
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
two	O
case	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
earthen	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
earthern	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
M'Cartey	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Dennis	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Sarah	O
,	O
March	O
17th	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
431.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BURLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
February	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
432.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
CASHMIN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
escaping	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
lighters	O
,	O
were	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sentenced	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
April	O
17th	O
.	O
The	O
Record	O
of	O
his	O
Conviction	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
the	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
hulk	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
confined	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
hulk	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
or	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
lost	O
,	O
near	O
Tottenham	O
court	O
road	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
iron	O
bazzle	O
(	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
fetter	O
)	O
on	O
each	O
of	O
his	O
legs	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
starved	O
to	O
death	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
never	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
but	O
would	O
escape	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
be	O
hanged	O
than	O
be	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
433	O
,	O
434.	O
ANN	B-pers
MITCHEL	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HOLLIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wateridge	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
May	O
20th	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WATERIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
lace	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
lace	O
for	O
a	O
cap	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
cap	O
made	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
sister	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
very	O
nice	O
lace	O
;	O
they	O
looked	O
over	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
laces	O
;	O
in	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Moravia	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
showing	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Moravia	O
in	O
the	O
farther	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
stayed	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
one	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
sister	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
please	O
the	O
ladies	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
much	O
confused	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
pass	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lace	O
that	O
would	O
suit	O
the	O
ladies	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
nudge	O
on	O
the	O
toe	O
with	O
her	O
foot	O
,	O
giving	O
me	O
to	O
understand	O
that	O
she	O
suspected	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hollis	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
suit	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fine	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
wish	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
lace	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
please	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
else	O
where	O
and	O
buy	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hollis	O
then	O
ordered	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
gauze	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
lace	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Moravia	O
to	O
watch	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
within	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Moravia	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
dropped	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
immediately	O
stooped	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
dropped	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
sister	O
pick	O
them	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
Hollis	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
you	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
lace	O
;	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Hollis	O
make	O
the	O
least	O
objection	O
to	O
going	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
ISRAEL	O
MORAVIA	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
to	O
settle	O
an	O
account	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
cheapening	O
some	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
genteelly	O
dressed	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
buy	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wateridge	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
my	O
business	O
was	O
;	O
we	O
stood	O
talking	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
settle	O
with	O
me	O
presently	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sister	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
very	O
earnestly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
my	O
brother	O
what	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
this	O
morning	O
?	O
I	O
observed	O
she	O
was	O
rather	O
confused	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
brother	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
sister	O
looks	O
confused	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
lace	O
;	O
go	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
looked	O
like	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
looking	O
at	O
one	O
card	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wateridge	O
showed	O
them	O
several	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
lace	O
will	O
suit	O
you	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hollis	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
good	O
enough	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
me	O
lay	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
without	O
I	O
could	O
please	O
myself	O
.	O
Before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
seek	O
for	O
lace	O
somewhere	O
else	O
that	O
might	O
please	O
her	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
supposed	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
cap	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
lace	O
elsewhere	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mitchell	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
want	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
gauze	O
;	O
they	O
purchased	O
that	O
,	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
sister	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
lace	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
caught	O
them	O
both	O
by	O
the	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
coming	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Hollis	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
Mitchell	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
Mitchell	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
upon	O
a	O
card	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
that	O
is	O
loose	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
either	O
her	O
cloak	O
or	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
dropped	O
the	O
lace	O
;	O
she	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
that	O
adjoins	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
bits	O
of	O
ribbond	O
concealed	O
under	O
Mitchell	O
's	O
stays	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
easy	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
found	O
but	O
7	O
d.	O
or	O
8	O
d.	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
bargaining	O
for	O
lace	O
of	O
7	O
s.	O
or	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
The	O
lace	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
buying	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
any	O
to	O
the	O
liking	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hollis	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
put	O
upon	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
lace	O
I	O
saw	O
drop	O
from	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
worth	O
a	O
yard	O
?	O
-	O
Five	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
import	O
lace	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
this	O
lace	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wateridge	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
MITCHELL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
lace	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs.	O
Hollis	O
accidentally	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bespeak	O
a	O
new	O
cap	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Hollis	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
(	O
Mitchell	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
MITCHELL	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
HOLLIS	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
435.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
called	O
Manchester	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Challener	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
6th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
436.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
437.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
EWINGTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixty	O
skins	O
of	O
parchment	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
30th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
identify	O
the	O
parchment	O
.	O
]	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
438	O
,	O
439	O
,	O
440.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
,	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
DRACOTT	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
WEBBER	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
stop	O
watch	O
,	O
capped	O
and	O
jewelled	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
May	O
7th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DICKENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
Garraway	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
Islington	B-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
near	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Allcombe	O
's	O
wall	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
stands	O
a	O
watch-box	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
box	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
fellows	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
passed	O
them	O
;	O
Mills	O
and	O
Dracott	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
Webber	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
clothes	O
and	O
hair	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
were	O
like	O
his	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
passed	O
the	O
watch	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
two	O
had	O
pistols	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
a	O
stick	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
woman	O
passed	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
!	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
money	O
directly	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Dracott	O
snapt	O
his	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
biggest	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
Webber	O
,	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
out	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
step	O
farther	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stratton	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
snatched	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
two	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
Mills	O
)	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Hatfield	O
,	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Stratton	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
pursued	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Dracott	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
from	O
ten	O
thousand	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
passed	O
Mr.	O
Dickens	O
that	O
evening	O
by	O
the	O
watch-box	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
behind	O
the	O
watch	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
my	O
oath	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mills	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
stood	O
together	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
passed	O
Mr.	O
Dickens	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
out	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
now	O
is	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Hatfield	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
three	O
men	O
were	O
robbing	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Hatfield	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
Mills	O
came	O
full	O
butt	O
at	O
us	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hatfield	O
had	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hatfield	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
Mills	O
knocked	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
night	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HATFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Foster	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
wanted	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
met	O
me	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
and	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
butter	O
firkin	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mills	O
come	O
running	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
forwards	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
stick	O
away	O
.	O
NELSON	B-pers
STRATTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Islington	O
:	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
robbing	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
walk	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
walk	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
two	O
up	O
Steward's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
up	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
two	O
;	O
one	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
Dracott	O
)	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
Dracott	O
up	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
bank	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
far	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
discovered	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
either	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
!	O
or	O
blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
!	O
you	O
are	O
dead	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
flashed	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Dickens	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
followed	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
you	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moonlight	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
delivered	O
Dracott	O
to	O
Green	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
Islington	O
.	O
Dracott	O
and	O
Mills	O
were	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
Dracott	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bullet-mould	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
rope	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
knot	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
Mills	B-pers
I	O
found	O
an	O
old	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
some	O
gunpowder	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
Webber	O
as	O
a	O
person	O
Dracott	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
;	O
and	O
Webber	O
also	O
answering	O
the	O
description	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
re-examined	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
rope	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
knot	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
Webber	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
MILL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
DRACOTT	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hornsey	O
house	O
.	O
Coming	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
shoot	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
myself	O
.	O
Webber	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
(	O
Dracott	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
Mills	O
one	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
MILLS	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
DRACOTT	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
WEBBER	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
441.	O
MARY	B-pers
GARDINER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
dimitty	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
March	O
27th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
442.	O
ANN	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Rutley	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
443.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
INGRAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
cast	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
May	O
1st	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
]	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
444	O
,	O
445	O
,	O
446.	O
SARAH	B-pers
STRICKLAND	I-pers
,	O
MARY	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ANN	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
brass	O
trinkets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Gaspar	B-pers
Fischer	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31st	O
.	O
GASPAR	B-pers
FISCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
is	O
on	O
his	O
travels	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
sixpence	O
for	O
some	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
another	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
Sarah	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Strickland	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
side	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Strickland	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
landlady	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
some	O
honest	O
people	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
two	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
Strickland	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
here	O
who	O
has	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
George-alley	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
foreigner	O
(	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
three	O
girls	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
body	O
two	O
crowns	O
that	O
would	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Day	O
delivered	O
herself	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Allen	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
shoe	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Strickland	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
STRICKLAND	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
us	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
us	O
with	O
some	O
raspberry	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
us	O
almost	O
drunk	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
found	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
ALLEN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
DAY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
;	O
Allen	O
ran	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
show	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
All	O
Three	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
447.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WALLACE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
448.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
four	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
teaspoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-caster	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
dimitty	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
sattin	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
2d	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
BARON	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
449.	O
ANN	B-pers
FARMER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bartram	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
450.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BULLOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
8th	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BARLOW	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hendon	B-place
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
my	O
garden	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Willington	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
table-cloths	O
under	O
a	O
hedge	O
in	O
my	O
field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
washes	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Cornwall	O
;	O
it	O
occurred	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
hedge	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
with	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
separated	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
ran	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
dropped	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
almost	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cornwall	O
's	O
washerwoman	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
linen	O
on	O
the	O
hedge	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
next	O
to	O
mine	O
.	O
ROGER	B-pers
WILLINGTON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
under	O
the	O
hedge	O
with	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
us	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
from	O
your	O
Lordship	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
open	O
pales	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
feet	O
high	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
could	O
see	O
over	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
daughter	O
took	O
the	O
linen	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
KEMPTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Cornwall	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
cloths	O
is	O
marked	O
I	O
C	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
C	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
hung	O
ten	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cornwall	O
's	O
table	O
cloths	O
on	O
the	O
hedge	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
two	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
's	O
fields	O
by	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Willington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
table	O
cloths	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
table	O
cloths	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Frances	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
at	O
Edgware	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
saw	O
men	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
451	O
,	O
452.	O
JAMES	B-pers
YORKE	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SIDAWAY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Deligne	I-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
steel-hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
odd	O
leather	O
shoe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Deligne	I-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Band	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
while	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
lives	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
28	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Newman-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
single	O
lock	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
double	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
rushed	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
both	O
dressed	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
part	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
to	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
sword	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
the	O
spoons	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
me	O
very	O
lately	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
sword	O
hanging	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
;	O
the	O
sword	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
witness	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
sword	O
and	O
shoes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
WOOTTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
;	O
the	O
accomplice	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shoes	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
WHITCOMB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Curry	O
,	O
in	O
Newman-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
forwards	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
sword	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HORSLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
with	O
the	O
children	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
in	O
Newman-street	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Yorke	O
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
passed	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
Sidaway	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
them	O
very	O
particularly	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
walked	O
about	O
several	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
which	O
Sidaway	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
not	O
suspecting	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
outcry	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
mentioned	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
them	O
very	O
plainly	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
walked	O
about	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
GRUBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Golden-square	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
in	O
their	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
keys	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
Sidaway	O
's	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
keys	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
looks	O
and	O
unlocks	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
proper	O
key	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
were	O
dropped	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gregory	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
dark-lanthorn	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Grubb	O
to	O
apprehend	O
them	O
.	O
YORKE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
SIDAWAY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
keys	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
keys	O
somewhere	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
get	O
40	O
l.	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
Both	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
453.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
STEVENSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
live	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
,	O
at	O
Hampstead	B-place
;	O
my	O
master	O
resides	O
chiefly	O
in	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
farm	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
sow	O
with	O
five	O
large	O
pigs	O
,	O
shut	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
stye	O
,	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
for	O
another	O
person	O
fed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stye	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
pigs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
;	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
the	O
stye	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
furlongs	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
came	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
his	O
pigs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pigs	O
shut	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
place	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
pigs	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
sow	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
the	O
marks	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
AND	O
THE	O
SOW	O
WOULD	O
SWEAR	O
TO	O
THEM	O
TOO	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
sow	O
and	O
they	O
perfectly	O
well	O
knew	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pigs	O
began	O
to	O
suck	O
immediately	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARPMEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
robbing	O
Lord	O
Onslow	O
's	O
fowl-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
Clapton	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Hatton-street	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
selling	O
turkeys	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
and	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
choosing	O
to	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
horse	O
take	O
his	O
own	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Hoxton	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
wife	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
pigs	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
five	O
pigs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
:	O
these	O
pigs	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
were	O
afterwards	O
shown	O
to	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
King	O
described	O
the	O
pigs	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BARRINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
Smithfield-market	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
cheapen	O
six	O
pigs	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
pigs	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
Prick	O
ear	O
ones	O
of	O
the	O
Norfolk	O
kind	O
.	O
How	O
large	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
trouble	O
yourself	O
about	O
these	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
man	O
money	O
before	O
;	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
were	O
the	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
Spotted	O
.	O
All	O
spotted	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
other	O
than	O
seeing	O
him	O
about	O
Smithfield-market	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
appear	O
here	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
are	O
as	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
his	O
friends	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
knew	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
Barrington	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
they	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
give	O
material	O
evidence	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
that	O
man	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Barrington	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
enquired	O
after	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
knew	O
better	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
news	O
paper	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
court	O
would	O
not	O
sit	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
OLIVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-master	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Pewter-platter	O
,	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
farmer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
many	O
loads	O
of	O
hay	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
this	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield-market	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged-staff	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Hog-market	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
he	O
taken	O
?	O
Carpmeal	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
he	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Oliver	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
misbehaviour	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
misfortunes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
towards	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
our	O
country	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Oliver	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
would	O
have	O
known	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
hay	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
454.	O
BURTON	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22d	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
.	O
We	O
are	O
hatters	O
and	O
hosiers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
wanted	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
black	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
big	O
enough	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
almost	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
candle	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
Wood	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
detained	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
Wood	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dusk	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
glass	O
door	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
for	O
the	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
coming	O
in	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
then	O
missed	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
George-yard	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BUTTLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
George-yard	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Berry	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
property	O
!	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
]	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
455.	O
PETER	B-pers
WOODCOCK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
,	O
6th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GIBSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
B	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
456.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BREMD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
82	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
cable	O
rope	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26th	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
lighterman	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
rope	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
LEONARD	B-pers
CASWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
a-shore	O
with	O
the	O
rope	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
stab	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
rope	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cut	O
the	O
rope	O
from	O
a	O
lighter	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wing	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LONDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
attempt	O
to	O
stab	O
Mr.	O
Caswell	O
;	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
They	O
threw	O
brickbats	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
457.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SWAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1st	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BUTLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
the	O
bonnet	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
six	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
picking	O
up	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
broken	O
hoop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Turnagain-lane	B-place
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
half-pennyworth	O
of	O
gooseberries	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
bonnet	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bonnet	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
parent	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
bonnet	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
bonnet	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bonnet	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Turn-again-lane	O
;	O
the	O
witness	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
by	O
his	O
appearance	O
that	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
458.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CARLISLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
brushes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19th	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
ASHMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brush-maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
brushes	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
JAMES	B-pers
CLIFF	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
where	O
the	O
brushes	O
are	O
kept	O
;	O
the	O
brushes	O
are	O
my	O
making	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MAYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
sold	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
brushes	O
for	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
past	O
;	O
the	O
brushes	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
brushes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
brushes	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
brushes	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mayer	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
so	O
particular	O
in	O
the	O
work	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
another	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
459.	O
ANN	B-pers
COX	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
May	O
14th	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
460.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ELWEE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Quiningham	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18th	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
QUININGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
his	O
coat	O
hang	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
liable	O
to	O
be	O
burnt	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
move	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
very	O
heavy	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
tools	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
apprentice	O
whose	O
coat	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
five	O
tools	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
place	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
apprentice	O
watch	O
who	O
the	O
coat	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
tool	O
.	O
LEVI	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
iron	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
tool	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
apprentice	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
wanted	O
to	O
raise	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
chair	O
club	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
other	O
conveniency	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
461	O
,	O
462.	O
MARY	B-pers
DRAPER	I-pers
and	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
OBDAY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14th	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wiggin	O
,	O
a	O
china-merchant	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
picked	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
Newtoner's-lane	B-place
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
lodge	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
cloaths	O
on	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
silver	O
and	O
halfpence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
remain	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
late	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
woman	O
rob	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
you	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
very	O
comfortably	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
coming	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
fastened	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
robbed	O
?	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
drinking	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
drunk	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
passed	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
Draper	O
keeps	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
[	O
William	B-pers
Patmore	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
received	O
of	O
Draper	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
]	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
463	O
,	O
464	O
,	O
465	O
,	O
466.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
HAY	I-pers
,	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
MURPHY	I-pers
,	O
FRANCES	B-pers
UTHERLEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
HANNAH	B-pers
REEVES	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1st	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
witness	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
their	O
recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
]	O
ALL	O
FOUR	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
467	O
,	O
468.	O
MARY	B-pers
HUGHES	I-pers
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
EDGERS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
's	O
man	O
at	O
Plaistow	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
:	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
flush	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
Edgers	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
Hughes	O
came	O
in	O
afterwards	O
;	O
Edgers	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
Hughes	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
after	O
Edgers	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
after	O
Edgers	O
left	O
you	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
your	O
breeches	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
from	O
Edgers	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
Hughes	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
Edgers	O
?	O
-	O
Four	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
when	O
Hughes	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
Hughes	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
waked	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
your	O
stockings	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
your	O
stockings	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
snatch	O
at	O
my	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
snatched	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
dropped	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
stocking	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
pulled	O
that	O
stocking	O
off	O
before	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
pulling	O
the	O
other	O
off	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LEVY	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
Edgers	O
went	O
down	O
Petticoat-lane	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
receiver	O
of	O
stolen	O
goods	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
too	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
bread	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Roxton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
Edgers	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
afternoon	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
GARDINER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
along	O
with	O
Edgers	O
and	O
Hughes	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Edgers	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
both	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
eighteenpence	O
to	O
Edgers	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
shillings	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
eighteenpence	O
;	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Edgers	I-pers
sat	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
Hughes	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Edgers	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
but	O
five	O
farthings	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indeed	O
asleep	O
when	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
Sarah	O
Edgers	O
would	O
not	O
divide	O
the	O
four	O
shillings	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
five	O
farthings	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
turn	O
evidence	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
five	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
for	O
thread	O
to	O
mend	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
torn	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
headborough	O
belonging	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hog-lane	O
I	O
was	O
spoke	O
to	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
this	O
girl	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
girls	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Edgers	I-pers
was	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
HUGHES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
handled	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
EDGERS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
They	O
swear	O
so	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
so	O
rigid	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
swear	O
black	O
is	O
white	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
us	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
469.	O
MARY	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-hook	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
13th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
470.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
George	B-pers
Strahan	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
May	O
17th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
471.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BANKS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
]	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
472.	O
CAROLINA	B-pers
MARIA	I-pers
QUEENLAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Theodore	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Broadhead	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
April	O
24th	O
.	O
THEODORE	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
BROADHEAD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
and	O
furniture	O
in	O
my	O
town-house	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
complaint	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
deficiency	O
in	O
the	O
linen	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LYONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
employed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
door	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
duplicates	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ARTZ	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Humphry	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
West-street	O
,	O
Seven-Dials	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Montgomery	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
in	O
Brook-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
13	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
together	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
]	O
MARY	B-pers
HARDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
laundry	O
maid	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Broadhead	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
articles	O
produced	O
.	O
To	O
Robert	B-pers
Artz	I-pers
.	O
What	O
name	O
;	O
had	O
she	O
done	O
business	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Montgomery	O
.	O
People	O
seldom	O
choose	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
their	O
real	O
name	O
that	O
deal	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
appearance	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
property	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
fine	O
sheets	O
there	O
that	O
do	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Broadhead	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Bon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
owner	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Blake	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Broadhead	O
:	O
When	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
up	O
two	O
keys	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Artz	O
.	O
She	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
some	O
,	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
ago	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
take	O
any	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
frequently	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
himself	O
knows	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
up	O
the	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pawn	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
to	O
wrong	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
prison	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Broadhead	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
on	O
her	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
prison	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
bills	O
coming	O
in	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
discharge	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
bills	O
were	O
out-standing	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
thirty-five	O
shillings	O
when	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
HOTHAM	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
473.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
YEATON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
Roquez	I-pers
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brick	O
,	O
to	O
,	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Judith	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
near	O
her	O
left	O
ear	O
,	O
a	O
mortal	O
contusion	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
until	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
