TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1779	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PLUMBE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
MDCCLXXIX	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PLUMBE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLACKSTONE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
The	O
Honourable	O
SIR	O
JAMES	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
MR.	O
MASSIERES	O
,	O
Cursitor	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
;	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Soppet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Samler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Iselton	I-pers
,	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Matthew	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Conner	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
and	O
Matthew	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Ayres	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Greenlaw	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Punderson	I-pers
,	O
Lacy	B-pers
Punderson	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wardell	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Grieve	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
Norrison	B-pers
Coverdale	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Woodfield	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
served	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Gale	O
on	O
the	O
tryal	O
of	O
Hackman	O
.	O
Griffin	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Theble	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blanquit	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Longley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Third	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fasson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chalmers	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brathwaite	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cowper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gunley	I-pers
,	O
Noah	B-pers
Chivers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
.	O
184.	O
MARY	B-pers
BRATTLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pinchbeck	I-pers
,	O
February	O
6th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PINCHBECK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
in	O
Oxford	B-place
Road	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
shirt	O
behind	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
bed-room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
pillows	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JORDAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Murphy	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-Road	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
were	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
shirt	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pinchbeck	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
got	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
pawned	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
pawned	O
things	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
owned	O
me	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
redeem	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
Pinchbeck	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
your	O
wife	O
ever	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.DEPUTY	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
185	O
.	O
186.	O
HENRY	B-pers
STEED	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDMONDS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Anne	B-pers
Brudenell	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
,	O
March	O
13th	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
BRUDENELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Park-Lane	B-place
,	O
in	O
my	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
nineteen	O
or	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
rememberance	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
was	O
exceeding	O
dark	O
.	O
Steed	O
was	O
stopped	O
offering	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
From	O
Steed	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
moon-light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
excessively	O
dark	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
nobody	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
your	O
servants	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
footman	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JEPPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brudenell	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
Park-lane	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
robbed	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
footman	O
was	O
getting	O
down	O
from	O
behind	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
his	O
place	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
shortest	O
(	O
Henry	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
)	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
shortest	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
their	O
faces	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
recollect	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
only	O
their	O
speech	O
and	O
size	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
by	O
their	O
speech	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
men	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
thing	O
over	O
their	O
faces	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHARLTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
footman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brudenell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
coachman	O
;	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
down	O
from	O
behind	O
,	O
when	O
another	O
man	O
made	O
his	O
appearance	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
my	O
place	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
tallest	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
my	O
place	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
in	O
a	O
broken	O
foreign	O
language	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
scarce	O
understand	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
foot	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
confess	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
them	O
confess	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
so	O
by	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Edmonds	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
attend	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fieldings	I-pers
more	O
than	O
once	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
once	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
came	O
and	O
offered	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
hand-bill	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Brudenell	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brudenell	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Was	O
Charlton	O
at	O
the	O
examination	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
You	O
attended	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
make	O
a	O
confession	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
recollect	O
.	O
Not	O
Edmonds	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
recollect	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
examination	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
Mrs.	O
Brudenell	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
signed	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
immediately	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
PROTHERO	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Steed	O
,	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
custody	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
by	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mean	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Edmonds	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
this	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Leicester-fields	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
immediately	O
back	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
this	O
Edmonds	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
in	O
St.	O
Alban's-street	O
.	O
Going	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Edmonds	O
,	O
in	O
Rupert-street	O
;	O
on	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
description	O
Steed	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Gibbons	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
St.	O
Alban's-Street	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Steed	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
lodgings	O
in	O
St.	O
Alban's-street	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
horse-pistols	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Edmonds	O
confess	O
the	O
robbery	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
and	O
servant	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
deny	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
confess	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
EDMOND	O
'S	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
Captain	O
Edwards	B-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
some	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
beforehand	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
seeing	O
the	O
cloth	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
America	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
consented	O
to	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
malice	O
in	O
his	O
heart	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
revenge	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Brown-Bear	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
say	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
this	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
clear	O
in	O
spite	O
of	O
my	O
teeth	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
speaker	O
he	O
could	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
pleased	O
.	O
STEED	O
'S	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
All	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
is	O
false	O
,	O
word	O
by	O
word	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
borrowed	O
any	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
master	O
wanted	O
to	O
raise	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
innocently	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
For	O
Steed	O
.	O
PHEBE	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
washed	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
for	O
Steed	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
home	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
calling	O
past	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
his	O
board	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
undressing	O
himself	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Saturday	O
.	O
To	O
Charlton	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
Steed	O
called	O
seven	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Edmonds	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.DEPUTY	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
187.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HACKMAN	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murther	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
7th	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
murther	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
M'NAMARA	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
playhouse	O
with	O
Miss	O
Ray	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
seeing	O
Miss	O
Ray	O
in	O
some	O
difficulties	O
at	O
the	O
playhouse	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
offer	O
my	O
assistance	O
to	O
hand	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
carriage	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
Past	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
precise	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
playhouse	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
piazzas	O
,	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
her	O
then	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
only	O
handed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
piazzas	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
quitted	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
fatal	O
accident	O
happened	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
in	O
the	O
piazzas	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
an	O
impression	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
arm	O
she	O
held	O
with	O
her	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
conceive	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
ball	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
passed	O
through	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
hit	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
she	O
instantly	O
dropped	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
had	O
you	O
proceeded	O
from	O
the	O
playhouse	O
door	O
when	O
this	O
accident	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
Within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
front	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
within	O
two	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
portico	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
piazzas	O
that	O
it	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
pistol	O
had	O
been	O
fired	O
out	O
of	O
wantonness	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
idea	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ball	O
though	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
impression	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
stooped	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
fainting	O
fit	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
conceived	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
fright	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
observe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
what	O
passed	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
Shakspeare	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
myself	O
upon	O
my	O
knees	O
to	O
attempt	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
hands	O
bloody	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
link-boy	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Shakspeare	O
tavern	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
secured	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
induced	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
could	O
possess	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
deed	O
?	O
or	O
some	O
question	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
me	O
by	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
place	O
to	O
ask	O
that	O
question	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
that	O
effect	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
precise	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
understood	O
from	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Hackman	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
pronounced	O
his	O
name	O
with	O
an	O
H.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
anybody	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
,	O
in	O
Craven-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
lady	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
somebody	O
else	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
objected	O
to	O
his	O
seeing	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
removed	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
blood	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
I	O
got	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
abou	O
t	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
heard	O
the	O
lady	O
was	O
dead	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
observations	O
in	O
your	O
hearing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
observation	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
play	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
you	O
standing	O
?	O
-	O
Close	O
by	O
the	O
lady	O
's	O
carriage	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
observed	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
post	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
the	O
play	O
broke	O
up	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
ladies	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
playhouse	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
black	O
followed	O
them	O
.	O
Lady	O
Sandwich	O
's	O
coach	O
was	O
called	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
carriage	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
handed	O
the	O
other	O
lady	O
into	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
that	O
was	O
shot	O
stood	O
behind	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
gentleman	O
could	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
hand	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
carriage	O
the	O
gentleman	O
in	O
black	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
two	O
pistols	O
;	O
he	O
shot	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
pistol	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
himself	O
.	O
She	O
fell	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
so	O
(	O
describing	O
it	O
as	O
being	O
on	O
her	O
forehead	O
)	O
and	O
died	O
before	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
lamp	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
died	O
immediately	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
head	O
hung	O
directly	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
at	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
fired	O
another	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
immediately	O
.	O
They	O
fell	O
feet	O
to	O
feet	O
.	O
He	O
beat	O
himself	O
violently	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
somebody	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
did	O
he	O
beat	O
himself	O
?	O
-	O
Just	O
about	O
the	O
right	O
temple	O
.	O
(	O
Describing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
His	O
own	O
head	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Tothilfields	O
Bridewell	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
person	O
you	O
saw	O
there	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
discharged	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
(	O
Pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
Mr.	O
Hackman	O
pulled	O
two	O
pistols	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
-	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
he	O
pulled	O
them	O
both	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
pocket	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
different	O
pockets	O
with	O
different	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
just	O
so	O
.	O
(	O
Describing	O
it	O
by	O
claping	O
her	O
hands	O
twice	O
,	O
one	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
one	O
taken	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
pistol	O
cocked	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
cock	O
both	O
the	O
pistols	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
pistols	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
let	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
make	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
pistol	O
before	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BLANDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Tell	O
what	O
you	O
observed	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
Coming	O
from	O
Drury-Lane	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
piazzas	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
pistols	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
say	O
two	O
people	O
were	O
killed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
surgeon	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Hackman	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mahon	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Mahon	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
by	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
faint	O
;	O
somebody	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shakspeare	O
tavern	O
;	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Mahon	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shakspeare	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
constable	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
what	O
situation	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
All	O
bloody	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
letters	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
delivered	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
Shakspeare	O
tavern	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
addressed	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Nor	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MAHON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Coming	O
through	O
the	O
piazzas	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
put	O
my	O
foot	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
step	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
pistols	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
It	O
struck	O
me	O
that	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
in	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
that	O
method	O
to	O
settle	O
the	O
difference	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
reclining	O
in	O
this	O
posture	O
(	O
describing	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
beating	O
himself	O
violently	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Hackman	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
wrenched	O
the	O
pistol	O
immediately	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
Blandy	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
dress	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
the	O
violent	O
effusion	O
of	O
blood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-Street	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Shakspeare	O
tavern	O
?	O
It	O
is	O
no	O
matter	O
what	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
lady	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
first	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
supported	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
mortal	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
give	O
her	O
no	O
assistance	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
O'BRYAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Miss	O
Ray	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
body	O
at	O
the	O
Shakspeare	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
murther	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mortal	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
vessels	O
of	O
sensation	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
every	O
other	O
way	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
perceive	O
any	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
pronounced	O
the	O
woman	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
wound	O
was	O
received	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Centra	O
coronalis	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ball	O
was	O
discharged	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
ear	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
troubled	O
the	O
court	O
with	O
the	O
examination	O
of	O
witnesses	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
charge	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
thought	O
that	O
the	O
pleading	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
indictment	O
gave	O
an	O
indication	O
of	O
contemning	O
death	O
not	O
suitable	O
to	O
my	O
present	O
condition	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
,	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
a	O
second	O
peril	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
likewise	O
thought	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
my	O
country	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
by	O
suffering	O
my	O
offence	O
to	O
be	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fact	O
established	O
by	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
stand	O
here	O
this	O
day	O
the	O
most	O
wretched	O
of	O
human	O
beings	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
myself	O
criminal	O
in	O
a	O
high	O
degree	O
;	O
yet	O
while	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
with	O
shame	O
and	O
repentance	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
determination	O
against	O
my	O
own	O
life	O
was	O
formal	O
and	O
complete	O
,	O
I	O
protest	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
regard	O
to	O
truth	O
which	O
becomes	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
will	O
to	O
destroy	O
her	O
who	O
was	O
ever	O
dearer	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
life	O
,	O
was	O
never	O
mine	O
till	O
a	O
momentary	O
phrensy	O
overcame	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
deed	O
I	O
now	O
deplore	O
.	O
The	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
meant	O
for	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
after	O
my	O
decease	O
,	O
will	O
have	O
its	O
due	O
weight	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
point	O
with	O
good	O
men	O
.	O
Before	O
this	O
dreadful	O
act	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
nothing	O
will	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
tenor	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
which	O
the	O
common	O
charity	O
of	O
mankind	O
will	O
not	O
excuse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
wish	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
punishment	O
which	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
my	O
country	O
appoint	O
for	O
my	O
crime	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
already	O
too	O
unhappy	O
to	O
feel	O
a	O
punishment	O
in	O
death	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
satisfaction	O
in	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
submit	O
myself	O
with	O
penitence	O
and	O
patience	O
to	O
the	O
disposal	O
and	O
judgement	O
of	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
this	O
enquiry	O
into	O
my	O
conduct	O
and	O
intention	O
.	O
Examination	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HALLIBURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
letter	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
letter	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
)	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mabon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
letter	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
particularly	O
the	O
hundred	O
pound	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
being	O
written	O
in	O
figures	O
;	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
sealed	O
up	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
opened	O
it	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
.	O
The	O
letter	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Frederick	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Craven	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
``	O
My	O
dear	O
Frederick	O
,	O
``	O
When	O
this	O
reaches	O
you	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
my	O
unhappy	O
fate	O
distress	O
you	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
strove	O
against	O
it	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
now	O
overpowers	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
well	O
know	O
where	O
my	O
affections	O
were	O
placed	O
;	O
my	O
having	O
by	O
some	O
means	O
or	O
other	O
lost	O
her	O
's	O
(	O
an	O
idea	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
support	O
)	O
has	O
driven	O
me	O
to	O
madness	O
.	O
The	O
world	O
will	O
condemn	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
good	O
heart	O
will	O
pity	O
me	O
.	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
Fred	O
.	O
Would	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sum	O
to	O
leave	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
convince	O
you	O
of	O
my	O
great	O
regard	O
:	O
you	O
was	O
my	O
only	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
hid	O
one	O
circumstance	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
gives	O
me	O
great	O
pain	O
.	O
I	O
owe	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
,	O
of	O
Gosport	O
,	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
writings	O
of	O
my	O
houses	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
God	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
matters	O
collected	O
,	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
nearly	O
enough	O
to	O
settle	O
our	O
account	O
.	O
May	O
Almighty	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
and	O
yours	O
with	O
comfort	O
and	O
happiness	O
;	O
and	O
may	O
you	O
ever	O
be	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
pangs	O
I	O
now	O
feel	O
.	O
May	O
heaven	O
protect	O
my	O
beloved	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
forgive	O
this	O
act	O
,	O
which	O
alone	O
could	O
relieve	O
me	O
from	O
a	O
world	O
of	O
misery	O
I	O
have	O
long	O
endured	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
ever	O
be	O
in	O
your	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
any	O
act	O
of	O
friendship	O
,	O
remember	O
your	O
faithful	O
friend	O
,	O
J	O
.	O
HACKMAN	O
.	O
''	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
188.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HORTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Blizard	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Blizard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
189.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
December	O
5th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
Bell-court	B-place
,	I-place
Gray's-Inn-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
or	O
fifth	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
shop	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
afterwards	O
,	O
by	O
Redgrave	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Careless	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
not	O
recoverable	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BERNONVILLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Careless	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Fox-court	O
,	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
brought	O
that	O
coat	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
190	O
,	O
191	O
,	O
192.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
,	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
,	O
and	O
MARY	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
POTTEN	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
carpetting	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
inlaid	O
writing	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brissenden	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
January	O
30th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRISSENDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
,	O
in	O
High	B-place
Holbourn	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
,	O
or	O
seven	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
carpeting	O
,	O
a	O
writing	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
valued	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
less	O
than	O
their	O
real	O
value	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
writing	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
writing	O
box	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
understood	O
brought	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
tea-chest	O
I	O
understood	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Harris	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRAWFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
writing	O
desk	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation-Office	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
writing	O
box	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
RACHAEL	B-pers
LYONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
in	O
this	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
robberies	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
connected	O
with	O
them	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
days	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
places	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
likely	O
to	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
this	O
upholsterer	O
's	O
window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
said	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
something	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Harris	O
and	O
Foster	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
took	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
piece	O
after	O
piece	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
whole	O
out	O
.	O
Potten	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Harris	O
brought	O
the	O
carpeting	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
writing	O
desk	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
.	O
They	O
fetched	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
except	O
the	O
box	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
Potten	O
and	O
Foster	O
boarded	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
They	O
lodged	O
at	O
a	O
different	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
recommended	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
January	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
pawned	O
this	O
writing	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
tea-chest	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Harris	O
's	O
lodging	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Lyons	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
than	O
Lyons	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
husband	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
Fillman	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
dead	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
dead	O
.	O
Yet	O
you	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Lyons	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
assume	O
the	O
name	O
.	O
Is	O
Barnard	O
your	O
brother	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
Lyons	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
officer	O
went	O
to	O
Harris	O
's	O
longing	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Lyons	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Foster	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Foster	O
and	O
Potten	O
together	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Harris	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
show	O
us	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
us	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
among	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
From	O
Harris	O
to	O
Lyons	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
a	O
coffee-pot	O
of	O
your	O
brother	O
Barnard	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
M'Donald	O
.	O
Harris	O
wanted	O
to	O
turn	O
evidence	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation-Office	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fill	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
hat	O
full	O
of	O
diamonds	O
if	O
he	O
might	O
turn	O
evidence	O
respecting	O
a	O
robbery	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Harris	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
robberies	O
commited	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
he	O
would	O
discover	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
magistrates	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
this	O
robbery	O
in	O
particular	O
?	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
no	O
robbery	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
Harris	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
M'Donald	O
.	O
Foster	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
civil	O
.	O
HARRIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
the	O
brother	O
of	O
Lyons	O
.	O
Harris	O
called	O
a	O
witness	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
Barnard	O
called	O
upon	O
her	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
to	O
Harris	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
foot	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
;	O
and	O
six	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
not	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
HARRIS	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
DEPUTY	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
china	O
tea	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
twelve	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
china	O
teapot	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
china	O
coffee	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
china	O
milk	O
pot	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PRIOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Coventry-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
top	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Hay-market	I-place
;	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
china	O
and	O
glass	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
22d	O
or	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
by	O
some	O
instrument	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
had	O
been	O
snapped	O
off	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
arm	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
whole	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
spring	O
latch	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
candles	O
were	O
lighted	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
with	O
my	O
partner	O
;	O
the	O
servants	O
were	O
both	O
out	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
were	O
they	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
after	O
six	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
glass	O
rattle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
any	O
pane	O
broke	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
china	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
so	O
particularly	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
taking	O
down	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
glass	O
lying	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Bradall	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
hole	O
did	O
you	O
perceive	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
large	O
hole	O
,	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
doubled	O
hand	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
looked	O
the	O
things	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
corner	O
for	O
some	O
glass	O
tumblers	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
,	O
is	O
he	O
your	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
advertised	O
with	O
a	O
guinea	O
reward	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
at	O
Litchfield-street	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
pattern	O
of	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
which	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
Crawford	O
,	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
brought	O
a	O
pattern	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
large	O
size	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
remarkable	O
pattern	O
;	O
the	O
gilder	O
says	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
set	O
he	O
ever	O
gilt	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
more	O
gilders	O
than	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
one	O
principal	O
one	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
none	O
that	O
gild	O
equal	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
RACHAEL	B-pers
LYONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Harris	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
Christmas	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
with	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
by	O
this	O
china	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
which	O
he	O
always	O
cut	O
glass	O
with	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
immediately	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
drank	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
we	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
quite	O
dark	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
putty	O
,	O
and	O
cracked	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
it	O
made	O
a	O
report	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
looked	O
all	O
round	O
the	O
shop-window	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
perceiving	O
a	O
ny	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
backwards	O
again	O
,	O
quite	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
Harris	O
put	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
loosened	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
You	O
concealed	O
yourselves	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
knife	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
loosened	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
piece	O
by	O
piece	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
china	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Windmill-street	O
,	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
china	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
chocolate	O
cups	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
them	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
against	O
Harris	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
chocolate	O
cups	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
.	O
Harris	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
only	O
wants	O
to	O
hang	O
me	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
brother	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
brother	O
eighteen-pence	O
for	O
the	O
three	O
cups	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
falsity	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
cups	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Mrs.	O
Lyons	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
affair	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Harris	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
coming	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
lodging	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
three	O
cups	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
for	O
eighteen-pence	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
us	O
to	O
some	O
persons	O
that	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
lordship	O
finding	O
he	O
had	O
escaped	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Barnard	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
Barnard	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRAWFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
150	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
twelve	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
and	O
stand	O
,	O
a	O
milk-pot	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
dealer	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
twenty-six	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
To	O
Lyons	O
.	O
Is	O
Barnard	O
your	O
brother	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
HARRIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Barnard	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
china	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
's	O
sale	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
three	O
coffee-cups	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
me	O
cheap	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
a	O
poor	O
person	O
to	O
give	O
for	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
eighteen-pence	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
a	O
spite	O
and	O
spleen	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
want	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
193.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
six	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
bed-pillows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
roasting	O
Jack	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
five	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
ten	O
pewter-plates	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
seven	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
japanned	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
pewter	O
wash-hand	O
basons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
looking	O
glasses	O
,	O
in	O
wooden	O
frames	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
pewter	O
chamber-pots	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pewter	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
other	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
powder-box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
hand-bell	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
eight	O
china	O
images	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
glass-bottle	O
for	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
riding	O
habit	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
cloggs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
hempen	O
bags	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
country-house	O
at	O
Mill-Hill	B-place
,	I-place
Hendon	I-place
;	O
our	O
town-house	O
is	O
in	O
Harp-Lane	O
,	O
Tower-Street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
Hendon	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
directly	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
last	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
down	O
afterwards	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
house	O
fast	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
you	O
word	O
?	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
things	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
eighteen	O
locks	O
broke	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coach-and-horses	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
where	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Muddock	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
Muddock	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
inventory	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
niece	O
took	O
the	O
inventory	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Muddock	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
LOWE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FULLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
at	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
with	O
a	O
lamb	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
little	O
cart	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
some	O
stolen	O
goods	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
upon	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
told	O
my	O
brother	O
watchman	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
up	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Osborne	O
,	O
Ball	O
,	O
and	O
Hilsdon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
beside	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
was	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Wilkins	O
?	O
-	O
Ball	O
.	O
Is	O
Wilkins	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
the	O
cart	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
drove	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
drove	O
against	O
a	O
brick-wall	O
,	O
and	O
overturned	O
it	O
,	O
just	O
above	O
the	O
pump	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
watchmen	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
household	O
furniture	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
overturned	O
they	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
Ball	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
neck	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Ball	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
goods	O
up	O
to	O
Muddock	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
SIMON	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
board	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
that	O
was	O
overturned	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Wilkins	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
;	O
witness	O
reads	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Bethnal-green	O
,	O
common	O
stage	O
cart	O
;	O
one	O
thousand	O
,	O
sixteen	O
hundred	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
common	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
carts	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MUDDOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
coat	O
upon	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
that	O
was	O
overturned	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
is	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
DENNIS	B-pers
M'DONALD	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
Wilkins	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Bethnal-Green	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
cart	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
carries	O
out	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
peas	O
and	O
beans	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
coat	O
that	O
is	O
produced	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
Grubb	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
To	O
Smith	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
person	O
wearing	O
such	O
a	O
coat	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
that	O
gentleman	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
wear	O
such	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
my	O
word	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
horse	O
and	O
cart	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
trouble	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
with	O
calling	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
194.	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
MURPHY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
neck-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Linnihan	I-pers
,	O
February	O
22d	O
.	O
OWEN	B-pers
LINNIHAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
;	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
my	O
trussel	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
appointed	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wooden	O
leg	O
;	O
she	O
heard	O
me	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
this	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
neckcloth	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
sheets	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
seised	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
wooden	O
leg	O
,	O
threw	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
sheets	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
this	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
poker	O
)	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Justice	O
Clark	O
discharged	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
and	O
indicted	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
indicted	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
till	O
my	O
neighbours	O
bailed	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
I	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
hurt	O
me	O
greatly	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
partnership	O
in	O
selling	O
greens	O
.	O
He	O
robbed	O
my	O
stall	O
because	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
supported	O
his	O
wife	O
nine	O
weeks	O
.	O
The	O
sheets	O
he	O
says	O
I	O
stole	O
were	O
hop	O
sacks	O
his	O
wife	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
sworn	O
falsely	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
LAWRENCE	B-pers
NEALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Justice	O
Clark	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
discharged	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
justice	O
and	O
have	O
revenge	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
prison	O
for	O
abusing	O
this	O
woman	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
BURT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Clark	O
on	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
sheets	O
he	O
speaks	O
of	O
are	O
nothing	O
but	O
hop-sacks	O
.	O
I	O
washed	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sworn	O
them	O
upon	O
me	O
afterwards	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
SOAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
sell	O
greens	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
195.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLOSE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
leather	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
ten	O
dollars	O
,	O
one	O
half-dollar	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
26th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
General	B-pers
Burgoyne	I-pers
's	O
regiment	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
lately	O
discharged	O
on	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
America	O
.	O
We	O
landed	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Hallifax	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
late	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
enquired	O
where	O
we	O
could	O
have	O
quarters	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
in	O
Chapel-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
We	O
laid	O
down	O
our	O
knapsacks	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
pretty	O
heartily	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
comrades	O
had	O
you	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Six	O
or	O
seven	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
us	O
his	O
bed	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
slept	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
War-Office	O
to	O
get	O
our	O
billets	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
for	O
our	O
package	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
countryman	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
comrades	O
,	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
on	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
billet	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
to	O
pass	O
away	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
and	O
Compass	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
four	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
two	O
hours	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
dinner	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
my	O
pocket	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
dollar	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ten	O
dollars	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
four	O
pisteroons	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
they	O
call	O
7	O
d	O
1/2	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
my	O
breast	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
dollar	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
walked	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
not	O
good	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
then	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
spend	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
kind	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
return	O
him	O
thanks	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
charged	O
nothing	O
for	O
my	O
eating	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
afterwards	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Queen	B-place
's	I-place
gardens	I-place
;	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
lame	O
arm	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
strength	O
in	O
that	O
arm	O
)	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
queen	O
's	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
guard	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
book	O
?	O
-	O
Immediately	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
turned	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
condition	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
use	O
me	O
worse	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
as	O
still	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
left	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
lodging	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MACARTNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
at	O
Buckingham-gate	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
brandy	O
to	O
treat	O
the	O
sentry	O
who	O
was	O
opposite	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
dollar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
foreign	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
America	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
fleshy	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
thigh	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
pains	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
loose	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
out	O
(	O
the	O
dollar	O
was	O
produced	O
)	O
.	O
HUGH	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
in	O
Chapel-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
regiment	O
of	O
foot	O
guards	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
74th	O
regiment	O
of	O
foot	O
,	O
came	O
from	O
America	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
recommended	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
sentries	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
lodgers	O
were	O
on	O
duty	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
lodging	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
and	O
victuals	O
after	O
their	O
march	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
their	O
company	O
.	O
Ward	O
and	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
countrymen	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
intimate	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
Close	O
went	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Ward	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Close	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
duty	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
clean	O
himself	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Ward	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
comrades	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
and	O
said	O
Ward	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
money	O
and	O
a	O
pocketbook	O
from	O
Ward	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
noised	O
among	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
Close	O
with	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
that	O
m	O
orning	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
perhaps	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pocketbook	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
it	O
to	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
book	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
two	O
bad	O
six-pences	O
,	O
eighteen-pence	O
in	O
half-pence	O
and	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pocket-book	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Ward	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
square	O
breast	O
buckle	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
nor	O
buckle	O
.	O
A	O
buckle	O
was	O
produced	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ARCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Petty-France	O
,	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
dollar	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
four	O
gallons	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
time	O
wanted	O
a	O
dollar	O
changed	O
;	O
I	O
changed	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
dollar	O
besides	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
change	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
dollars	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
To	O
Ward	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
dollars	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
dollars	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
fetching	O
the	O
beer	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PANTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
his	O
duty	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
196.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
IRELAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Flanagan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
large	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cornelian-stone	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
bombazeen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
camblet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
stuff	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
work	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Flanagan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
FLANAGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Flanagan	I-pers
.	O
We	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Tabernacle-walk	B-place
,	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
seven	O
and	O
returned	O
at	O
eight	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
spring-lock	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
upon	O
the	O
dining	O
table	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
but	O
one	O
room	O
on	O
a	O
floor	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
a	O
lady	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
missed	O
the	O
gowns	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
below	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
watch	O
which	O
hung	O
over	O
the	O
mantle	O
piece	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
apprehend	O
by	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
key	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
on	O
the	O
Wednedsay	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
there	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
charge	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
first	O
charged	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
kept	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
eight	O
hours	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
your	O
family	O
consist	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
husband	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HEPWORTH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
New	O
Town	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
brought	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
gowns	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
not	O
made	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
four	O
pounds	O
eight	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
part	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
bundle	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
brought	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
chandler's-shop	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler's-shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
needle	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
clear	O
starching	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
gowns	O
to	O
Phillips	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
my	O
property	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
's	O
.	O
One	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
girl	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
's	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Boon	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
Mile-End	O
New	O
Town	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
from	O
a	O
Mr	O
.	O
Boon	O
's	O
,	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
's	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
's	O
to	O
Mile-End	O
New	O
Town	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
miles	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
,	O
Phillips	O
and	O
Barnett	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
property	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
PERCIVAL	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
gowns	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
at	O
Hepworth	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Flanagan	O
and	O
Mills	O
have	O
combined	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Flanagan	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Kepworth	O
deals	O
in	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
clothes	O
and	O
run	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
tea	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mills	O
deals	O
in	O
stolen	O
goods	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
tried	O
for	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Mills	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
is	O
an	O
encourager	O
of	O
thieves	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
So	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
.	O
To	O
Mills	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
encourager	O
of	O
thieves	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
So	O
has	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
.	O
To	O
Mills	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
tried	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
never	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
or	O
Westminster	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
TIBSHAW	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charring	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
till	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
eleven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
finished	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
indeed	O
,	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
not	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRIANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Ireland	O
a	O
week	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
197.	O
JACOB	B-pers
JONAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holbrook	I-pers
,	O
February	O
24th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
White-hart-court	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
White-hart-court	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
linen	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
loose	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
:	O
that	O
raised	O
my	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
linen	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
enquiry	O
whether	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
robbery	O
committed	O
.	O
On	O
enquiry	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Holbrook	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
linen	O
:	O
A	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOLBROOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bedroom	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
drawers	O
quite	O
stripped	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
cutlary	O
ware	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
Church-Yard	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
minute	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
the	O
servant	O
said	O
he	O
heard	O
somebody	O
jump	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
dark	O
.	O
The	O
window	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
seven	O
feet	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
one	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
footsteps	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
under	O
an	O
arch-way	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
lying	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
lying	O
loose	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
this	O
man	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
DEPUTY	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
198.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
JAMES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
February	O
21st	O
.	O
2d	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
three	O
pounds	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
rappee	O
snuff	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
February	O
28th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
concealed	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
snuff-room	O
,	O
took	O
some	O
paper	O
,	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
dipped	O
his	O
hand	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
stand	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
twisted	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
tobacco	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
a	O
stand	O
up	O
.	O
My	O
apprentice	O
was	O
concealed	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
tobacco	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
him	O
take	O
snuff	O
three	O
sundays	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
his	O
sister	O
came	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
to	O
receive	O
parcels	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
I	O
desired	O
one	O
Badcock	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
ready	O
against	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
;	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
concealed	O
myself	O
again	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
snuff-room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
three	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
rappee	O
snuff	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
snuff	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
suits	O
of	O
clothes	O
and	O
tobacco	O
in	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
constable	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
concealed	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
that	O
was	O
ready	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
second	O
parcel	O
tobacco	O
or	O
snuff	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COUCHMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
mistrusted	O
of	O
stealing	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
almost	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
rappee	O
snuff	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
mend	O
;	O
the	O
snuff	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
alderman	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
some	O
real	O
rappee	O
snuff	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
used	O
to	O
adulterate	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
understand	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BADCOCK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
suspected	O
his	O
servant	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
watch	O
his	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
three	O
Sunday	O
mornings	O
running	O
;	O
he	O
sometimes	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
sister	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
stop	O
for	O
?	O
Couchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
snuff	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
forget	O
the	O
name	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
lives	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Westmoreland-buildings	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
snuff	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
more	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
that	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
is	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
goods	O
to	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
snuff	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
that	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
vineyard	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
the	O
grapes	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
snuff	O
retail	O
without	O
adulterating	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
sort	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
master	O
duely	O
and	O
truely	O
as	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
DEPUTY	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
December	O
4th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Whetstone	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
white	O
heel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
star	O
in	O
the	O
forehead	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
son-in-law	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
Mitcham	B-place
Common	I-place
.	O
My	O
son-in-law	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
knew	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
my	O
son-in-law	O
took	O
his	O
affidavit	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
mare	O
having	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
acquit	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BLACKSTONE	O
.	O
200	O
,	O
201.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
MARKLIN	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COX	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
and	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Barnwell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9th	O
.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
BARNWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk-dyer	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	B-place
,	I-place
Kingsgate-street	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
dye	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
received	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
petticoats	O
from	O
the	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jakes	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
George-Inn	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
colour	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
shop	O
was	O
then	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Jaques	O
sent	O
a	O
child	O
with	O
some	O
fringe	O
to	O
be	O
dyed	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
silk	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
clean	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
those	O
women	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
cleaned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
compters	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
moved	O
the	O
the	O
silks	O
to	O
make	O
room	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
