TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1779	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PLUMBE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
MDCCLXXIX	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PLUMBE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
The	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
MASSIERES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Cursitor	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Hexham	I-pers
George	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hulme	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
George	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
John	B-pers
Blackett	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sheringdon	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Nash	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Theobald	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
Chambers	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
William	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
William	B-pers
Willey	I-pers
Humphry	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
James	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Nicholas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
William	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
William	B-pers
Oddy	I-pers
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Angus	B-pers
M'Kinnon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Edkins	I-pers
Golden	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stable	I-pers
255.	O
MARY	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
JOHN	I-pers
FRASIER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3d	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
WELCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
makes	O
clothes	O
for	O
the	O
army	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
four	O
coats	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
from	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
four	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
eight	O
coats	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Frasier	O
had	O
opened	O
her	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Frasier	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
and	O
taken	O
four	O
coats	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
three	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
there	O
been	O
twenty	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
thought	O
they	O
all	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
256	O
,	O
257.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
and	O
ANNE	B-pers
BOLTON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-hook	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
base-metal	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
3d	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Carter	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
apartment	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
in	O
Cross-lane	B-place
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
compos	O
mentis	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
it	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
hook	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
base-metal	O
key	O
.	O
She	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
turned	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
order	O
the	O
beer	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
came	O
in	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
really	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
after	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
it	O
wanted	O
ten	O
minutes	O
to	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
married	O
or	O
single	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
single	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
Carter	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
person	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
she	O
picked	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
WEVERTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wire-worker	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
an	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
proper	O
judge	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
but	O
18	O
s.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
confisticated	O
it	O
.	O
Bolton	O
keeps	O
a	O
clothes	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Weverton	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Gatty	O
in	O
North	O
Audley-street	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
as	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
CONSTABLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Mrs.	O
Gatty	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
evidence	O
in	O
jail	O
that	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
Bolton	O
.	O
BOLTON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
As	O
Weverton	O
had	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
one	O
came	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
CARTER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
women	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
one	O
Anne	B-pers
Tidmarsh	I-pers
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
other	O
girls	O
first	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
up	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
two	O
other	O
girls	O
who	O
were	O
discharged	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
charge	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
girls	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
both	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
258.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HEDGE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
light	O
glazed	O
window	O
sashes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lamb	O
's	O
Conduit-street	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
five	O
sashes	O
last	O
Monday	O
from	O
a	O
building	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Lamb	B-place
's	I-place
Conduit-street	I-place
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
finished	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
places	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
hung	O
for	O
use	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
parts	O
of	O
them	O
found	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
loss	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
affects	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
the	O
frames	O
fixed	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
places	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
weights	O
nor	O
lines	O
,	O
nor	O
beads	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
up	O
with	O
temporary	O
pieces	O
of	O
wood	O
.	O
They	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
again	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
lines	O
in	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHARLES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
sashes	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
or	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
sashes	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
whole	O
sashes	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
pieces	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
fitted	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
cross	O
upon	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
chissel	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
pieces	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
sashes	O
.	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
put	O
in	O
temporarily	O
.	O
Must	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
hung	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
weights	O
and	O
lines	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
the	O
common	O
practice	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
sashes	O
before	O
they	O
are	O
hung	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
completed	O
?	O
-	O
So	O
far	O
as	O
that	O
they	O
only	O
wanted	O
hanging	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
hung	O
and	O
the	O
beads	O
nailed	O
they	O
are	O
complete	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
this	O
cross	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
fitted	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
this	O
cross	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
generally	O
make	O
private	O
marks	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
fit	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
carpenter	O
.	O
Carpenters	O
make	O
sashes	O
do	O
n't	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
other	O
carpenters	O
make	O
marks	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
no	O
carpenter	O
makes	O
a	O
cross	O
for	O
a	O
mark	O
but	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shop	O
besides	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
new	O
sashframes	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
fellow	O
sash	O
now	O
marked	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
sashes	O
glazed	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Fully	O
glazed	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
the	O
weather	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
here	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
MARK	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glazier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Jewry-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
sashes	O
from	O
a	O
building	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Seagrow	O
,	O
in	O
Constitution-Row	O
,	O
leading	O
to	O
Pancras	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
sixteen	O
squares	O
of	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
him	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
coming	O
again	O
with	O
sixteen	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
squares	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
informed	O
of	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
six	O
sashes	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
sales	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
from	O
old	O
houses	O
he	O
pulled	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
and	O
made	O
rounds	O
of	O
ladders	O
of	O
the	O
frames	O
.	O
Can	O
they	O
take	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
frames	O
without	O
breaking	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
must	O
break	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
;	O
those	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
were	O
not	O
broke	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
by	O
the	O
glass	O
when	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
frames	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
new	O
frames	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
glass	O
?	O
-	O
Sixpence	O
a	O
foot	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
gives	O
for	O
old	O
glass	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
Sixteen	O
years	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
sashes	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
place	O
without	O
being	O
hung	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
houses	O
that	O
were	O
inhabited	O
where	O
the	O
sashes	O
were	O
in	O
their	O
place	O
but	O
not	O
hung	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
carpenters	O
frequently	O
buy	O
sash	O
frames	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
old	O
sash	O
frames	O
and	O
glass	O
together	O
?	O
Do	O
not	O
they	O
sell	O
the	O
glass	O
to	O
glaziers	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
if	O
they	O
choose	O
it	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
frames	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
I	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
frames	O
;	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
my	O
knowledge	O
goes	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
frames	O
I	O
made	O
;	O
they	O
answer	O
the	O
dimensions	O
in	O
every	O
point	O
.	O
They	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
remarkably	O
stout	O
frames	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
two	O
inch	O
sashes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pieces	O
of	O
frames	O
and	O
a	O
square	O
glass	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
remarkably	O
crooked	O
square	O
and	O
it	O
fits	O
the	O
putty	O
in	O
that	O
frame	O
exactly	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Maddox	O
's	O
timber-yard	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
old	O
sashes	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
five	O
pence	O
a	O
foot	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
fit	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
glazier	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
putty	O
being	O
hard	O
,	O
without	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
six	O
pence	O
a	O
foot	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
a	O
man	O
brought	O
me	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
sashes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
widow	O
who	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
back	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
glass	O
out	O
;	O
one	O
Kelley	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
four	O
shillings	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
Smith	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
bring	O
you	O
two	O
whole	O
sashes	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
little	O
sashes	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
business	O
but	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
safe	O
in	O
buying	O
them	O
.	O
Kelly	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Excise-office	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
my	O
tryal	O
would	O
come	O
on	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
foot	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
five	O
pounds	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
near	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
are	O
with	O
me	O
now	O
.	O
He	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
just	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
sober	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
suspicion	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
other	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
be	O
here	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
inclined	O
to	O
be	O
dishonest	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
scores	O
of	O
pounds	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Kelly	O
was	O
to	O
appear	O
here	O
to-day	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Kelly	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
goods	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
KILDAGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
a	O
just	O
and	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
258.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LAWDON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
LEADER	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rising	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2d	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RISING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
tap	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
in	I-place
Warwick-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
walked	O
to	O
Barking	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
clock	O
which	O
stands	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
to	O
clean	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
buckles	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
I.	O
R.	O
CHARLES	O
BAXTER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
's	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
candles	O
were	O
lighted	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
buckles	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Rising	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
buckles	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
mornings	O
with	O
fruit	O
and	O
fowls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
those	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
upon	O
duty	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
NEALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
Coldstream	O
regiment	O
,	O
which	O
regiment	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
duplicate	O
for	O
these	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
near	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
church	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
corps	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
subject	O
.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
RISING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
buckles	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
at	O
Norwich	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
marked	O
I.	O
R.	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
use	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
fire-arms	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
'S	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LAWDON	I-pers
otherwise	O
LEADER	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rising	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RISING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
I	O
put	O
this	O
spoon	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
tap-room	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Upton	O
,	O
who	O
owns	O
the	O
inn	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
NEALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
who	O
was	O
upon	O
duty	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
thieving	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
spoon	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Rising	I-pers
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
259.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STODDART	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
34	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WHEELHOUSE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
watch	O
yesterday	O
in	O
the	O
Steel-yard	O
while	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
two	O
bars	O
into	O
one	O
pocket	O
and	O
one	O
into	O
another	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
yards	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
keeping	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
bars	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
stamp	O
upon	O
them	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
brought	O
me	O
these	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
bars	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
yard	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260.	O
ANNE	B-pers
MATHEWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Gosset	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
13th	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
GOSSET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
Thursday	O
at	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
after	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
Highgate	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mathews	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
Long-lane	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
gin	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
swore	O
bitterly	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
secured	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
who	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
hat	O
again	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
RAYMOND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
her	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
Poll	O
Keith	O
.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
COLEBROOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Gossett	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
faster	O
than	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
on	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
call	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
without	O
her	O
hat	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
261.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STOUT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
for	O
27	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Bath	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
the	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
payable	O
and	O
secured	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
notes	O
,	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
.	O
February	O
2d	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PHILLIPS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
supped	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
evening	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
,	O
at	O
Barnet	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Northampton	O
corps	O
of	O
officers	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
us	O
came	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
Finchley-common	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
property	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
and	O
notes	O
,	O
of	O
51	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
hotel	O
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
boots	O
off	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
forgot	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
boot	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
I	O
recollected	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
my	O
boot	O
;	O
not	O
finding	O
my	O
boots	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
rang	O
for	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
boots	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
cleaned	O
them	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
this	O
hotel	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
winter	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
porter	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
any	O
pocketbook	O
in	O
my	O
boots	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
reward	O
him	O
properly	O
for	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
persisted	O
in	O
declaring	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
porters	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	B-pers
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
advertise	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
offering	O
ten	O
guineas	O
reward	O
for	O
their	O
restoration	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
exact	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
.	O
After	O
receiving	O
that	O
description	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
post-bill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Bath	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
was	O
payable	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
A	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Langston	O
,	O
a	O
banker	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement's-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Bath	O
bills	O
are	O
payable	O
,	O
informing	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
bill	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
notice	O
of	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
for	O
acceptance	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
receipt	O
of	O
that	O
letter	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
(	O
who	O
has	O
indeed	O
been	O
indefatigable	O
in	O
the	O
matter	O
)	O
attended	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
a	O
porter	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Cannon	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
porter	O
there	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
banker	O
could	O
not	O
identify	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
from	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
circumstances	O
,	O
we	O
presumed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
loose	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
pocketbook	O
contained	O
eight	O
guineas	O
;	O
a	O
bank	O
bill	O
for	O
twenty-seven	O
pounds	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
a	O
Bath	O
bank	O
bill	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
fifty-one	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
where	O
you	O
pulled	O
your	O
boots	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
circumstance	O
I	O
should	O
mention	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
very	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
tired	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
chamberlain	O
to	O
undo	O
the	O
boot	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
manner	O
at	O
the	O
knee	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
recollect	O
the	O
boots	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
subsequent	O
to	O
the	O
chamberlain	O
's	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
boots	O
away	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
You	O
sat	O
up	O
very	O
late	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
well	O
enough	O
to	O
recollect	O
every	O
circumstance	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ride	O
on	O
horse-back	O
to	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
the	O
leg	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
or	O
under	O
your	O
foot	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
below	O
my	O
calf	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
a	O
Newmarket	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
when	O
the	O
chamberlain	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
for	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
your	O
boots	O
down	O
and	O
had	O
cleaned	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
usual	O
some	O
times	O
for	O
the	O
chamberlain	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
boots	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
for	O
the	O
porter	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
bed-chambers	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
unusual	O
thing	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
porter	O
in	O
a	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
is	O
rung	O
for	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
take	O
property	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
three	O
times	O
that	O
amount	O
;	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
always	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
frequently	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
This	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
back	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
at	O
Barnet	O
from	O
an	O
apprehension	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
book	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
said	O
possibly	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
dropped	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
or	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
market	O
,	O
Captain	O
Phillips	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
the	O
circumstance	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
related	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
the	O
porter	O
whose	O
turn	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
strongly	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
before	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
such	O
behaviour	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
offered	O
all	O
the	O
servants	O
a	O
reward	O
for	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
Barnet	O
,	O
that	O
probably	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
inn	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
away	O
,	O
we	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Clement	O
's	O
Lane	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
guinea	O
Bath	O
bill	O
being	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
letter	O
to	O
Captain	O
Phillips	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
recollect	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
man	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
which	O
nearly	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
porter	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Cannon	O
coffee-house	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
turned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
away	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cannon	O
coffee-house	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
porter	O
much	O
resembling	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
banker	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
they	O
thought	O
him	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
identify	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
the	O
porter	O
several	O
questions	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
knew	O
one	O
Matthews	O
who	O
had	O
formerly	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
likewise	O
was	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Matthews	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
having	O
been	O
rather	O
kind	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Will	O
that	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
yesterday	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
no	O
bad	O
friend	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
your	O
telling	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
notes	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
seen	O
him	O
full	O
of	O
cash	O
lately	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
a	O
Bath	O
bank	O
note	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
man	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
note	O
from	O
Stout	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
accepted	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
the	O
Bath	O
bank	O
bill	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
accepted	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
in	O
Clement	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Stout	O
with	O
any	O
other	O
bills	O
or	O
with	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
for	O
twentyseven	O
pounds	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
bank	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
something	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
banker	O
refused	O
to	O
accept	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
afraid	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
recollected	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Prothero	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
it	O
up	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
David	B-pers
Prothero	I-pers
.	O
)	O
DAVID	B-pers
PROTHERO	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
putting	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
insisting	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
bill	O
out	O
himself	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
note	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
of	O
Mr.	O
PHILLIPS	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
for	O
an	O
exact	O
description	O
of	O
these	O
notes	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
made	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
note	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
a	O
description	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
from	O
another	O
note	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
value	O
?	O
-	O
Certainly	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
with	O
precision	O
to	O
this	O
note	O
but	O
only	O
from	O
a	O
description	O
sent	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
from	O
that	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
private	O
memorandum	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
mother	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
posts	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
statement	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
recollect	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
this	O
note	O
before	O
you	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
recollected	O
the	O
value	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
payable	O
,	O
and	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
indorsed	O
by	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
of	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
During	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
continual	O
opportunity	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
disposed	O
to	O
have	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
much	O
entrusted	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
received	O
and	O
paid	O
great	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Phillips	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
Barnet	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
any	O
notes	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
or	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
landlord	O
informed	O
me	O
;	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
To	O
Wood	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
after	O
you	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
note	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Portugal-street	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
Out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
cut	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
in	O
Clement	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
three	O
minutes	O
past	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
from	O
the	O
Cannon	O
coffee-house	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
speak	O
before	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
other	O
note	O
of	O
twenty-seven	O
pounds	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
I	O
should	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
shown	O
to	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
pass	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
this	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
where	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
question	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Allen	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
Road	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
four	O
guineas	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
found	O
this	O
loose	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
never	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
once	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
persuade	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
note	O
of	O
27	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
me	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
with	O
all	O
its	O
contents	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
living	O
once	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
10	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
10	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
only	O
four	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
knowledge	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
applied	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
.	O
-	O
ALLEN	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
John-street	O
,	O
Tottenham-Court	O
Road	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
intimate	O
with	O
Matthews	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
waited	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
Matthews	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
story	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
drawn	O
him	O
in	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
this	O
Bath	O
bank	O
bill	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
post	O
bill	O
of	O
27	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
likewise	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
notes	O
,	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
Matthews	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
go	O
yourself	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
book	O
and	O
its	O
contents	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
Matthews	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
inform	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
carpenter	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
pick	O
the	O
book	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
know	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
give	O
up	O
every	O
circumstance	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
had	O
the	O
pocket-book	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
PRISONER	O
.	O
A	O
witness	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
fellow-servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
262.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BREEZE	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Lander	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
LANDER	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oilman	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
;	O
upon	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lander	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
only	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
open	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
up	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
backwards	O
;	O
hearing	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
peeped	O
through	O
the	O
rails	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
softly	O
along	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
coat	O
off	O
the	O
nail	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
her	O
within	O
four	O
doors	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
great	O
coat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
first	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lander	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
scuffle	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
lay	O
the	O
coat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
thumps	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
WILLES	O
.	O
263.	O
ANNE	B-pers
CROW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Worthy	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27th	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
HAWLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Worthy	O
,	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
and	O
silk	O
mercer	O
in	O
Hanway	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
busy	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
serving	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
follow	O
her	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
a	O
lady	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
cotton	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
passing	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
walk	O
back	O
quietly	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
door	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
cloth	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
wished	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
has	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
ribband	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Mantuamaker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
cotton	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
To	O
Hawley	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
bundle	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
left	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
believe	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLOUGHBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
complaint	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
against	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
sufficient	O
warning	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
WILLES	O
.	O
264.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
containing	O
twenty-four	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
17th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PEARSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
best	O
for	O
trimming	O
,	O
muslin	O
or	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
agreed	O
for	O
four	O
yards	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
ship	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
winked	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
nearer	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
it	O
up	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lace	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
detect	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
without	O
letting	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
offence	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BOSWORTH	I-pers
FARN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
writing	O
behind	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
conceal	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lace	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
steal	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
stolen	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
steal	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
my	O
while	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
which	O
he	O
values	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
twenty-four	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
petticoats	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
265.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PULLEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
December	O
23d	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PUGH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blackall	O
's	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
82	I-place
,	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
seat	O
of	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
rather	O
clear	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blackall	O
.	O
My	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
pawned	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
West	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hewitson	O
brought	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
to	O
pledge	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
five	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
HEWITSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
banker's-clerk	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
arrested	O
for	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
five	O
guineas	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HEWITSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Hewitson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
arrested	O
by	O
a	O
tailor	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
five	O
guineas	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
either	O
John	O
or	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
banker	O
's	O
clerk	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
To	O
Pugh	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
often	O
;	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
once	O
to	O
mend	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PULLEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
year	O
1777	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
My	O
watch	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
's	O
watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
five	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Above	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
clock	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
clock	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
him	O
one	O
to	O
wear	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
him	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
making	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
lent	O
him	O
old	O
ones	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
set	O
the	O
church	O
clock	O
by	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
266.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
surtout	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
,	O
May	O
7th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ORME	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
from	O
my	O
lodging	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
coat	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
She	O
alarmed	O
her	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BOWKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
backwards	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Ormes	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
coat	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
wrapped	O
round	O
him	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Bowker	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
hang	O
on	O
the	O
curtain-rod	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
267.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KENNEDY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
whole	O
pepper	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19th	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BRADFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
pepper	O
;	O
but	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAMELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bradford	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
steal	O
twelve	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
black	O
pepper	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
parcel	O
on	O
a	O
tea	O
cannister	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
warehouse	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bradford	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
the	O
pepper	O
down	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
?	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
populace	O
.	O
Ramell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LESSARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
immediately	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
parcel	O
down	O
on	O
Ramell	O
's	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
transaction	O
.	O
The	O
pepper	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
N.	O
3	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
268.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dalby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
demanding	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Sheering	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
May	O
10th	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
DALBY	I-pers
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Thirteen	O
last	O
March	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
?	O
-	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
take	O
as	O
oath	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
doing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
swearing	O
falsely	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
punished	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
your	O
catechism	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
call	O
God	O
to	O
witness	O
to	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
an	O
untruth	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
under	O
an	O
obligation	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
obliges	O
you	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
HEWITSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
goods	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
On	O
yesterday-was-week	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
minutes	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
boy	O
(	O
Dalby	O
)	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
boys	O
at	O
play	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
watchman	O
,	O
run	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
robbing	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
with	O
two	O
bundles	O
;	O
his	O
hands	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bundles	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
begging	O
the	O
prisoner	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
over	O
him	O
forcing	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
too	O
soon	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
bitterly	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
going	O
to	O
Harry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Tothilfields	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
the	O
bundles	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
bundles	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
gave	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
opened	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
DALBY	I-pers
again	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
what	O
is	O
meant	O
by	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
;	O
but	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
proper	O
,	O
and	O
fit	O
,	O
and	O
necessary	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
boy	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
hell	O
flames	O
burning	O
in	O
fire	O
and	O
brimstone	O
for	O
ever	O
and	O
ever	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
come	O
determined	O
to	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
Remember	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
called	O
God	O
to	O
witness	O
that	O
you	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Opposite	O
Clement's-Inn	O
,	O
by	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
on	O
Monday-was-week	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
tell	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
-	O
Home	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
Poland-street	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
a	O
tavern	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
bundles	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Sheering	I-pers
's	O
son	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundles	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
please	O
to	O
show	O
me	O
the	O
right	O
way	O
to	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
part	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Poland-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
Newman-street	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
both	O
go	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
a	O
dark	O
alley	O
by	O
Clare	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
lamps	O
nor	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
this	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
the	O
highest	O
way	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Long-Acre	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
began	O
singing	O
nasty	O
songs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
showed	O
me	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chapel-street	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
up	O
there	O
is	O
Newman-street	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
let	O
us	O
shake	O
hands	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Portman-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
shall	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
said	O
well	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hated	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
none	O
?	O
he	O
rattled	O
a	O
few	O
buttons	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
wrists	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
snatch	O
the	O
bundles	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
them	O
fast	O
;	O
he	O
swung	O
me	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
now	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
bundles	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
kill	O
me	O
now	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
the	O
watchman	O
hearing	O
me	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
he	O
fell	O
over	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
straddling	O
over	O
me	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
assaulted	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
going	O
to	O
Harry	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
's	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
doing	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
you	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
Clare-market	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
a	O
dark	O
alley	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
lad	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
N.	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
BARON	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
269.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HUTTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
sixty	O
books	O
of	O
leaf	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
leaf	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
April	O
10th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SPARROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Turned	O
of	O
fifteen	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
gold-beater	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
to	O
the	O
Blossoms	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Lawrence-lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
sixty	O
books	O
of	O
leaf	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
leaf	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Blossoms	B-place
Inn	I-place
Passage	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Blossoms	O
Inn	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
you	O
fool	O
loose	O
the	O
box	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
from	O
running	O
after	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Lawrence-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
turning	O
in	O
King's-street	O
thinking	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
lamps	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
features	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
his	O
dress	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
or	O
black	O
coat	O
buttoned	O
close	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positively	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
by	O
the	O
persuasion	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
that	O
he	O
swears	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
never	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
runners	O
took	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
singled	O
him	O
out	O
immediately	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
boy	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
to	O
the	O
Blossoms	O
Inn	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
crying	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
bookkeeper	O
you	O
fool	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
held	O
him	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
him	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
stature	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
complexion	O
,	O
brown	O
hair	O
tied	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
longish	O
chin	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
boy	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
dressed	O
in	O
black	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
him	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
property	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
EARL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
circulating-library	O
in	O
Carnaby-Market	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
lodges	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sedate	O
sober	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
SEDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
-	O
BALL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
lately	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
within	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Two	O
years	O
.	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Three	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tailor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
as	O
a	O
person	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
no	O
business	O
,	O
kept	O
good	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HUNT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
decent	O
and	O
sober	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
270.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
FLANAGAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
steel	O
saws	O
with	O
wooden	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
carpenter	O
's	O
plow	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
wood	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
carpenter	O
's	O
bowling-stock	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Justin	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6th	O
.	O
JUSTIN	B-pers
M'CARTY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Suffolk-street	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Hay-Market	I-place
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
I	O
could	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
four	O
saws	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
week	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
M'KENZIE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
my	O
rounds	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
Mary-le-Bonne	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
at	O
full	O
length	O
on	O
the	O
plane	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
much	O
used	O
to	O
the	O
saws	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
but	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
Suppose	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
with	O
ten	O
carpenters	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
had	O
six	O
saws	O
each	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
pick	O
your	O
saws	O
from	O
among	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
fifty	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
the	O
stock	O
is	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
bit	O
here	O
that	O
fits	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
given	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
tools	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
without	O
asking	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
often	O
has	O
taken	O
tools	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
intent	O
now	O
I	O
leave	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
under	O
my	O
shutter	O
that	O
was	O
neglected	O
to	O
be	O
bolted	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
tools	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
any	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
asked	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GOLDNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lurking	O
about	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
;	O
my	O
comrade	O
bid	O
the	O
watchman	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mary-le-Bonne	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
an	O
odd	O
way	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
le-Bonne	O
to	O
Drury-Lane	O
through	O
Sutton-street	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Little	O
Earl	O
street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
tools	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
punctually	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
recourse	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
blemish	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
introduced	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
benefit	O
society	O
which	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
borne	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
impeach	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LANE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
have	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
tools	O
at	O
a	O
late	O
hour	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
late	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
job	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
taken	O
tools	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
271.	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
COLEMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
glass	O
bottles	O
of	O
red	O
Port	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
bottle	O
of	O
Calcavalla	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
bottle	O
of	O
Frontiniac	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Madeira	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baldero	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
May	O
13th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baldero	O
,	O
in	O
Bedford-square	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Boldero	O
's	O
butler	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hide	O
five	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
pantry	O
to	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
secret	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
twice	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
wine	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Baldero	O
's	O
cellar	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Madeira	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
Frontiniac	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
containing	O
some	O
linen	O
;	O
the	O
wine	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
upon	O
the	O
sacking	O
under	O
the	O
bedclothes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
wine	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
cellar	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HINCEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
servants	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
under	O
his	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
under	O
the	O
bedclothes	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baldero	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
wine	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
bottles	O
was	O
not	O
full	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
asked	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
pardon	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Baldero	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
locker	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
was	O
kept	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
YOUNG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
round-house	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
roundhouse	O
that	O
was	O
impressed	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
commissioners	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
handed	O
it	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bedford	O
Arms	O
in	O
Charlotte-street	O
,	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Baldero	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bedford-square	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
basket	O
with	O
three	O
bottles	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bottles	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
here	O
JOHN	O
BALDERO	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
small	O
key	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
locker	O
off	O
the	O
side	O
board	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
locker	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
wine	O
vaults	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
wine	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wine	O
vaults	O
.	O
This	O
confession	O
related	O
to	O
the	O
five	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Whether	O
this	O
confession	O
came	O
freely	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
obtained	O
by	O
promises	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
promises	O
whatsoever	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
being	O
ungrateful	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
off	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
certainly	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
bottle	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
apprehend	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
wine	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
different	O
days	O
?	O
-	O
Different	O
days	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
sent	O
for	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
wine	O
several	O
times	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Walden	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
always	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
locker	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baldero	O
went	O
to	O
Bath	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
delivered	O
me	O
out	O
five	O
bottles	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
drinking	O
the	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
her	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
opened	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
locker	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
port	O
wine	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
while	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
at	O
Bath	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baldero	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
locker	O
where	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
was	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
DEPUTY	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
272.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
commonly	O
called	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
feloniously	O
demand	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
May	O
8th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WEATHALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
second	O
coachman	O
to	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
driving	O
the	O
Marquis	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopped	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
cloth	O
manufactory	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Rutland	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
a	O
sharp	O
pace	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
immediately	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
!	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
stop	O
as	O
he	O
desired	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
run	O
perhaps	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
carriage	O
stopped	O
I	O
watched	O
his	O
motions	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
fellowservant	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
LUKE	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
footman	O
to	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
chariot	O
when	O
my	O
lord	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Rutland	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
first	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
passed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
leaned	O
my	O
head	O
over	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
-	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
!	O
When	O
the	O
chariot	O
stopped	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Granby	O
-	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
immediately	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
wheels	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
unhorsed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Knowing	O
myself	O
clear	O
of	O
any	O
robbery	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
call	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ships	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
my	O
trial	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
till	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
his	O
lordship	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
never	O
my	O
intention	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
I	O
had	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
To	O
West	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
fire-arms	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
none	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
273.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Bank	O
note	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
Bank	O
note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
another	O
Bank	O
note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
another	O
Bank	O
note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
another	O
Bank	O
note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
11th	O
.	O
CAPTAIN	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BARRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
on	O
May	O
the	O
10th	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
taken	O
a	O
glass	O
too	O
much	O
;	O
still	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
recollection	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
to	O
the	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Munday	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
Round	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
through	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
accosted	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
