TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1779	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
THIRD	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PLUMBE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell	O
Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
MDCCLXXIX	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PLUMBE	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
The	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BULLER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
GLYNN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NUGENT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
,	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
Ippediah	O
Vincent	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
William	I-pers
Cullibin	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sibbald	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lambkin	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Kennett	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burnthwaite	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Collett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lay	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fosticks	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Glanville	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Felts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pennington	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tremlett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Talboys	I-pers
,	O
Blacket	O
Bulmer	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Evance	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
134.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
33	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
fat	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
saltpetre	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
,	O
February	O
,	O
5th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
KEELING	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
at	O
Twickenham	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
concealed	O
some	O
fat	O
and	O
salt	O
petre	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
moved	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
chamber	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
some	O
oats	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
chamber	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sewed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
.	O
The	O
chamber	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
leather	O
trunk	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
confessed	O
that	O
the	O
fat	O
and	O
saltpetre	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
confession	O
reduced	O
into	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
promises	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Nor	O
threatenings	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
HATTERED	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
fat	O
and	O
saltpetre	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Keeling	O
's	O
chamber	O
locked	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
deserved	O
punishment	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
135	O
,	O
136	O
,	O
137.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARSH	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
MARSH	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARLOW	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
lamp	O
braces	O
,	O
sixty	O
pound	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
parish	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Le	I-pers
Bonne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
January	O
23d	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
in	O
Cranbourn-alley	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
braces	O
,	O
I	O
fitted	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
places	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Henrietta-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Wimpole-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
not	O
being	O
laid	O
on	O
the	O
statute	O
which	O
makes	O
this	O
offence	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
138.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DARE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
slide	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Rachael	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
,	O
January	O
27th	O
.	O
HENRIETTA	B-pers
EGERTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
Rachael	B-pers
Ambrose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
diamond	O
slider	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
desk	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
very	O
early	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
great	O
search	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
on	O
Thursday	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Leighton	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Wardour	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
suffered	O
a	O
loss	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
diamond	O
slider	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
stopped	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
VINCENT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leighton	O
,	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
a	O
gold	O
slider	O
which	O
I	O
stopped	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
borrow	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
staggered	O
at	O
the	O
question	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
his	O
mistress	O
came	O
late	O
from	O
the	O
masquerade	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
all	O
over	O
mud	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
suspected	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
his	O
mistress	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
slider	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
DEATH	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
139.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
containing	O
eighteen	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
,	O
February	O
11th	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
RUTTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bartholomew-close	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
callico-glazer	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
damping	O
these	O
cloths	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
directly	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
callico	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
damping	O
these	O
cloths	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
damped	O
them	O
he	O
laid	O
them	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
master	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
buildings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
round	O
the	O
buildings	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
breath	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
stop	O
me	O
for	O
?	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
came	O
up	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
pieces	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
dropped	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
HOLLER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
Somebody	O
laughed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
meant	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
wonder	O
how	O
any	O
man	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
140.	O
LEVY	B-pers
LAZAROUS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Dawkins	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1st	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
DAWKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
a	O
cart	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Broad-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
till-board	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cart	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Broad-street	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
steal	O
a	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BUCKLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
him	O
too	O
light	O
heeled	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
some	O
soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
soldiers	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
141.	O
RALPH	B-pers
ALLISON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Steers	I-pers
.	O
BARNARD	B-pers
STEERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
a	O
sale	O
of	O
goods	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
catalogue	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
at	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
began	O
the	O
sale	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
impression	O
of	O
the	O
plates	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
stand	O
convicted	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
convicted	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
plates	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
142.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TAIT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hanss	B-pers
Tonnis	I-pers
,	O
February	O
6th	O
.	O
HANSS	O
TONNIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Broad-street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
cryed	O
out	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
tucked	O
into	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
challenged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
hit	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
him	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
143	O
,	O
144	O
,	O
145.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DEMPSEY	I-pers
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
WOOLLEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TODD	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-four	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sudlow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
January	O
21st	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SUDLOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
and	O
hosier	O
in	O
Wigmore-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
purchase	O
for	O
a	O
particular	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
particular	O
sort	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Waller	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Waller	O
's	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Wigmore-street	O
.	O
Having	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
stockings	O
were	O
stolen	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
such	O
remarks	O
on	O
them	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
make	O
and	O
the	O
size	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
my	O
servant	O
informed	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
me	O
out	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
being	O
written	O
on	O
the	O
wrapper	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
sent	O
first	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Waller	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
apprentices	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
and	O
informed	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
24	O
pair	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
22	O
pair	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
pair	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
each	O
parcel	O
;	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
sealed	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
office	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ATWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrol	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
22	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sealed	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
burglary	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Butcher	O
,	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Dempsey	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	O
James	O
,	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
stockings	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
stockings	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
their	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
direction	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
wrappers	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
bought	O
these	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
magistrate	O
sent	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sudlow	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
dozen	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
stockings	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
into	O
this	O
room	O
on	O
another	O
business	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
burglary	O
having	O
been	O
committed	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoners	O
all	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
them	O
what	O
you	O
came	O
about	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
James	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
Dempsey	O
,	O
and	O
Dempsey	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
any	O
apprehensions	O
,	O
or	O
uneasy	O
at	O
your	O
coming	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Dempsey	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
myself	O
guilty	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
?	O
Atwood	O
.	O
He	O
only	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
shop	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
bed	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
black	O
mask	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
ANNE	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sudlow	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
hatter	O
;	O
I	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
stockings	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
stockings	O
were	O
brought	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
lit	O
candles	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
only	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
one	O
.	O
What	O
size	O
was	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
youth	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
head	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Woolley	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
this	O
matter	O
be	O
transacting	O
between	O
his	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
stockings	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
minute	O
taking	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
minute	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
positively	O
swear	O
from	O
seeing	O
him	O
one	O
minute	O
that	O
that	O
person	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
parlour	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
stockings	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
persons	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
!	O
-	O
Another	O
young	O
man	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
off	O
;	O
Woolley	O
was	O
running	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
seemed	O
to	O
laugh	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observation	O
upon	O
that	O
lad	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
clothes	O
(	O
Dempsey	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
DEMPSEY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
turning	O
a	O
wheel	O
for	O
twopence	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
room	O
that	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
twopence	O
a	O
night	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
asleep	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
hung	O
up	O
a	O
usual	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
the	O
woman	O
waked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
three	O
were	O
too	O
many	O
in	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Atwood	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
lodging	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
another	O
twopenny	O
lodging	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
examined	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
outin	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
WOOLLEY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
almost	O
constantly	O
open	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
twopenny	O
lodging	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
directly	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
almost	O
always	O
open	O
.	O
Other	O
lads	O
and	O
disorderly	O
women	O
too	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farrier	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
call	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
there	O
does	O
not	O
seem	O
sufficient	O
ground	O
for	O
a	O
charge	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
DEMPSEY	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
WOOLLEY	O
GUILTY	O
Death	O
.	O
TODD	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Woolley	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
146.	O
JANE	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Johnson's-change	B-place
,	I-place
Rosemary-lane	I-place
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Friday	O
last	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
asking	O
for	O
her	O
namesake	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
her	O
namesake	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
Williamson	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
Scotchman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
much	O
loved	O
the	O
Scotch	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
newspaper	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
purse	O
with	O
bank	O
notes	O
and	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
three	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
dine	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Sabbath-day	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	O
Bear	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
cloak	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
another	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
cloak	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cloak	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dutton	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cloak	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
FRANCES	B-pers
WILLIAMSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dutton	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
describing	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
marks	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
cloak	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
on	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
nail	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
DUTTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
slop-shop	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
clothes	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
cloak	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Friday	O
afternoon	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
cloak	O
of	O
another	O
woman	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
147.	O
ANNE	B-pers
PRESTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
December	O
15th	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
NOBLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
;	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
the	O
lieutenant	O
of	O
a	O
press-gang	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
was	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
lieutenant	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
lieutenant	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Bank	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
ten	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
look	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
that	O
is	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
trembled	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
lieutenant	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
prosecute	O
me	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
148.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
walnut-tree	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
seven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
womans	O
red	O
morocco	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
small	O
print	O
in	O
a	O
wooden	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pick	I-pers
,	O
January	O
29th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
timber	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
as	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
move	O
our	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
patrol	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ROWLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
drawers	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Greek-street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Fullwood's-rents	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
barber	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
patrol	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
we	O
examined	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Atwood	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
patrol	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ATWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
brought	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
labour	O
;	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
midwife	O
,	O
in	O
Short's-gardens	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
drawers	O
asked	O
me	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
down	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
to	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
on	O
while	O
he	O
made	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
stopped	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
the	O
watchman	O
secured	O
me	O
.	O
Atwood	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
round	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
neck	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
DRIVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
no	O
trade	O
yet	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
fourteen-years	O
old	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
lad	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisonar	O
's	O
mother	O
also	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
149.	O
EMANUEL	B-pers
LOVEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
knife	O
tray	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
case	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
seven	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
wooden	O
drawer	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pick	I-pers
,	O
January	O
29th	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary-le-bonne	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
fire	O
broke	O
out	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Collings	O
's	O
yard	O
minding	O
that	O
some	O
horses	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
somebody	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
box	O
,	O
some	O
knives	O
,	O
two	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dish	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
towards	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
tray	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
person	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
publick-house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
past	O
the	O
first	O
publick-house	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
Collings	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Banbury-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
young	O
man	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
publick-house	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
opposite	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
That	O
publick-house	O
is	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Berner	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
past	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
150.	O
HENRY	B-pers
TODD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
live	O
pigs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
February	O
8th	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tothill-street	B-place
,	I-place
Little	I-place
Gray's-Inn-Lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
pigs	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tons	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Isaacs	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
piece	O
being	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
tail	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
mark	O
in	O
particular	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
that	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
small	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
five	O
weeks	O
old	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
boar	O
pigs	O
or	O
sow	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
with	O
the	O
tail	O
cut	O
was	O
a	O
boar	O
pig	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
sow	O
pig	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Three	O
Tons	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
two	O
pigs	O
in	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
three	O
shillings	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
first	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
warm	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
stuck	O
them	O
with	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
blood	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hands	O
were	O
bloody	O
;	O
the	O
pigs	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
killed	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
about	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
were	O
the	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
Both	O
white	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
old	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
mark	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
tail	O
of	O
one	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
sow	O
or	O
boar	O
pigs	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
one	O
a	O
sow	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
boar	O
;	O
the	O
boar	O
pig	O
had	O
the	O
tail	O
cut	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Charter-house	O
wall	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
across	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
pigs	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
nine	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
six	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
allowed	O
them	O
me	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick-house	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
bag	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
Isaacs	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
changed	O
the	O
pigs	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
pigs	O
for	O
other	O
people	O
he	O
has	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
pigs	O
for	O
other	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Are	O
those	O
your	O
own	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
151.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
January	O
25th	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
SINCLAIR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	B-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
one-pair-of-stairs	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
;	O
it	O
hung	O
over	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
lodging	O
out	O
of	O
compassion	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
boy	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
an	O
apron	O
to	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
misfortune	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
His	O
mother	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
trounce	O
me	O
for	O
saying	O
they	O
had	O
stolen	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
their	O
boy	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
that	O
therefore	O
I	O
pretended	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DANIEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
boy	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
somebody	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
or	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
raffled	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
publick-house	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
cleaning	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
's	O
name	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
Plastrerer	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
into	O
my	O
possession	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
;	O
the	O
son	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
M'FARSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
ten	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
corresponds	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ARCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
be	O
said	O
his	O
son	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
mud	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Thames	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
wheels	O
were	O
rusty	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chain	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dropping	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
suppose	O
some	O
poor	O
fellow	O
had	O
fallen	O
overboard	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
worth	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
have	O
his	O
advice	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
repaired	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
repairing	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
customer	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
afterwards	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRADSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
told	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
purchase	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
before	O
she	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
publick-house	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
expected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
publican	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
certain	O
of	O
the	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
only	O
wanted	O
her	O
property	O
again	O
.	O
Instead	O
of	O
bringing	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
abused	O
her	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
.	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
that	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
that	O
repaired	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
summoned	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
over-ruled	O
.	O
Archer	O
.	O
Will	O
your	O
lordship	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
Bradshaw	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
woman	O
say	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
152.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BALLARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
January	O
31st	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
COULSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
sadler	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
some	O
where	O
near	O
Clare-market	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
beyond	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
dial	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
cypher	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
till	O
last	O
Friday	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
house	O
between	O
Chancery-lane	O
and	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
not	O
did	O
I	O
between	O
those	O
places	O
discover	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
touch	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
brush	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
EVERITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
watch	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
eight	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
pledged	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
dial	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
hand-bill	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
watch	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
I	O
discovered	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
real	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
positive	O
his	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
One	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
advertised	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WHITEHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
not	O
above	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
days	O
ago	O
,	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
string	O
.	O
Whether	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
poor	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
else	O
I	O
can	O
call	O
myself	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
bread	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
husband	O
gets	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
blessed	O
be	O
God	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement's-lane	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
.	O
TERESIA	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GUNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
Lord	O
Petre	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
foot	O
guard	O
s	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
his	O
duty	O
in	O
every	O
thing	O
according	O
to	O
order	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
born	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
The	O
woman	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
him	O
was	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
not	O
an	O
hour	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Gunn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
here	O
yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
runners	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
!	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
you	O
will	O
clear	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
place	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Coulson	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
She	O
declared	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
in	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
153.	O
HUGH	B-pers
O'NEAL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Micheal	B-pers
Hinde	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13th	O
.	O
MICHEAL	B-pers
HINDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
after	O
dark	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
for	O
fear	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
lost	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bradshaw	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRADSHAW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cummings	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
used	O
my	O
shop	O
three	O
years	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
ballast-heaver	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
buckles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
occasionally	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
Hinde	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
serve	O
his	O
majesty	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Hinde	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
Hinde	O
left	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
chest	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
three	O
days	O
and	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
box	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
people	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
154.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GOODERICK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
and	O
breaking	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
two	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Society	B-pers
of	I-pers
New-Inn	I-pers
,	O
January	O
22d	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAGGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
steward	O
of	O
the	O
Society	O
of	O
New-Inn	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
iron	O
bars	O
were	O
ripped	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
stone	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
5	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
New-Inn	I-place
.	O
The	O
persons	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
are	O
the	O
trustees	O
of	O
a	O
long	O
term	O
of	O
three	O
hundred	O
years	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
granted	O
to	O
that	O
society	O
by	O
the	O
Middle	O
Temple	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
the	O
freehold	O
of	O
New-Inn	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
porter	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
pole	O
at	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
accused	O
with	O
wrenching	O
the	O
bars	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
pole	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
bars	O
were	O
ripped	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
instrument	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
a	O
paddock	O
,	O
or	O
long	O
pole	O
about	O
six	O
feet	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
scaffoldings	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
FELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
pole	O
between	O
the	O
curb	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
the	O
bars	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
with	O
that	O
pole	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bannister	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bannister	O
's	O
men	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
bars	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
was	O
ripped	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
loosened	O
;	O
thereupon	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WINTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
Some	O
bars	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
this	O
window	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
these	O
bars	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
had	O
been	O
replaced	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
Inn	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
safe	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STEPHENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mason	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
my	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
stone-work	O
,	O
in	O
replacing	O
those	O
two	O
bars	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bannister	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
objectionable	O
in	O
his	O
behaviour	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
smith	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
replaceing	O
the	O
bars	O
,	O
which	O
before	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
assisted	O
in	O
doing	O
the	O
work	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Wych-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
gate	O
upon	O
a	O
pressing	O
occasion	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
thought	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
good	O
woman	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
The	O
porter	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cathed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
bar	O
away	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
hauled	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
their	O
oath	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
pulled	O
the	O
bar	O
up	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
clear	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
here	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
PERRYN	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
155.	O
SOLOMON	B-pers
GABRIEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Marseilles	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
five	O
checked	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Fasey	I-pers
,	O
October	O
24th	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
]	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRADY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
my	O
mother	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
can	O
tell	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
mother	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
King	O
Edward's-street	O
,	O
Coverley's-fields	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
bell	O
;	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
ring	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
linen	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
wait	O
about	O
there	O
till	O
either	O
me	O
or	O
my	O
mother	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
London	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
man	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
wondered	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
stay	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
boy	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
mother	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
done	O
sooner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
where	O
he	O
must	O
call	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
safe	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
save	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
those	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
like	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
court	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
JENNY	B-pers
BRADY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
him	O
which	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
SOPHIA	B-pers
CHAMBERLAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
down	O
Jewry-street	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
gown	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
among	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
who	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
mend	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
LEVY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gabriel	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dear	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
word	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
his	O
wife	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
shillings	O
change	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
mantua-maker	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
directly	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
apprentice	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
mantua-maker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
mantua-maker	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
brought	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
,	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brady	O
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
having	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Fasey	O
respecting	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
had	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Fasey	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
mantua-maker	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
you	O
went	O
with	O
to	O
have	O
this	O
matter	O
settled	O
?	O
-	O
Solomon	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
sent	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
five	O
guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
make	O
an	O
application	O
to	O
2	O
Mrs.	O
Neiden	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
desire	O
Mrs.	O
Neiden	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
desired	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
desire	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
persuaded	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
,	O
or	O
on	O
what	O
business	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Neiden	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
then	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
you	O
bought	O
these	O
clothes	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Neiden	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
's	O
to	O
desire	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
that	O
these	O
clothes	O
were	O
not	O
obtained	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
,	O
but	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
is	O
not	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
-	O
Who	O
persuaded	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Solomon	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
you	O
must	O
suspect	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
stolen	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
offer	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
knows	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
To	O
Sophia	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
gown	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
that	O
was	O
washed	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
FASEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
petticoat	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
's	O
gown	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
Levy	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
carried	O
a	O
gown	O
to	O
the	O
mantua-maker	O
's	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
her	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
her	O
telling	O
you	O
who	O
she	O
bought	O
these	O
goods	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
NEIDEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
Friday	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
affair	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
and	O
said	O
why	O
did	O
she	O
first	O
say	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
without	O
any	O
application	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
your	O
going	O
;	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
affair	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
She	O
wanted	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
place	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
who	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Fasey	O
said	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Gabriel	I-pers
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
gentleman	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
over	O
and	O
above	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
matter	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
without	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
LYONS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
been	O
at	O
Aylesbury	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
from	O
the	O
twenty	O
second	O
to	O
the	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Aylesbury	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-second	O
of	O
October	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
and	O
Friday	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
sabbath	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
and	O
slept	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
JUDAH	B-pers
LEVY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Holborn	O
after	O
a	O
parcel	O
that	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
Aylesbury	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
October	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
memory	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
parcel	O
from	O
the	O
Bull	O
on	O
Monday	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gabriel	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
parcel	O
you	O
want	O
and	O
pulled	O
fourteen	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
GIBSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
;	O
I	O
serve	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
bread	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
sells	O
bread	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
every	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
his	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
22d	O
to	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
generally	O
see	O
him	O
every	O
day	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
occasionally	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
bread	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
18th	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
punctual	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
156.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HORSLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Anne	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hannams	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
seven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
six	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anne	O
,	O
December	O
8th	O
.	O
ANNE	B-pers
HANNAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Houndsditch	B-place
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
upon	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
containing	O
seven	O
shirts	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
somebody	O
came	O
behind	O
with	O
his	O
full	O
force	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
another	O
who	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
bundle	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
up	O
your	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
partly	O
saw	O
the	O
statue	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
him	O
nor	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
SAKEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
lottery-office	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
four	O
fellows	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Binns	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnsley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Connolly	I-pers
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Coming	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
lottery	O
office	O
I	O
met	O
Anne	B-pers
Hannams	I-pers
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
th	O
e	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Woolpack-alley	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Connolly	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
Bird	O
and	O
Binns	O
ran	O
down	O
another	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Connolly	O
down	O
Woolpack-alley	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Bird	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
discourse	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
last	O
sessions	O
Bird	O
knocked	O
the	O
woman	O
down	O
and	O
Binns	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Binns	O
did	O
not	O
knock	O
the	O
woman	O
down	O
,	O
nor	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Levi	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
apprehended	O
them	O
every	O
one	O
.	O
LEVI	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eight	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Woolpack-alley	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
-	O
BARBER	O
sworn	O
.	O
Moses	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
Levi	O
and	O
I	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
city	O
marshal	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
serve	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
157.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LAVAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1st	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JARVIS	I-pers
WHITEHEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
patrol	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
iron	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
DUNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
patrol	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
iron	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
,	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Russell	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
iron	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sedgwick	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
iron	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Robert	B-pers
Sedgwick	I-pers
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
his	O
servant	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
under	O
a	O
gateway	O
in	O
Cateaton-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
that	O
iron	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
158.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MILLION	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
hammer-cloth	O
for	O
coach	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
coach	O
at	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
Isaacs	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
hammer-cloth	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
mercy	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
mention	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
?	O
-	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
at	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
hammer-cloth	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
mercy	O
promised	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
To	O
West	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
understand	O
my	O
question	O
?	O
did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
any	O
mercy	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
friends	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
yet	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
159	O
,	O
160.	O
JACOB	B-pers
DANIEL	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LEVI	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
duty	O
some	O
times	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
station	O
to	O
examine	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
a	O
waterman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
chaps	O
following	O
me	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
offered	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
trap	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
up	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
seeing	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
seised	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Daniel	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Daniel	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
DANIEL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
a	O
gateway	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
being	O
nothing	O
to	O
affect	O
Levi	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
DANIEL	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
LEVI	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Military/Naval	O
duty	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
161.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NORMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Susannah	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Class	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
eleven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
February	O
5th	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
CLASS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
Mark-lane	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Hart-street	I-place
,	O
of	O
eleven	O
shirts	O
,	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
stock	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
linen	O
home	O
.	O
Whose	O
linen	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
married	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
him	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Can	O
you	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
circumstances	O
attending	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
was	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
followed	O
me	O
some	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
the	O
bundle	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
hit	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
twisted	O
the	O
bundle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Hart-street	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
you	O
some	O
way	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
steps	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
till	O
he	O
hit	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
a	O
tallow-chandler	O
's	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hart-street	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
murther	O
and	O
thieves	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
my	O
bundle	O
into	O
the	O
highway	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
bulk	O
,	O
and	O
fainted	O
away	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
You	O
recovered	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
bundle	O
up	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
might	O
it	O
be	O
till	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
seven	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
You	O
fainted	O
away	O
;	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
light	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
light	O
at	O
the	O
tallow-chandler	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Hart-street	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
took	O
this	O
bundle	O
off	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HAYWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Crutched	O
Friars	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Seething-lane	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
walked	O
ten	O
yards	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
short	O
round	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
bundle	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
continued	O
running	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
close	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
opposite	O
Savage-gardens	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
discharged	O
himself	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
recovered	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
SHIRLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Crutched-friars	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
stepped	O
into	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
opposite	O
Savage-gardens	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
stop	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eleven	O
shirts	O
,	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stock	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Class	I-pers
,	O
on	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London-street	O
,	O
which	O
leads	O
into	O
Crutched-friars	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brother	O
officer	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
saving	O
,	O
thank	O
God	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
bundle	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
immediately	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
To	O
Class	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
this	O
package	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
This	O
gentleman	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
'	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
man	O
not	O
to	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WOODGAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
borne	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
it	O
impeached	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
-	O
HILLYER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
tractable	O
sober	O
lad	O
,	O
dutiful	O
to	O
his	O
parents	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Widegate-street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
plasterer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
several	O
jobs	O
within	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
-	O
KENNETT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
borne	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
instrious	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GRIFFIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Widegate-street	O
,	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
better	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
imputation	O
on	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
sometimes	O
did	O
a	O
job	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
fronted	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
great	O
property	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
He	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ATLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
his	O
birth	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
above	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GREEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
lad	O
going	O
on	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
indeed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
about	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAUGH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
thirteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
great	O
trust	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
and	O
great	O
delight	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
ANOTHER	O
WITNESS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
been	O
very	O
assiduous	O
in	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
character	O
goes	O
he	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
established	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
witnesses	O
.	O
A	O
witness	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
as	O
many	O
more	O
as	O
have	O
been	O
examined	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
-	O
BOTT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
almost	O
daily	O
at	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FORREST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
understood	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lad	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
and	O
industrious	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
his	O
father	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
surmise	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
DEATH	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
BARON	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
162	O
,	O
163.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOPPY	I-pers
and	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
gallons	O
of	O
lamp	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
above	O
oil	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
February	O
6th	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tin-plate-worker	O
and	O
lamp	O
lighter	O
in	O
White	B-place
Cross	I-place
Street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
my	O
servant	O
s.	O
I	O
employed	O
them	O
to	O
light	O
lamps	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
them	O
their	O
wages	O
,	O
Hoppy	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
thief	O
to	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
May	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
threatnings	O
of	O
his	O
fellow	O
servants	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
threatened	O
to	O
throw	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
ladder	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
oil	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
sometimes	O
a	O
pint	O
,	O
sometimes	O
a	O
quart	O
;	O
sometimes	O
more	O
sometime	O
less	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
fellow	O
servants	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
two	O
quarts	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
at	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
quart	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
off	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
life	O
was	O
uneasy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
,	O
where	O
Martin	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
oil	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
Martin	O
had	O
a	O
locker	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
gallons	O
of	O
oil	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Martin	O
's	O
room	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Martin	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
oil	O
below	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
oil	O
below	O
is	O
your	O
property	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Hoppy	O
.	O
Was	O
Hoppy	O
present	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
That	O
oil	O
you	O
found	O
below	O
was	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
oil	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Hoppy	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Hoppy	O
made	O
a	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
oil	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
ever	O
since	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Martin	O
for	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
quart	O
beer	O
measure	O
.	O
Was	O
Martin	O
present	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Martin	O
acknowledged	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
Hoppy	O
.	O
Did	O
Martin	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
if	O
from	O
Hoppy	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
