TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1780	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIRST	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
.	O
Sir	O
WATKIN	B-pers
LEWES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
MDCCLXXX	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WATKIN	B-pers
LEWES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
The	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
ADAIR	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Eleazar	B-pers
Chater	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wooton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
William	B-pers
Portal	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Vaughanbrooks	I-pers
John	B-pers
Elliott	I-pers
William	B-pers
Brandon	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Gall	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Crabb	I-pers
Lloyd	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Dodd	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
George	B-pers
Herbst	I-pers
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
John	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
Giles	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
James	B-pers
Dowler	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
William	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brownley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lepard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tongue	I-pers
James	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Paybody	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Roe	B-pers
Rotheram	I-pers
1	O
,	O
2.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
HAMBLEN	I-pers
and	O
HAYES	B-pers
GILES	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cane	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
informed	O
the	O
court	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
3.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
DANIEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LANE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hillingdon	O
,	O
near	O
Uxbridge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
servant	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
mile-stones	O
at	O
Shepherd's-Bush	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
stopped	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
alone	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
were	O
,	O
come	O
sir	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
let	O
the	O
glass	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
again	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
hand	O
or	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
purse	O
with	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
pistol	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
presented	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
person	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
immediately	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
alarmed	O
every	O
person	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
people	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
both	O
on	O
foot	O
and	O
horseback	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
very	O
few	O
minutes	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
meet	O
or	O
overtake	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
met	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
postillion	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
door	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
such	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
[	O
a	O
lightish	O
colour	O
]	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
disguise	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
clear	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observations	O
of	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
his	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
long	O
enough	O
with	O
you	O
and	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
positively	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
about	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
,	O
very	O
clear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
TOBIAS	B-pers
PLEASANT	I-pers
(	O
a	O
negro	O
)	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
thirty-two	O
years	O
last	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
his	O
carriage	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
it	O
happen	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
what	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
possibly	O
guess	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Shepherd's-Bush	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
very	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
bay	O
mare	O
:	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
post	O
chaise	O
boy	O
stop	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
would	O
not	O
stop	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
waved	O
his	O
pistol	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
stop	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
door	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
commit	O
a	O
rash	O
action	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
pistol	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
master	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
purse	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
leaned	O
forward	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
!	O
When	O
my	O
master	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
his	O
purse	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
across	O
his	O
thigh	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
money	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
offered	O
him	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
French-horn	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
fire-arms	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
presented	O
his	O
pistol	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
footpace	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
his	O
eye	O
upon	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
looked	O
every	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
chiefly	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
imagined	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
fire-arms	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
loose	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
my	O
master	O
has	O
now	O
on	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
him	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Positively	O
sure	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
he	O
read	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
bird	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
net	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
I	O
begged	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
somebody	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
three	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directly	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
waited	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
there	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
before	O
four	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
;	O
life	O
is	O
sweet	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
could	O
save	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
flapped	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
which	O
hung	O
down	O
to	O
your	O
heels	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
under	O
clothes	O
,	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
covered	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
laying	O
the	O
purse	O
across	O
his	O
thigh	O
,	O
and	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
purse	O
he	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
old	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
reply	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
chaise	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
Mr.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Gunnersbury	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
chaise	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
servant	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Gravel-pits	O
and	O
Shepherd's-Bush	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
waved	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
highwayman	O
.	O
I	O
passed	O
on	O
,	O
going	O
very	O
fast	O
to	O
Shepherd's-Bush	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
chaise	O
turn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Action	O
road	O
for	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
riding	O
across	O
the	O
green	O
,	O
which	O
gentlemen	O
frequently	O
do	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
round	O
,	O
he	O
gallopped	O
pretty	O
fast	O
across	O
the	O
green	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
ditch	O
upon	O
the	O
causeway	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
before	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
short	O
and	O
stopped	O
that	O
chaise	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
black	O
servant	O
had	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
from	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
stopped	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
with	O
the	O
chaise	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
left	O
that	O
chaise	O
,	O
he	O
walked	O
his	O
horse	O
on	O
into	O
the	O
Action	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
;	O
began	O
to	O
gallop	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
put	O
n	O
horse	O
into	O
a	O
gallop	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
again	O
and	O
leaped	O
over	O
the	O
ditch	O
upon	O
the	O
green	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Gravelpits	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
rode	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
causeway	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
chaise	O
towards	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
horse	O
.	O
Just	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
came	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Hurd	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
robbed	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
pursue	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
rode	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
passed	O
the	O
chaise	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
stop	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
servant	O
as	O
I	O
rode	O
by	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
that	O
man	O
robbed	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
man	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
down	O
Brook-green	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
side	O
of	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
away	O
for	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
pursuing	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
certainly	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
man	O
is	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
''	O
?	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
no	O
assistance	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
through	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
Instead	O
of	O
going	O
the	O
great	O
road	O
through	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
towards	O
the	O
water-side	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
water-side	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
assistance	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
very	O
narrow	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
supposing	O
he	O
had	O
fire-arms	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
horse	O
about	O
and	O
rode	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
keep	O
before	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
broad-way	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
expected	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
assistance	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
lane	O
near	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
that	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
again	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
pretty	O
close	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
got	O
through	O
that	O
lane	O
into	O
the	O
great	O
road	O
,	O
some	O
people	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
They	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
a	O
powder	O
horn	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
balls	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
him	O
any	O
further	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
light	O
surtout	O
coat	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
a	O
bay	O
mare	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
high	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
you	O
passed	O
the	O
chaise	O
with	O
the	O
black	O
behind	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
met	O
that	O
chaise	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
more	O
than	O
twenty-five	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
passed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
miles	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
a	O
sharp	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
presented	O
any	O
pistol	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
draw	O
his	O
pistol	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
DAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Queen's-Arms	O
,	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pursued	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
as	O
the	O
highwayman	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
rode	O
in	O
a	O
furious	O
manner	O
over	O
the	O
stones	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
highwayman	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
seen	O
him	O
rob	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
mounted	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
overtake	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
take	O
towards	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
double	O
and	O
come	O
round	O
Angel-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Angel-lane	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
The	O
lane	O
is	O
very	O
narrow	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
little	O
out	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
snatched	O
his	O
bridle	O
and	O
stopped	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
pass	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
not	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
came	O
up	O
almost	O
the	O
instant	O
I	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
up	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
seised	O
his	O
bridle	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
at	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
at	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
felt	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
small	O
screw-barrel	O
pistol	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
bag	O
with	O
balls	O
and	O
a	O
powder-horn	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
likewise	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Miller	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
was	O
ill	O
;	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
horse	O
was	O
he	O
mounted	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
bay	O
mare	O
with	O
a	O
switch	O
tail	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
high	O
,	O
almost	O
blind	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
flapped	O
round	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
riding	O
dress	O
or	O
jacket	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
gloves	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
sweat	O
.	O
The	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
beadle	O
let	O
his	O
hands	O
go	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
gloves	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
clinched	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
opening	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
purse	O
with	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
pistol	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
pistol	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
purse	O
the	O
prisoner	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
one	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
present	O
from	O
a	O
lady	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MEREDITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
highwayman	O
gone	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Angel-lane	O
I	O
should	O
meet	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
overtook	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
his	O
cuff	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
some	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
some	O
balls	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
powder-horn	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
)	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
servant	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
office	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
a	O
witness	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
an	O
ostler	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
BARON	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
4.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
groat	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-three	O
medals	O
,	O
value	O
23	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
Cocks	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
September	O
1st	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SUMMERS	I-pers
COCKS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
box	O
and	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
copper	O
and	O
silver	O
coins	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Downing-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
a	O
message	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
silver	O
coins	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
coins	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
hardware	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
months	O
ago	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
own	O
property	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
grandmother	O
left	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
sore	O
eye	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hand-bill	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Lord	O
Aylesbury	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
thousand	O
pound	O
's	O
worth	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lord	O
Aylesbury	O
's	O
and	O
showed	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
person	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
these	O
twenty-three	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
curious	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
own	O
property	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
hand-bill	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
lord	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
silver	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
more	O
pocket-pieces	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
silver	O
box	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Cocks	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pocket-pieces	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
.	O
Moses	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Lord	O
Aylesbury	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
his	O
Lordship	O
was	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
voluntarily	O
confessed	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cocks	O
,	O
the	O
banker	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
this	O
information	O
Mr.	O
Cocks	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
Henry	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
silver	O
box	O
.	O
Imp	O
.	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
5.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ANDREWS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pounds	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
printed	O
books	O
bound	O
in	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Noton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Noton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18th	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
NOTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Noton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
some	O
tea	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
bag	O
,	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
staircase	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
leading	O
to	O
some	O
warehouses	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
again	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
At	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
we	O
paid	O
our	O
men	O
their	O
wages	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
paid	O
them	O
we	O
shut	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
searched	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
package	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
tea	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
belief	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
raisins	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
lodging	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
coffee	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
books	O
of	O
small	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penknife	O
;	O
the	O
penknife	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
book	O
was	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
your	O
own	O
separate	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
separate	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
partnership	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
our	O
separate	O
property	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Upwards	O
of	O
five	O
years	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
tea	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
possible	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
book	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
printed	O
book	O
of	O
accounts	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
6.	O
JANE	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
two	O
half-crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
November	O
the	O
8th	O
ESTHER	B-pers
STEWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
My	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
of	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
opposite	O
the	O
Mansion-house	B-place
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
PARK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
cornmarket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
crowd	O
standing	O
opposite	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
through	O
the	O
crowd	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
curiosity	O
to	O
stop	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Steward	O
was	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
second	O
door	O
from	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
court	O
almost	O
facing	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
near	O
her	O
but	O
two	O
little	O
boys	O
,	O
one	O
I	O
understand	O
is	O
her	O
son	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
crowd	O
within	O
about	O
a	O
door	O
of	O
Mildred-street	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
round	O
the	O
people	O
's	O
pockets	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
standing	O
.	O
Where	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Steward	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
kirb-stone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
little	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
her	O
working	O
into	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
stood	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
support	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
an	O
hackney-coach	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
her	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
coach	O
went	O
by	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
opportunity	O
would	O
permit	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
feel	O
if	O
your	O
pocket	O
is	O
not	O
picked	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
Exactly	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
to	O
obstruct	O
my	O
fight	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
clear	O
to	O
me	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
whether	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
pocket	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
if	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
?	O
She	O
was	O
frightened	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
answer	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
dropped	O
;	O
she	O
recovered	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
boy	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
up	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
by	O
sight	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
examined	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
attack	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
coach	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
.	O
To	O
Steward	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
recover	O
the	O
money	O
or	O
find	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
pocket	O
cut	O
off	O
or	O
the	O
money	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
picked	O
out	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
STEWARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
came	O
over	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
near	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
accused	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
honourable	O
court	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
7.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
MAPPE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
ingots	O
of	O
tin	O
27	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kinman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Kinman	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9th	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
KINMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
foundery	O
business	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
William	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
carter	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
information	O
he	O
had	O
frequent	O
meetings	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
on	O
Westminster-bridge	O
,	O
who	O
received	O
tin	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
led	O
us	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
an	O
ingot	O
of	O
tin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
two	O
shops	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
;	O
the	O
cart	O
is	O
kept	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
the	O
ingot	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
lay	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
bag	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
stopped	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
detect	O
the	O
receiver	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
lost	O
above	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
piece	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
afterwards	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
tin	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
eight	O
pence	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kinman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
followed	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
tin	O
which	O
my	O
master	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
my	O
master	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
your	O
master	O
ordered	O
you	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
down	O
the	O
ditch	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
apprehensive	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
person	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
stop	O
likewise	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
nearer	O
to	O
the	O
tollhouse	O
at	O
Black-friars-bridge	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stop	O
,	O
seeming	O
determined	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
was	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
crossed	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bridge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
threw	O
this	O
piece	O
over	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
waterman	O
's	O
boy	O
at	O
low	O
water	O
mark	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
Temple-bar	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
heavy	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
stopped	O
at	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
avoid	O
coming	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
into	O
discourse	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
glove	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
imagining	O
he	O
meant	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
piece	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
ingot	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Forbes	O
's	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
deals	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Forbes	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
that	O
tin	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
such	O
tin	O
.	O
Any	O
person	O
who	O
deals	O
with	O
Forbes	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
may	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
metal	O
for	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
7.	O
MARY	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
ELIZABETH	I-pers
CARPENTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hebden	I-pers
,	O
October	O
12	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HEBDEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
all	O
work	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
story	O
of	O
her	O
distress	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Essex	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
great	O
inconvenience	O
and	O
expence	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
representation	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
without	O
a	O
character	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
dinner	O
was	O
over	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
and	O
eight	O
spoons	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
at	O
dinner	O
into	O
the	O
wash-house	O
to	O
clean	O
;	O
having	O
done	O
so	O
she	O
found	O
some	O
opportunity	O
of	O
slipping	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
bonnet	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
and	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
one	O
Henley	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
brought	O
home	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
-	O
HENLEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
these	O
five	O
spoons	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
,	O
)	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
who	O
the	O
spoons	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
upon	O
the	O
spoons	O
;	O
she	O
described	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
spoons	O
pledged	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
secured	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
confess	O
by	O
my	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
likely	O
the	O
court	O
would	O
be	O
more	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
give	O
in	O
evidence	O
any	O
thing	O
she	O
said	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
promise	O
as	O
that	O
being	O
made	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
George	B-pers
Whitby	I-pers
another	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
at	O
his	O
shop	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
herself	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
these	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
-	O
Worthy	O
produced	O
a	O
tankard	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
circumstance	O
.	O
Another	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
another	O
spoon	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
deposed	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
their	O
different	O
shops	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
spoons	O
so	O
produced	O
were	O
proved	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Hebden	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
seven	O
months	O
gone	O
with	O
child	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imp	O
.	O
12	O
Months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
9.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
BLAKEY	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COLOURS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jeffreys	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
ten	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
cloth	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Jeffreys	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JEFFREYS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Battle-Bridge	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
my	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
(	O
indeed	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
that	O
room	O
)	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
cut	O
down	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
casement	O
could	O
be	O
opened	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
shut	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
shutters	O
to	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
opened	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
on	O
the	O
line	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JEFFREYS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
my	O
child	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
school	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
was	O
fastened	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
low	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
dangerous	O
situation	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
that	O
morning	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Litchfield	O
's	O
across	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Blakey	O
under	O
our	O
window	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
shut	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
immediately	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
help	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
are	O
Blakey	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
accomplice	O
was	O
taken	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
open	O
and	O
a	O
pane	O
broke	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
clothes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
worn	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
people	O
lurk	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
your	O
clothes	O
?	O
-	O
Ten	O
shillings	O
at	O
least	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DINMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
noon	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
Blakey	O
swore	O
most	O
bitterly	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
only	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
burn	O
it	O
and	O
her	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
REDGRAVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Blakey	O
say	O
what	O
Dinmore	O
has	O
related	O
;	O
they	O
each	O
charged	O
the	O
other	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
with	O
having	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HACKET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
George	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
the	O
accomplice	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
birds	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
house	O
empty	O
;	O
we	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
cut	O
the	O
lead	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
knife	O
I	O
had	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
then	O
Blakey	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
and	O
Colours	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
petticoat	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
on	O
the	O
lines	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
first	O
to	O
Blakey	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
Blakey	O
gave	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
coming	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
is	O
so	O
low	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
easily	O
get	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
first	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
empty	O
.	O
(	O
Colours	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Blakey	O
called	O
his	O
mother	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NIXON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
White	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
housekeeper	O
in	O
Liquorpond-street	B-place
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
girl	O
and	O
boy	O
servants	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rumbling	O
noise	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
partition	O
that	O
goes	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
boards	O
were	O
wrenched	O
off	O
that	O
parted	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
lumber	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
where	O
the	O
boards	O
were	O
wrenched	O
off	O
and	O
saw	O
an	O
hat	O
lying	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
boys	O
to	O
bring	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
the	O
neighbours	O
were	O
alarmed	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
cellars	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
coal	O
cellar	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
piled	O
up	O
together	O
like	O
a	O
dog	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
accomplices	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
buggered	O
if	O
he	O
impeached	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
two	O
hours	O
longer	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
by	O
wrenching	O
up	O
the	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
mark	O
of	O
violence	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
the	O
slap	O
was	O
shut	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
slap	O
and	O
two	O
folding	O
doors	O
with	O
a	O
bar	O
across	O
,	O
the	O
dog	O
of	O
the	O
slap	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
bent	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
before	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
easy	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
they	O
wrenched	O
down	O
a	O
board	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
cellar	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
PORTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
Mr.	O
White	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Robinson	B-pers
the	O
soldier	O
pull	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
the	O
partition	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
sliding-door	O
that	O
has	O
a	O
communication	O
with	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
turned	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
where	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
cellar	O
open	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
there	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
11.	O
JOSHUA	B-pers
CADDIE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Newstead	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
stature	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
NEWSTEAD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rutland-court	B-place
,	I-place
Glasshouse-yard	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
child	O
said	O
my	O
bell	O
rang	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
think	O
my	O
bell	O
rings	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
double-locked	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
the	O
bell	O
rang	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
rushed	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Caddie	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Newbond	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
person	O
lived	O
here	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
person	O
wanted	O
him	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Argyle	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
directly	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
picklock	O
keys	O
,	O
a	O
crow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bag	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
light	O
when	O
you	O
held	O
this	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
actually	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
recovered	O
from	O
your	O
fright	O
did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
observed	O
any	O
mark	O
of	O
violence	O
upon	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
got	O
open	O
with	O
the	O
picklock	O
keys	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
daughter	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Argyle	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
place	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
attempt	O
to	O
escape	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
left	O
alone	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
that	O
you	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
lecture	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
double-locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
bell	O
you	O
heard	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
opens	O
the	O
door	O
it	O
gives	O
the	O
alarm	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ARGYLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Newstead	O
called	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
first	O
and	O
light	O
her	O
lamp	O
and	O
double-lock	O
her	O
door	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
advised	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
lamp	O
and	O
double-lock	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
at	O
tea	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
my	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
bell	O
rings	O
,	O
somebody	O
is	O
going	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
that	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
here	O
?	O
We	O
all	O
listened	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
bell	O
ring	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
opened	O
our	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
door	O
is	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
shout	O
man	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
feet	O
ten	O
inches	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
She	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Newbond	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
sidled	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
.	O
I	O
seised	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
might	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
brown	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
five	O
picklock	O
keys	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
him	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TRAFFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
five	O
picklock	O
keys	O
,	O
this	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
this	O
court	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
necessary	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
this	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
afterwards	O
this	O
man	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
sir	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
an	O
hair	O
of	O
your	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
jail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
swore	O
her	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
Now	O
she	O
swears	O
she	O
has	O
lost	O
nothing	O
.	O
To	O
Argyle	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
necessary	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
LANGFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
baby	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
paper	O
hanger	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LANGFORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
things	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
brought	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
militia	O
once	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
keys	O
were	O
tried	O
and	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
To	O
Trafford	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
keys	O
tried	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
tried	O
at	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
To	O
Argyle	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
try	O
these	O
keys	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
lock	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
12.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LUCAS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
pincers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pegging	O
awls	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winns	I-pers
,	O
November	O
15	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WINNS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cobler	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
a	O
stall	O
I	O
keep	O
in	O
Lemon-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman	I-place
's	I-place
fields	I-place
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
forced	O
off	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
screw	O
lock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
work	O
till	O
near	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
over	O
night	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
double	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
lay	O
within	O
the	O
stall	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
my	O
shoes	O
except	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
property	O
at	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pinchers	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
Lucas	O
and	O
the	O
accomplice	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
confessed	O
who	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
confession	O
:	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RICHES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrole	O
of	O
Christ	O
Church	O
parish	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
three	O
other	O
patroles	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
White	O
Row	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
under	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
some	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Lucas	O
and	O
Davis	O
strove	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
escape	O
backwards	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
stopped	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
Lucas	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
confined	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
granted	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
we	O
found	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
shoe	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pinchers	O
and	O
an	O
awl	O
in	O
his	O
work	O
shop	O
underneath	O
the	O
bellows	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
smith	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
pair	O
upon	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Winns	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
with	O
Lucas	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
cobler	O
's	O
stall	O
in	O
Lemon-street	O
;	O
Lucas	O
picked	O
the	O
lock	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
intention	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
he	O
handed	O
me	O
over	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
filled	O
his	O
own	O
apron	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
more	O
shoes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pinchers	O
.	O
Riches	O
.	O
The	O
great	O
coat	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
To	O
Davis	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
knowledge	O
of	O
his	O
intent	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Lucas	B-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
the	O
lock	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
mostly	O
used	O
was	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
lock	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
men	O
took	O
us	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
the	O
stall	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
shoes	O
were	O
left	O
by	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
till	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
w.	O
and	O
imp	O
.	O
6	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
13.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BENNET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
Mr.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
phaeton	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
it	O
rained	O
very	O
hard	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
Kilburn-wells	O
for	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
phaeton	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Kilburn-wells	B-place
,	O
two	O
highwaymen	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
horse	O
back	O
;	O
one	O
came	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
my	O
phaeton	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
my	O
servant	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
sat	O
on	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
phaeton	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
man	O
servant	O
attending	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
man	O
servant	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
tucked	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
robbed	O
my	O
servant	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
observations	O
upon	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rode	O
a	O
good	O
looking	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
white	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
rather	O
a	O
low	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
and	O
the	O
circumstances	O
attending	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bond	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
shewn	O
another	O
man	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
ground	O
of	O
your	O
suspicion	O
?	O
-	O
His	O
person	O
and	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
robbery	O
in	O
committing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pretty	O
quick	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
make	O
haste	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
much	O
conversation	O
passed	O
?	O
-	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
``	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
watch	O
``	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
family	O
``	O
watch	O
,	O
''	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
and	O
was	O
rather	O
in	O
spirits	O
and	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
them	O
pretty	O
boldly	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
refused	O
to	O
return	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
conversation	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
conversation	O
was	O
first	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
head	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
phaeton	O
;	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
conversation	O
you	O
had	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
give	O
me	O
time	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
come	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
prate	O
;	O
they	O
talked	O
in	O
that	O
stile	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
advertised	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
phaeton	O
with	O
him	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
reach	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
me	O
and	O
rob	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
the	O
robbery	O
in	O
being	O
committed	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
an	O
attack	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
put	O
you	O
into	O
confusion	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
frightened	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
possess	O
yourself	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
you	O
only	O
saw	O
him	O
for	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
on	O
horseback	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
at	O
Kilburn-wells	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
at	O
Kilburn-wells	O
between	O
a	O
quarter	O
and	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
with	O
another	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
they	O
stood	O
under	O
the	O
trees	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
weather	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
front	O
room	O
which	O
looked	O
towards	O
those	O
trees	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
particular	O
observations	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
rained	O
prodigious	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wondered	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
their	O
horses	O
?	O
-	O
Both	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
bay	O
horses	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
person	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
phaeton	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
hesitate	O
,	O
but	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
purse	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
ask	O
;	O
do	O
n't	O
hesitate	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hold	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
hesitate	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
pistol	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
held	O
his	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
pistol	O
was	O
held	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
withdraw	O
his	O
pistol	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
servant	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
about	O
me	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
further	O
to	O
relate	O
respecting	O
the	O
robbing	O
of	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
demanded	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
desiring	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
said	O
``	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
one	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoner	O
repied	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
had	O
pulled	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
at	O
Kilburn-Wells	O
.	O
They	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Daniel	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
the	O
ostler	O
at	O
Kilburn-wells	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
his	O
recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
difficulty	O
of	O
confessing	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
heavy	O
affair	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
14.	O
JEFFERIES	B-pers
HOPLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Frear	I-pers
,	O
November	O
7th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FREAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
chaiseman	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
my	O
boots	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
in	O
the	O
coachhouse	O
.	O
Towards	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
employ	O
the	O
prisoner	O
occasionally	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
next	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
confession	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
my	O
shoes	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
those	O
shoes	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
my	O
foot	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
judgement	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ev	O
er	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
were	O
your	O
shoes	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
shoes	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Mews	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
15.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
HYLETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Winshill	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
November	O
10th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WINSHILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
going	O
to	O
Deptford	O
with	O
a	O
drummer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
us	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
round	O
my	O
waist	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
one	O
George	O
Bacon	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
drummer	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
ourselves	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
change	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
purse	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
took	O
my	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
right-hand	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
right-hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
between	O
her	O
thighs	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
claimed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
robbery	O
against	O
us	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ROVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
purse	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
girl	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
America	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
woman	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
,	O
passed	O
by	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
house	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
sixpence	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
compulsion	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
the	O
drummer	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
bloody	O
liver	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
Rover	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
soldier	O
and	O
the	O
drummer	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
She	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
16.	O
ANN	B-pers
MULLINS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Canks	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
October	O
26th	O
.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
CANKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
from	O
the	B-place
Coach	I-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
,	I-place
Belton-street	I-place
,	I-place
Coal-yard	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
my	O
pots	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lodgers	O
.	O
Upon	O
missing	O
them	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
,	O
in	O
Short's-gardens	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Brownlow-street	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
promises	O
or	O
threatenings	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
Little	O
St.	O
Andrew's-street	O
,	O
and	O
Lumber-court	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
gown	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
AGNES	B-pers
STEEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes-shop	O
in	O
Lumber-court	O
,	O
Seven-Dials	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
court	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
petticoat	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
I	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
at	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
her	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cane	O
with	O
a	O
gilt	O
head	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
cane	O
with	O
an	O
ivory	O
head	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
November	O
13th	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HANKEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
cane-shop	O
in	O
Coventry-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
reading	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
canes	O
rattle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
very	O
genteel	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
canes	O
rattle	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
canes	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
gone	O
a	O
few	O
steps	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
canes	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HIDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
cane	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
farthing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
canes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
this	O
stick-shop	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
sticks	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
any	O
justice	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
MARIA	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
children	O
's	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
children	O
's	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
three	O
children	O
's	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Spickard	I-pers
,	O
October	O
31st	O
.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
SPICKARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Rose-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
several	O
particulars	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Thirteen	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
eleven	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
thread	O
,	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
frocks	O
,	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
apartment	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
legs	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
voluntarily	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
particulars	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
ELISABETH	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
deal	O
she	O
has	O
sworn	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
friend	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
youth	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
twenty	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
seven	O
months	O
gone	O
with	O
child	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
W.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
19.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BEAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Delevitt	I-pers
,	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
DELEVITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
house	O
drying	O
linen	O
.	O
The	O
shop	O
is	O
forward	O
where	O
my	O
husband	O
worked	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
skipping	O
across	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
but	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Upon	O
being	O
taken	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
STEVENSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
dimity	O
night-cap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Allam	I-pers
,	O
November	O
22d	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
ALLAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Allam	I-pers
,	O
I	O
had	O
washed	O
the	O
linen	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
them	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
holding	O
him	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOODLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
a	O
garden	O
which	O
adjoins	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Ormond-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
linen	O
being	O
wet	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
tumbled	O
between	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
stumble	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
near	O
throwing	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
full	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
seised	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
near	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
ready	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
this	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Allam	O
.	O
Afterward	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Foundling-Hospital	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
hat	O
blew	O
over	O
these	O
pales	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
MARY	B-pers
DERBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
seven	O
cloth	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long-acre	B-place
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cloak	O
and	O
coat	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
cloaks	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
cloaks	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
cloaks	O
brought	O
back	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
cloaks	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
even	O
know	O
perhaps	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Beard	O
,	O
a	O
pastry-cook	O
,	O
in	O
Sydney's-alley	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
's	O
parlour	O
when	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Hart-street	O
,	O
Covent	O
garden	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
An	O
hundred	O
or	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
running	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
cloaks	O
.	O
She	O
found	O
somebody	O
was	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
wish	O
to	O
drop	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
six	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
,	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
cloaks	O
hang	O
across	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
to	O
mind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
stolen	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
pursued	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
caught	O
her	O
.	O
One	O
cloak	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
How	O
happened	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
cloaks	O
that	O
hung	O
up	O
hindered	O
my	O
seeing	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Had	O
any	O
person	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
latched	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
you	O
shut	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
latch	O
catch	O
so	O
as	O
never	O
to	O
deceive	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
How	O
large	O
is	O
this	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
large	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
were	O
these	O
things	O
hanging	O
loose	O
about	O
?	O
-	O
These	O
cloaks	O
laid	O
close	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
folded	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
MACKAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Long-acre	O
with	O
my	O
basket	O
of	O
oysters	O
upon	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
across	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
Bird-in-hand	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Long-acre	O
Bagnio	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
and	O
alarmed	O
them	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
backwards	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
(	O
The	O
cloaks	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
prison	O
before	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Long-acre	O
I	O
met	O
that	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
had	O
something	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
her	O
head	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
lies	O
so	O
white	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
stoop	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
basket	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
that	O
parcel	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
bundle	O
they	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
oyster	O
girl	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
DAVID	B-pers
DUCKWORTH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
;	O
my	O
husband	O
lives	O
in	O
Peter-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
us	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
passed	O
as	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
he	O
broke	O
my	O
window	O
open	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
gave	O
his	O
wife	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
At	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
somebody	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
clock	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
where	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
hung	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
six	O
o'clock	O
by	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
washed	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
somebody	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
;	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
short	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
came	O
through	O
another	O
persen	O
's	O
pales	O
into	O
my	O
back	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
two	O
cases	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
