TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
.	O
Sir	O
WATKINLEWES	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORTHAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
MDCCLXXXI	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WATKIN	B-pers
LEWES	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
ADAIR	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
James	B-pers
Shuckford	I-pers
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
James	B-pers
Moffitt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wontner	I-pers
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
William	B-pers
Johnston	I-pers
William	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Carns	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
William	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
John	B-pers
Birchell	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bakewell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Royle	I-pers
*	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
*	O
Francis	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Glassop	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sime	I-pers
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
James	B-pers
Tregent	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
John	B-pers
Maclane	I-pers
David	B-pers
Scale	I-pers
Polling	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
William	B-pers
Potier	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wilshar	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Standage	I-pers
Roger	B-pers
Brackin	I-pers
464.	O
MARY	B-pers
DOOLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
tortoise-shell	O
snuffbox	O
inlaid	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Penton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
August	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
PENTON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
person	O
about	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
towards	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
that	O
person	O
's	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
struck	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
stolen	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
denied	O
.	O
Upon	O
putting	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
my	O
snuff-box	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
stolen	O
my	O
snuff-box	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
her	O
left-hand	O
immediately	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
seized	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
drawn	O
it	O
from	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
other	O
hand	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
shifting	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
right-hand	O
,	O
keeping	O
the	O
other	O
fast	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
drop	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
snuff-box	O
:	O
I	O
kept	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
hackney-coach	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
watch-house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
croud	O
immediately	O
after	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
the	O
lamps	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
perfect	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
myself	O
innocent	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GOULD	O
.	O
465.	O
HENRY	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
half-guinea	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
JEFFERIES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Lady	O
Drake	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
my	O
mistress	O
in	O
the	O
carriage	O
in	O
Bushy	B-place
Park	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
rode	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
purse	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
gave	O
him	O
her	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
is	O
black	O
shagreen	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
purse	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
weapon	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
footman	O
to	O
Lady	O
Drake	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
my	O
mistress	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
carriage-door	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
blow	O
her	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
gave	O
him	O
her	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bushy	O
Park	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
the	O
footman	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
lady	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
with	O
a	O
flapped	O
hat	O
,	O
riding	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
cropped	O
tail	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
through	O
Hampton-gate	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
at	O
Hampton-bridge	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
bridge	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
rode	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
Hampton	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
house	O
into	O
a	O
shed	O
of	O
a	O
public-house	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Smokey-lane	O
:	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
public-house	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
shed	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
horse	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
it	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
the	O
footman	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
headborough	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
headborough	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
purse	O
with	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Neale	O
,	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
to	O
Lady	O
Drake	O
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Lady	O
Drake	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
Edward	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
four	O
years	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Patient	I-pers
two	O
years	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
three-quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
466.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STONEHILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Edward	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
swordstick	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bangs	O
,	O
of	O
Lyon's-Inn	O
,	O
an	O
attorney	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
Battle-bridge	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
the	O
rope-walk	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
persons	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
presented	O
my	O
pistol	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
!	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
more	O
prudent	O
to	O
make	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
keeping	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
,	O
seeing	O
me	O
watchful	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
were	O
fearful	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
two	O
more	O
men	O
started	O
up	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
better	O
to	O
stop	O
:	O
I	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
surrounded	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
my	O
hat	O
over	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
a	O
swordstick	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
exactly	O
remember	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
quitted	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
shilling	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
three	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
those	O
three	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
presented	O
the	O
pistol	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
about	O
the	O
distance	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
rather	O
dark	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
three	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
his	O
hair	O
was	O
curled	O
round	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
size	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
from	O
his	O
voice	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
that	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARPMEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
small	O
serew-barrel	O
pistol	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
across	O
Holborn	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
King's-Head	O
court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
lodgings	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
claimed	O
some	O
clothes	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Bangs	O
's	O
pistol	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
morning	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Carpmeal	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
across	O
Holborn	O
.	O
This	O
pistol	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
467	O
,	O
468.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BLAND	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ticking	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
dimity	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
russel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Aramintha	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
WEBB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rathbone-place	B-place
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
thieves	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
garret-window	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
some	O
thieves	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
ARAMINTHA	O
HOW	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Webb	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
still	O
greater	O
noise	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
some	O
foul	O
linen	O
:	O
the	O
maid	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
neighbours	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
uproar	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
had	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hit	O
a	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
DODD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Howe	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
garret	O
window	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
coming	O
along	O
Rathbone-place	O
,	O
a	O
bundle	O
fell	O
from	O
a	O
house	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
or	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
Capt	O
.	O
Fremantle	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
somebody	O
was	O
a-top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
cieling	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
broke	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
could	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
servant	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
with	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Webb	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HARVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
alarmed	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
!	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
tiles	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
near	O
a	O
trap-door	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
unbolt	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
upon	O
touching	O
the	O
trap-door	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
seized	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
silver	O
spoon	O
sticking	O
out	O
of	O
Bland	O
's	O
breeches-pocket	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
without	O
their	O
hats	O
and	O
shoes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
upon	O
Williams	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
apron	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Webb	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
several	O
articles	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Aramintha	O
How	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
hats	O
,	O
in	O
Rathbone-place	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
back-garret	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
from	O
whence	O
these	O
bundles	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
hats	O
and	O
shoes	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
property	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
between	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
small	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wrapper	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GRAHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bundle	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
leads	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Fremantle	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
several	O
articles	O
were	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
How	O
,	O
Webb	O
,	O
and	O
Dodd	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAMS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Rathbone-place	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
thieves	O
given	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
round	O
the	O
door	O
presently	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
lamp-lighters	O
there	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
up	O
there	O
;	O
take	O
my	O
burner	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
perceive	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
tiles	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
slippery	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
shoes	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
stacks	O
of	O
chimnies	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
things	O
lying	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
to	O
pick	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
some	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
.	O
BLAND	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
some	O
butter	O
for	O
my	O
mother	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mob	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
cock-loft	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
jumped	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
hauled	O
me	O
through	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
another	O
house	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
469.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HYATT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
signed	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whitebread	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gipps	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
GIPPS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Canterbury	O
.	O
Upon	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
races	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Whitebread	O
's	O
on	O
Messrs.	O
Carey	O
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
race-ground	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
book	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
an	O
express	O
to	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
to	O
stop	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
draught	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
having	O
the	O
draught	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
:	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
strange	O
thing	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
understood	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
on	O
a	O
dunghill	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
book	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
among	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
memorandums	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
a	O
lottery-ticket	O
with	O
my	O
indorsement	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
STEVENSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Carey	O
and	O
Co.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
.20	O
draught	O
for	O
payment	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Hyatt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
write	O
that	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
draught	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
require	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
the	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
that	O
morning	O
we	O
had	O
received	O
an	O
express	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
with	O
the	O
draught	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
partners	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
draught	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
exactly	O
corresponded	O
with	O
the	O
statement	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Joseph	B-pers
Delvin	I-pers
proved	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
names	O
Samuel	B-pers
Whitebread	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Sawkins	I-pers
were	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
those	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
as	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
draught	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
in	O
Canterbury	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
tea	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
;	O
he	O
always	O
went	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
freightage	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
share	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
cash	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
without	O
he	O
indorsed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
indorsed	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
being	O
tried	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
470.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BARNSLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
called	O
harrateen	O
,	O
containing	O
48	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
WYCHELOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
take	O
up	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
harrateen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
dyer	O
.	O
The	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
follow	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
about	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
:	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
assisted	O
me	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
and	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
other	O
servant	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Wychelow	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
harrateen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawford	I-pers
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Webb	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
live	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
very	O
innocently	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
N.	O
one	O
year	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
471.	O
MARY	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
BECK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
my	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
14	O
s.	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
My	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
gown	O
which	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
mark	O
which	O
is	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
.	O
She	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
gown	O
from	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
discharged	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
gown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
examination	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
another	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
life	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
made	O
him	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
M	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
472.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CALWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilford	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
errand-boy	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
glass	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilford	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILFORD	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
two	O
hats	O
and	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
Turner's-cerate	O
;	O
seeing	O
the	O
hats	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
473.	O
MARY	B-pers
SKAFE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
German	O
flute	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAILEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
four	O
weeks	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
We	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
deposes	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
she	O
pawned	O
a	O
flute	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
From	O
its	O
appearance	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
examination	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
she	O
voluntarily	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
flute	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
474.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
watch	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
watch	O
string	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Strem	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
JONAS	B-pers
STREM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
the	B-place
Ship	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
sleepy	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
benches	O
in	O
the	O
taproom	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
seat	O
;	O
between	O
sleeping	O
and	O
waking	O
,	O
Williams	O
threw	O
his	O
hat	O
down	O
over	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
why	O
did	O
he	O
throw	O
the	O
hat	O
over	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
waked	O
,	O
Mills	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Mordant	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
Mills	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Mills	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Mordant	O
,	O
and	O
Forrester	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
Mills	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Nobody	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
-	O
MORDANT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
complained	O
of	O
losing	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
Williams	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
brought	O
Mills	O
back	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Mills	O
brought	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
discovered	O
it	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
enquiry	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
Williams	O
said	O
to	O
Mills	O
,	O
Bugger	O
the	O
watch	O
!	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
before	O
Mills	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
landlord	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back-room	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
himself	O
easy	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Mills	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
this	O
expression	O
by	O
Williams	O
to	O
Mills	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
time	O
after	O
Mills	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
that	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
left	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
Williams	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
except	O
denying	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
MILLS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
had	O
dropped	O
underneath	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
WILLIAMS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
dropped	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
475.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
QUIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Pater-noster	B-place
Row	I-place
,	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
strangers	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
so	O
did	O
one	O
Spriggs	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
and	O
Spriggs	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
Thompson	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
Spriggs	O
pulled	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Thompson	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Spriggs	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
intention	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Constable	O
produces	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Landlord	O
deposes	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
made	O
an	O
alarm	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
calling	O
for	O
the	O
fourth	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
made	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
fellow	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
us	O
:	O
he	O
wanted	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
soldiers	O
:	O
the	O
young	O
fellow	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
knowing	O
himself	O
guilty	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
476.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WHITAKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LOWE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
from	O
a	O
field	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
Potter	B-place
's	I-place
Bar	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
corn	O
harvest	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
it	O
to	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JELLOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
officers	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
young	O
fellow	O
has	O
been	O
offering	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
stolen	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
and	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
horse	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
horse	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
close	O
behind	O
the	O
horse	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Honiton	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
loaded	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
took	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
other	O
pocket	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
wrong	O
name	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
:	O
the	O
same	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lowe	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
horse	O
led	O
out	O
and	O
shewn	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
Lowe	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
horse-stealing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
horse	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
was	O
the	O
horse	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
Lowe	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
mane	O
and	O
tail	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blaze	O
in	O
his	O
forehead	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
black	O
legs	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
white	O
heels	O
behind	O
:	O
I	O
bred	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
colt	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
field	O
shut	O
or	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
inclosed	O
field	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
horses	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
ready	O
for	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
477.	O
MARY	B-pers
HALCROW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
canvas	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
eight-pence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
paid	O
some	O
money	O
at	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
stairs	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
me	O
pull	O
my	O
purse	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Old	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
.	O
I	O
supped	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St.	B-place
James's-street	I-place
:	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
along-side	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
waist	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HANNING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
to	O
lock	O
her	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
some	O
odd	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
rented	O
a	O
garret	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
week	O
.	O
The	O
purse	O
was	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
bag	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
die	O
this	O
minute	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARTLEMEW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
forty	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
supped	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
soldier	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
magistrate	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
soldier	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
three	O
golden	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
478.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BOND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
77	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
moist	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
The	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
all	O
the	O
locks	O
were	O
safe	O
in	O
Dice-Key	B-place
gate	I-place
:	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
lock	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
Berry	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
behind	O
the	O
hogshead	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hogshead	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
handfuls	O
of	O
sugar	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
77	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
had	O
been	O
fastened	O
.	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
twice	O
before	O
on	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
confirms	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
witness	O
was	O
a	O
custom-house	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
dismissed	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
oath	O
should	O
not	O
stand	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
N.	O
1	O
year	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
479	O
,	O
480.	O
CHARLOTTE	B-pers
BROOKE	I-pers
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
HYDE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
callimanco	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
their	O
recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
)	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
481.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FREE	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BOWMAN	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Anthony	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
base-metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Anthony	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Portuguese	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
understanding	O
the	O
English	O
language	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
ANTHONY	B-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodge	O
,	O
in	O
White-yard	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
gave	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
pushed	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
did	O
they	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
force	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
stood	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
talking	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
they	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
stood	O
playing	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
touching	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
in	O
Wapping	O
parish	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
foreign	O
sailor	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
,	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
only	O
seeing	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
FLEMING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FARRELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
applied	O
for	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
watches	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pig's-foot	O
for	O
supper	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Me	O
swear	O
!	O
me	O
swear	O
!	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
482.	O
MARY	B-pers
ROSE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
execution	O
of	O
De	O
la	O
Motte	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
shopman	O
was	O
shewing	O
some	O
lace	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
bought	O
some	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
shopman	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
suspected	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
shopman	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
looking	O
over	O
her	O
shoulder	O
.	O
My	O
shopman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
both	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
her	O
round	O
suddenly	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
open	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
card	O
of	O
lace	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
shopman	O
.	O
She	O
held	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
waist	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
declaring	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
any	O
amount	O
for	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
some	O
persons	O
rescued	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
afterwards	O
retaken	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
retaken	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
assistance	O
to	O
rescue	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
prosecute	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
utmost	O
rigour	O
,	O
and	O
hang	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
lace	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
George	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
shopman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
.	O
)	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
BARRIER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
mob	O
rescued	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
retaken	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
again	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
7	O
s.	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
shopman	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
cards	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
change	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
lace	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
change	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
guineas	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
scandalized	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
laid	O
out	O
12	O
l.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
483	O
,	O
484.	O
HENRY	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newport	I-pers
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Cook	B-pers
Trollope	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
base-metal	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cook	O
Trollope	B-pers
.	O
COOK	O
TROLLOPE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Jones	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
pulled	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
by	O
the	O
ancles	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
New	B-place
Prison	I-place
,	O
of	O
which	O
Samuel	B-pers
Newport	I-pers
is	O
the	O
keeper	O
.	O
Jones	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
half-crown	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
a	O
brother	O
shop-mate	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
pay-table	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
awake	O
when	O
they	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
breeches	O
lay	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Davis	O
pulled	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
by	O
the	O
ancles	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Jones	B-pers
,	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
set	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
centry	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
half-a-crown	O
garnish-money	O
,	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
night-charge	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
robbed	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
JONES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
impossible	O
we	O
could	O
rob	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
ironed	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
To	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
all	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
in	O
another	O
bed	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
darkness	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
darkness	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
knocked	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
before	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
465	O
.	O
)	O
485	O
,	O
486	O
,	O
487.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
JAMES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
MOULDY	I-pers
CLOAK	I-pers
,	O
and	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
WATERS	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Nathan	B-pers
Vezey	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nathan	O
.	O
NATHAN	O
VEZEY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glazier	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
from	O
Enfield	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Ball's-pond	B-place
turnpike	I-place
,	O
a	O
man	O
asked	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
?	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
reason	O
for	O
asking	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
robbed	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
doubled	O
them	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
man	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
or	O
on	O
horseback	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
foot	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
on	O
foot	O
too	O
.	O
We	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
We	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
unless	O
we	O
are	O
overpowered	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
about	O
fourscore	O
yards	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
foremost	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
was	O
close	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
that	O
man	O
who	O
calls	O
himself	O
James	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Mouldy	O
Cloak	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Waters	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
plainly	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
when	O
Mouldy	O
Cloak	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Blast	O
your	O
bloody	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
bloody	O
thief	O
!	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
!	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
your	O
watch	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
push	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
buttons	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
White	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
let	O
his	O
guts	O
out	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
rusty	O
cutlass	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
guard	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
Cloak	O
,	O
White	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
jarred	B-pers
all	O
my	O
fingers	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
dropped	O
my	O
stick	O
.	O
They	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
tuck	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
drop	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
fishing-rod	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
about	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
man	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
engaged	O
with	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
Cloak	O
told	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
look	O
back	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drawed	O
his	O
hat	O
over	O
his	O
eyes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
stedfastly	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
with	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
begged	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
murder	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
but	O
consider	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
blasting	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
hesitate	O
for	O
?	O
Blast	O
him	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
;	O
blast	O
him	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
head	O
off	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
ago	O
since	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
with	O
White	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
twenty	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
knows	O
me	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
fishing	O
rod	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
saw	O
it	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
with	O
my	O
friend	O
's	O
hat	O
.	O
Waters	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Blast	O
your	O
bloody	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
look	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
cutlass	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
blasting	O
their	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
did	O
they	O
not	O
rip	O
my	O
guts	O
out	O
?	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
not	O
three	O
minutes	O
under	O
or	O
over	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Plenty	O
of	O
light	O
to	O
distinguish	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
in	O
making	O
my	O
remarks	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
they	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
near	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
you	O
never	O
knew	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
in	O
observing	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Thatched-House	O
,	O
got	O
pistols	O
and	O
cutlasses	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
carried	O
back	O
the	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
at	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Chick-Lane	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
waited	O
there	O
till	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sight	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
repaired	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
lobby	O
of	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
for	O
some	O
hours	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
coming	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
before	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
White-Chapel	O
Turnpike	O
.	O
Cloak	O
and	O
White	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
chaise-cart	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Phillips	O
and	O
Waters	O
.	O
Waters	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
along	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
except	O
Phillips	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
like	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
accosted	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
;	O
therefore	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
follow	O
that	O
chaise-cart	O
till	O
we	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
through	O
White	O
Chapel	O
,	O
down	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
into	O
Long-Lane	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
stoppage	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
and	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
now	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
think	O
Phillips	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
Phillips	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
was	O
hanged	O
for	O
that	O
robbery	O
,	O
somebody	O
else	O
should	O
suffer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
glazier	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
A	O
master	O
or	O
journeyman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
business	O
eleven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
served	O
all	O
Ward	O
and	O
Parish	O
Offices	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
man	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Committed	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
examined	O
and	O
sent	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Bow-Street	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
fully	O
committed	O
,	O
you	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
positively	O
sworn	O
to	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wished	O
rather	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
by	O
somebody	O
else	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
told	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
your	O
school-fellow	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
minute	O
;	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
tender	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
having	O
been	O
my	O
school-fellow	O
,	O
I	O
wished	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
examined	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
advert	O
sed	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
other	O
persons	O
might	O
appear	O
against	O
them	O
rather	O
than	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
RIMMINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Vezey	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
.	I-pers
As	I-pers
we	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
therestood	O
a	O
very	O
tall	O
,	O
strait	O
,	O
decent	O
young	O
fellow	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
confident	O
which	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
smiled	O
to	O
my	O
companion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
lose	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
afraid	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
But	O
we	O
will	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
double	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
company	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
Kingstand	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
caught	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
bloody	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
you	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Have	O
what	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
directly	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
might	O
easily	O
have	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
or	O
very	O
little	O
,	O
besides	O
some	O
change	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
my	O
reckoning	O
with	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
terrified	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
it	O
me	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
hesitate	O
another	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
cut	O
your	O
head	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
Whiskin	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
strived	O
to	O
stop	O
my	O
mouth	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
round	O
to	O
resist	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
chap	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
that	O
Waters	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
stooped	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
hesitate	O
about	O
?	O
cut	O
his	O
guts	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
pulled	O
his	O
hat	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
Waters	O
from	O
his	O
stature	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
black	O
fellow	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
turned	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
half-pence	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
likewise	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
watch	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
along	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
joined	O
company	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
villains	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
had	O
done	O
him	O
.	O
Said	O
one	O
,	O
You	O
should	O
have	O
cut	O
his	O
guts	O
out	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
White	O
well	O
for	O
years	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
speak	O
positive	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
But	O
rather	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Waters	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
light	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
pleasant	O
fine	O
evening	O
as	O
we	O
walked	O
from	O
Enfield	O
together	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
fully	O
committed	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
they	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
owing	O
to	O
my	O
timorousness	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
them	O
speak	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
their	O
voices	O
differed	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
timorousness	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
Justice	O
Blackborow	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
heard	O
Vezey	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Islington	O
town	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
pick	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
two	O
hundred	O
persons	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rimmington	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
somebody	O
else	O
to	O
assist	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
parties	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Kipping	O
and	O
Redgrave	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
descriptions	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Field-Lane	O
:	O
there	O
we	O
staid	O
watching	O
and	O
looking	O
to	O
see	O
somebody	O
come	O
from	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
habitation	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
lodge	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
seeing	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sight	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
:	O
we	O
proceeded	O
from	O
thence	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
to	O
this	O
sight	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mile-End	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kipping	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Redgrave	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike-gate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
certain	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
case	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
We	O
never	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
chaise	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
cart	O
were	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
immediately	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Long-Lane	O
:	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
describe	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
these	O
people	O
,	O
did	O
they	O
answer	O
that	O
description	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
describe	O
their	O
dress	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
dressed	O
in	O
brown	O
cloaths	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
.	O
W	O
hite	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
on	O
;	O
Mouldy	O
Cloak	O
has	O
now	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
on	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
Waters	O
likewise	O
,	O
the	O
shortest	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
particularly	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
mark	O
upon	O
his	O
buttons	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
that	O
mark	O
on	O
his	O
buttons	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
now	O
upon	O
his	O
buttons	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
Waters	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
stag	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
bird	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
which	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
(	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Redgrave	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Kipping	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
)	O
WHITE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
CLARK	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rimmington	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
dark	O
and	O
light	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
discern	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taller	O
than	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
mouth	O
was	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
teeth	O
out	O
.	O
Rimmington	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
party	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
plain	O
that	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
EYRE	I-pers
.	O
488.	O
ANN	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
(	O
no	O
person	O
then	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Duncan	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
JANET	B-pers
ROSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
lives	O
in	O
White-hart-yard	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
shut	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
candle	O
upon	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
some	O
children	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
sash-window	O
;	O
any	O
person	O
may	O
get	O
in	O
by	O
lifting	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
window-sash	O
was	O
shut	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
8	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
gold	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
leather	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
silk	O
purse	O
was	O
likewise	O
put	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
supposed	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
cloaths	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
naked	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
bargain	O
for	O
cloaths	O
at	O
several	O
shops	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-court	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
new	O
cloaths	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
.	O
That	O
neighbour	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
ned	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
should	O
ever	O
go	O
to	O
gaol	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
purses	O
were	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
seek	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
cunning	O
enough	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
return	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
red	O
gown	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
ROSE	B-pers
GRANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
red	O
gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
hitched	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
she	O
loosed	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
constable	O
who	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
red	O
cloak	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
She	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
489.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STEWART	I-pers
and	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ATKINS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Arthur	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
.	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
and	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
crystal	O
stone	O
seal	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
chain	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
hook	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Arthur	O
.	O
ARTHUR	B-pers
SHAKESPEAR	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
my	O
carriage	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
near	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
the	O
carriage	O
stopped	O
with	O
a	O
violent	O
jerk	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
thrown	O
against	O
the	O
blinds	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
flash	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
horses	O
had	O
fallen	O
down	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
it	O
occurred	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
carriage	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
fellows	O
,	O
with	O
cutlasses	O
and	O
pistols	O
,	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
man	O
in	O
green	O
(	O
Stewart	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
Bath	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
stouter	O
than	O
he	O
does	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
convicted	O
I	O
conceive	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
then	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
cut	O
me	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
His	O
comrade	O
(	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
)	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
carriage	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
very	O
imprudently	O
caught	O
at	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
struggle	O
,	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
dropped	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
Stewart	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
was	O
opened	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
with	O
cutlasses	O
and	O
pistols	O
,	O
threatened	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
very	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
that	O
opened	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
alarmed	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
.	O
They	O
threatened	O
much	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
It	O
struck	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
best	O
way	O
was	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
attention	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
first	O
attacked	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
.	O
They	O
uttered	O
horrid	O
imprecations	O
:	O
They	O
would	O
cut	O
me	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
mind	O
killing	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
dog	O
.	O
That	O
little	O
man	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
)	O
appears	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
faint	O
remembrance	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
resembling	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
his	O
voice	O
struck	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
something	O
like	O
his	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
comrade	O
of	O
that	O
little	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
man	O
that	O
opened	O
the	O
carriage	O
door	O
,	O
begged	O
his	O
fellow	O
robbers	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
all	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
hurt	O
thim	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
much	O
taller	O
than	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
:	O
they	O
then	O
desired	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
nobody	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Sherwood	O
's	O
runners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
carriage	O
,	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
houses	O
I	O
could	O
think	O
of	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
strong	O
in	O
my	O
eye	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
meeting	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
than	O
trust	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mind	O
afterwards	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
speak	O
positively	O
to	O
Stewart	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
something	O
alarmed	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
decline	O
speaking	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
got	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
AVERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
beyond	O
the	O
Toll-bar	O
,	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
sail-cloth	O
manufactory	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
four	O
footpads	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
flash	O
from	O
the	O
pan	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
pistol	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
flash	O
,	O
the	O
carriage	O
stopped	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Stewart	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
was	O
crying	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
light	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
hangers	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
The	O
off	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
first	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
They	O
demanded	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
One	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
.	O
This	O
Stewart	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
from	O
behind	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
chariot	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
almost	O
as	O
possibly	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
attention	O
was	O
wholly	O
upon	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
those	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Atkins	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
that	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Stewart	O
shut	O
the	O
carriage	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
that	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
shut	O
the	O
carriage	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
drive	O
on	O
,	O
coachman	O
!	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
,	O
Stewart	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
you	O
bugger	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
your	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
!	O
The	O
coachman	O
drove	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hit	O
me	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
enable	O
you	O
to	O
distinguish	O
the	O
counnance	O
of	O
Stewart	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
rough	O
Bath	O
coat	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Stewart	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
appearance	O
was	O
such	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
his	O
hair	O
was	O
not	O
powdered	O
or	O
curled	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
hair	O
is	O
black	O
or	O
dark	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
loose	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
buttoned	O
round	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
then	O
a	O
bit	O
stouter	O
than	O
he	O
does	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
clear	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
given	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
given	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
reward	O
had	O
you	O
last	O
sessions	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
expect	O
?	O
-	O
What	O
is	O
my	O
share	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
share	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
If	O
this	O
man	O
is	O
convicted	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
expect	O
some	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
expect	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
so	O
generous	O
in	O
one	O
instance	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
this	O
:	O
did	O
not	O
Jellous	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
blood-money	O
you	O
set	O
this	O
man	O
down	O
at	O
?	O
How	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
reckon	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
upon	O
his	O
life	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
wish	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
it	O
fairly	O
and	O
honestly	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
expect	O
it	O
from	O
Gough	O
more	O
than	O
for	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
speak	O
truth	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
before	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
loose	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hair	O
hanging	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
his	O
voice	O
,	O
and	O
person	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
hind-wheel	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
as	O
close	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Why	O
could	O
not	O
he	O
rob	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
carriage	O
told	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
on	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
could	O
stop	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
master	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
certainly	O
stop	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
August	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
about	O
these	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
appear	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
hint	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
hint	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
the	O
servants	O
?	O
-	O
Drinking	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
:	O
I	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
You	O
understand	O
drinking	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
few	O
servants	O
go	O
to	O
Ranelagh	O
without	O
drinking	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
your	O
case	O
;	O
you	O
was	O
drunk	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
,	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
turnpike	O
,	O
by	O
four	O
footpads	O
.	O
They	O
attempted	O
to	O
fire	O
two	O
pistols	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
pistols	O
flashed	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Stewart	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
foot-board	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
stand	O
still	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
cut	O
your	O
throat	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
carriage	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
drive	O
on	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JELLOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
horse-pistol	O
,	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARPMEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
cutlass	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
-	O
FARRELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
Atkins	O
.	O
STEWART	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Gosport	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
Stewart	O
called	O
John	O
Wall	O
and	O
Sophia	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Gosport	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Whit-Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
)	O
Jury	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
Avery	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
staid	O
out	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
drink	O
sometimes	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
night	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
drinking	O
the	O
least	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
379	O
,	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
]	O
490.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
