TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1782	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SIXTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PLOMER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
Bookseller	O
,	O
removed	O
from	O
Bell-Yard	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Leather-lane	O
.	O
MDCCLXXXII	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PLOMER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BULLER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
ADAIR	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
George	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Peach	I-pers
Patrick	B-pers
Hearne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sewell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wathen	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mexton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Darvin	I-pers
William	B-pers
Greenhill	I-pers
John	B-pers
Winstanley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Elliott	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Calderwood	I-pers
George	B-pers
Manville	I-pers
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hobcraft	I-pers
William	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Giffard	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Humanitas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
Stone	B-pers
Tuppin	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
I'Anson	I-pers
Ambrose	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Everitt	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
William	B-pers
Ricketts	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Randell	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
James	B-pers
Fendon	I-pers
416	O
,	O
417	O
,	O
418.	O
ANN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
,	O
ANN	B-pers
DELANEY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
edging	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
shop	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Francis	O
Thompson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
thread	O
lace	O
edging	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bought	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kendrick	O
immediately	O
stepped	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
upon	O
examination	O
we	O
missed	O
two	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Horse	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
Davis	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
two	O
cards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
This	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
burnt	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
this	O
is	O
our	O
property	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
are	O
marks	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Delaney	O
whispered	O
to	O
Wilson	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Wilson	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
Delaney	O
herself	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shopman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
thread	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
Delaney	O
bought	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
money	O
of	O
Wilson	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
edging	O
,	O
they	O
laughed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Kendrick	O
immediately	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
upon	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
cards	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
shewed	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
this	O
card	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
shewn	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KENDRICK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop-window	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
me	O
to	O
suspect	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
them	O
of	O
my	O
suspicions	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
DELANEY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
WILSON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
DELANEY	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
WILSON	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
419.	O
MARY	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
400	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
-	O
200	O
yards	O
of	O
narrow	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watridge	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
80	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
140	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Watridge	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WATRIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shopkeeper	O
,	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
used	O
my	O
shop	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
very	O
well	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
my	O
shop-woman	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
called	O
me	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stolen	O
some	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
immediately	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
return	O
presently	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
shop-woman	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
soon	O
come	O
back	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
we	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
stolen	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shop-woman	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
being	O
searched	O
thoroughly	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
these	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
as	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
laid	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
lodging	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favor	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
confession	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
mention	O
her	O
confession	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
secrete	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Watridge	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
search	O
her	O
any	O
further	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
pocket	O
on	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
still	O
persisted	O
in	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
secreted	O
some	O
lace	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Watridge	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
her	O
searched	O
thoroughly	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ribbons	O
in	O
her	O
other	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Count	O
,	O
but	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
420	O
,	O
421.	O
DAVID	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
and	O
JAMES	B-pers
MAHEN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
50	O
pounds	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
men	O
's	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
stuff	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
ALICE	B-pers
REDMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
not	O
being	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
children	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
till	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
slum	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
by	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
back-window	O
and	O
the	O
back-door	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
safe	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
crack	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
thrown	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
several	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
ANDREW	B-pers
HOPKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
Church-lane	O
;	O
Jones	O
had	O
a	O
stitch	O
of	O
bacon	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Rose-and-Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Rose-and-Crown	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
stolen	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
fetch	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
first	O
the	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
a	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
Mahen	O
,	O
but	O
Jones	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
Mahen	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
thence	O
to-day	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DEMPSEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
breeches-pocket	O
,	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
bed-side	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
waked	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
and	O
door	O
both	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
secure	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mahen	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
FISH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
Hopkins	O
in	O
taking	O
Mahen	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
RATLAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church-street	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Hopkins	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Hopkins	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
produce	O
the	O
party	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
stay	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
fetch	O
the	O
party	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
escape	O
:	O
Mahen	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
Jones	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Jones	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LEVI	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Fish	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
brought	O
Mahen	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stitch	O
of	O
bacon	O
.	O
Mahen	O
said	O
Jones	O
was	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Dempsey	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
mentioned	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Dempsey	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
blue	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
remembered	O
Mahen	O
having	O
one	O
on	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
fit	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
Jones	O
at	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
bacon	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
hell	O
.	O
JONES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mahen	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
an	O
alley	O
with	O
the	O
bacon	O
and	O
bag	O
of	O
things	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
that	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
MAHEN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Farthing-fields	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bacon	O
,	O
and	O
bag	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
pursued	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
:	O
Jones	O
is	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
319.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
STANLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Letitia	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
eight	O
dimity	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Letitia	O
.	O
LETITIA	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Berkeley-street	O
,	O
Portman-square	O
,	O
to	O
Highgate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
New	O
Norfolk-street	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
stage	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
the	O
stage	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
walk	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
from	O
Kentish-Town	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
lying	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
grass	O
,	O
started	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
fast	O
up	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brown	O
linen	O
apron	O
;	O
his	O
hat	O
was	O
pushed	O
back	O
from	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
perfect	O
view	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
horrid	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
throat	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
quiet	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
me	O
fast	O
by	O
one	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
felt	O
into	O
both	O
my	O
pockets	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
likewise	O
took	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
in	O
it	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
dimity	O
pockets	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
wa	O
nted	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
cloak	O
off	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
things	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
very	O
plain	O
:	O
he	O
kept	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
point	O
out	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
locket	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
wrapped	O
in	O
white	O
lawn	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
my	O
pardon	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
through	O
Soho-square	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Nothing	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
he	O
resisted	O
that	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
altercation	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
he	O
submitted	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
search	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
brown	O
linen	O
apron	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Dennis	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
Leather-lane	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
bundle	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
walked	O
about	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Dixon	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Chatham	O
for	O
a	O
marine	O
;	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
fetched	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
:	O
they	O
do	O
it	O
through	O
spite	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
421.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
(	O
a	O
negro	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Turnbull	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turnbull	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
(	O
Stephen	B-pers
Turnbull	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
his	O
mother	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rushed	O
by	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
bundle	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
clothes	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
422.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BARRETT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
mugs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
two	O
silver	O
sauce-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
wine-strainer	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
stand	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Broad-court	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
side-board	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
plate	O
had	O
been	O
missed	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
whole	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
20	O
l.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BOWATER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walk	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
door	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
child	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
walked	O
to	O
Cross-court	O
,	O
which	O
leads	O
into	O
Broad-court	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
walked	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
stop	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pushed	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
sweetheart	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
maids	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
(	O
Upon	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
garret-window	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Broad-court	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
dress	O
;	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
some	O
weeks	O
after	O
.	O
)	O
MARTHA	B-pers
PUGH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
The	O
plate	O
was	O
kept	O
open	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
side-board	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
past	O
the	O
house	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
six	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
missed	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Office	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
came	O
with	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
another	O
man	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
description	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
servant	O
.	O
Somebody	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
said	O
Barrett	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
423.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
horse-roller	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
's	O
coachman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
returned	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
stable	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
424.	O
ANN	B-pers
M'FARLAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Oddey	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ODDEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
.	O
The	O
printed	O
callico	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
At	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
clear	O
lawn	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
which	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
carefully	O
to	O
conceal	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
the	O
callico	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
callico	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
callico	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Another	O
young	O
woman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
callico	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
425.	O
ANN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-board	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
426.	O
ANN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
earthen	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
earthen	O
teacups	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
earthen	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
half-pint	O
tumbler	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
bed-rug	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
evidence	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
prove	O
a	O
felony	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
427.	O
ARCHIBALD	B-pers
LIVINGSTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lunn	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
charge	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
428.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
8th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
keeps	O
the	O
Four	O
Swans	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
sheets	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
429.	O
MARY	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
lid	O
of	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
steel	O
snuffers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
immediately	O
followed	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
hold	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
430.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheque	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
counterpane	O
made	O
of	O
cotton	O
and	O
linen	O
patches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
431	O
,	O
432	O
,	O
433.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
,	O
GRIFFIN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
,	O
and	O
GEORGE	B-pers
KING	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
5	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lamb	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
steams	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
chopper	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hardmeat	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
identify	O
the	O
meat	O
.	O
)	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
434.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
FIELDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
printed	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
cheque	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EADES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Foster	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
stopping	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
apparel	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
bundle	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
435.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
HAWKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
groce	O
of	O
pewter	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RAFFAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
workshop	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bean	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
her	O
searched	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
produced	O
two	O
groce	O
of	O
pewter	O
buttons	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
upon	O
her	O
concealed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bean	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
,	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
buttons	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
RANDALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Raffan	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
There	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
buttons	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
buttons	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
436	O
,	O
437.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
SAMPSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Angus	B-pers
M'Kenzie	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
ANGUS	B-pers
M'KENZIE	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
came	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
dust	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
table-spoon	O
was	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
:	O
the	O
dust	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
spoon	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
back-board	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
:	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
dust	O
,	O
slightly	O
covered	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
constables	O
were	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
Jones	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Sampson	O
denied	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
missed	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Ann	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
met	O
Jones	O
on	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
JONES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
spoon	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
dust	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
Sampson	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
JONES	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
SAMPSON	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
438.	O
ANN	B-pers
AGER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hair	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
trunk-maker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Southampton-buildings	B-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
walking	O
down	O
Southampton-buildings	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
Suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrington	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
trunk	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
439.	O
ANN	B-pers
QUINES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whitcher	I-pers
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Whitcher	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Catherine-wheel-alley	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
on	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
awaked	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
extremely	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
stripped	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
440.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
KEELING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maylin	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MAYLIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
in	O
Cursitor-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
staid	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
PEARCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
evening	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
silver	O
tankard	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
except	O
Mr.	O
Keeling	O
.	O
The	O
tankard	O
was	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
parted	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Chancery-lane	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
parted	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Keeling	O
overtook	O
me	O
.	O
His	O
coat	O
was	O
buttoned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
HOGG	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
society	O
at	O
Maylin	O
's	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
club	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
us	O
staid	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
but	O
one	O
that	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Keeling	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
declined	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Francis	B-pers
Hearne	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
441.	O
PHEBE	B-pers
BLANDON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
round	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
crystal	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
egg	O
trinket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hogermoolen	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOGERMOOLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hackney	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Shoreditch	B-place
church	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
girl	O
,	O
much	O
larger	O
than	O
she	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
those	O
words	O
,	O
the	O
biggest	O
girl	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
push	O
upon	O
my	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
big	O
girl	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
She	O
struggled	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
clock	O
had	O
struck	O
twelve	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
called	O
Watch	O
!	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
gold	O
one	O
,	O
enamelled	O
;	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
was	O
metal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
since	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GARDINER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
at	O
nigh	O
t	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Watch	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
greater	O
girl	O
than	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
442.	O
PETER	B-pers
MONRO	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dolman	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
30th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LOCKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
girl	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
Castle-court	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
BARNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dolman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
cloth	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Locke	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
443.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PRESTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
feloniously	O
did	O
falsely	O
make	O
,	O
forge	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
a	O
certain	O
note	O
,	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
``	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Dartford	O
,	O
7th	O
March	O
,	O
1782	O
.	O
Six	O
weeks	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
received	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
Messrs.	O
Drummonds	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
''	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
count	O
:	O
For	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
the	O
said	O
note	O
,	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
-	O
WHITE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
brewer	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-Road	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
a	O
partner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kinnersley	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
for	O
twopenny	O
,	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
ale	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
10	O
l.	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
first	O
bill	O
,	O
upon	O
account	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
bill	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
drawn	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Dartford	O
,	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Dartford	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
agent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
the	O
lime-kilns	O
at	O
Dartford	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
cash	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Drummond	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
strength	O
of	O
this	O
note	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kinnersley	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
30	O
l.	O
more	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
at	O
Messrs.	O
Drummond	O
's	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
good	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
note	O
you	O
received	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
indorse	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
knew	O
this	O
Jones	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Cook	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
limekilns	O
,	O
at	O
Dartford	O
;	O
that	O
Jones	O
was	O
his	O
agent	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
in	O
breeze	O
.	O
CROSS-EXAMINATION	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
not	O
an	O
action	O
now	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
commenced	O
an	O
action	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
balance	O
of	O
his	O
account	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
commenced	O
an	O
action	O
for	O
his	O
debt	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
this	O
note	O
is	O
included	O
in	O
that	O
demand	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
out	O
that	O
bill	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
50	O
l.	O
Was	O
this	O
note	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
account	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
action	O
upon	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
or	O
goods	O
sold	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
goods	O
sold	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
frequently	O
in	O
town	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
dealt	O
largely	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
very	O
largely	O
:	O
he	O
often	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
called	O
last	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NETTLEPOLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Dartford	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
lime-kilns	O
are	O
there	O
at	O
Dartford	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
proprietor	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
one	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
such	O
persons	O
as	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
there	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
proprietor	O
of	O
that	O
kiln	O
?	O
-	O
Nine	O
years	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
had	O
it	O
nineteen	O
.	O
During	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
has	O
there	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
or	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
kiln	O
,	O
or	O
acted	O
as	O
agents	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
our	O
business	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
large	O
as	O
to	O
need	O
agents	O
;	O
we	O
do	O
it	O
ourselves	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
buy	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
breeze	O
a	O
year	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
use	O
no	O
breeze	O
;	O
we	O
use	O
coals	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DORMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
proprietor	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
lime-kiln	O
at	O
Dartford	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
Six	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
it	O
thirty	O
years	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
or	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
as	O
proprietor	O
,	O
or	O
agent	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
such	O
persons	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
note	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
Dartford	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
value	O
received	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
stated	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
is	O
false	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
served	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
That	O
gentleman	O
knows	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dorman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
represented	O
himself	O
as	O
a	O
schoolmaster	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
Dartford	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
an	O
indictment	O
preferred	O
for	O
this	O
matter	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
.	O
And	O
it	O
was	O
thrown	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
mistake	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
value	O
for	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
CROSS	O
EXAMINATION	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
books	O
for	O
trades-men	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
of	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
deal	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Pray	O
who	O
may	O
be	O
your	O
banker	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
banker	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Nor	O
Mr.	O
Gosling	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
cash	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Nor	O
never	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
notes	O
did	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
give	O
;	O
promissory	O
notes	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
March	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
7th	O
or	O
8th	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
repeat	O
the	O
note	O
you	O
drew	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
drawn	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
``	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
.	O
''	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Signed	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
or	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
?	O
-	O
John	O
.	O
John	O
,	O
at	O
length	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
drawn	O
upon	O
any	O
banker	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
cash	O
at	O
any	O
banker	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
just	O
to	O
write	O
your	O
name	O
on	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
.	O
-	O
(	O
He	O
does	O
so	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
right	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
had	O
,	O
nor	O
pretended	O
to	O
have	O
,	O
cash	O
at	O
any	O
banker	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
never	O
lived	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
or	O
pretended	O
it	O
!	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
live	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
proprietor	O
of	O
any	O
brick-kilns	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Nor	O
lime-kilns	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
reside	O
,	O
or	O
intended	O
to	O
reside	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
They	O
do	O
not	O
call	O
you	O
Lord	O
Jones	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
reside	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
meant	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Dartford	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
school	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
note	O
.	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
handwriting	O
.	O
You	O
write	O
very	O
differently	O
to-day	O
,	O
to	O
what	O
you	O
did	O
then	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
jury	O
inspected	O
the	O
name	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
wrote	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
signature	O
on	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hands	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
different	O
.	O
)	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
wish	O
the	O
witness	O
would	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
in	O
a	O
larger	O
hand	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witness	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
often	O
give	O
notes	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
ever	O
draw	O
bills	O
upon	O
any	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
the	O
note	O
you	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
directed	O
to	O
any	O
banker	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
re-	O
recollect	O
that	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
Counsel	O
asked	O
you	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
shewed	O
you	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
directed	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Drummond	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
cash	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
due	O
.	O
They	O
arrested	O
the	O
man	O
for	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
not	O
content	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
now	O
try	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
the	O
Counsel	O
you	O
never	O
kept	O
cash	O
there	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
it	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
will	O
say	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Drummond	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
know	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Tottenham-Court	O
Road	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
date	O
your	O
note	O
from	O
Tottenham-Court	O
Road	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
live	O
down	O
at	O
Dartford	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
school	O
there	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KEMP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
and	O
farrier	O
,	O
in	O
Tottenham-Court	O
Road	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
to	O
that	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
that	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
witness	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
bill	O
here	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
.	O
Does	O
Jones	O
write	O
out	O
your	O
bills	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
does	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
perfectly	O
know	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
(	O
shewing	O
the	O
paper	O
he	O
wrote	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
)	O
-	O
The	O
J	O
is	O
much	O
like	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
intimidated	O
here	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
much	O
unlike	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
lived	O
at	O
Dartford	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
lived	O
at	O
Dartford	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
man	O
decayed	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
business	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Preston	O
?	O
-	O
Fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
earned	O
many	O
a	O
score	O
pound	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CHINEA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Jones	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
well	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
judge	O
of	O
writing	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
:	O
he	O
keeps	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
tradesmen	O
's	O
books	O
about	O
us	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
general	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
Kemp	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
general	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
bad	O
word	O
,	O
perhaps	O
;	O
they	O
may	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
dealt	O
honestly	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
connections	O
with	O
.	O
Farther	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
ALEX	O
.	O
SINCLAIR	B-pers
GORDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Drummond	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
cash	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
note	O
was	O
drawn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
that	O
note	O
being	O
tendered	O
for	O
payment	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
living	O
at	O
Dartford	O
,	O
keep	O
cash	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
draft	O
ever	O
tendered	O
for	O
payment	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
Jones	O
)	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
ever	O
kept	O
cash	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
not	O
happen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
a	O
banker	O
,	O
that	O
notes	O
are	O
drawn	O
on	O
a	O
particular	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
cash	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
banker	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
paying	O
those	O
notes	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
ever	O
having	O
happened	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Death	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
444.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SAMUEL	I-pers
WATSON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
JOSEPH	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
WESTON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Bath	O
and	O
Bristol	O
mail	O
,	O
Jan.	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
1781	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
In	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
corner	O
house	O
in	O
Wardour-street	O
;	O
after	O
being	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
hands	O
in	O
their	O
pockets	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
armed	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
pass	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
hue-and-cry	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
hands	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
each	O
hand	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
upon	O
Joseph	O
,	O
four	O
Bank	O
post-bills	O
,	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
a	O
70	O
l.	O
a	O
40	O
l.	O
another	O
,	O
33	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
lottery-ticket	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
28,257	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
George	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bills	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
are	O
clerk	O
at	O
the	O
post-office	O
at	O
Maidenhead	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
sending	O
off	O
the	O
mail	O
from	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
for	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
Hounslow	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
dead	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
What	O
bags	O
did	O
that	O
mail	O
contain	O
?	O
-	O
Every	O
thing	O
appeared	O
in	O
its	O
usual	O
state	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
Reading	O
,	O
or	O
Bristol	O
mail	O
,	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
mail	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
bag	O
that	O
contains	O
the	O
letters	O
to	O
Windsor	O
.	O
The	O
Bath	O
and	O
Reading	O
bags	O
,	O
likewise	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
mail	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROOKES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
post-master	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
the	O
mail	O
from	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
name	O
who	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
dead	O
:	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
it	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
He	O
takes	O
the	O
mail	O
down	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
brings	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
does	O
the	O
mail	O
generally	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
it	O
comes	O
in	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
at	O
three	O
,	O
four	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
.	O
To	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
mail	O
sent	O
out	O
from	O
Maidenhead	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRODSHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
magistrates	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
information	O
(	O
shewing	O
the	O
witness	O
a	O
paper	O
)	O
given	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Wrighte	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
it	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
signed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
information	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wrighte	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
informant	O
faith	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
bringing	O
the	O
Bristol	O
mail	O
from	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
near	O
the	O
eleven-mile	O
stone	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
single	O
highwayman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
crape	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
black	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
who	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
mail	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
highwayman	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
informant	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
passed	O
him	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
RICHARD	O
NEW	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
employed	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
mail	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Hanger-hill	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
road	O
leading	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
?	O
-	O
Five	O
miles	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
beside	O
?	O
Look	O
at	O
those	O
two	O
papers	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
those	O
two	O
papers	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
those	O
papers	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Thrown	O
about	O
the	O
meadow	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
there	O
besides	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
afterwards	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Post-office	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
all	O
the	O
letters	O
and	O
papers	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
Post-office	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
to	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
peace	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
bills	O
of	O
charges	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
called	O
,	O
both	O
from	O
Bath	O
and	O
Bristol	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
From	O
Bath	O
,	O
27th	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
letters	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
470	O
,	O
at	O
4	O
d.	O
Unpaid	O
letters	O
,	O
7	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
-	O
25	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
At	O
4	O
d.	O
paid	O
letters	O
,	O
8	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
From	O
Bristol	O
,	O
26th	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
letters	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
577	O
,	O
at	O
4	O
d.	O
Unpaid	O
letters	O
,	O
9	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
At	O
4	O
d.	O
paid	O
letters	O
,	O
1	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
William	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
.	O
-	O
To	O
unpaid	O
letters	O
,	O
nothing	O
;	O
to	O
paid	O
letters	O
,	O
nothing	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
TURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Nottingham	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair-dresser	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
those	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Blackmoor	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
be	O
dressed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
dressed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
the	O
waiter	O
to	O
a	O
banker	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
cash	O
for	O
a	O
bill	O
.	O
The	O
waiter	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
banker	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
bankers	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
there	O
himself	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
dressing	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Nottingham	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
at	O
Nottingham	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
naval	O
uniform	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
lappell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
.	O
The	O
clerk	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
cash	O
for	O
a	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
premium	O
which	O
we	O
always	O
have	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
quarter	O
per	O
cent	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
we	O
always	O
had	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
take	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
allow	O
it	O
you	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
travel	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
cash	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
from	O
our	O
own	O
number	O
that	O
is	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
G	O
3	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
T	O
1062	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
dated	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
seven	O
days	O
sight	O
,	O
to	O
Matthew	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
100	O
l.	O
sterling	O
.	O
ADAM	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
keep	O
the	O
inn	O
at	O
Enfield	O
highway	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
George	O
Weston	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
recollection	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1781	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
a	O
midshipman	O
's	O
uniform	O
.	O
What	O
chaise	O
had	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
chaise	O
and	O
four	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
FILLATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
partner	O
with	O
Messrs.	O
Cam	O
and	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
bankers	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
r	O
ecollect	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
what	O
day	O
in	O
that	O
month	O
,	O
forwarding	O
any	O
letter	O
to	O
town	O
by	O
the	O
mail	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
I	O
forwarded	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Boldero	O
,	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
bankers	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
forty-four	O
bills	O
,	O
under	O
cover	O
of	O
two	O
sheets	O
of	O
paper	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Boldero	O
,	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
inclosed	O
in	O
cover	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
London	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
jury	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
notes	O
forwarded	O
by	O
you	O
to	O
London	O
by	O
the	O
mail	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
note	O
forwarded	O
by	O
me	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
mail	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
No	O
.	O
T	O
1062	O
,	O
40	O
l.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
T	O
1060	O
,	O
T	O
1061	O
,	O
and	O
T	O
1063	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
date	O
and	O
tenour	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
this	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
you	O
forwarded	O
also	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
number	O
has	O
been	O
altered	O
since	O
.	O
What	O
alteration	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
number	O
?	O
-	O
Here	O
is	O
an	O
addition	O
of	O
a	O
0	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
original	O
number	O
was	O
T	O
1063	O
;	O
it	O
appears	O
now	O
T	O
10630	O
.	O
That	O
alteration	O
is	O
made	O
by	O
putting	O
a	O
0	O
after	O
the	O
figures	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
able	O
to	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bills	O
you	O
forwarded	O
to	O
London	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
the	O
number	O
being	O
altered	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
for	O
believing	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
copy	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
of	O
the	O
bills	O
,	O
which	O
corresponds	O
with	O
these	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
great-coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
corresponds	O
but	O
the	O
0	O
,	O
which	O
clearly	O
is	O
an	O
addition	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
there	O
that	O
induces	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
10630	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
originally	O
issued	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
the	O
date	O
and	O
sum	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
0	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
added	O
since	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
memorandum	O
is	O
,	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
T	O
1063	O
,	O
dated	O
January	O
16th	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Matthew	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
days	O
after	O
sight	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
a	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
always	O
drawn	O
at	O
seven	O
days	O
sight	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
bill	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
I	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
post	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
this	O
very	O
particularly	O
.	O
My	O
copy	O
says	O
,	O
A	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
S	O
9864	O
,	O
dated	O
January	O
8th	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Shelly	I-pers
,	O
not	O
signed	O
;	O
33	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
but	O
I	O
observe	O
here	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
signature	O
added	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
.	O
You	O
forwarded	O
this	O
by	O
the	O
usual	O
course	O
;	O
you	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
post-office	O
at	O
Bath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ALDRIDGDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
a	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Branscomb	O
,	O
a	O
lottery-office	O
keeper	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
person	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
office	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
lottery-tickets	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
gentleman	O
about	O
this	O
ticket	O
,	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
28,257	O
.	O
)	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
that	O
came	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
midst	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
very	O
thronged	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
recollection	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
ticket	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
100	O
l.	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
cash	O
enough	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
change	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Branscomb	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
this	O
100	O
l.	O
note	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
25	O
l.	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
make	O
the	O
rest	O
up	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Joseph	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
vast	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
vast	O
many	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
eight	O
days	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
gentleman	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
another	O
ticket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
one	O
ticket	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
partial	O
to	O
any	O
number	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
undrawn	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
particular	O
about	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
little	O
red	O
Morocco	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
bill	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
cast	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
that	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
clapped	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
thigh	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
my	O
purse	O
in	O
some	O
place	O
he	O
mentioned	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
retired	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
the	O
ticket	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
me	O
a	O
bill	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
;	O
it	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
now	O
certain	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
positive	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
so	O
positive	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
ticket	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
ticket	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
that	O
ticket	O
was	O
sold	O
at	O
your	O
office	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
ticket	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
indorsed	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Mr.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BRANSCOMB	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
lottery-office	O
keeper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
possessed	O
of	O
that	O
100	O
l.	O
bill	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
100	O
l.	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
entry	O
to	O
inform	O
yourself	O
what	O
you	O
received	O
it	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
my	O
clerk	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
change	O
100	O
l.	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
three	O
25	O
l	O
.	O
Bank	O
notes	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
sum	O
exactly	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
clerk	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Waldron	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
note	O
directly	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
accepted	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALDRON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Branscomb	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
witnessing	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
number	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
issued	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
bears	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
went	O
out	O
originally	O
1063	O
;	O
now	O
it	O
stands	O
10630	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
number	O
was	O
altered	O
after	O
it	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
never	O
issue	O
any	O
Bank	O
post-bills	O
above	O
the	O
number	O
10,000	O
.	O
I	O
referred	O
to	O
the	O
books	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
altered	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
figure	O
,	O
the	O
ink	O
is	O
very	O
different	O
from	O
any	O
ink	O
we	O
use	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
Bank	O
post	O
bill	O
for	O
33	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
name	O
Nixon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
:	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Nixon	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KEENE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
merchant	O
at	O
Bristol	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
I	O
inclosed	O
sundry	O
bills	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
William	O
,	O
Henry	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
London	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
sundry	O
bank-notes	O
and	O
bills	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
about	O
400	O
l.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
cover	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
bill	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
bills	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
number	O
is	O
altered	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
0	O
added	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
174080	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bills	O
you	O
sent	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Hanson	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
K	O
17408	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
number	O
that	O
is	O
altered	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Bank	O
number	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3304	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
bill	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
bills	O
;	O
the	O
Bank	O
number	O
is	O
not	O
altered	O
,	O
nor	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
private	O
number	O
altered	O
.	O
I	O
forwarded	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
;	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
the	O
bills	O
into	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
This	O
bill	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1333	O
,	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
bills	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
;	O
the	O
Bank	O
number	O
is	O
1333	O
,	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
letter	O
delivered	O
by	O
your	O
master	O
to	O
you	O
into	O
the	O
post	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
original	O
letter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hanson	O
,	O
as	O
directed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
HANSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
cover	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Post-office	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
condition	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
now	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
bills	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
stopped	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Keene	O
.	O
This	O
letter	O
is	O
my	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
it	O
contained	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
bills	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
,	O
addressed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
William	O
,	O
Henry	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
London	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
bills	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
shop	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1781	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
purchase	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
how	O
he	O
paid	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
40	O
l.	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
I	O
received	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
wrote	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Dun-Horse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
write	O
that	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
enquired	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
indorse	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
S	O
3304	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
2d	O
Nov.	O
1780.	O
JAMES	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Draycot	O
,	O
in	O
Staffordshire	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
their	O
infancy	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
farmer	O
's	O
sons	O
brought	O
up	O
.	O
Whose	O
sons	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
brothers	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
sons	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LYON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
year	O
1780	O
,	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
Booth's-court	O
,	O
Wells-street	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
come	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
Christmas	O
?	O
-	O
George	O
did	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
he	O
then	O
assume	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
name	O
of	O
Watson	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
Johnson	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
George	O
continue	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Twenty-four	O
weeks	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
regular	O
in	O
coming	O
home	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
regular	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HAZELWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Norwich-court	O
,	O
Swallow-street	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
standing	O
there	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
Joseph	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
name	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
name	O
of	O
Johnson	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1780	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
name	O
of	O
Watson	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
my	O
evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
I	O
say	O
;	O
therefore	O
my	O
saying	O
so	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Our	O
evidence	O
is	O
not	O
prepared	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
a	O
question	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
slept	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
he	O
slept	O
out	O
two	O
nights	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
slept	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
first	O
night	O
was	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
night	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
so	O
particularly	O
to	O
notice	O
the	O
nights	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
slept	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
mere	O
lodger	O
who	O
slept	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
maid	O
lit	O
the	O
fire	O
for	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
because	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
home	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
to	O
Lyon	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
my	O
being	O
from	O
home	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
28th	O
,	O
29th	O
,	O
or	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
my	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
it	O
indeed	O
.	O
I	O
recollect	O
your	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
his	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
after	O
Christmas	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
in	O
summer	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
my	O
lodgings	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
445.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
SAMUEL	I-pers
WATSON	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
an	O
indorsement	O
upon	O
a	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
which	O
indorsement	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Dun	O
Horse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bole	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
count	O
.	O
For	O
forging	O
an	O
acceptance	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
,	O
by	O
writing	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lateward	I-pers
(	O
a	O
person	O
authorised	O
by	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
to	O
accept	O
their	O
post-bill	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
bill	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
Third	O
count	O
.	O
For	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
,	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
acceptance	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
live	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Bole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
are	O
an	O
haberdasher	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
ever	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Inform	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
jury	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
when	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1781	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
several	O
articles	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
tendered	O
this	O
note	O
for	O
payment	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
seeing	O
him	O
indorse	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Dun	O
Horse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
and	O
farther	O
,	O
from	O
our	O
bill-book	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
difference	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
cash	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
of	O
at	O
the	O
Dun	O
Horse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
tying	O
on	O
the	O
goods	O
on	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
German-Town	O
,	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
a	O
farmer	O
and	O
grazier	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
No	O
.	O
3,304	O
.	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
.	O
``	O
London	O
,	O
2d	O
Nov.	O
1780	O
.	O
At	O
seven	O
days	O
sight	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
this	O
my	O
solar	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
forty	O
pounds	O
sterling	O
,	O
value	O
received	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Burrough	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Governor	O
and	O
Company	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
''	O
Entered	B-pers
,	I-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
Padman	O
.	O
Accepted	O
,	O
23d	O
Nov.	O
1781.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lateward	I-pers
.	O
Indorsed	O
,	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Dun	O
Horse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
German-Town	O
,	O
Norfolk	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
You	O
keep	O
a	O
considerable	O
shop	O
at	O
Hackney	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
linen-drapery	O
way	O
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
customers	O
coming	O
into	O
that	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
have	O
.	O
How	O
have	O
you	O
so	O
well	O
refreshed	O
your	O
memory	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
positively	O
sworn	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
has	O
my	O
partner	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
induces	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
clear	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
passed	O
the	O
bill	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
Rotation-Office	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
discounted	O
this	O
bill	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
for	O
granted	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
bill	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
particular	O
cause	O
which	O
induced	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
countenance	O
or	O
features	O
?	O
-	O
As	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
before	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
more	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
your	O
reason	O
for	O
taking	O
more	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Undoubtedly	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
stranger	O
passes	O
a	O
bill	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
persons	O
of	O
half	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
passed	O
the	O
bill	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
PADMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Take	O
that	O
Bank	O
post-bill	O
into	O
your	O
hand	O
;	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
acceptance	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Lateward	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
well	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
note	O
issued	O
by	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
accepted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lateward	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
clerk	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Cross-examination	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Lateward	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
,	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
.	O
What	O
induces	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
opinion	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Lateward	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
wrote	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
free	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
stiff	O
laboured	O
hand	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
no	O
similitude	O
between	O
this	O
and	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
his	O
writing	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
cut	O
of	O
the	O
letters	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
point	O
out	O
the	O
difference	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Lateward	O
wrote	O
a	O
free	O
easy	O
hand	O
.	O
This	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
free	O
easy	O
hand	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
so	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
is	O
mere	O
matter	O
of	O
opinion	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
writing	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
men	O
,	O
writing	O
sometimes	O
with	O
one	O
pen	O
,	O
sometimes	O
another	O
,	O
write	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
alike	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
may	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
difference	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
turn	O
of	O
the	O
letters	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Lateward	O
would	O
have	O
written	O
a	O
better	O
hand	O
with	O
a	O
worse	O
pen	O
,	O
