TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
,	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middle	O
sex	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1782	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PLOMER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
,	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
(	O
the	O
PROPRIETOR	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
M.	O
GURNEY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
MDCCLXXXII	O
.	O
[	O
PRICE	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PLOMER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
ADAIR	I-pers
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
Erasmus	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Pricket	I-pers
John	B-pers
Vickerman	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Michael	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
*	O
Edmund	B-pers
Godsall	I-pers
*	O
Elias	B-pers
South	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
stead	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Godsall	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lingham	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Little	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
James	B-pers
Small	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pilton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Golden	I-pers
George	B-pers
Locket	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
William	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
George	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
John	B-pers
Flock	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Kane	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fulford	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
John	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Segrist	I-pers
345.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GARDINER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
bridles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
leather	O
collars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
leather	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
breast-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
sieve	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
Crosby	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
;	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
stable	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
HURRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
groom	O
to	O
Sir	O
Harry	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Hill-street	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp-lighter's-ladder	O
in	O
Lord	O
Scarborough	O
's	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
that	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
built	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Lord	O
Scarborough	O
's	O
wall	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
saddle	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
saddle	O
that	O
was	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
's	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
Sir	O
James	O
's	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
but	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
oilman	O
in	O
Rupert-street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Coach-and-Horses	O
,	O
in	O
Hill-street	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Coach-and-Horses	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Crosby	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
MILES	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crosby	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
I	O
hung	O
up	O
on	O
some	O
pegs	O
in	O
a	O
chamber	O
over	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
again	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
stable-door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
riding	O
till	O
late	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
when	O
Miles	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
hay-loft	O
fastened	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
by	O
a	O
nail	O
in	O
the	O
hasp	O
,	O
inside	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
lamp-lighter	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
sash-windows	O
;	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
whether	O
those	O
windows	O
were	O
quite	O
down	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
346.	O
CATHARINE	B-pers
BUTLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
of	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rose	B-pers
Hannah	I-pers
Elmes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
featherbeds	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
bolsters	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
woollen	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Adam	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
.	O
ADAM	B-pers
PEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tide-waiter	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldgate	B-place
parish	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
lower	I-place
precinct	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
prove	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
WESTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peal	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
has	O
some	O
lodgers	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
the	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
dirty	O
foot	O
of	O
somebody	O
who	O
had	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bed	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
parcel	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
,	O
which	O
alarmed	O
me	O
,	O
supposing	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
came	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
cooper	O
's	O
adze	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
the	O
garret	O
chimney	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
pulled	O
her	O
down	O
:	O
the	O
blue	O
jacket	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
made	O
me	O
suppose	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
a	O
chimney	O
sweeper	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
first	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
or	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
The	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blankets	O
,	O
sheets	O
,	O
pillows	O
,	O
and	O
bolster	O
,	O
were	O
scattered	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
bed	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
untied	O
.	O
Who	O
lodged	O
in	O
this	O
garret	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
Adam	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
in	O
that	O
garret	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
alarm	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
beds	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coverlid	O
;	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
made	O
fit	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
order	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
bed	O
that	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
sheet	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Peal	O
's	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
she	O
forced	O
the	O
staple	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
got	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
put	O
the	O
staple	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Adam	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
's	O
bed	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
5	O
l.	O
DAVID	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Weston	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
fire	O
!	O
thieves	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Elmes	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
adze	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
butcher	O
there	O
besides	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Elmes	O
and	O
the	O
butcher	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Weston	O
followed	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
garret-door	O
shut	O
;	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
shot	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
bed-clothes	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
blue	O
jacket	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Elwes	O
went	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
chimney	O
with	O
his	O
hatchet	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
light	O
through	O
it	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Elmes	O
took	O
his	O
axe	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
tail	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
rags	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
thigh	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fire	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
breeches	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
foot	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
nearly	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
a	O
coal	O
.	O
She	O
burst	O
out	O
a	O
crying	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
his	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
rob	O
somebody	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
killed	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
who	O
the	O
blue	O
jacket	O
belonged	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
promises	O
of	O
favour	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
Peal	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
brokering	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
above	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
that	O
bed	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
50	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shoes	O
were	O
off	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
pole-axes	O
,	O
a	O
false	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
wanted	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
shirts	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
To	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
two	O
axes	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
small	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
buried	O
the	O
eldest	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
lodged	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
garret	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
drop	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
coming	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
the	O
bed	O
stood	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
pole-axes	O
belonged	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Peal	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
347.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRYAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
damask	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
bed-gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
printed	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
printed	O
muslin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
printed	O
cotton	O
jacket	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
blue	O
sattin	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SHEFFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Spital-fields	B-place
Market	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
thieves	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
back-garret	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
about	O
ten	O
weeks	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
from	O
my	O
service	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
attempting	O
to	O
get	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
lay	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
loose	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
floor	O
:	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
she	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
-	O
NICKLIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
person	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back-chamber	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
thieves	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
face	O
;	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
lay	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
PIKE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
alarm	O
,	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
348.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
NEWTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
62	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
tallow	O
candles	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merriman	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
a	O
felony	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
349.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SIMMONDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
collar	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SIMMONDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brass	O
collar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	B-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
bitch	O
's	O
neck	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
relation	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
men	O
brought	O
the	O
collar	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CARPMEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
information	O
we	O
had	O
received	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
court	O
,	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
some	O
dogs	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
four	O
dogs	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
carcases	O
of	O
nine	O
dogs	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
skinned	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
carcases	O
more	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
carcase	O
of	O
the	O
bitch	O
skinned	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
collar	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
collar	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
came	O
together	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
wife	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
collar	O
upon	O
the	O
shelf	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
my	O
bitch	O
home	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
six	O
puppies	O
at	O
home	O
starving	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charing	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
collar	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
publicly	O
Whipped	O
,	O
&	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
350.	O
ANN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BRADY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
three	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
woollen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
ROSETTA	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LA	I-pers
NE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
gown	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
351.	O
BRYAN	B-pers
BURTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDMONDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Two	B-place
Blue	I-place
Posts	I-place
in	I-place
Old	I-place
Bond-street	I-place
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
four	O
pots	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
three	O
hours	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
containing	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
tenant	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
canvas	O
bag	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
reckoning	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
opposite	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
home	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
bag	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
bench	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
EDMONDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
breeches-pocket	O
,	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
tuck	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
shilling	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
shilling	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
father	O
in	O
change	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
352.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hair	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
eight	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
eight	O
stocks	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
nine	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
four	O
napkins	O
,	O
five	O
linen-sheets	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WISEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
oilman	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
A	O
trunk	O
,	O
with	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Hammersmith	O
coach	O
,	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
,	O
running	O
very	O
fast	O
along	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
?	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
immediately	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FORD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
driver	O
of	O
the	O
Hammersmith	O
coach	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
's	O
trunk	O
behind	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
London	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Adam-and-Eve	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
from	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
off	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Adam-and-Eve	O
like	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
smartly	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
trunk	O
,	O
with	O
its	O
contents	O
,	O
as	O
stated	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
people	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
on	O
very	O
briskly	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
353.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BROOKES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
dining-table	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Burnett	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
BURNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Fountain	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Wych-street	I-place
.	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
informed	O
me	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
table	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
back-room	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
mahogany	O
dining-table	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
table	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Burnett	I-pers
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
table	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
354.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BIGGS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
copper	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
355.	O
PETER	B-pers
AIREY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
and	O
outside	O
case	O
both	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
seals	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Awbrey	I-pers
,	O
esquire	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
opera-house	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
masquerade-night	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
a	O
man	O
drawing	O
his	O
domino	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
seised	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
verily	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
stole	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
handed	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
recovered	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
called	O
upon	O
for	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
356.	O
LAZARUS	B-pers
JACOBS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DOBEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
worth	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop-window	O
.	O
CHRISTIAN	B-pers
SADLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
in	O
my	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
DANIEL	B-pers
SERJEANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shoes	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
toss	O
the	O
shoes	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
;	O
myself	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seised	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
had	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
a	O
lad	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
directed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shoes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
shoes	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
eight	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
357.	O
JANE	B-pers
LAMECROTE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
callico	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Briddell	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
358.	O
DOROTHY	B-pers
FLEMING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Coyle	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
COYLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
our	O
garret	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
nail	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
pawn	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
my	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
359.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
and	O
outside	O
cases	O
both	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lavenu	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LAVENU	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
women	O
standing	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Bear	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
cost	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
put	O
another	O
shilling	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sleep	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
taking	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Bear	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
British	B-place
Hotel	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Shug-lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
What	O
age	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Eighteen	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
situation	O
of	O
life	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
French	O
teacher	O
.	O
Who	O
employs	O
you	O
in	O
that	O
capacity	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
father	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
clerk	O
's	O
place	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
at	O
the	O
Hotel	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
apiece	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
agreeable	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
joking	O
together	O
,	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
engaged	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
engaged	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
my	O
watch	O
would	O
hurt	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
consent	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
sofa	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
sofa	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
-	O
Rather	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
this	O
does	O
not	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
law	O
amount	O
to	O
felony	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
intrusted	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
360.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
361.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BROAD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
JANES	O
JONES	O
sworn	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
live	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
coachman	O
;	O
he	O
pays	O
the	O
rent	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
at	O
a	O
carpenter	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
two	O
men	O
rushed	O
in	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
opened	O
a	O
dark	O
lantern	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
off	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
a	O
ring	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Tom	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
usually	O
carry	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
five	O
guineas	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
light	O
but	O
from	O
the	O
dark	O
lantern	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
room	O
was	O
quite	O
light	O
from	O
the	O
lantern	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
his	O
face	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
goes	O
out	O
a	O
washing	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
next	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
The	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lantern	O
reflected	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
pocket	O
off	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
cook	O
in	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
families	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Carey-street	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
they	O
rushed	O
in	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
rooms	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dressed	O
now	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
then	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
plain	O
proof	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
hour	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
ten	O
miles	O
off	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
OXTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bargeman	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Waltham-abbey	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bargeman	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bridge	O
,	O
of	O
Cheshunt	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
wharf	O
in	O
Cheshunt	O
parish	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
unload	O
our	O
coals	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
hour	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
barge	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
and	O
this	O
man	O
were	O
a-bed	O
together	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
a-sleep	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
Bagley	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
a-bed	O
together	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
At	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
too	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
doing	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
any	O
other	O
day	O
in	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
twelfth	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
getting	O
the	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
Waltham-abbey	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
six	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
is	O
Waltham-abbey	O
from	O
Stoke-Newington	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
seven	O
miles	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
examined	O
the	O
toll-books	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
barges	O
pass	O
.	O
PHEBE	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
so	O
familiarly	O
Tom	O
Broad	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
it	O
so	O
often	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
362.	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
LEECH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
half-pint	O
mug	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
French	O
plate	O
;	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
having	O
committed	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
she	O
afterwards	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
did	O
break	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
my	O
street-door	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
servant	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
some	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
watchmen	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
examining	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
contained	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
deliver	O
up	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
French-plate	O
half	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
your	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
little	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
greater	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
recommended	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
steal	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
the	O
first	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
escape	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
month	O
within	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
person	O
live	O
that	O
recommended	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
day-light	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
till	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
in	O
Mansfield-street	O
,	O
Goodman's-fields	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Swan-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Minories	I-place
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
bundle	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
master	O
had	O
come	O
home	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
discharged	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
put	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
into	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
by	O
itself	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
master	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
her	O
mistress	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
Swan-court	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
's	O
door	O
a-jar	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
shoved	O
it	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
bundle	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
see	O
her	O
mistress	O
:	O
we	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Luke	B-pers
Herrod	I-pers
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
To	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Had	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
family	O
been	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
doors	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
particular	O
in	O
my	O
defence	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
but	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
363.	O
BARNARD	B-pers
ISAACS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
49	O
yards	O
of	O
worsted	O
binding	O
lace	O
,	O
71	O
yards	O
of	O
seaming	O
worsted	O
lace	O
,	O
36	O
yards	O
of	O
seaming	O
one	O
edge	O
lace	O
,	O
24	O
worsted	O
roses	O
,	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
glass-strings	O
and	O
holders	O
,	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
strings	O
,	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
plain	O
white	O
worsted	O
lace	O
,	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
binding	O
white	O
worsted	O
lace	O
,	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
plain	O
drab	O
worsted	O
lace	O
,	O
24	O
yards	O
of	O
binding	O
drab	O
worsted	O
lace	O
,	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
drab	O
worsted	O
lace	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
glass-string	O
trimmings	O
,	O
2	O
sets	O
of	O
worsted	O
footmen	O
's	O
holders	O
,	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
green	O
spring	O
curtain	O
lines	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
orange	O
worsted	O
footmen	O
's	O
holders	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Lyall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BUSH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lyall	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Bear	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
warehouse	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
booking	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
sending	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
carrier	O
.	O
The	O
parcel	O
alluded	O
to	O
came	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
booked	O
it	O
;	O
i	O
t	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Morton	O
and	O
Co.	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
coachmakers	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
booked	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Bath	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
soon	O
after	O
wrote	O
a	O
way-bill	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
one	O
Burton	O
,	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
go	O
that	O
afternoon	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
another	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
ZACHARIAH	B-pers
BATTERBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
who	O
deals	O
in	O
coach	O
and	O
livery	O
laces	O
;	O
Messrs	O
Morton	O
and	O
Co.	O
of	O
Bath	O
,	O
deal	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
for	O
coach	O
laces	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
a	O
paper	O
parcel	O
,	O
containing	O
the	O
articles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Morton	O
and	O
Co.	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
delilivered	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Rees	I-pers
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Bear	O
Inn	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Bath	O
coach	O
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
REES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Batterby	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
delivered	O
me	O
a	O
paper	O
parcel	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Bear	O
Inn	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Morton	O
and	O
Co.	O
at	O
Bath	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bush	O
.	O
To	O
Bush	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
this	O
parcel	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
rooms	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
NATHANIEL	B-pers
HEATHCOTE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
,	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
and	O
Birmingham	O
coaches	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
Amos	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
hearing	O
an	O
indifferent	O
character	O
of	O
Amos	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
of	O
one	O
Barnard	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
consulted	O
with	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gaoler	O
of	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
open	O
the	O
box	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
contained	O
lace	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
was	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
letters	O
.	O
(	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Batterby	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
produced	O
by	O
Heathcote	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
packed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Morton	O
and	O
Co.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
letters	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Batterby	I-pers
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
inclosed	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
directed	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Morton	O
and	O
Co.	O
)	O
Heathcote	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
these	O
two	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
to	O
Justice	O
Addington	O
.	O
This	O
letter	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
wrote	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
for	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
inadvertently	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
letter	O
was	O
read	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
dated	O
April	O
29	O
,	O
1782	O
;	O
directed	O
,	O
Dear	O
Mother	O
and	O
Friend	O
Archer	O
;	O
and	O
signed	O
,	O
Barnard	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
.	O
In	O
a	O
postscript	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
coachmaker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
your	O
best	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Bath	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Heathcote	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
not	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
besides	O
what	O
is	O
contained	O
in	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
few	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
Amos	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
a	O
Middlesex	O
magistrate	O
,	O
backed	O
by	O
an	O
alderman	O
,	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
letters	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I.	O
read	O
.	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
30th	O
,	O
1782	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
Expecting	O
a	O
parcel	O
by	O
this	O
day	O
's	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
their	O
not	O
sending	O
the	O
parcel	O
home	O
,	O
therefore	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
found	O
the	O
parcel	O
is	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
hand	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
immediately	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Swan-with-two-Necks	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
You	O
will	O
answer	O
this	O
with	O
the	O
morrow	O
coach	O
.	O
(	O
Signed	O
)	O
AMOS	B-pers
ARCHER	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Directed	O
)	O
To	O
Barnard	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Archer	O
to	O
Barnard	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
,	O
dated	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
May	O
4	O
,	O
1782	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
box	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
desires	O
Isaac	O
to	O
copy	O
a	O
fictitious	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Isaac	O
,	O
of	O
different	O
quantities	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
10	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
as	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
imagined	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
had	O
in	O
truth	O
been	O
intercepted	O
by	O
Heathcote	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
defence	O
to	O
his	O
counsel	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
bring	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
inclosed	O
in	O
a	O
parcel	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
called	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watch-string	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
364.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COMMINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
of	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
men	O
in	O
Stepney-fields	B-place
.	O
They	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
kicked	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
with	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
right-hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
dark	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
sufficient	O
light	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
countenance	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dusk	O
,	O
neither	O
light	O
nor	O
dark	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hat	O
flapped	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
very	O
much	O
frightened	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
little	O
frightened	O
;	O
God	O
kept	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
prisoners	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
You	O
sulky	O
negro	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
fixed	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
What	O
description	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
you	O
laid	O
the	O
information	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
red-faced	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
description	O
you	O
gave	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
Upon	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
dressed	O
either	O
in	O
blue	O
or	O
brown	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
any	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
expressed	O
no	O
doubt	O
whatever	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
identity	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
GLENTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
by	O
direction	O
of	O
Justice	O
Staples	O
,	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
persons	O
who	O
were	O
tried	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
and	O
convicted	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
had	O
cutlasses	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
stick	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
(	O
John	B-pers
M'Guire	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
confirmed	O
his	O
testimony	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
womb	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
-	O
LEVI	O
sworn	O
,	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Commins	O
by	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
four	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
face	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LAKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Erith	O
,	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
my	O
son	O
being	O
there	O
on	O
a	O
charge	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Commins	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
sworn	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brick-maker	O
,	O
and	O
employ	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
men	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CASTLEDINE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
King	O
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
in	O
Bluecross-street	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
particularly	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
hurt	O
my	O
arm	O
on	O
the	O
preceding	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
any	O
longer	O
;	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Feathers	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
what	O
dress	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
supposed	O
that	O
I	O
robbed	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
coat	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
dress	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
robbed	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Lake	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
Justice	O
Sherwood	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
that	O
question	O
about	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
should	O
ask	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
ask	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
ask	O
it	O
.	O
SUSANNA	B-pers
GUTHELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
clothes	O
he	O
was	O
possessed	O
of	O
on	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
brown	O
close-bodied	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
coat	O
:	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
I	O
keep	O
company	O
with	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
without	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
365.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FRENLOW	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Mr.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
two	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
Warwick-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
turned	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
dropped	O
it	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
hastily	O
into	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
occasioned	O
me	O
to	O
suspect	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
secured	O
both	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
struggled	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
before	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
ward	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
:	O
in	O
that	O
pocket	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
clasp	O
knife	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
otherwise	O
I	O
am	O
persuaded	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
secured	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Proctor	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
for	O
trial	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Proctor	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
PROCTOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
knife	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
else	O
in	O
that	O
pocket	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
other	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
leather	O
strap	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
what	O
purpose	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
leather	O
strap	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
&	O
Imp	O
.	O
12	O
M	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
366.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BURN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Capell	B-pers
Cure	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PYOT	I-pers
WESTLAKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Bennetts	O
and	O
Cure	O
.	O
In	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
tea	O
to	O
be	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
story	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Paul	B-pers
Etheredge	I-pers
weigh	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
loose	O
on	O
a	O
cover	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
men	O
went	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
be	O
weighed	O
again	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pound	O
deficient	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bennett	O
said	O
the	O
men	O
should	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
immediately	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
was	O
shifting	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
or	O
hiding	O
it	O
:	O
after	O
calling	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
porters	O
were	O
all	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bennett	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
,	O
searched	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
spot	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
,	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
foul	O
paper	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
block	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
tie	O
up	O
parcels	O
occasionally	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
agree	O
exactly	O
in	O
quantity	O
and	O
quality	O
with	O
the	O
tea	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
put	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
following	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
secreted	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
what	O
passed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
ordered	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
to	O
quit	O
the	O
warehouse	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
pull	O
the	O
paper	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
bag	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
tea	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
hunted	O
a	O
few	O
seconds	O
eagerly	O
among	O
the	O
papers	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
discover	O
the	O
bag	O
:	O
upon	O
his	O
finding	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
reached	O
the	O
second	O
story	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
name	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
tea	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
theft	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
you	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
PAUL	B-pers
ETHERIDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shop-porter	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Bennetts	O
and	O
Cure	O
.	O
I	O
weighed	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
spread	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
cover	O
;	O
I	O
weighed	O
the	O
tea	O
again	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
missing	O
then	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
wanting	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
move	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
their	O
scheme	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
seen	O
his	O
face	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
under	O
the	O
block	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
answered	O
in	O
quantity	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Wken	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
kicked	O
my	O
foot	O
against	O
this	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
story	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Daniel	B-pers
Knowlan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
soap-maker	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
367.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
MILLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
moist	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Gallopine	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
ROLLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
89	O
,	O
in	O
Tower-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Johnson	O
,	O
a	O
journeyman	O
cooper	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
turned	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Gallopine	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
11	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
sugar	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gallopine	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
used	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
keeping	O
sugar	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
closet	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
Upon	O
comparing	O
the	O
sugar	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
as	O
that	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gallopine	O
's	O
sugar	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
sugar	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
three	O
fatherless	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
sugar	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
a	O
sugar-porter	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
eat	O
some	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
broken	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
thankful	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
these	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
apron	O
from	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
nose	O
bleed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
&	O
Imp	O
.	O
6	O
M	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
368.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
half-pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Friday-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Lasts	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
and	O
a	O
half-pint	O
pot	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Blue	O
Lasts	O
;	O
in	O
Distaff-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
the	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
pots	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
pots	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
gathering	O
in	O
her	O
pots	O
,	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
pots	O
among	O
hers	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
369.	O
ANDREW	B-pers
GIFFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
perukes	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Callahan	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
CALLAHAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Little	B-place
Bell-alley	I-place
,	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
men	O
's	O
perukes	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
just	O
made	O
for	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
customers	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
old	O
wig	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
old	O
tail	O
wigs	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
might	O
produce	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
opposite	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
shop	O
,	O
beckoned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
wigs	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
could	O
she	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
information	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
neighbours	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
wigs	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
describe	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
directly	O
sent	O
out	O
her	O
servant-girl	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
.	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
wigs	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
.	O
Some	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
from	O
the	O
blocks	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
wigs	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
probably	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public-house	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sleeping	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
soldier	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
rescued	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
STEELE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brady	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
with	O
these	O
six	O
wigs	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
she	O
stopped	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
such	O
wigs	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Callahan	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
those	O
wigs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
them	O
over	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
old	O
clothes	O
and	O
old	O
wigs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
six	O
wigs	O
were	O
offered	O
me	O
for	O
sale	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
till	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
proof	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
with	O
the	O
wigs	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
wigs	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
's	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brady	O
's	O
before	O
you	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
3	O
s.	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
Before	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
3	O
s.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
370.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
LEVY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
woollen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hammelburg	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HAMMELBURG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
crimson	O
coat	O
and	O
breeches	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
clothes	O
home	O
by	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
wrapper	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HAMMELBURG	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
clothes	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
loitering	O
upon	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
return	O
me	O
the	O
woollen	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
clothes	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
.	O
He	O
returned	O
me	O
the	O
clothes	O
and	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
towards	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
clothes	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
returned	O
me	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
off	O
down	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
through	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
clothes	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
servant	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
they	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
this	O
public-house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
clothes	O
from	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
crying	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
NICHOLAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
whom	O
these	O
clothes	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
behaviour	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
clothes	O
from	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
returned	O
them	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
TRUELOVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother-in-law	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
joined	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
the	O
publican	O
turned	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
orders	O
to	O
a	O
taylor	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
clothes	O
of	O
a	O
maroon	O
colour	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
these	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
clothes	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
371.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
ALLINGHAM	I-pers
(	O
a	O
negro	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baptista	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BAPTISTA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Orange	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
twelve	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
compulsion	O
went	O
to	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
2.	I-place
in	I-place
Gloucester-court	I-place
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
let	O
us	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
smelt	O
so	O
strong	O
and	O
disagreeable	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
enough	O
to	O
poison	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
My	O
breeches-pocket	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
coat-pocket	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
;	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
valuable	O
pocketbook	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
button	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
shallow	O
one	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
she	O
forced	O
her	O
way	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
struggle	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
HATTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
near	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
being	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
black	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
concealed	O
in	O
Gloucester-court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
purse	O
with	O
six	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
saved	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
BATEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Gloucester-court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
once	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
before	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
:	O
They	O
both	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
minutes	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
woman	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
water	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Ma'am	O
,	O
you	O
brought	O
the	O
gentleman	O
in	O
;	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
rushed	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
spoke	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Another	O
young	O
lady	O
came	O
in	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
This	O
money	O
they	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
saved	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
gentleman	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
woman	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
and	O
white	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
was	O
entirely	O
unbuttoned	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
rails	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
towards	O
Pall-Mall	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
stone	O
of	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
Gloucester-court	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
house	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
into	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
woman	O
;	O
my	O
money	O
is	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pin	O
valued	O
at	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
at	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
As	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
carcase	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
liberty	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
water	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
dry	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
my	O
cloak	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
what	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
neither	O
fit	O
for	O
God	O
nor	O
the	O
devil	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
neither	O
fit	O
for	O
a	O
black	O
woman	O
,	O
nor	O
a	O
white	O
woman	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
expressed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
put	O
a	O
shock	O
upon	O
my	O
spirits	O
,	O
and	O
frightened	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
Take	O
this	O
man	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
be	O
meer	O
wickedness	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
condescend	O
to	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
he	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
close	O
quarters	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
arm	O
's	O
length	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
GAGG	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
almost	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
:	O
she	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
saved	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
lived	O
upon	O
bread	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
good	O
cloaths	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
guineas	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
What	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
was	O
she	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
.	O
)	O
372	O
,	O
373.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MERRY	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
straw	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fox	B-place
and	I-place
Knot	I-place
yard	I-place
.	O
I	O
looked	O
after	O
the	O
yard	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tarlin	O
:	O
Mess	O
.	O
William	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
who	O
are	O
oilmen	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
stable	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
kept	O
their	O
cart	O
horses	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
straw	O
,	O
handed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
loft	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Price	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
the	O
stables	O
.	O
Davis	O
stood	O
below	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
hay	O
and	O
straw	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
trusses	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
was	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bedell	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
general	O
superintendant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
affairs	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
truss	O
was	O
carrying	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Bedell	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
after	O
Davis	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
.	O
Davis	O
had	O
been	O
turned	O
off	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
new	O
carter	O
,	O
the	O
porter	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
horses	O
till	O
a	O
new	O
carter	O
should	O
be	O
appointed	O
.	O
Bedell	O
has	O
absconded	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Ann	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
PRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
in	O
the	O
oil	O
business	O
.	O
Davis	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
turned	O
off	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Merry	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
Davis	O
had	O
been	O
turned	O
away	O
,	O
one	O
or	O
other	O
of	O
our	O
porters	O
drove	O
our	O
horses	O
.	O
Davis	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
many	O
years	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
neither	O
Merry	O
or	O
Davis	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
Davis	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
Merry	O
.	O
Merry	O
asked	O
,	O
For	O
what	O
am	O
I	O
taken	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
hay	O
and	O
straw	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
denied	O
the	O
matter	O
:	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
second	O
examination	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
hay	O
and	O
straw	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
.	O
MERRY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
obey	O
Bedell	O
's	O
orders	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
ordered	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Bedell	O
had	O
the	O
general	O
management	O
of	O
the	O
oil	O
business	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
eating	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
dinner	O
,	O
in	O
Fox	O
and	O
Knot	O
yard	O
,	O
Bedell	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
:	O
he	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
throw	O
out	O
the	O
hay	O
and	O
straw	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
borrowed	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
hay	O
and	O
straw	O
was	O
flung	O
out	O
,	O
Bedell	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
and	O
help	O
Davis	O
carry	O
it	O
.	O
DAVIS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
horses	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
stable-yard	O
;	O
Bedell	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
carry	O
a	O
tru	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
present	O
near	O
the	O
loft	O
till	O
the	O
hay	O
and	O
straw	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
(	O
Merry	O
called	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
.	O
)	O
374	O
,	O
375.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BASS	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PICKERING	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1213	O
yards	O
of	O
spotted	O
cotton	O
gauze	O
,	O
value	O
70	O
l.	O
-	O
93	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
spotted	O
cotton	O
gauze	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
-	O
99	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
-	O
6	O
silk	O
gauze	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gatfee	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GATFEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Skinner-street	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
gauzes	O
to	O
Bass	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
a	O
particular	O
place	O
.	O
-	O
GATFEE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
goods	O
myself	O
to	O
Bass	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gatfee	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
Bass	O
:	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
sleepy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Pickering	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
proposed	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
consented	O
to	O
;	O
and	O
Pickering	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
actually	O
bought	O
