TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1788	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E	B-pers
.	I-pers
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCLXXXVIII	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BURNELL	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHHURST	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
ADAIR	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
John	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
*	O
William	B-pers
Corrock	I-pers
*	O
John	B-pers
Warboys	I-pers
served	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Corrock	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Dolly	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
William	B-pers
Geeve	I-pers
William	B-pers
Munt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Skillman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
Edmund	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchinson	I-pers
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boyes	I-pers
+	O
Archibald	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
served	O
on	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boyes	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gosford	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
James	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
William	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
Joyce	B-pers
Coombes	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
George	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Norbery	I-pers
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Allaway	I-pers
253.	O
LUKE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arundell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	O
ARUNDELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Pennington-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Old	I-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
,	O
one	O
door	O
was	O
double	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
was	O
bolted	O
with	O
two	O
bolts	O
;	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
bolted	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
get	O
into	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
home	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
chamber	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
candle	O
moving	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Fox	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
double	O
locked	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
nobody	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
the	O
garret	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
we	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
laughed	O
at	O
us	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
moved	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
drawer	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
clothes	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
bid	O
been	O
moved	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ABBOTT	I-pers
.	O
What	O
age	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
eleven	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
ten	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
eleven	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
my	O
little	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
Sir	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
will	O
happen	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
swear	O
falsely	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
happen	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Everlasting	O
punishment	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ABBOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Take	O
care	O
to	O
tell	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
getting	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Arundell	O
's	O
window	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
man	O
get	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
get	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
seven	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
light	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
getting	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
on	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
alight	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
day-light	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Besides	O
the	O
candle	O
then	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
daylight	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ARLINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
getting	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
pounds	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
!	O
these	O
old	O
clothes	O
worth	O
three	O
pounds	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
25	O
s.	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
254.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
BRICKMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wenman	I-pers
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value10	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wenman	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
younger	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wenman	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WENMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
West	B-place
Drayton	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Uxbridge	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
nobody	O
else	O
;	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
out	O
a	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
hedging	O
and	O
ditching	O
;	O
about	O
two	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Wenman	I-pers
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
all	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
broke	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
rag	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
before	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
new	O
broken	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crown-piece	O
belonging	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
half-a-guinea	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
lad	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
he	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
lad	O
that	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WENMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
further	O
than	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Leather-seller	O
's	O
Arms	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
near	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
ALLWIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
waistcoat	O
that	O
Lloyd	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
never	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
near	O
Drayton	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
waistcoat	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wenman	I-pers
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
button	O
being	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
spot	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
little	O
girl	O
set	O
up	O
)	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Nine	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
.	O
(	O
No	O
answer	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
an	O
oath	O
means	O
.	O
(	O
No	O
answer	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
would	O
happen	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
swear	O
false	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
learned	O
your	O
catechism	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
this	O
child	O
is	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
evidence	O
without	O
the	O
child	O
of	O
the	O
capital	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
besides	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
character	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
far	O
off	O
home	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
But	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
255.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILLOUGHBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sir	O
Ralph	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
cloth	O
box	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
three	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
;	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Damarain	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
DAMARAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
;	O
Sir	O
Ralph	O
Milbank	O
's	O
son	O
married	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
's	O
sister	O
;	O
Sir	O
Ralph	B-pers
Milbank	I-pers
's	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Harley-street	O
,	O
Mary-le-bone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
things	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
coach-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
between	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
and	O
half	O
after	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
stables	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
five	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
spring	O
lock	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
light	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
stables	O
;	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
either	O
by	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
pick-lock	O
key	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
coat	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach-house	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stables	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
coat	O
and	O
sheets	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Chambers	O
;	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
stables	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
in	O
the	O
stables	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
one	O
coat	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
cloth	O
coats	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
only	O
one	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
POPPLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
hackney	O
coaches	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
clothes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Damarain	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
coat	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
coat	O
belongs	O
to	O
Captain	O
Chambers	B-pers
;	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
servant	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
Twenty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Brice	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
one	O
coat	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
value	O
half-a-guinea	O
.	O
Damarain	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
to	O
Damarain	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Captain	O
Chambers	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Sir	O
Ralph	O
Milbank	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
Captain	O
Chambers	B-pers
lives	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
31	O
,	O
in	O
Norton-street	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
horses	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
doors	O
are	O
there	O
to	O
those	O
stables	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
doors	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
laundry	O
into	O
the	O
stables	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
into	O
the	O
coach-house	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stables	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
five	O
hours	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
coat	O
of	O
that	O
appearance	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
sheets	O
were	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
POPPLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
clothes	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
where	O
my	O
brother	O
has	O
stables	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
your	O
brother	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
clothes	O
?	O
-	O
Thirty-seven	O
shillings	O
for	O
these	O
three	O
that	O
I	O
produce	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
.	O
Would	O
they	O
sell	O
for	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
that	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
would	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
,	O
conscientiously	O
,	O
as	O
old	O
clothes	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
an	O
old	O
clothes-man	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
again	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ZEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Donner	I-pers
and	O
another	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
office	O
in	O
Poland-street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
who	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Blacketer	I-pers
went	O
to	O
the	O
stables	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
Blacketer	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
coats	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
Popple	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
.	O
What	O
conversation	O
passed	O
previous	O
to	O
his	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
coats	O
were	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
was	O
between	O
Blacketer	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
Blacketer	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
coats	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
expression	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
into	O
the	O
stables	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
down	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Blacketer	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
to-day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
sister	O
,	O
also	O
attended	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Counsel	O
declined	O
calling	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
256.	O
PHEBE	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
containing	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Faulding	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FAULDING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Coventry-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
printed	O
callico	O
;	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
remnants	O
of	O
callicoes	O
;	O
after	O
looking	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
small	O
quantity	O
,	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
she	O
took	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
myself	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
twice	O
had	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
publick	O
office	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
I	O
concealed	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
false	O
address	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
called	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
spite	O
;	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
cotton	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
hang	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
257.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COTTERELL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
containing	O
ten	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
in	O
Dartmouth-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
losta	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
cloak	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
down	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
beside	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
dropped	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
confidently	O
say	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
her	O
right	O
arm	O
;	O
it	O
dropped	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
the	O
end	O
next	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
three	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
many	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
drop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
it	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
TOKELEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
shopwoman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
that	O
lawn	O
that	O
your	O
master	O
has	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
served	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
piece	O
she	O
supported	O
against	O
the	O
counter	O
by	O
leaning	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
serving	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
measuring	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
serve	O
her	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
observed	O
the	O
lawn	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
Before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
near	O
where	O
she	O
stood	O
,	O
just	O
under	O
her	O
feet	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
lawn	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
observed	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
like	O
that	O
lawn	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Seeing	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
feet	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
that	O
unless	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
This	O
lawn	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lawn	O
just	O
under	O
her	O
feet	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
lawn	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Has	O
that	O
lawn	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
marking	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
counsel	O
.	O
Richard	O
Perry	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
an	O
oath	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
quaker	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
an	O
oath	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
objection	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
?	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
call	O
God	O
to	O
witness	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
:	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
objection	O
to	O
taking	O
such	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
PHEBE	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
labours	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
bread	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
258.	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
FLANNAGAN	I-pers
and	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
COLLETT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
box	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BARRETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Crescent	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Crescent	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
gates	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
not	O
more	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Moses	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
indicted	O
as	O
receiver	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
from	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Moses	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
immediately	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Moses	O
threw	O
the	O
coat	O
away	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
Mrs.	O
Moses	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
justified	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
take	O
the	O
earliest	O
opportunity	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
coat	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
FLANNAGAN	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
COLLETT	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
I	O
kicked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Flannagan	O
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
value	O
.	O
HUMPHREY	B-pers
FLANNAGAN	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
COLLETT	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
259.	O
ANN	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Albermarle-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
informed	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
's	O
Esq	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
46	O
,	O
Albermarle-street	O
;	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
entire	O
stranger	O
to	O
us	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
speaking	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
her	O
within	O
two	O
steps	O
of	O
the	O
top	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
water-cresses	O
for	O
the	O
man-cook	O
that	O
I	O
serve	O
every	O
morning	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
gown	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
none	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
for	O
;	O
Itold	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
giving	O
the	O
man-cook	O
his	O
water-cresses	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
260.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JULKS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
,	O
affixed	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LUMLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bell-yard	B-place
,	I-place
Temple-bar	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
from	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sucker	O
from	O
the	O
cistern	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
cistern	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
it	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BULLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patrol	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
past	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
,	O
but	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
questions	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
lead	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lumley	O
's	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lumley	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
compare	O
that	O
lead	O
with	O
what	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lumley	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
upon	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
the	O
privy	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
fitted	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lead	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
some	O
work	O
;	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
discerned	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
patrol	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
261.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
CONNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
weight	O
twenty-four	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwin	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
affixed	O
to	O
his	O
stable	O
.	O
-	O
ALVERTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Compton-street	B-place
facing	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
stables	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
doing	O
something	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
getting	O
the	O
bar	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
scuffled	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
just	O
dropped	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
patrol	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
crow	O
which	O
he	O
dropped	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bar	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
dropped	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bloomsbury-square	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
iron	O
bar	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
crow	O
;	O
andhe	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
with	O
these	O
five	O
bars	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
fully	O
committed	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
GADDY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
these	O
bars	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
bars	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
(	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
bar	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
a	O
nonplus	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
262.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DUFF	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dance	O
,	O
in	O
Mortimer-street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
STENSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
gowns	O
belong	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dance	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
gowns	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dance	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
married	O
to	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Dance	I-pers
;	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
gowns	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
four	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dance	O
in	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
it	O
opens	O
to	O
a	O
passage	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARREN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Dance	O
's	O
dressing-room	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
four	O
by	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dance	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
that	O
lead	O
to	O
the	O
servant	O
's	O
apartments	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
in	O
confusion	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
confusion	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
otherwise	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
equivocating	O
manner	O
,	O
spoke	O
chimnies	O
,	O
chimnies	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
about	O
the	O
chimnies	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
Donnellan	O
in	O
Portugal-street	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
the	O
under	O
butler	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
,	O
seeing	O
these	O
things	O
lay	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
into	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Hyde-Park-corner	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
wire	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
The	O
CONSTABLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
boy	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
wire	O
with	O
a	O
hook	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Warren	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dance	O
's	O
two	O
gowns	O
were	O
on	O
some	O
steps	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stenson	O
.	O
You	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
after	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Dance	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
wear	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
another	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dance	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
gown	O
by	O
my	O
wearing	O
it	O
and	O
buying	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
sweep	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
sweeping	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
chimnies	O
wanted	O
sweeping	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
area	O
gate	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
attacked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
me	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
dead	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
263.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
four	O
horse-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
horse-buckle	O
tongues	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
JACOB	B-pers
GLOVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
harness-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
tongues	O
.	O
BRIDGET	B-pers
ELWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
buckles	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
set	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
;	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
set	O
ready	O
by	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
four	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
these	O
buckles	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
shop	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
agreement	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
hesitated	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
brought	O
the	O
tongues	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
other	O
six-pence	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
tongues	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
and	O
gone	O
to	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
tongues	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
came	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
Simpson	O
had	O
brought	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
.	O
BENJ	O
.	O
DOUGHTY	O
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Jacob	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
bring	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
These	O
buckles	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
iron	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
file	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
they	O
are	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
iron	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
may	O
never	O
see	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
my	O
maker	O
;	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GLOVER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
taking	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
them	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
must	O
not	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
must	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
out	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
I	O
chose	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
numerous	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
young	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
264.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
BIRD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
side	O
of	O
an	O
iron	O
grate	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
an	O
iron	O
axle-tree	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
and	O
steel	O
anvil	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foley	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FOLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Penington-street	O
,	O
Ratcliffe-highway	O
;	O
my	O
work-shop	O
is	O
in	O
White	B-place
's	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
Rosemary-lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
,	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
anvil	O
covered	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
;	O
(	O
Produced	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
anvil	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
remarkable	O
as	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
mended	O
it	O
once	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
broke	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
it	O
a	O
great	O
weight	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
Can	O
a	O
man	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ELBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
anvil	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
seven	O
weeks	O
,	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
laying-in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
walking	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
late	O
,	O
I	O
lighted	O
on	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
the	O
anvil	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
little	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
eighteen-pence	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
going	O
any	O
further	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
abide	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
drove	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
neighbourly	O
action	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
dangerous	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
my	O
own	O
case	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
set	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officers	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
265.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BAYLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
leaden	O
glue-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
;	O
a	O
glue-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
glue-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
patrol	O
with	O
the	O
glue-pots	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHHURST	O
.	O
266.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
BRAGG	I-pers
was	O
indictedfor	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
taylor	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
shirts	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
ware-house	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Scott	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
Scott	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
continued	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
took	O
up	O
the	O
shirts	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
in	O
Phoenix-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
Smith	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
ran	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
rather	O
walking	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
bundle	O
over	O
his	O
shoulders	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirts	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HIGHFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
half-a-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
ding	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
hang	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
the	O
two	O
shirts	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
grate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
a	O
man	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
267.	O
ANN	B-pers
BREWER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
French	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
FRENCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
;	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
drawers	O
usually	O
kept	O
locked	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
another	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
bureau	O
inher	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
drawers	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FENNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
in	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
duplicates	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Miss	O
French	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coney	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Miss	O
French	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
Mrs.	O
Rowley	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
thirty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
268.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SALMON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
ten	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
cardamums	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Grote	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Meyer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Meyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
Meyer	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
STULPNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Messrs.	O
Grote	O
and	O
Co.	O
merchants	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
between	O
two	O
heaps	O
of	O
cardamums	O
that	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Lovat	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
pilfering	O
the	O
cardamums	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
our	O
porters	O
generally	O
lock	O
up	O
the	O
warehouse	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
communicated	O
my	O
suspicions	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
discovered	O
him	O
through	O
the	O
keyhole	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
discovered	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
material	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
collared	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
about	O
ten	O
pound	O
of	O
cardamums	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
pockets	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
contained	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
them	O
and	O
filled	O
the	O
linings	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
porters	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
occasionally	O
employed	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
discharged	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
borne	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
to	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ELLIOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Grote	O
and	O
Co.	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
by	O
the	O
cardamums	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
key-hole	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
view	O
was	O
so	O
imperfect	O
,	O
that	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Lovat	I-pers
,	O
the	O
warehouseman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
contain	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
cardamums	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
empty	O
his	O
pockets	O
upon	O
the	O
cardamums	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
emptied	O
ten	O
pounds	O
of	O
cardamums	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
piece	O
of	O
conduct	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
has	O
he	O
borne	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
any	O
family	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
wife	O
and	O
children	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LOVAT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouseman	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Groteand	O
Co.	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
defence	O
to	O
my	O
Counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
269.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LANGDON	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
fifty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sixpenny	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
Banner	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
270.	O
DAVID	B-pers
CLARY	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GOMBERT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
did	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
and	O
burn	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
David	B-pers
Clary	I-pers
;	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Imray	I-pers
being	O
near	O
his	O
dwelling	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
whereof	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
and	O
burnt	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
and	O
burn	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Imray	I-pers
,	O
in	O
manner	O
and	O
form	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
peace	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
that	O
he	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
,	O
did	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
and	O
burn	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Imray	I-pers
.	O
A	O
third	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
unlawfully	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
Fourth	O
,	O
fifth	O
,	O
and	O
sixth	O
Counts	O
.	O
Calling	O
it	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Alex	B-pers
.	I-pers
Durham	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Imray	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
called	O
over	O
and	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ordered	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
prisoners	O
Counsel	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
particular	O
circumstances	O
of	O
this	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
rather	O
feel	O
myself	O
hurt	O
when	O
I	O
address	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
stage	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
;	O
for	O
although	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
be	O
stated	O
now	O
,	O
yet	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
prosecution	O
evidently	O
carried	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-office	O
,	O
against	O
which	O
this	O
party	O
has	O
a	O
claim	O
if	O
he	O
be	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
charge	O
;	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
the	O
indictment	O
is	O
ill	O
conceived	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
wrong	O
to	O
quash	O
it	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
these	O
counts	O
exhibit	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
and	O
felony	O
;	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
therefore	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
first	O
count	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
is	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
only	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
count	O
is	O
clearly	O
for	O
a	O
felony	O
;	O
if	O
that	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
objection	O
.	O
The	O
substantive	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
,	O
did	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
and	O
burn	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
feloniously	O
to	O
burn	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Imray	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
count	O
stopped	O
there	O
;	O
-	O
does	O
it	O
stop	O
there	O
?	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
goes	O
on	O
,	O
``	O
by	O
means	O
whereof	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Imray	I-pers
was	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
and	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Imray	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Now	O
the	O
adjective	O
there	O
is	O
attached	O
to	O
the	O
intention	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
they	O
come	O
to	O
found	O
that	O
this	O
house	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
also	O
charged	O
that	O
he	O
feloniously	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
David	B-pers
Clary	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
certainly	O
a	O
felony	O
distinctly	O
charged	O
;	O
a	O
felony	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
intervention	O
of	O
a	O
misdemeanor	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Silvester	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
am	O
I	O
admited	O
to	O
speak	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Though	O
you	O
are	O
permitted	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
greatly	O
to	O
your	O
own	O
disadvantage	O
to	O
begin	O
your	O
defence	O
before	O
they	O
begin	O
your	O
charge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
God	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
justice	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
innocent	O
man	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
endeavour	O
to	O
do	O
you	O
justice	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
on	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Silvester	O
,	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
:	O
My	O
Lord	O
and	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
;	O
the	O
charge	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
is	O
for	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Imray	O
,	O
laid	O
in	O
one	O
count	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Durham	O
and	O
Imray	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
state	O
the	O
out-lines	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
witnesses	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
go	O
into	O
great	O
length	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
rather	O
to	O
state	O
it	O
generally	O
,	O
than	O
particularly	O
;	O
the	O
charge	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
adjoining	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
law	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
who	O
only	O
burns	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
whether	O
as	O
tenant	O
at	O
will	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
as	O
tenant	O
for	O
years	O
;	O
therefore	O
,	O
the	O
charge	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
was	O
burnt	O
and	O
consumed	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
charge	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
he	O
burnt	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
his	O
neighbour	O
;	O
that	O
makes	O
this	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
triable	O
before	O
you	O
as	O
such	O
.	O
In	O
cases	O
of	O
this	O
nature	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
being	O
committed	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
people	O
are	O
asleep	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
proved	O
by	O
circumstantial	O
evidence	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
no	O
evidence	O
is	O
so	O
strong	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
which	O
depends	O
on	O
circumstances	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
that	O
evidence	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
fabricated	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
but	O
must	O
arise	O
from	O
the	O
transaction	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
arise	O
from	O
the	O
conduct	O
and	O
demeanor	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
that	O
offence	O
:	O
You	O
will	O
therefore	O
consider	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
,	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
the	O
defendant	O
,	O
his	O
conduct	O
previous	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
his	O
conduct	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
his	O
conduct	O
subsequent	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
:	O
if	O
from	O
his	O
conduct	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
manner	O
and	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
the	O
different	O
circumstances	O
that	O
arise	O
from	O
that	O
conduct	O
,	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
behaviour	O
,	O
it	O
convinces	O
you	O
that	O
this	O
fire	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
accidental	O
fire	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
done	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
then	O
be	O
to	O
judge	O
,	O
whether	O
these	O
circumstances	O
which	O
will	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convince	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
honest	O
men	O
,	O
on	O
your	O
oaths	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
alone	O
,	O
were	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
offence	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
circumstances	O
I	O
shall	O
lay	O
before	O
you	O
are	O
shortly	O
these	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Clary	O
is	O
by	O
trade	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
but	O
sold	O
ready-made	O
clothes	O
,	O
in	O
Little	O
Poultney-street	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
cohabited	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
housekeeper	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
previous	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
fire	O
happened	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
they	O
occupied	O
the	O
front	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
clothes	O
he	O
sold	O
were	O
hung	O
to	O
view	O
;	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
were	O
let	O
out	O
to	O
lodgers	O
,	O
some	O
unfurnished	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
ready-furnished	O
;	O
during	O
the	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
which	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
once	O
thought	O
of	O
insuring	O
his	O
property	O
till	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
insured	O
his	O
property	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
900	O
l.	O
stating	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
household	O
goods	O
were	O
worth	O
136	O
l.	O
his	O
utensils	O
in	O
trade	O
,	O
620	O
l.	O
his	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
50	O
l.	O
plate	O
46	O
l.	O
china	O
and	O
glass	O
,	O
48	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
insurance	O
he	O
makes	O
,	O
amounting	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
900	O
l.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
evidence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
a	O
lodger	O
who	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
heard	O
persons	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
parlor	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
warehouse	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Clary	O
;	O
at	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
lodger	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
at	O
eleven	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
continued	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
doing	O
some	O
business	O
with	O
some	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
the	O
cracking	O
of	O
a	O
wainscot	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
burning	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
parlor	O
,	O
the	O
manand	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
dressed	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
breeches	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
stockings	O
on	O
;	O
in	O
that	O
situation	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
without	O
attempting	O
or	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
save	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
stood	O
,	O
perfectly	O
cool	O
and	O
indifferent	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
desiring	O
the	O
woman	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
frightened	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
clothes	O
and	O
assist	O
;	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
confirmed	O
by	O
several	O
witnesses	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
state	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
compleatly	O
dressed	O
:	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
fix	O
your	O
attention	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
undressed	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
shoes	O
or	O
stockings	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
were	O
alarmed	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
smelling	O
fire	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
two	O
people	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
or	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
no	O
answer	O
at	O
all	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
but	O
heard	O
hush	O
!	O
hush	O
!	O
from	O
one	O
person	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
neighbours	O
were	O
alarmed	O
;	O
the	O
persons	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
ware-room	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
stated	O
was	O
all	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
burst	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
room	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
observed	O
a	O
chest	O
,	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
some	O
loose	O
boards	O
joining	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wainscot	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
consumed	O
;	O
another	O
person	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
observed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
exceedingly	O
anxious	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
fire	O
came	O
from	O
below	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
flames	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
?	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Now	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
floor	O
on	O
that	O
very	O
room	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
partly	O
burnt	O
,	O
that	O
floor	O
never	O
was	O
consumed	O
;	O
observations	O
were	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
goods	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
that	O
even	O
the	O
small	O
quantity	O
of	O
clothes	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
hanging	O
up	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
:	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
evidence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
no	O
trade	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
evidence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
clothes	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
the	O
same	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
very	O
few	O
goods	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
plate	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
evidence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
before	O
this	O
fire	O
happened	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
dined	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
pewter	O
spoon	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
minute	O
circumstances	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
other	O
circumstances	O
which	O
are	O
decisive	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
being	O
applied	O
to	O
for	O
his	O
rent	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
applied	O
to	O
for	O
his	O
taxes	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
being	O
applied	O
to	O
for	O
money	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
on	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
this	O
fire	O
happened	O
;	O
one	O
man	O
applied	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
sue	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
will	O
enter	O
an	O
appearance	O
,	O
and	O
defend	O
the	O
action	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
and	O
me	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
insured	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
pay	O
all	O
my	O
creditors	O
now	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
poverty	O
,	O
unable	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
rent	O
,	O
unable	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
taxes	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
application	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
property	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
his	O
conduct	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
was	O
not	O
like	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
500	O
l.	O
in	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
coolness	O
and	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
behaved	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
surveyor	O
and	O
fire-	O
fire-men	O
were	O
round	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
property	O
to	O
a	O
large	O
amount	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
contained	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
ware-room	O
:	O
I	O
stated	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
wainscot	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
in	O
that	O
chest	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
500	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
that	O
ware-room	O
were	O
his	O
plate	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pickaxe	O
to	O
dig	O
for	O
his	O
chest	O
,	O
knowing	O
very	O
well	O
that	O
the	O
guineas	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
melted	O
,	O
the	O
plate	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
melted	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
melted	O
,	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
an	O
appearance	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
consumed	O
;	O
on	O
digging	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
it	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
it	O
being	O
consumed	O
,	O
only	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
consumed	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
finding	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
guineas	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
plate	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
contain	O
nothing	O
but	O
hay-bands	O
,	O
and	O
pieces	O
of	O
paper	O
wet	O
with	O
oil	O
,	O
stinking	O
with	O
oil	O
,	O
clear	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
dipped	O
in	O
oil	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
papers	O
and	O
the	O
hay-bands	O
;	O
the	O
moment	O
the	O
man	O
perceived	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
disperse	O
the	O
hay-bands	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
by	O
the	O
surveyor	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
also	O
be	O
in	O
evidence	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
part	O
alone	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
this	O
chest	O
was	O
;	O
just	O
the	O
cover	O
of	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
boards	O
adjoining	O
the	O
wainscot	O
,	O
which	O
boards	O
were	O
burnt	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
floor	O
was	O
not	O
consumed	O
.	O
On	O
examining	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
stated	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
town	O
but	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
this	O
very	O
chest	O
500	O
l.	O
in	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
call	O
them	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
notes	O
,	O
for	O
those	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
.	O
The	O
story	O
was	O
incredible	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
would	O
a	O
man	O
be	O
pestered	O
for	O
money	O
by	O
his	O
landlord	O
and	O
the	O
tax-gatherers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
possessed	O
of	O
500	O
l.	O
?	O
Being	O
asked	O
to	O
describe	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
describe	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
drawers	O
or	O
acceptors	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
exactly	O
describe	O
the	O
different	O
amounts	O
of	O
the	O
different	O
sums	O
;	O
he	O
therefore	O
described	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
that	O
was	O
possible	O
;	O
six	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
ten	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
making	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
Now	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
apt	O
to	O
suppose	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
given	O
under	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
signed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
among	O
these	O
notes	O
were	O
ten	O
Bank	O
of	O
England	O
notes	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
each	O
.	O
Describing	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
sixty	O
gross	O
of	O
buttons	O
,	O
twenty	O
gross	O
of	O
metal	O
coat	O
buttons	O
,	O
forty	O
gross	O
of	O
metal	O
waistcoat	O
buttons	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
surveyor	O
directed	O
the	O
earth	O
to	O
be	O
sifted	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
in	O
that	O
fact	O
the	O
man	O
spoke	O
true	O
;	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
finding	O
a	O
gross	O
of	O
buttons	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
six	O
buttons	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
dust	O
so	O
sifted	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
fire	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
consumed	O
them	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
metal	O
had	O
been	O
melted	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
described	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
Portsmouth	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
contained	O
in	O
this	O
chest	O
,	O
two	O
hundred	O
pieces	O
of	O
nankeen	O
;	O
now	O
the	O
chest	O
itself	O
could	O
not	O
contain	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
chest	O
will	O
be	O
produced	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
judge	O
from	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
contain	O
that	O
quantity	O
of	O
nankeen	O
:	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
plate	O
that	O
he	O
stated	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
dozen	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
not	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
silver	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dust	O
;	O
for	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
the	O
surveyor	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
marked	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
property	O
was	O
found	O
whatever	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
prove	O
these	O
facts	O
to	O
your	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
prove	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
debt	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
prove	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
even	O
his	O
taxes	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
rent	O
,	O
nor	O
money	O
to	O
different	O
people	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
so	O
late	O
as	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
makes	O
an	O
insurance	O
of	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
claim	O
,	O
he	O
makes	O
it	O
amount	O
to	O
2000	O
l.	O
where	O
could	O
all	O
that	O
property	O
be	O
?	O
for	O
previous	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
I	O
will	O
prove	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
from	O
undeniable	O
evidence	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
property	O
at	O
all	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
prove	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
during	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
a	O
lamp-lighter	O
who	O
got	O
in	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
clothes	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
have	O
stated	O
these	O
facts	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
seen	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
carrying	O
out	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
walking	O
out	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
coolness	O
and	O
composure	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
without	O
alarming	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
walking	O
away	O
from	O
that	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
walked	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
complaining	O
of	O
this	O
loss	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
prove	O
these	O
facts	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
prove	O
that	O
this	O
combustible	O
matter	O
was	O
contained	O
in	O
this	O
chest	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
you	O
that	O
can	O
have	O
a	O
doubt	O
of	O
their	O
guilt	O
?	O
and	O
when	O
you	O
consider	O
likewise	O
that	O
I	O
prove	O
them	O
up	O
during	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
prove	O
a	O
witness	O
was	O
heard	O
,	O
after	O
calling	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
smell	O
of	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
answer	O
was	O
hush	O
,	O
hush	O
,	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
calling	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
prove	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
save	O
theirproperty	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
adjoining	O
;	O
they	O
themselves	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
dressed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
perfectly	O
cool	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
their	O
property	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
up	O
and	O
alarmed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
being	O
so	O
strong	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
saved	O
:	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
this	O
,	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
doubt	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
heavy	O
charge	O
to	O
bring	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
charge	O
difficult	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
proved	O
,	O
deserves	O
the	O
severest	O
punishment	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
to	O
urge	O
or	O
to	O
inflame	O
you	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
say	O
if	O
the	O
facts	O
are	O
proved	O
to	O
your	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
mercy	O
which	O
they	O
deserve	O
;	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
a	O
blacker	O
dye	O
can	O
not	O
come	O
before	O
a	O
Court	O
and	O
a	O
Jury	O
;	O
it	O
involves	O
every	O
other	O
offence	O
of	O
robbery	O
and	O
murder	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
whenever	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
idea	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
being	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
on	O
purpose	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
about	O
an	O
enquiry	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
province	O
to	O
judge	O
whether	O
the	O
evidence	O
which	O
we	O
produce	O
will	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
your	O
conviction	O
;	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
must	O
depend	O
on	O
circumstances	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
man	O
alive	O
sets	O
fire	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
another	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
night	O
:	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
must	O
depend	O
on	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
if	O
these	O
circumstances	O
are	O
proved	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
your	O
duty	O
to	O
pronounce	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
,	O
being	O
for	O
burning	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Imray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
their	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
floor	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
was	O
consumed	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
was	O
not	O
consumed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
wholly	O
consumed	O
:	O
my	O
Lord	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
burned	O
and	O
consumed	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
sufficient	O
for	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
third	O
and	O
the	O
sixth	O
counts	O
in	O
your	O
indictment	O
are	O
bad	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
one	O
word	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
desired	O
when	O
I	O
insured	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
insurance	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
inspect	O
into	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
customary	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
to	O
reserve	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
your	O
defence	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
is	O
given	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
by	O
entering	O
into	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
defence	O
now	O
,	O
you	O
give	O
them	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
applying	O
their	O
evidence	O
to	O
your	O
answer	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
behove	O
you	O
to	O
attend	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
witnesses	O
say	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
this	O
trial	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
permitted	O
me	O
to	O
address	O
the	O
Jury	O
:	O
My	O
Lord	O
will	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
SARAH	O
BISHOP	O
sworn	O
.	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
fire	O
happened	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
in	O
Little	O
Pultney-street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
of	O
Clary	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
did	O
this	O
fire	O
happen	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
began	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
after	O
two	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
near	O
ten	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
clock	O
had	O
gone	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
happen	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoners	O
occupied	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
parlor	O
of	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
lodgers	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
ware-room	O
,	O
a	O
parlor	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
bed-room	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
except	O
myself	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
stairs	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
like	O
somebody	O
opening	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
restless	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
slept	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
nights	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
Ihad	O
something	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
sleep	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
;	O
says	O
Clary	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
me	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
would	O
order	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
for	O
her	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
order	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
her	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Lion	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parlor	O
,	O
about	O
particular	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
she	O
spoke	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
wished	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
being	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
convenient	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
think	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
two	O
I	O
was	O
disturbed	O
with	O
the	O
smell	O
of	O
something	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
like	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
under	O
a	O
painted	O
board	O
with	O
oil	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
strong	O
or	O
faint	O
smell	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
smell	O
of	O
oil	O
,	O
very	O
strong	O
and	O
powerful	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
somebody	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
candle	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
smell	O
of	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
close	O
at	O
top	O
by	O
about	O
two	O
inches	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
sulphur	O
and	O
smoak	O
came	O
in	O
so	O
powerful	O
,	O
it	O
suffocated	O
me	O
almost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cracking	O
of	O
the	O
wainscot	O
,	O
cracked	O
like	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
deal	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
a	O
cracking	O
of	O
wood	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
turned	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
sleep	O
;	O
I	O
shook	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
awake	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
box	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bed-clothes	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
nor	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
rag	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
bedclothes	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
parlour	O
is	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
bed-room	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
front-room	O
;	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
parlour	O
is	O
in	O
front	O
,	O
the	O
passage	O
is	O
between	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
on	O
his	O
hips	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
night	O
cap	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hands	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
breeches	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Before	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
alarm	O
given	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
fire	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
stirring	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
alarm	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
light	O
in	O
Clary	O
's	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
lighted	O
,	O
and	O
candlestick	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
dresser	O
with	O
drawers	O
in	O
this	O
parlour	O
,	O
which	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
was	O
standing	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
room	O
and	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
passage	O
between	O
these	O
two	O
rooms	O
only	O
a	O
partition	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
put	O
on	O
your	O
clothes	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
alarm	O
yourself	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
petticoat	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
says	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
light	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
spare	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
candlestick	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
instantly	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
fire	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
grocer	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
a	O
fire	O
happening	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fire-place	O
,	O
nor	O
nobody	O
worked	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Remainder	O
of	O
this	O
Trial	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Part	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1788	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J	B-pers
.	I-pers
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCLXXXVIII	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Continuation	O
of	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Clary	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Gombert	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
to	O
Sarah	O
Bishop	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
in	O
fact	O
any	O
fire-place	O
in	O
the	O
ware-room	O
as	O
he	O
called	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
fire	O
kept	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fire-place	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
ware-room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
were	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
attempting	O
to	O
save	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
work-shop	O
,	O
I	O
begged	O
somebody	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
not	O
open	O
then	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Clary	O
never	O
attempted	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Gombert	O
opened	O
the	O
street-door	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
shoved	O
out	O
the	O
boxes	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
took	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
milk	O
cellar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
continued	O
at	O
the	O
milk	O
cellar	O
in	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
flame	O
broke	O
out	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
observe	O
in	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
flames	O
first	O
broke	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
broke	O
the	O
shutters	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
house	O
was	O
entirely	O
consumed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
sure	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
flames	O
or	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
came	O
at	O
all	O
from	O
the	O
kitchen	O
floor	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
certainly	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
about	O
seven	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
away	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
opportunities	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Clary	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
did	O
he	O
carry	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
taylor	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
work	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
once	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
He	O
sold	O
ready-made	O
clothes	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
His	O
stock	O
consisted	O
of	O
a	O
few	O
clothes	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
coat	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
or	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
without	O
having	O
a	O
command	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
shuts	O
up	O
with	O
moving	O
shutters	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
a	O
few	O
clothes	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
or	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
did	O
exceed	O
that	O
.	O
What	O
number	O
of	O
coats	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
any	O
coats	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
linen	O
ones	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
goods	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
shelves	O
or	O
drawers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
mercer	O
's	O
or	O
draper	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
way	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
shop	O
fitted	O
up	O
with	O
drawers	O
or	O
shelves	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
came	O
intirely	O
round	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
corner	O
next	O
to	O
Wardour-street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
partition	O
was	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
standing	O
besides	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
partition	O
between	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
ware-room	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
counter	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
next	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
conceive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
large	O
property	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
dined	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
them	O
twice	O
;	O
nobody	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
them	O
but	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
.	O
Their	O
stock	O
