TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
1788	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SEVENTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCLXXXVIII	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BURNELL	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
GOULD	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
NASH	B-pers
GROSE	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
ADAIR	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blakesley	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Findlay	I-pers
William	B-pers
Evett	I-pers
John	B-pers
Tugwell	I-pers
James	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
George	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
William	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lyme	I-pers
George	B-pers
Michell	I-pers
Simon	B-pers
Leife	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Faulder	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
George	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
William	B-pers
Selby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Chowles	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Carbery	I-pers
Frederick	B-pers
Besk	I-pers
John	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ogilvie	I-pers
*	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Birchall	I-pers
served	O
sometime	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ogilvie	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
George	B-pers
Gow	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Logan	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Fagg	I-pers
.	O
497.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Black	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
two	O
brass	O
cocks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
goods	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ASHTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
at	O
Saltpetre	B-place
Bank	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
alarmed	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
all	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
my	O
house	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
immediately	O
;	O
my	O
doors	O
were	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
liquors	O
all	O
running	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
made	O
to	O
my	O
street	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nobody	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
board	O
laid	O
over	O
;	O
in	O
my	O
fright	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
undone	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
brass	O
cocks	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
found	O
again	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
all	O
along	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
blunderbuss	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
and	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
brass	O
cocks	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
casks	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
leather	O
pipes	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
there	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PENTELOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
when	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
every	O
time	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
home	O
when	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
work	O
,	O
that	O
gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
they	O
get	O
my	O
money	O
till	O
I	O
spend	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
myself	O
in	O
liquor	O
many	O
and	O
many	O
a	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
trusted	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
many	O
a	O
night	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
shipmates	O
and	O
me	O
drinking	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
lent	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
on	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
passage	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shipmate	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
master	O
said	O
that	O
my	O
shipmate	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
drunk	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Pentelow	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
498.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DANCER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
base-metal	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
note	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
receipt	O
signed	O
by	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Messrs.	O
Hoare	O
and	O
Co.	O
dated	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1787	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
325	O
l.	O
to	O
account	O
for	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
note	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
being	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
thereon	O
secured	O
then	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
DANIEL	B-pers
DANCER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
at	O
Harrow-Weald-Common	B-place
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
place	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
towork	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
days	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
somewhere	O
else	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
job	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
lay	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
hedge	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
which	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
lopsed	O
about	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
his	O
breaking	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
nobody	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
doors	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
that	O
I	O
locked	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
open	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
opened	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
fastened	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
force	O
appeared	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
by	O
a	O
turnkey	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
I	O
also	O
missed	O
a	O
pacquet	O
with	O
several	O
writings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
rags	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
nobody	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
but	O
myself	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bedroom	O
;	O
I	O
constanly	O
kept	O
my	O
bed-room	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
woman	O
to	O
attend	O
it	O
but	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
locked	O
it	O
that	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
lost	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed-room	O
which	O
lay	O
at	O
top	O
of	O
another	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bed-room	O
likewise	O
,	O
nobody	O
but	O
myself	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
bed-room	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
also	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
bed-room	O
also	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
lost	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
mention	O
;	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
count	O
the	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
pieces	O
that	O
were	O
not	O
mentioned	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
guineas	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
white	O
stocking	O
foot	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
rather	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
note	O
from	O
a	O
banker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
to	O
settle	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
my	O
papers	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
rags	O
and	O
pacquet	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
almost	O
three	O
weeks	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Whose	O
house	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
house	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
nobody	O
lived	O
in	O
it	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TROTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
Pigs	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
eight	O
miles	O
from	O
Harrow-Weald	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tossing	O
up	O
for	O
pies	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
such	O
a	O
property	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
bank-notes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
tied	O
up	O
and	O
read	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brown	O
paper	O
like	O
a	O
book	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
where	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Lee	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Lee	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
look	O
them	O
over	O
;	O
he	O
thought	O
Lee	O
might	O
know	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
Lee	O
came	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
except	O
the	O
person	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
any	O
man	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
Lee	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
he	O
whipped	O
over	O
a	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
these	O
writings	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
over	O
the	O
gate	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
writings	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Kibbol	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Pigs-lane	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
same	O
gate	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
gate	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
lane	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
this	O
first	O
search	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
the	O
nextmorning	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
under	O
the	O
rick	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
just	O
on	O
the	O
stands	O
hardly	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
straw	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
been	O
cutting	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
wet	O
;	O
no	O
one	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
Mr.	O
Kibbol	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
looked	O
over	O
by	O
Kibbol	O
and	O
Lee	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
Captain	O
Holmes	B-pers
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dancer	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
at	O
Kibbol	O
's	O
;	O
Kibbol	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
was	O
there	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
parish	O
is	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
's	O
house	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Harrow	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
us	O
some	O
writings	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
or	O
read	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Pigs-lane	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
perfectly	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
some	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
bottle	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Trott	I-pers
and	O
me	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
whipcord	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
brown	O
paper	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
but	O
the	O
proprietor	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
bank	O
notes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
beer	O
we	O
all	O
came	O
down	O
Pig-lane	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
leaped	O
over	O
this	O
gate	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
get	O
over	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
absent	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
overtook	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Plume	O
of	O
Feathers	O
that	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Kibbol	I-pers
;	O
nothing	O
else	O
passed	O
only	O
about	O
these	O
writings	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
;	O
Trott	O
found	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Kibbol	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
papers	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
KIBBOL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Plume	O
of	O
Feathers	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Kibbol	O
the	O
landlord	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
tea-cannister	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Trott	O
and	O
Lee	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
particularly	O
say	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
cannister	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
marked	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cannister	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
this	O
witness	O
.	O
)	O
To	O
Lee	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
cannister	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
scratched	O
out	O
a	O
mark	O
here	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
scratched	O
out	O
the	O
mark	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
scratch	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
cannister	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
cannister	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
put	O
but	O
sixpence	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
put	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
CAPTAIN	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOLMES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
New-Road	O
,	O
St	O
Georges	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.Dancer	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dancer	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
;	O
the	O
papers	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
Trott	O
and	O
Lee	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
papers	O
that	O
were	O
then	O
produced	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
until	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
seal	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
examined	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
box	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
by	O
John	O
Trott	O
.	O
Trott	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
papers	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
of	O
Hoare	O
's	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
papers	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Trott	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
that	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Read	B-pers
the	O
accountable	O
receipt	O
.	O
(	O
Read	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
Received	O
,	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
1787	O
,	O
of	O
``	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
,	O
325	O
l.	O
to	O
account	O
``	O
for	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
for	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
``	O
Bart	O
.	O
and	O
Messrs.	O
Hoares.	O
``	O
Charles	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
325	O
l.	O
''	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
Pinner	O
Common	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
kept	O
them	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
resigned	O
myself	O
up	O
to	O
justice	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
499.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRAWFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Byas	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
chattels	O
,	O
and	O
monies	O
therein	O
,	O
being	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BYAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ten-foot-way	B-place
,	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Nightingale-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
sash	O
thrown	O
quite	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
eight	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
bed	O
made	O
and	O
sash	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
me	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
returned	O
just	O
at	O
eleven	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
bed-room	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
son	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
caught	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
bed-clothes	O
were	O
all	O
gathered	O
up	O
of	O
a	O
heap	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
tied	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
son	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
chap	O
that	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
light	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
people	O
came	O
with	O
candles	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BYAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
middling	O
light	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
year	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
eleven	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
stop	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
six	O
feet	O
high	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
up	O
stairs	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
right	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
round	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
people	O
coming	O
past	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
youlay	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rogue	O
,	O
why	O
should	O
I	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
actually	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
sir	O
;	O
he	O
resisted	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
mob	O
came	O
up	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
to	O
ask	O
pardon	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
this	O
prisoner	O
was	O
fully	O
committed	O
for	O
trial	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
some	O
instrument	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
lock-up	O
room	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Friday	O
fortnight	O
following	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
by	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
it	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
four	O
bad	O
shillinge	O
instead	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
mother	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
500.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
eleven	O
live	O
tame	O
geese	O
,	O
value	O
44	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
live	O
tame	O
duck	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
chimney-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
hair	O
brush	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
scraper	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
wooden	O
shovel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
ALLEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Hampstead	O
Heath	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
that	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
geese	O
and	O
ducks	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
doors	O
where	O
my	O
geese	O
were	O
,	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
geese	O
were	O
kept	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
roof	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
passage	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
case	O
it	O
rains	O
where	O
the	O
tools	O
are	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
get	O
into	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
tools	O
and	O
ducks	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
geese	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
geese	O
were	O
kept	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
where	O
the	O
tools	O
and	O
the	O
ducks	O
are	O
kept	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
where	O
the	O
geese	O
were	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
blood	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
geese	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
tool	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
passage	O
door	O
open	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
where	O
the	O
tools	O
are	O
kept	O
;	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
chimney-cloths	O
,	O
sacks	O
,	O
scrapers	O
,	O
shovels	O
,	O
and	O
brushes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
duck	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
tools	O
were	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
these	O
things	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
my	O
own	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ISAAC	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
office	O
to	O
apply	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
one	O
Gough	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
welcome	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
boy	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
information	O
;	O
and	O
Gough	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
here	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
fine	O
pice	O
of	O
work	O
about	O
some	O
geese	O
again	O
;	O
master	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
fine	O
piece	O
of	O
work	O
at	O
Johnson	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
officers	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
goose	O
.	O
Was	O
Johnson	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
butwe	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
court	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
place	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
Wooden	O
World	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
goose	O
and	O
these	O
chimney-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
sacks	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
things	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
directly	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
geese	O
warm	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
my	O
premises	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
Tucker	O
's	O
premises	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
lodge	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BRACKNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
further	O
than	O
Isaacs	O
has	O
told	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
goose	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloths	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
further	O
than	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
mistresses	O
cloths	O
.	O
(	O
Cloths	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
three	O
patches	O
;	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
almost	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
.	O
Had	O
Tucker	O
and	O
he	O
a	O
room	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
each	O
a	O
separate	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
pays	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Tucker	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Tucker	O
,	O
Johnson	O
and	O
me	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
cloths	O
and	O
goose	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
that	O
you	O
slept	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
wanted	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Tucker	O
sleep	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
Johnson	O
sleep	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
Tucker	O
and	O
Johnson	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
bring	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
goose	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
how	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
nigh	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
this	O
property	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
apt	O
every	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
this	O
Tucker	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
particular	O
answer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
lad	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
that	O
Johnson	O
should	O
ask	O
him	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
into	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Walker	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
Johnson	B-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
time	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
fastened	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
like	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
Tucker	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Walker	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
work	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Allen	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Johnson	O
say	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
this	O
conversation	O
pass	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
501.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DARBY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
her	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
.	O
For	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
dwelling-house	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
afterwards	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
502.	O
MARY	B-pers
GITTOS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
two	O
white	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
brown	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
coloured	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GRIFFIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Abe	O
Robinson	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
my	O
room-door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sleep	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
neighbour	O
let	O
her	O
be	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
my	O
room-door	O
and	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
three	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
my	O
room-door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
directly	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
my	O
room-door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
staple	O
was	O
broke	O
out	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
ELLIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
neighbour	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Griffin	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
eleven	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
her	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
valued	O
at	O
one	O
guinea	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jury	O
.	O
As	O
this	O
indictment	O
is	O
laid	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
capital	O
offence	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
any	O
person	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
BARON	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
503.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
IVES	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
three	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
plain	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
value4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
groat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
robbery	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
BOTH	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
504.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ROUND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Northam	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
tenant	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
identify	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
505.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
deal	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
worsted	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
10	O
d.	O
Imprisoned	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Correction	O
Six	O
Months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
506.	O
JOHN	B-pers
GOSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
dropping	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
507.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
containing	O
four	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richard	I-pers
Ripley	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
muslin	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
drawers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
my	O
masters	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
508.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
watch	O
string	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
plain	O
stone	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
glass	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
watch-key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
St.	B-place
Catharine's-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
past	O
me	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
on	O
last	O
Sunday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
crying	O
past	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
those	O
two	O
gents	O
that	O
are	O
here	O
stoppedhim	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
then	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SKIRSLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
houseman	O
belonging	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
sailor	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
asked	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
directed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
post	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
say	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
!	O
will	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
!	O
then	O
immediately	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
the	O
officer	O
was	O
then	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
stop	O
you	O
till	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
comes	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
immediately	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
trowsers	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
shew	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
watch	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
descriptions	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
(	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
is	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Howard	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
opened	O
it	O
this	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
it	O
goes	O
on	O
a	O
diamond	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Open	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mills	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
flurried	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
whether	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
MOORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
,	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
past	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
directed	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
immediately	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
immediately	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
houseman	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
trowsers	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
the	O
houseman	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
described	O
the	O
particulars	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
answered	O
his	O
description	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
St.	O
Catharine's-lane	O
last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
girl	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
or	O
two	O
along	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
passed	O
him	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
he	O
sung	O
out	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
a	O
man	O
passed	O
with	O
a	O
jacket	O
and	O
trowsers	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
arms	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
trowsers	O
pocket	O
;	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
question	O
most	O
probably	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
509.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
COX	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COX	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Simon	B-pers
Matthien	I-pers
Detreme	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
monies	O
numbered	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
SIMON	B-pers
MATTHIEN	I-pers
DETREME	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
fields	O
that	O
are	O
between	O
Hampstead	O
and	O
Kilburne	O
Wells	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
Six	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Rotation	O
Office	O
;	O
between	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
wasvery	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
of	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
Which	O
man	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
demanded	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
resembles	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
back	O
turned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
directly	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
sixpences	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
threaten	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
dispelled	O
all	O
kind	O
of	O
fear	O
,	O
by	O
assuring	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
arms	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
with	O
a	O
knob	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
mahogany	O
chair	O
,	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
square	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
he	O
blest	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
,	O
perhaps	O
the	O
man	O
would	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
nex	O
field	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
loading	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
footpads	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
have	O
they	O
robbed	O
you	O
;	O
have	O
they	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
afterwards	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
justices	O
?	O
-	O
Six	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
justices	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
of	O
this	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
exactly	O
like	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
my	O
belief	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
So	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
suspected	O
afterwards	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
one	O
innocent	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
I	O
say	O
of	O
this	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
about	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Kilburn	O
Wells	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Errington	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
you	O
can	O
run	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
do	O
run	O
after	O
these	O
two	O
footpads	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
robbed	O
a	O
gentleman	O
within	O
a	O
field	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
just	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
this	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
men	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
waggoners	O
frocks	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
not	O
many	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
fields	O
off	O
Mr.	O
Errington	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
was	O
rather	O
taller	O
and	O
thinner	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
shorter	O
and	O
broader	O
set	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
leaped	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
to	O
the	O
field	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
very	O
near	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
,	O
I	O
descried	O
a	O
man	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
valley	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
rise	O
of	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
smock	O
frock	O
as	O
before	O
described	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
very	O
near	O
Primrose-Hill	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
to	O
Paddington	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
just	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Mr.	O
Wellin	O
's	O
hay-ricks	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
is	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
miles	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Cox	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
suppose	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Scott	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
just	O
now	O
robbed	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
field	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wellin	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
ran	O
you	O
from	O
Kilburn	O
Wells	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
;	O
wekept	O
him	O
in	O
Mary-le-Bone	O
watch-house	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
confess	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
You	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Shakespeare	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
Pimlico	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Hobbs	O
and	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Pimlico	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
smock	O
frock	O
to	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Kilburn	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
upon	O
hearing	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
immediately	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
robbed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Hobbs	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
sixpences	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
sixpence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
advertised	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
Thomas	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
hedge	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
which	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wellin	O
's	O
field	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
New	O
Workhouse	O
in	O
Marybone	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
beckoned	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	O
,	O
made	O
answer	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Shakespeare	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Pimlico	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
waiting	O
about	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
door	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
easy	O
and	O
quiet	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
would	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
soon	O
taken	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
this	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
sixpence	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
with	O
running	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
understand	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
from	O
Kilburn	O
to	O
Highgate	O
?	O
-	O
Those	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
ran	O
round	O
that	O
way	O
to	O
Highgate	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
at	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
somewhere	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
at	O
this	O
public-house	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
Edward	O
came	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
ERRINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kilburn	O
Wells	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
seventeen	O
years	O
almost	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
forward	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
reluctance	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
EDWARD	B-pers
COX	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
,	O
because	O
all	O
his	O
confession	O
,	O
or	O
supposed	O
confession	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
promise	O
ofreward	O
,	O
therefore	O
you	O
must	O
acquit	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
question	O
will	O
be	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
;	O
upon	O
those	O
cases	O
where	O
the	O
transaction	O
never	O
lasts	O
long	O
,	O
one	O
wishes	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
both	O
positive	O
and	O
circumstantial	O
evidence	O
:	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
positive	O
evidence	O
,	O
you	O
hear	O
how	O
it	O
stands	O
,	O
then	O
from	O
the	O
circumstantial	O
evidence	O
,	O
this	O
gentleman	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
publickly	O
made	O
notorious	O
that	O
robbery	O
.	O
At	O
some	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Scott	O
thinks	O
fit	O
to	O
pursue	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
makes	O
a	O
confession	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
immaterial	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
consider	O
any	O
otherwise	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
tells	O
you	O
that	O
Edward	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Shakespeare's-Head	O
,	O
Pimlico	O
;	O
they	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	O
is	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
without	O
any	O
promise	O
whatever	O
,	O
he	O
confesses	O
that	O
he	O
robbed	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
now	O
what	O
gentleman	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
question	O
is	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Detreme	O
,	O
the	O
present	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
sixpences	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
one	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
offence	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
therefore	O
to	O
consider	O
,	O
whether	O
on	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
apply	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
confession	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
you	O
will	O
consider	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
reward	O
,	O
that	O
reward	O
will	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
adding	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
the	O
confession	O
may	O
make	O
the	O
reward	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
not	O
this	O
to	O
throw	O
any	O
imputation	O
on	O
the	O
witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
consider	O
again	O
and	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
mere	O
confessional	O
evidence	O
before	O
you	O
can	O
convict	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
tells	O
you	O
very	O
freely	O
and	O
honestly	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
sixpences	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
circumstance	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
learn	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
material	O
circumstance	O
indeed	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
COX	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COX	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
510.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
TAMBROOK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair	O
dresser	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
tea-spoons	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
breakfast	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HIBBARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
to	O
my	O
customers	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
precipitate	O
powder	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
up	O
Duke-street	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
spoons	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
rattle	O
loose	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
held	O
them	O
off	O
from	O
touching	O
his	O
thigh	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
God	O
you	O
have	O
something	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
oh	O
,	O
my	O
good	O
fellow	O
do	O
not	O
!	O
they	O
are	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
missed	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
thespoons	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
511.	O
SARAH	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
in	O
a	O
mahogany	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cherrington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Henning	I-pers
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
CHERRINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet	O
maker	O
and	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
David	B-pers
Henning	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
looking	O
glass	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
immediately	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
myself	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
It	O
rained	O
very	O
hard	O
last	O
Friday	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
this	O
glass	O
stand	O
by	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
moving	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
tore	O
a	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
gown	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
512.	O
MALACHI	B-pers
PORTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
two	O
leaden	O
garden	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Johanna	B-pers
Altham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
pots	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pots	O
at	O
Pancrass	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
correction	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
513.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RYAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Willam	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
slithering	O
off	O
this	O
building	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
in	O
a	O
vault	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
LAWRENCE	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
things	O
drop	O
from	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lead	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
514.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SEDGWICK	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Peter	B-pers
William	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
515.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
HARLING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
gun	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
property	O
being	O
wrong	O
layed	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
516.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
LACEY	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1785	O
,	O
one	O
chesnut	O
gelding	O
,	O
price	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Pegrim	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
PEGRIM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1785	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
so	O
late	O
with	O
this	O
prosecution	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
horse	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
No	O
.	O
64	O
,	O
London	O
Wall	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
stable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hired	O
my	O
horse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Croydon	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
.	O
You	O
keep	O
an	O
inn	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
ask	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
wanted	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Croydon	O
for	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
never	O
returned	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
an	O
entire	O
stranger	O
have	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
information	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
code	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
name	O
James	O
Smith	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
Cable-street	O
,	O
Wellclose-square	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
make	O
any	O
enquiry	O
for	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
enquiry	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
directed	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shopman	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
horse	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
advertisement	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
some	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
then	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
undertake	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
you	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
?	O
-	O
Ten	O
minutes	O
perhaps	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
and	O
wrote	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
shewn	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
officer	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
description	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
not	O
on	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stole	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
or	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
qustions	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
once	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Why	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
time	O
ago	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Campion	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
these	O
ten	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
partners	O
in	O
the	O
horse	O
dealing	O
line	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
deal	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
job	O
way	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
livery	O
horses	O
may	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
?	O
-	O
More	O
than	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
horses	O
.	O
But	O
riding	O
horses	O
;	O
how	O
many	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
pretty	O
near	O
three	O
years	O
at	O
Christmas	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
PEGRIM	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
we	O
always	O
do	O
of	O
stranger	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
getting	O
the	O
horse	O
ready	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
distance	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
but	O
once	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
mole	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
that	O
mole	O
now	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
us	O
how	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
great-coat	O
on	O
.	O
A	O
pretty	O
large	O
great-coat	O
?	O
-	O
Middling	O
about	O
that	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pocket	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
happen	O
to	O
mistake	O
one	O
man	O
for	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BEAR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
indictment	O
in	O
Surrey	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
repeated	O
his	O
blows	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Borough	O
and	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Pegrim	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
custody	O
that	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
Jacob	O
Hobbs	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Pegrim	O
describe	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
man	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
Mr.	O
Lacey	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pegrim	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
this	O
horse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pegrim	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
offend	O
my	O
Counsel	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
ask	O
a	O
single	O
question	O
of	O
young	O
Mr.	O
Pegrim	O
;	O
Whether	O
that	O
advertisement	O
of	O
the	O
mole	O
on	O
my	O
cheek	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
advertised	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
recollect	O
,	O
the	O
elder	O
Pegrim	O
swore	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
.	O
Pegrim	O
the	O
elder	O
.	O
Hobbs	O
was	O
advertised	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
man	O
advertised	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
advertisement	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
or	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
mention	O
the	O
mole	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Bear	O
.	O
What	O
description	O
did	O
Pegrim	O
give	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
tall	O
slim	O
man	O
of	O
swarthy	O
complexion	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
particular	O
mark	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kingdom	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
respectable	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
eight	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
517.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COYLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
six	O
earthen	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
six	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
glass	O
tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pint	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
mustard-pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Staffordshire	O
and	O
glass	O
warehouse	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Fleet	B-place
Market	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
twenty-eight	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
losing	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
concerning	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
pockets	O
loaded	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hearing	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Sainsbury	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
remanded	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
house	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
property	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
concealed	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
QUIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
widow	O
woman	O
that	O
works	O
for	O
my	O
living	O
,	O
washing	O
and	O
spinning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
search	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
six	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
and	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
at	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
washed	O
for	O
him	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
two-pence	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
HUGH	B-pers
MORGAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milkman	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
his	O
right	O
pocket	O
was	O
quite	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
top	O
thing	O
was	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
saucer	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
I	O
acquainted	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Pray	O
what	O
mark	O
have	O
you	O
on	O
those	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
What	O
particular	O
marks	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
marks	O
,	O
only	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
What	O
marks	O
exclusive	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
crockery	O
ware	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
plates	O
were	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
never	O
sent	O
any	O
to	O
London	O
but	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
pay	O
him	O
about	O
400	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
for	O
them	O
plates	O
and	O
dishes	O
.	O
BRIDGET	B-pers
DUFFER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black	O
Swan	O
Court	O
,	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Quin	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
at	O
twice	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
plates	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
your	O
other	O
man	O
keep	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
bolted	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
spoiled	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
used	O
.	O
LEMON	O
CASEBY	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hearing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
remanded	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Davis	O
to	O
his	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
morning	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
linen	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
meant	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
unknown	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Those	O
things	O
I	O
never	O
stole	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
understood	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
question	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
was	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
says	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
on	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
is	O
doing	O
all	O
he	O
can	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GROSE	O
.	O
518.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GUY	I-pers
,	O
JAMES	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
,	O
and	O
ROBERT	B-pers
FENVELL	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
price	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Pinner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Harrow	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
horse	O
either	O
the	O
22d	O
or	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
twenty	O
miles	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
gelding	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
brown	O
bay	O
gelding	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
him	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
rather	O
of	O
a	O
brownish	O
colour	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
three	O
inches	O
high	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
;	O
three	O
years	O
old	O
at	O
most	O
,	O
bald-faced	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
two	O
white	O
feet	O
behind	O
or	O
one	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Kettle	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
magistrate	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
Hill	O
,	O
a	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
the	O
22d	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
;	O
the	O
road	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
gates	O
fast	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
school	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
gate	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
more	O
gates	O
than	O
one	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
particularly	O
say	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
boarders	O
very	O
often	O
throw	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
away	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
long	O
tailed	O
grey	O
colt	O
got	O
away	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
grey	O
colt	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
gelding	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
about	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
heard	O
how	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Paddington	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
gelding	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
here	O
examined	O
separate	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FENNING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
These	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
passed	O
us	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Carter	O
,	O
a	O
cow-keeper	O
,	O
three	O
miles	O
from	O
Paddington	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Dawson	O
and	O
Guy	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
milking	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
met	O
us	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
's	O
horse	O
took	O
fright	O
;	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
said	O
he	O
wished	O
some	O
Irishmen	O
would	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pails	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
young	O
men	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
drop	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
coming	O
for	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
having	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
turn	O
then	O
,	O
they	O
kept	O
on	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
light	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
light	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
yourself	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
these	O
three	O
young	O
men	O
,	O
from	O
that	O
cursory	O
view	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
information	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
gelding	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
tail	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
particularly	O
say	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
face	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Had	O
your	O
gelding	O
a	O
long	O
tail	O
?	O
-	O
Middling	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
a	O
longish	O
swish	O
tail	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
tail	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
us	O
turn	O
these	O
horses	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
us	O
take	O
these	O
horses	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milkman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Fenning	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
pitching	O
our	O
milk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
came	O
by	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
milk	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
horse	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Dawson	O
and	O
Guy	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
gelding	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
tail	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
son	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
thieves	O
;	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
said	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
faces	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
bald	O
faced	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
nigh	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Kettle	O
's	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BUDGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
four	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
by	O
my	O
dog	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
leading	O
away	O
an	O
ass	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoners	O
Fenvell	O
and	O
Dawson	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
know	O
that	O
;	O
they	O
immediately	O
slipt	O
the	O
halter	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
it	O
loose	O
;	O
I	O
dressed	O
myself	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
horses	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
turned	O
the	O
horses	O
loose	O
on	O
the	O
green	O
opposite	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
What	O
horses	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
bay	O
horse	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
immediately	O
down	O
the	O
green	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
into	O
Black	O
Lion	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
watchman	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
thieves	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Fenvell	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
ass	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
three	O
thieves	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
pulled	O
a	O
horse-cloth	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
with	O
some	O
poultry	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
fowls	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
horses	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
green	O
facing	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WALTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
common	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
two	O
horses	O
in	O
Paddington	O
pound	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
his	O
horse	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Birch	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
Hill	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
was	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
green	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Dawson	O
.	O
We	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
BARON	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
519.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
CONNER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
arraigned	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
thus	O
addressed	O
by	O
the	O
Recorder	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
right	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
fully	O
informed	O
of	O
the	O
consequences	O
of	O
your	O
plea	O
before	O
it	O
is	O
recorded	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
expect	O
to	O
receive	O
any	O
favor	O
from	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
your	O
sovereign	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
pleading	O
guilty	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
probably	O
be	O
deceived	O
in	O
that	O
expectation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
your	O
pleading	O
guilty	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
recorded	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
whatever	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
by	O
a	O
verdict	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
;	O
therefore	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
consider	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
will	O
abide	O
by	O
your	O
plea	O
of	O
guilty	O
,	O
or	O
take	O
your	O
chance	O
of	O
acquittal	O
by	O
a	O
jury	O
of	O
your	O
country	O
:	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
gates	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gates	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
to	O
hinder	O
me	O
or	O
to	O
stop	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
at	O
my	O
liberty	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
small	O
children	O
and	O
a	O
wife	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
support	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
served	O
my	O
king	O
and	O
country	O
abroad	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
war	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
here	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
plea	O
of	O
guilty	O
;	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
the	O
court	O
has	O
a	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
give	O
judgment	O
of	O
death	O
against	O
you	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
matter	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
excuse	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
it	O
must	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
petition	O
to	O
your	O
sovereign	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
matter	O
to	O
lay	O
before	O
the	O
court	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
by	O
evidence	O
;	O
then	O
this	O
prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
certificate	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
conviction	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
Read	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Shelton	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
Goal	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
and	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
Bambridge-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
convicted	O
in	O
April	O
sessions	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
trial	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
receive	O
sentence	O
;	O
I	O
recollect	O
his	O
being	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edger	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
yard	O
filling	O
a	O
barrow	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
rubbish	O
or	O
mortar	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
some	O
work	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
escaped	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
retook	O
him	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
escape	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
I	O
doing	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
filling	O
a	O
barrow	O
with	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
three	O
small	O
children	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
children	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
distressed	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
confinement	O
,	O
knowing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
this	O
distress	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
walking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
strangers	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
walked	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
trying	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
fetch	O
them	O
tomorrow	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
bring	O
my	O
master	O
who	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
these	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
520.	O
DAVID	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DERRY	I-pers
,	O
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DERRY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
firkin	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
salted	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
INNIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROLFE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
these	O
lads	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Vaughan	O
's	O
warehouse	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
lads	O
,	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
upon	O
a	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Derry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
firkin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
out	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
receive	O
something	O
from	O
this	O
little	O
lad	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
with	O
the	O
butter	O
,	O
Evans	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
into	O
custody	O
with	O
the	O
butter	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
lads	O
made	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
lads	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
butter	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Evans	O
were	O
secured	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARVEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
opposite	O
this	O
gateway	O
where	O
the	O
warehouse	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
watch	O
these	O
people	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
young	O
one	O
bring	O
out	O
a	O
firkin	O
;	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
held	O
out	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
received	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
Evans	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
Evans	O
with	O
the	O
butter	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
watching	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Willliam	O
Derry	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
along	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
both	O
