TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1788	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FIFTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCLXXXVIII	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BURNELL	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HENRY	I-pers
ASHURST	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
PERRYN	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
JAMES	B-pers
ADAIR	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ribright	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
Steele	O
Edward	B-pers
Winwood	I-pers
Jeremiah	B-pers
Branson	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Cannadine	I-pers
George	B-pers
Torrington	I-pers
Elias	B-pers
Hibbs	I-pers
Hector	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bayliss	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
John	B-pers
Raunce	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
David	B-pers
Moody	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
William	B-pers
Sterch	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sanger	I-pers
James	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
Joshuah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Saul	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
Newman	B-pers
Row	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Short	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
Jonathan	O
Thompson	O
Joshua	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
Edward	O
Paddon	O
John	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Locke	I-pers
James	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
John	O
Warder	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
John	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
331.	O
JANE	B-pers
WHITAKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
away	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
two	O
copper	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
flat-iron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
lodgingroom	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
HAMILTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Barrat's-court	B-place
,	I-place
Manchester-square	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
passed	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
lost	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
bedding	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
twelve	O
duplicates	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
sheets	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
break	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ELLIOT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
not	O
answering	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
break	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
twelve	O
twelve	O
duplicates	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
sheets	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
copper	O
pot	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Whitaker	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NEALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
this	O
saucepan	O
and	O
flat-iron	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
pledged	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
and	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Whitaker	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
what	O
Mrs.	O
Hamilton	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
for	O
being	O
continually	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
pledged	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
stand	O
before	O
God	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
sold	O
,	O
were	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
twenty-four	O
or	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
of	O
a	O
milk-score	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
porridge-pot	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
Is	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
story	O
true	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
single	O
syllable	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
pledge	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
set	O
up	O
this	O
defence	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
I	O
pawned	O
two	O
gowns	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
To	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
pass	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
332.	O
DAVID	B-pers
KINCARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
laying	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
YARROW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Graid's-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Wellclose-square	I-place
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
cried	O
out	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
run	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
stopped	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
next	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
side-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
oh	O
!	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
cleaned	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
know	O
the	O
pattern	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
just	O
so	O
many	O
pair	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
lately	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
property	O
between	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
made	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
of	O
the	O
kind	O
.	O
Joshua	O
Grey	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Cut	O
,	O
Radcliffe	O
highway	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
buckles	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Yarrow	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
near	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
as	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
Sessions	O
house	O
is	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
333.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EVERSALL	I-pers
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROBERTS	I-pers
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BARNEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
King's-highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Troughton	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
TROUGHTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cherry-tree-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-lan	I-place
e	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
alley	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
narrow	O
place	O
I	O
made	O
way	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
pass	O
me	O
;	O
seeing	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
got	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
they	O
collected	O
themselves	O
into	O
a	O
body	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinctly	O
hear	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
Barney	O
,	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
into	O
my	O
eyes	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
threw	O
in	O
your	O
eyes	O
?	O
-	O
Snuff	O
or	O
tobacco	O
dust	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
it	O
was	O
tobacco	O
dust	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
or	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Barney	O
,	O
the	O
farthest	O
prisoner	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
seized	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
struggled	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
outof	O
the	O
alley	O
into	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
discover	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
Barney	O
and	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
struggled	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
some	O
blows	O
about	O
my	O
face	O
and	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
defended	O
myself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
blows	O
drove	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
I	O
staggered	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
position	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
my	O
wig	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
gone	O
almost	O
instantly	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
seeing	O
they	O
took	O
different	O
ways	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Barney	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
of	O
an	O
apron	O
tied	O
round	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
by	O
that	O
particular	O
mark	O
through	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
Basket-alley	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
a	O
dark	O
passage	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
little	O
struggle	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
the	O
watchman's-rattle	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
stopped	O
Roberts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
had	O
taken	O
Eversall	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
got	O
your	O
hat	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
hat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
pursued	O
Barney	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
something	O
he	O
had	O
tied	O
round	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
threw	O
tobacco	O
dust	O
in	O
your	O
eyes	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
who	O
threw	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
are	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
Barney	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
only	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
Roberts	O
striking	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
attacked	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamp	O
.	O
Which	O
is	O
Roberts	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
tall	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
Eversall	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
Eversall	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
you	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
you	O
examined	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Justice	O
Blackborow	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sign	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
alley	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
before	O
you	O
observed	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
was	O
something	O
was	O
thrown	O
in	O
your	O
eyes	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
having	O
tobacco	O
dust	O
thrown	O
in	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
persons	O
you	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Barney	O
;	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
with	O
tobacco	O
dust	O
in	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
alley	O
,	O
knew	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
after	O
the	O
struggle	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
came	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
Barney	O
and	O
Roberts	O
attacked	O
me	O
in	O
front	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
cleared	O
your	O
eyes	O
of	O
the	O
tobacco	O
dust	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
thief-takers	O
have	O
thrown	O
some	O
gold	O
dust	O
in	O
your	O
eyes	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
thief-takers	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
three	O
forty	O
pounds	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
convicted	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
here	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
your	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
believe	O
you	O
said	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
immediately	O
recollect	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
should	O
swear	O
so	O
here	O
,	O
these	O
men	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
convicted	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
reward	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
Atfield-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
Perfectly	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
seldom	O
otherwise	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
particularly	O
recollect	O
whether	O
you	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
your	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
wastaken	O
off	O
;	O
you	O
believed	O
you	O
might	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
then	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
was	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
true	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
recollect	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
your	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
clear	O
now	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
off	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
clear	O
of	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
clear	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
confused	O
and	O
bruised	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
remember	O
better	O
now	O
,	O
what	O
happened	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
than	O
you	O
did	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
the	O
circumstance	O
very	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
then	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
error	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
wilful	O
one	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
remember	O
it	O
better	O
now	O
than	O
you	O
did	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
state	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
wounds	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
bruised	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BIRD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Eversall	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
passage	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
beadle	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
the	O
beadle	O
took	O
this	O
hat	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
just	O
then	O
Troughton	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
Barney	O
whom	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
;	O
Troughton	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
badly	O
used	O
and	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JEWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
beadles	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
Bird	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
upon	O
Eversall	O
,	O
between	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WATTS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
foot	O
running	O
very	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
Roberts	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
wall	O
very	O
softly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
left	O
their	O
defence	O
to	O
their	O
Counsel	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
Eversall	O
and	O
Roberts	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
Barney	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
334.	O
SARAH	B-pers
MILLS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
David	B-pers
Waddey	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
;	O
and	O
half-a-crown	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
.	O
DAVID	B-pers
WADDEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
to	O
Wapping	O
;	O
coming	O
up	O
Nightingale-lane	B-place
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
we	O
let	O
her	O
drink	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
set	O
down	O
by	O
Ross	O
,	O
and	O
enticed	O
him	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
watch	O
andsome	O
silver	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
after	O
Ross	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
enough	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
followed	O
us	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
chucked	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
again	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
staircase	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
place	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
got	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
from	O
her	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
kept	O
me	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
entry	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mob	O
said	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
cry	O
blood	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
rescued	O
;	O
she	O
beat	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
temples	O
with	O
her	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
besides	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
catched	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
another	O
place	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
among	O
such	O
a	O
mob	O
and	O
confusion	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
what	O
place	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
will	O
settle	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
beat	O
and	O
bruised	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
rescued	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
assistance	O
?	O
-	O
One	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
officers	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
myself	O
;	O
Ross	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ROSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
drink	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
partner	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
satisfied	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
glass	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
she	O
followed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Waddey	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
something	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
watch	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
struggling	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
handed	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
Did	O
Waddey	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pot	O
boy	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Radcliffe-highway	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
where	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
who	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
Mr.	O
Waddey	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Ross	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
To	O
Ross	O
.	O
If	O
this	O
woman	O
kept	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
struggled	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
strong	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WILKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hermitage-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Waddey	O
struggling	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
(	O
if	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
hat	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
your	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
people	O
assisted	O
her	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
gown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
turbulently	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
nose	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
he	O
tore	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
neck	O
;	O
tore	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
beat	O
me	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
ill.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
335.	O
LENOX	B-pers
GORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
near	O
Sadler's-wells	B-place
.	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
To	O
save	O
the	O
Court	O
trouble	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
observe	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peer	O
of	O
the	O
realm	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
peers	O
only	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
must	O
be	O
your	O
peers	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
Haynes	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
dinner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
veal	O
cutlet	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
fat	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
very	O
rich	O
sauce	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
public	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
every	O
thing	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
quick	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
twenty	O
times	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Haynes	O
.	O
He	O
ordered	O
some	O
potatoes	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
ready	O
;	O
some	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
boiled	O
and	O
some	O
roasted	O
on	O
the	O
gridiron	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
wine	O
and	O
some	O
porter	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
dinner	O
was	O
served	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
;	O
the	O
waiter	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
gentleman	O
wanted	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
one	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
oath	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
ordered	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
and	O
hosier	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
again	O
very	O
hard	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
spoon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
tax	O
me	O
with	O
your	O
spoon	O
,	O
Madam	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
nobleman	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
me	O
naked	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
magpie	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
that	O
magpies	O
were	O
notorious	O
thives	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
kingdom	O
;	O
I	O
acquainted	O
the	O
king	O
with	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
enraged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
immediately	O
to	O
be	O
liberated	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
's	O
speeches	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
legislator	O
;	O
a	O
maker	O
of	O
laws	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
absurd	O
idea	O
to	O
suppose	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
a	O
breaker	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
an	O
action	O
so	O
base	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
degrading	O
to	O
human	O
nature	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
had	O
fifty	O
servants	O
at	O
command	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
estate	O
of	O
Lord	O
Hertford	O
of	O
forty	O
nine	O
thousand	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
old	O
I	O
had	O
eighteen	O
thousand	O
a	O
year	O
allowed	O
for	O
my	O
education	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
this	O
man	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
in	O
his	O
behaviour	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
his	O
manner	O
,	O
ringing	O
the	O
bell	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	O
TAYLOR	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waiter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
shewed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
fire	O
to	O
be	O
lighted	O
immediately	O
;	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
and	O
hosier	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
his	O
slippers	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
clean	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
a	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
it	O
was	O
well	O
dressed	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
liked	O
it	O
he	O
should	O
dine	O
there	O
often	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
up	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
red	O
port	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
dinner	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
customary	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
cloth	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
without	O
putting	O
a	O
spoon	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
a	O
spoon	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
magpye	O
,	O
or	O
jackdaw	O
,	O
perhaps	O
that	O
may	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
Sir	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
kept	O
here	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
expect	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
if	O
her	O
things	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
spoon	O
might	O
be	O
mislaid	O
any	O
where	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
opened	O
his	O
shirt	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
fumbling	O
about	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
soul	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
cleaning	O
a	O
horse	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
joining	O
this	O
necessary	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
search	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
necessary	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
PHILIP	B-pers
BRISTOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
parliament	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Akerman	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behaved	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
outrageously	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
before	O
for	O
debt	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
insolently	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
this	O
outrageous	O
manner	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
highest	O
sense	O
of	O
the	O
impartial	O
justice	O
of	O
this	O
honourable	O
court	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
336.	O
ANN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
gown	O
and	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
NELSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
muslin	O
shirt	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
muslin	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
own	O
to	O
taking	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
articles	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
touched	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
the	O
duplicate	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
,	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
.	O
A	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
produced	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
gown	O
,	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pairof	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
left	O
me	O
two	O
months	O
a	O
go	O
with	O
two	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
distressed	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Nelson	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
could	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
borne	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
337.	O
JAMES	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
29	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
;	O
a	O
woollen	O
jacket	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Kimpton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maddocks	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
338.	O
MARY	B-pers
CHAMBERS	I-pers
and	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
MARTIN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king's-highway	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Montague	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
a	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
339.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
COOLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
compasses	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
box	O
wooden	O
sector	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
box	O
wooden	O
scale	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
protractor	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
drawing	O
pen	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
brass	O
compass	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Meredith	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
MEREDITH	I-pers
sworn	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mathematical	O
instrument-maker	O
,	O
in	O
New	B-place
Bond-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
shaving	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
foreman	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
hair-pencils	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
foreman	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
excuse	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
;	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
instruments	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
anybody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
either	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
family	O
,	O
or	O
strangers	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
instruments	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
again	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
lead	O
pencils	O
;	O
my	O
neighbour	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
instruments	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
foreman	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
instruments	O
with	O
another	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
Long-acre	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
favour	O
made	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
?	O
-	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
THEOPHILUS	B-pers
BEVERLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
's	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
fourpenny	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
were	O
walking	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
;	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
another	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
case	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
instruments	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
up	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
some	O
instruments	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
any	O
person	O
to	O
attend	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
boy	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
's	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Meredith	O
's	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
;	O
but	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Harrow	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
bad	O
company	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Aged	O
9	O
Years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
340.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FLOYD	I-pers
and	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HAWLEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
an	O
eight-day	O
table	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
MARY	O
WILKINSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
minutes	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
cup	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
clock	O
instantly	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
Floyd	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
clock	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
?	O
-	O
Four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dartmouth-row	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
row	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
row	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
coach	O
standing	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Floyd	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
balt	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
no	O
good	O
intent	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
perceive	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
past	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Hawley	O
came	O
out	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
property	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
clock	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Hawley	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
collared	O
Floyd	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
behind	O
a	O
shutter	O
place	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
Another	O
man	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LAMBERT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Edwards	O
take	O
Floyd	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
run	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
syllable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoners	O
together	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ASHTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
them	O
along	O
,	O
Floyd	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
ca	O
n't	O
hang	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
shall	O
only	O
go	O
to	O
Botany-Bay	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
my	O
age	O
,	O
will	O
soon	O
whip	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
behaved	O
very	O
civil	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
clock	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
)	O
HAWLEY	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Floyd	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Tothill-fields	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
To	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Did	O
these	O
boys	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
Floyd	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
past	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
followed	O
Floyd	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
Dartmouth-row	O
together	O
.	O
Hawley	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
.	O
FLOYD	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Stutton-ground	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
nobody	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
clock	O
lying	O
behind	O
a	O
shutter	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Hawley	O
before	O
.	O
HAWLEY	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
FLOYD	O
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
Aged	O
13	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
341.	O
TIMOTHY	B-pers
FOLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
watch	O
rim	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
base	O
metal	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Urbie	O
;	O
last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
fast	O
asleep	O
against	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
Oxford-buildings	B-place
;	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
.	O
GEORGE	O
CUMING	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
where	O
this	O
man	O
lay	O
in	O
Oxford-buildings	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
returned	O
about	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sat	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
fast	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
asleep	O
then	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
drunk	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
will	O
do	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watchman	O
pull	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
within-side	O
his	O
own	O
great-coat	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
the	O
beadle	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
dispute	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thing	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
very	O
well	O
how	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BIDDINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
beadle	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
watch-house	O
keeper	O
,	O
and	O
Cuming	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
who	O
the	O
watch	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
recollect	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
among	O
the	O
ashes	O
under	O
the	O
grate	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
Cumingdescribed	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
seals	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
very	O
perfectly	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
cried	O
the	O
hour	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
laying	O
drunk	O
in	O
the	O
buildings	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
I	O
came	O
my	O
rounds	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
lying	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
home	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
ashes	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
play	O
any	O
games	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
locked	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
beadle	O
knows	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
To	O
Biddington	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
does	O
he	O
bear	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
excused	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privily	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
342.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SINCLAIR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
eighteen	O
same	O
live	O
pigeons	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
tame	O
live	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
343.	O
JAMES	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ivy-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Newgate-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
counterpane	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JENNINGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
counterpane	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
counterpane	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Aged	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
344.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARCOURT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
NICHOLSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
23	I-place
,	I-place
Barbican	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
the	O
glass	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
theprisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
people	O
round	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
345.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HARBOTTLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
containing	O
13	O
in	O
number	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tilsley	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
346.	O
HENRY	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Forshaw	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
borrowed	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
borrowed	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
347.	O
HENRY	B-pers
POWEL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mathew	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
MATHEW	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Custom-house	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
near	O
Holborn-court	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
prisoner	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
ROSE	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
348.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANDERSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cotton	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
child	O
's	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
clock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
WHITING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Virginia-street	B-place
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
myown	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
walk	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
missed	O
a	O
cloak	O
and	O
bonnet	O
,	O
besides	O
what	O
she	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
My	O
friends	O
live	O
at	O
Bristol	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
than	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
349.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
BENJAMIN	O
FOX	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
about	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
one	O
Brown	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
cloak	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
sheet	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
folded	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
sheet	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
.	O
ALEXANDER	B-pers
DOWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
350.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
INGRAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Castle	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Portugal-street	I-place
,	I-place
Lincoln's-inn-fields	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
pot-boy	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
we	O
missed	O
two	O
table-spoons	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
the	O
cook	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
burst	O
out	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Mr.	O
Turton	O
and	O
partner	O
,	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
,	O
Cripplegate	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TURTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
working	O
silversmith	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
spoons	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
melted	O
.	O
To	O
Ingram	O
.	O
Has	O
Mr.	O
Turton	O
ever	O
been	O
examined	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
Wright	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Turton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
spoon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
master	O
taylor	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
bought	O
the	O
first	O
spoon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
with	O
another	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
almost	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
came	O
in	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
boy	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
sayshe	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
make	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
our	O
boy	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
melt	O
the	O
property	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
owners	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
I	O
inelred	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
we	O
take	O
silver	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
our	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
as	O
many	O
spoons	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
And	O
do	O
you	O
buy	O
of	O
any	O
stranger	O
that	O
comes	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
boy	O
came	O
with	O
so	O
plausible	O
a	O
story	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
suspected	O
him	O
then	O
you	O
melted	O
it	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
a	O
week	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mean	O
any	O
harm	O
.	O
Buying	O
plate	O
of	O
strangers	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
destroying	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
improper	O
conduct	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
promise	O
you	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
my	O
name	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
in	O
question	O
now	O
;	O
we	O
work	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
capital	O
houses	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
?	O
-	O
Indeed	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
examined	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
examined	O
you	O
now	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Turton	O
's	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
13	O
years	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
351.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BATES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
two	O
odd	O
boots	O
off	O
my	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
boots	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
boots	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
boots	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
15	O
years	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
352.	O
HARRIOT	B-pers
DONKLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
three	O
wooden	O
bobbins	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dutch	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dutch	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
silk	O
warehouse	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
bobbins	O
of	O
silk	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
three	O
bobbins	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Dutch	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WEST	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
place	O
the	O
bobbins	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
near	O
her	O
own	O
mill	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
Court	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
stooped	O
over	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
through	O
her	O
pocket-hole	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Wall	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
and	O
Arthur	O
Lawrence	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
neverwronged	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
To	O
Wall	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
serve	O
her	O
time	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dutch	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
some	O
years	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
her	O
character	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
353.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FLETCHER	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LING	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MEDCALF	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
FIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
clothes	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Fletcher	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
second-hand	O
shirt	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
Ling	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
Fletcher	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
fit	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
that	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
nail	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
jerk	O
to	O
disengage	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
nail	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
did	O
Ling	O
and	O
Fletcher	O
speak	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
Ling	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LARKIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Russel-court	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Fletcher	O
and	O
another	O
running	O
;	O
Fletcher	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
across	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
went	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Jealous	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Nag's-head-court	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
gown	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
middle	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Ling	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
JEALOUS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
Nag's-head-court	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Ling	O
's	O
voice	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
voice	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
gown	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
FLETCHER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
LING	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
sister	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Medcalf	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
upon	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FLETCHER	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LING	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
MEDCALF	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
354.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DUNFORD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Buckmaster	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
thirty-six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Roger	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
stolen	O
the	O
said	O
goodsdid	O
afterward	O
break	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
ROGER	B-pers
BUCKMASTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
meat	O
and	O
cloth	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
cloth	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
one	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
meat	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
state	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
front	O
door	O
was	O
unbolted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
open	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
ANDREW	O
MARTIN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Buckmaster	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
His	O
back	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
larch	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
from	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
fifty-two	O
pounds	O
of	O
meat	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
cloth	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
Almighty	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
!	O
John	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
confirmed	O
his	O
evidence	O
;	O
and	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
property	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
property	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
lie	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gates	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
minute	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
what	O
they	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
To	O
Martin	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
day-light	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
moon-light	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
beginning	O
to	O
be	O
day-light	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
day-light	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
coming	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
To	O
Laurence	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
Buckmaster	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
so	O
little	O
account	O
of	O
your	O
meat	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
lose	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
without	O
missing	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
missed	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
355.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
HOUNSUM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
George	I-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Baronet	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	O
NICHOLSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Sir	O
Henry	O
George	B-pers
Little	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
assistant	O
to	O
the	O
cook	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
dismissed	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
table-spoons	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Muncaster	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
MUNCASTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Chandler-street	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
by	O
some	O
questions	O
I	O
put	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
answers	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
dustman	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
at	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Little	I-pers
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Nicholson	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
spoon	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
dust	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
dustman	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
eat	O
my	O
porridge	O
with	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
356.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MACSALL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Heald	I-pers
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
HEALD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pork-butcher	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
horse	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
ten	O
weeks	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
upon	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
excuse	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Nor	O
threatening	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
about	O
Barnet	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CAVELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gate-keepers	O
at	O
Battle-bridge	O
turnpike	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
riding	O
a	O
horse	O
without	O
a	O
bridle	O
or	O
saddle	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
grass	O
;	O
he	O
eat	O
there	O
I	O
suppose	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
move	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mincher	O
,	O
a	O
horse-boiler	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
horse	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
horse	O
worth	O
more	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
judgment	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
MINCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
horse-boiler	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
horse	O
of	O
Cavell	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
More	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
uncommon	O
poor	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
getting	O
it	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
To	O
Heald	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
day	O
labouring	O
man	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
riding	O
the	O
horse	O
off	O
the	O
common	O
with	O
a	O
halter	O
,	O
by	O
Barnet	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Edgeware	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
miles	O
from	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Cavell	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
another	O
to	O
morrow	O
.	O
To	O
Heald	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
another	O
horse	O
on	O
the	O
common	O
?	O
-Yes	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
taking	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
rid	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Aged	O
70	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
357.	O
SARAH	B-pers
HOUSE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Courtland	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
COURTLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
seven	O
shirts	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Henry	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
see	O
if	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
safe	O
:	O
on	O
missing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
BARLOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
cloak	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
shirt	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
shirt	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Barlow	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
358.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
GOULDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Goffee	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
pawning	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
359.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BARNETT	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RILEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
seen	O
drawing	O
the	O
ribbon	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ASHURST	O
.	O
360.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
GRACE	I-pers
and	O
MARGARET	B-pers
SULLIVAN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
base	O
coin	O
resembling	O
the	O
current	O
silver	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
falsly	O
and	O
deceitfully	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
traiterously	O
did	O
colour	O
with	O
materials	O
,	O
producing	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
a	O
round	O
blank	O
of	O
base	O
metal	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
fit	O
size	O
and	O
figure	O
to	O
be	O
coined	O
into	O
counterfeit	O
milled	O
money	O
,	O
did	O
colour	O
with	O
materials	O
producing	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
silver	O
.	O
Third	O
and	O
fourth	O
Counts	O
,	O
for	O
colouring	O
with	O
materials	O
producing	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
base	O
coin	O
of	O
a	O
fit	O
size	O
to	O
be	O
coined	O
into	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
sixpence	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Silvester	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WHITEWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
Examined	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Reeve	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
for	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Wapping	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Tennis-court	B-place
,	I-place
Middle-row	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Peter	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
;	O
according	O
to	O
our	O
information	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
;	O
we	O
let	O
ourselves	O
in	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
very	O
softly	O
;	O
Mayne	O
went	O
first	O
,	O
Robinson	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
next	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
partners	O
,	O
(	O
Mayne	O
)	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
position	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
opened	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
object	O
that	O
drew	O
my	O
attention	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
table	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
six-pence	O
in	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
stuff	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
,	O
rubbing	O
it	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
stuff	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
right	O
arm	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
woman	O
!	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
engage	O
in	O
so	O
dangerous	O
a	O
business	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
back	O
in	O
her	O
chair	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
thatwere	O
with	O
me	O
took	O
the	O
six-pence	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Robinson	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
here	O
sealed	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
nothing	O
from	O
her	O
but	O
this	O
black	O
stuff	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
phial	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
some	O
scowering	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
file	O
that	O
was	O
also	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
leather	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
box	O
;	O
all	O
those	O
things	O
were	O
laying	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brush	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
else	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
.	O
Describe	O
the	O
situation	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
,	O
boiling	O
something	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
cooking	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
situation	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
Robinson	O
,	O
in	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
light	O
before	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
door	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
latch	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
Whiteway	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
her	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
rubber	O
drop	O
into	O
her	O
lap	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
why	O
will	O
you	O
tell	O
such	O
cursed	O
stories	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
six-pences	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
loose	O
;	O
then	O
with	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
she	O
took	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
lap	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
ham	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
new	O
shoe	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
shoe	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
sample	O
of	O
money	O
unfinished	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
brown	O
paper	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
shoe	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
shoe	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
foot	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
file	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
pliers	O
;	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
this	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
,	O
was	O
latched	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
knob	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
fitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
woman	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
had	O
two	O
shoes	O
on	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
shoe	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
foot	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
in	O
his	O
flurry	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
slipper	O
on	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
suppose	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
suppose	O
;	O
had	O
the	O
man	O
two	O
shoes	O
on	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
slipper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
shoe	O
.	O
Both	O
his	O
feet	O
were	O
covered	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
pardon	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
foot	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
slipper	O
,	O
not	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
heel	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
new	O
shoe	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
new	O
shoe	O
on	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
new	O
shoe	O
on	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
out	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Till	B-pers
that	O
time	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
shoe	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
shoe	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
shoe	O
directly	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
cooking	O
his	O
supper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
cooking	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
fitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
kettle	O
of	O
some	O
sort	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kettle	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
examine	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
potatoes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
might	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
his	O
supper	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
possibly	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
blowing	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Nothing	O
on	O
the	O
fire	O
but	O
these	O
potatoes	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
you	O
are	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
What	O
kind	O
of	O
officer	O
?	O
-	O
Headborough	O
.	O
Where	O
chosen	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
Easter	O
;	O
out	O
parish	O
officers	O
are	O
generally	O
sworn	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sworn	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
parish	O
officer	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
regular	O
officer	O
for	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
headborough	O
?	O
-	O
Four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Regularly	O
elected	O
every	O
year	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
substitute	O
for	O
another	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
headborough	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
substitute	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
who	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
attend	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
offices	O
as	O
runner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
ROBINSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
almost	O
facing	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
138	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
green	O
stall	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Quenton	O
's	O
glass-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
former	O
witnesses	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
information	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
this	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
table	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seemingly	O
was	O
doing	O
something	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
seemingly	O
,	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
?	O
-	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
me	O
give	O
my	O
evidence	O
easy	O
;	O
in	O
her	O
fingers	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
rubbing	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Whiteway	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
twisted	O
the	O
six-pence	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
fingers	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whiteway	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
marked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Whiteway	O
's	O
keeping	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
this	O
paper	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
)	O
the	O
seal	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
opened	O
.	O
Whiteway	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
six-pence	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
rubbing	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
article	O
I	O
took	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
place	O
over	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
china	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
looking	O
in	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
twenty-four	O
base	O
sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
base	O
shillings	O
;	O
on	O
a	O
mantle	O
piece	O
,	O
over	O
the	O
fire	O
places	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
eleven	O
sixpences	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
tea	O
cup	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
shillings	O
on	O
the	O
mantle	O
piece	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
shilling	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
prisoner	O
's	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
in	O
looking	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
copper	O
.	O
To	O
Robinson	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
Quenton	O
's	O
glass	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
space	O
man	O
,	O
constantly	O
with	O
the	O
stoker	O
,	O
one	O
week	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mayne	O
and	O
Whiteway	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
tea	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
always	O
passed	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
officers	O
of	O
Justice	O
.	O
Runners	O
at	O
some	O
office	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
but	O
in	O
one	O
business	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
their	O
abilities	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
seeing	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
taking	O
some	O
people	O
once	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
?	O
-	O
For	O
a	O
felony	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
will	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
God	O
knows	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
stop	O
peoples	O
ears	O
when	O
they	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
sixpence	O
in	O
my	O
month	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Whiteway	O
marked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Whiteway	O
after	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
gaol	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
keep	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
mouth	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
separate	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
never	O
any	O
bad	O
sixpences	O
of	O
shillings	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
,	O
frequently	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
taken	O
many	O
such	O
a	O
shilling	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
might	O
,	O
or	O
might	O
not	O
;	O
see	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
liable	O
to	O
take	O
bad	O
money	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
many	O
such	O
a	O
six-pence	O
as	O
this	O
too	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
employed	O
many	O
years	O
for	O
the	O
mint	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
coiners	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
things	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
your	O
opinion	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
