TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1789	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
S	B-pers
.	I-pers
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
;	O
and	O
J	O
.	O
BELL	O
,	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
MDCCLXXXIX	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GILL	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Beaumont	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Holbird	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Gammon	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Scammell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Serle	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hargrave	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kineleside	I-pers
James	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Eshelby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Muskett	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Clunn	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Dinning	I-pers
Lacey	B-pers
Funderson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Edridge	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Durand	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
George	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gallard	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
William	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
.	O
741.	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
another	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
metal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
shagreen	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
outside	O
watch	O
cases	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ihon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
IHON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	B-place
,	I-place
East	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
he	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
that	O
day	O
at	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
room	O
,	O
adjoing	O
to	O
a	O
sleeping	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
more	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
;	O
they	O
walked	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
ordered	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
company	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
information	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
quick	O
round	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
again	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watches	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
on	O
hooks	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
work	O
board	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch	O
maker	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
valued	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
at	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
watch	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
valued	O
at	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cases	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
two	O
silver	O
outside	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
about	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
with	O
certainly	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
seem	O
to	O
state	O
very	O
fairly	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
watches	O
left	O
with	O
you	O
for	O
repair	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
A	O
hundred	O
years	O
ago	O
there	O
would	O
not	O
fetch	O
forty	O
shillings	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
RUSHBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
taken	O
.	O
CHARLES	O
FOX	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
watches	O
and	O
two	O
watch	O
cases	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
watches	O
and	O
cases	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
MELLING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
business	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
742.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOLLOWAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
most	O
noble	O
James	B-pers
Brydges	I-pers
,	O
duke	O
of	O
Chandos	O
,	O
affixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Silvester	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
PEARCE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Eyles	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
leadwas	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
chissel	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
were	O
given	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Keen	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
DANIEL	B-pers
KEEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
eight	O
miles	O
from	O
Stanmore	O
church	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Eyles	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
laid	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
resigned	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Fitch	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
counted	O
the	O
pieces	O
;	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fitch	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
lead	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Eyles	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
lead	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
PRESTON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
compared	O
the	O
lead	O
with	O
the	O
duke	O
's	O
mausoleum	O
;	O
I	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
hips	O
;	O
every	O
part	O
matched	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
pieces	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
cut	O
off	O
like	O
a	O
tally	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
that	O
mausoleum	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
fresh	O
cut	O
;	O
the	O
mausoleum	O
is	O
built	O
against	O
the	O
church	O
.	O
-	O
FITCH	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
agent	O
to	O
the	O
duke	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
this	O
very	O
lead	O
being	O
put	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
duke	O
and	O
his	O
family	O
always	O
kept	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Kentish-town	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
743.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
SHUTE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berger	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Berger	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Woodyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
Kelly	O
called	O
on	O
their	O
recognizances	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
The	O
recognizances	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
744.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
tablespoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
COCKRAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
above	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
when	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
most	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
going	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
articles	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
these	O
articles	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
no	O
promise	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
BELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
Peter	O
street	O
,	O
Golden-square	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
shirt	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
marked	O
W.	O
C.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
one	O
year	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
745.	O
MARY	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
and	O
SARAH	B-pers
MALONE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ADAMSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Rag-fair	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
Saltpetre-bank	B-place
,	O
all	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
having	O
some	O
beer	O
and	O
gin	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
out	O
betwixt	O
themselves	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
neither	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
a	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
rascal	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
that	O
they	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
turned	O
my	O
pocket	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
by	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
quitted	O
me	O
immediately	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
rushed	O
from	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
coat	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
two	O
houses	O
with	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
liquor	O
and	O
gin	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
them	O
any	O
thing	O
besides	O
;	O
how	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
sober	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
sober	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
turning	O
your	O
pocket	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
threatened	O
me	O
with	O
words	O
.	O
What	O
words	O
?	O
-	O
Says	O
they	O
,	O
we	O
want	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
money	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
threatening	O
words	O
?	O
-	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
audacious	O
names	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
my	O
clothes	O
off	O
my	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
words	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
words	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
was	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
perfectly	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
frightened	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
two-pence	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
ever	O
seeing	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
pence	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
officer	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CHAPMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lodges	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
blood	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoners	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
PETER	B-pers
MAYNE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
MARY	O
OWEN	O
-	O
SARAH	B-pers
MALONE	I-pers
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
746.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOW	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
GILES	I-pers
,	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
INKINS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
long	O
ells	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
stating	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Silvester	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
AUGUSTUS	I-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
wharfingers	O
at	O
Chamberlain	B-place
's	I-place
wharf	I-place
;	O
there	O
were	O
ninety	O
bales	O
of	O
flannels	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wingate	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Perrins	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
consigned	O
;	O
we	O
received	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
landed	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
five	O
;	O
there	O
appeared	O
no	O
deficiency	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
bale	O
that	O
was	O
afterwards	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
safe	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
at	O
Chamberlain	O
's	O
wharf	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
bale	O
of	O
white	O
flannel	O
cut	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
clerks	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
five	O
pieces	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
;	O
such	O
bales	O
always	O
contain	O
ten	O
pieces	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERRINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
factor	O
;	O
each	O
bale	O
should	O
contain	O
ten	O
pieces	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
STUBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
40	O
,	O
Upper	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
buckle	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
balance	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Joseph	B-pers
Inkins	I-pers
first	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
flannel	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
concern	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
How	O
and	O
Giles	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
flannel	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
immediately	O
the	O
officers	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Whiteway	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Beyer	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
Giles	O
and	O
How	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
Inkins	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Inkins	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
swear	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
nothing	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
STUBBS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
Giles	O
and	O
How	O
brought	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
them	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Inkins	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WHITEWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
the	O
publick	O
office	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
on	O
information	O
,	O
with	O
Beyer	O
to	O
Stubbs	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
How	O
and	O
Giles	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Stubbs	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
flannel	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Stubbs	O
said	O
the	O
flannels	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
flannel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
bundles	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
Inkins	O
and	O
Wells	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wells	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
flannel	O
;	O
Beyer	O
ran	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Inkins	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
men	O
and	O
the	O
flannel	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
BEYER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Whiteway	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
How	O
and	O
Giles	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Joseph	B-pers
Inkins	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
flannel	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
our	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
flannel	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Perrins	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Windage	I-pers
of	O
Devonshire	O
,	O
consigned	O
to	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
they	O
appear	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bale	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
pieces	O
;	O
they	O
correspond	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
HOW	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
to	O
my	O
chest	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
both	O
swore	O
different	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
that	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trowsers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cast	O
in	O
his	O
eye	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
GILES	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
anything	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
this	O
flannel	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
yard	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
eight-pence	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
measure	O
to	O
measure	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
WELLS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
coach	O
come	O
by	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Inkins	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOW	I-pers
JOHN	B-pers
GILES	I-pers
ROBERT	B-pers
WELLS	I-pers
JOSEPH	B-pers
INKINS	I-pers
GUILTY	O
,	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
747.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OLDING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
hair	O
trunk	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
eight	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
dimity	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
bed-gowns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Merriday	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
muslin	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
robbins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
callico	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jemima	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
;	O
two	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
riding	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
riding	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.a	O
linen	O
riding	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
twenty	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sterne	B-pers
Figg	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Merriday	I-pers
,	O
Jemima	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
called	O
on	O
their	O
recognizances	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
The	O
recognizances	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
748.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CARGILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
STANHOPE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Winchmore-hill	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
repeats	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
THEOPHILUS	B-pers
BUTCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Barnet	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
jew	O
,	O
Barnet	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
three	O
pronged	O
fork	O
with	O
a	O
crest	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
bring	O
proof	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Wilmot	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
a	O
fork	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
a	O
fork	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Francis	O
.	O
-	O
FRANCIS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
old	O
silver	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
a	O
fork	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
positively	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
boy	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
employ	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
only	O
drove	O
for	O
one	O
person	O
at	O
Dunstable	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
was	O
Palmer	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
these	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
spoon	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
R.	O
H.	O
and	O
numbered	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
employ	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
out	O
an	O
advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
daily	O
advertiser	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
draft	O
of	O
the	O
advertisement	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
daily	O
advertiser	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
my	O
wishing	O
to	O
keep	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
the	O
daily	O
advertiser	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
be	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
learn	O
what	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
know	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
means	O
of	O
saving	O
him	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
749.	O
JANE	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
linen	O
pin-cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
PRUDENCE	B-pers
BERRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
glasses	O
of	O
liquor	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
lap	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
750.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BROOMHEAD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
ewe	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jewson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JEWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
partner	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
wether	O
sheep	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
three	O
ruddle	O
strokes	O
over	O
the	O
shoulder	O
;	O
one	O
across	O
the	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brand	O
mark	O
;	O
we	O
bought	O
it	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
skin	O
since	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HARWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
in	O
Newport-market	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
;	O
with	O
a	O
sheep	O
skin	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
my	O
skin	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
skin	O
he	O
wished	O
to	O
send	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
mine	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
twenty-one	O
pence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
my	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Jewson	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
talking	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
skin	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MERRYMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
drover	O
for	O
Jack	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
;	O
I	O
am	O
aged	O
seventeen	O
;	O
I	O
drove	O
some	O
sheep	O
to	O
field	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
sheep	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
five	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
these	O
sheep	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
ewes	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
all	O
four	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Skin	O
produced	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Jewson	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harwood	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
ruddle	O
marks	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
brand	O
marks	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
drover	O
while	O
he	O
drove	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
marks	O
are	O
not	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fair	O
skin	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Harwood	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
my	O
next	O
neighbour	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
concealment	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
Newport-alley	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
751.	O
DAVID	B-pers
BRAITHWAITE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
flannel	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
three	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
pincloths	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
a	O
nankeen	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
nankeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
trowsers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
MARTHA	B-pers
STAPLES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
of	O
no	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
34	I-place
,	I-place
Virginia-street	I-place
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
past	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
house	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
till	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
my	O
back	O
parlour	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
clothes	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
opened	O
;	O
that	O
pane	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
seven	O
striped	O
,	O
and	O
checked	O
linen	O
shirts	O
;	O
five	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
one	O
dropped	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
tub	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
hanging	O
on	O
the	O
cock	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
tub	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
lost	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
a	O
shirt	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
value	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
dirty	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
found	O
one	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
purchased	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
;	O
this	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
just	O
before	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dirty	O
shirt	O
and	O
hat	O
laying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
COOK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
20th	O
instant	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shirt	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
produce	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
for	O
one	O
Peters	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
.	O
Has	O
Peters	B-pers
any	O
more	O
shirts	O
of	O
that	O
make	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
hat	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
buckle	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
To	O
Baker	O
.	O
Was	O
Peters	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
to	O
Cook	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
understood	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
common	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
understood	O
they	O
slept	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BAWTREY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
misfortunate	O
woman	O
of	O
thetown	O
;	O
at	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
calls	O
it	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
something	O
down	O
;	O
it	O
waked	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
drowsy	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
immediately	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
afterwards	O
,	O
this	O
same	O
David	B-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
beside	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
a	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
ticket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
for	O
his	O
ticket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
brought	O
such	O
things	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
premunire	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
muttered	O
something	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
somebody	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	O
Powell	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
place	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
;	O
accordingly	O
she	O
helped	O
me	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Cooke	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
observe	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
shirt	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
752.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RICHARDSON	I-pers
and	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
DUKE	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
hundred	O
and	O
eight	O
halfpence	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
JOHN	O
M'CARTY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
eleven	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
last	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
about	O
two	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
this	O
room	O
they	O
broke	O
into	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
shutter	O
inside	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
bolt	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
wood	O
off	O
where	O
it	O
fixes	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
about	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
tired	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
supper	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
property	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
Richardson	O
was	O
the	O
mussin	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
remarkable	O
half	O
crown	O
on	O
Richardson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clothes	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
lodging	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
remarkable	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
an	O
inch	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
draft	O
board	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
dropped	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
with	O
the	O
halfpence	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Duke	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
on	O
Duke	O
was	O
found	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
made	O
no	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
MARY	O
M'CARTY	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
up	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
itwas	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
room	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
burnt	O
a	O
lamp	O
;	O
the	O
window	O
looks	O
out	O
into	O
a	O
passage	O
outside	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Cockpit-alley	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
supped	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
up	O
five	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
at	O
two	O
;	O
immediately	O
,	O
both	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
me	O
bounced	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
mussin	O
man	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
bird	O
catcher	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Richardson	O
was	O
searched	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
some	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
remarkable	O
shilling	O
,	O
bit	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
bad	O
.	O
DENNIS	B-pers
AUSTIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
my	O
round	O
,	O
front	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
parlour	O
window	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
light	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
alarmed	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
TREADWAY	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
property	O
there	O
;	O
two	O
coats	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Duke	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
near	O
Exeter-change	O
concealed	O
under	O
the	O
stair-case	O
;	O
the	O
mussin	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
apartments	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
mussin	O
man	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
remarkable	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
by	O
itself	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
shilling	O
I	O
produce	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
places	O
I	O
bit	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
know	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
plain	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Handed	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
Duke	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
M'Carty	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
Duke	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
Richardson	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
half	O
crown	O
pieces	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Treadway	O
.	O
The	O
half	O
crown	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Richardson	O
,	O
was	O
rolled	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
letter	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BEAMISH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
clothes	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
RICHARDSON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
one	O
opposite	O
Beaufort-buildings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
changed	O
at	O
Norfolk-street	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
landlady	O
let	O
me	O
into	O
my	O
lodging	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
;	O
Treadway	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
to	O
mark	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
them	O
half	O
crowns	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
know	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten-pence	O
halfpenny	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
keep	O
that	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Treadway	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
M'Carty	O
mark	O
these	O
half	O
crowns	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
directions	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
changed	O
them	O
in	O
Norfolk-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
DUKE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate-market	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
country-men	O
not	O
being	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
in	O
our	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Duke	O
called	O
six	O
witnesses	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Richardson	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
JOHN	O
RICHARDSON	O
NICHOLAS	B-pers
DUKE	I-pers
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
753.	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
brushes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
card	O
with	O
iron	O
teeth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pewter	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
puff	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
horn	O
combs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
dressing	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
curling	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
hatchet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
curtain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
powder	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
prints	O
with	O
wooden	O
frames	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
fire	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
Sutton-street	O
,	O
Goswell-street	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hair-dresser	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
fire	O
irons	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
dangerously	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
be	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
pictures	O
,	O
and	O
powder	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
razors	O
,	O
and	O
puffs	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
,	O
a	O
window	O
curtain	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
constables	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
dress	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
with	O
curtains	O
and	O
fire	O
irons	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
hired	O
above	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
possession	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
jack	O
towel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
dress	O
my	O
customers	O
with	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
YATES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
patroll	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
poor	O
woman	O
's	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
scuffle	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
this	O
curtain	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
prints	O
in	O
frames	O
,	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
articles	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
curling	O
tongs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
combs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
tails	O
,	O
one	O
small	O
brush	O
with	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
chain	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
green	O
handled	O
powder	O
knife	O
,	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
large	O
scissars	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
actually	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
scuffle	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WILLEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
another	O
patroll	O
;	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
direction	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
towel	O
and	O
the	O
dressing	O
cloth	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
Peter-street	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
paying	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
described	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
puff	O
and	O
this	O
comb	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
of	O
the	O
action	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
paltry	O
one	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prints	O
and	O
frames	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dressing	O
cloth	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
;	O
the	O
major	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
were	O
only	O
dressing	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
trifling	O
things	O
might	O
be	O
carelessly	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
without	O
thinking	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
754.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
seafaring	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Emanuel	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Virginia-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
night'slodging	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
chest	O
;	O
he	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
buckles	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
buckles	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Alexandria	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
off	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
that	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
buckles	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
threaten	O
or	O
promise	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
only	O
wanted	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EMANUEL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
This	O
prosecutor	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
seven	O
weeks	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Alexdria	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
price	O
is	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
night	O
following	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
mercy	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Prier	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
promise	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
silversmith	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
the	O
silversmith	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FORRESTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
seven	O
shillings	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
guinea	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
for	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
slept	O
in	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
us	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
people	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Smith	O
.	O
Who	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
man	O
here	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
that	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
man	O
that	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
black	O
man	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
755.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RICE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fulcher	I-pers
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FULCHER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
whitesmith	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
smith	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
shilling	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
slept	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
awake	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
half	O
dressed	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
shillings	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
seize	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
proper	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
things	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
wherehe	O
put	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
756.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OXFORD	I-pers
and	O
DANIEL	B-pers
HURLEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
eighty-four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trother	I-pers
,	O
and	O
affixed	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Daley	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stillwell	I-pers
called	O
on	O
their	O
recognizances	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
BOTH	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
The	O
recognizances	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
757.	O
HENRY	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
DANIELS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
Clement	B-pers
Debney	I-pers
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
CLEMENT	B-pers
DEBNEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
at	O
Thomas	O
Hand	O
's	O
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
at	O
Knights-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Constitution-hill	B-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
alone	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
dusk	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
nigh	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
dressed	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
;	O
nobody	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
sight	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
red	O
jacket	O
,	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
this	O
;	O
(	O
a	O
great	O
bludgeon	O
)	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
quick	O
from	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
pursued	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
Lloyd	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
bludgeon	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
shine	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
in	O
struggling	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Daniels	O
I	O
pushed	O
down	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lloyd	O
immediately	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
this	O
bludgeon	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lloyd	O
asked	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
brown	O
jacket	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
red	O
jacket	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
brown	O
jacket	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
red	O
jacket	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
brown	O
jacket	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
blast	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Daniels	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
knife	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
red	O
jacket	O
;	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
put	O
to	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
which	O
left	O
a	O
mark	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
off	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
left	O
their	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
all	O
this	O
employ	O
?	O
-	O
very	O
nigh	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Did	O
no	O
one	O
come	O
in	O
sight	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
centry	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
hill	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
opposite	O
the	O
pond	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
pond	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
water	O
frightened	O
me	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
might	O
you	O
be	O
from	O
the	O
centry	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
hundred	O
yards	O
fromthe	O
centry	O
of	O
the	O
queen	O
's	O
kitchen	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
nearest	O
centry	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
pursuing	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
own	O
hat	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
overtake	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
And	O
can	O
you	O
then	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
no	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
during	O
such	O
a	O
transaction	O
;	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
their	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
carefully	O
considered	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
swore	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
them	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
with	O
a	O
clear	O
conscience	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
them	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
doubt	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
;	O
I	O
carefully	O
considered	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
before	O
I	O
spoke	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
men	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
robbery	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
these	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
careful	O
after	O
the	O
circumstance	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
watch	O
been	O
found	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
brown	O
jacket	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
this	O
jacket	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Tothilfields-bridewell	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SOWERBY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winnall	I-pers
,	O
pledged	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
since	O
find	O
,	O
is	O
Hodges	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
advanced	O
one	O
pound	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
two	O
dots	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
hour	O
three	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
wiped	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
(	O
Shewn	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
:	O
I	O
pledged	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sowerby	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
you	O
pledge	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
my	O
maiden	O
name	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Winnall	I-pers
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
pledge	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HODGES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
coldstream	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
,	O
in	O
Colonel	O
Morgan	B-pers
's	O
company	O
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
in	O
that	O
regiment	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
watch	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
it	O
from	O
Lloyd	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
quite	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
Lloyd	O
asked	O
me	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
or	O
otherwise	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Daniels	I-pers
:	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
or	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Daniels	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
then	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
comrades	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
before	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
Lloyd	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
Daniels	O
had	O
pawned	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
Hodges	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRIDLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
toward	O
Bays-water	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
more	O
;	O
three	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
:	O
going	O
down	O
Bays-water-hill	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
:	O
Lloyd	O
had	O
this	O
bludgeon	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
knife	O
concealed	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
Daniels	O
let	O
his	O
fall	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bludgeon	O
where	O
Daniels	O
let	O
it	O
drop	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
VYNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
chain	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
she	O
was	O
distressed	O
for	O
a	O
meal	O
's	O
victuals	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
MORANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Produced	O
the	O
chain	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Vyner	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
duplicate	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
watch	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
chain	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
five	O
,	O
up	O
Constitution-hill	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
queen	O
's	O
gardens	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bludgeon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
buckle	O
;	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
appears	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
chain	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
below	O
the	O
gate	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RHODES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
company	O
the	O
prisoners	O
belong	O
to	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
,	O
on	O
guard	O
at	O
Kensington	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Daniels	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
after	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Daniels	O
again	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Shew	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
(	O
looks	O
at	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
makes	O
you	O
recollect	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
the	O
minutes	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
taken	O
notice	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
since	O
then	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
conversation	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
,	O
respecting	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
LLOYD	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
barracks	O
,	O
Daniels	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Hodges	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
pawned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
DANIEL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
last	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
canal	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
watch	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
all	O
my	O
comrades	O
at	O
the	O
barracks	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barracks	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
all	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
call	O
serjeant	O
Rhodes	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Well	O
serjeant	O
,	O
we	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
LLOYD	I-pers
JOHN	B-pers
DANIELS	I-pers
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
758.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CUNNINGHAM	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
three	O
callico	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
three	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
stuff	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
callico	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
furtout	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
CATHERINE	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
;	O
our	O
house	O
was	O
unlocked	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
locks	O
were	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
saloop	O
stand	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
on	O
hearing	O
my	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
one	O
Winter	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
callico	O
gown	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
(	O
describing	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
value	O
all	O
my	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
for	O
saloop	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
china	O
bason	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
shopman	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
in	O
his	O
bundle	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
new	O
gown	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
lodger	O
;	O
a	O
low	O
apartment	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
lets	O
out	O
the	O
lodgings	O
,	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
he	O
lets	O
out	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
tenements	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
house	O
let	O
out	O
entirely	O
to	O
lodgers	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
this	O
gown	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
apartments	O
four	O
times	O
.	O
Any	O
body	O
might	O
see	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
undoubtedly	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
sometimes	O
people	O
are	O
locked	O
out	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
some	O
young	O
man	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apartment	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
new	O
gown	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
WINTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
optician	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
Catherine	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
very	O
much	O
flurried	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
reply	O
;	O
her	O
doors	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
too	O
narrow	O
a	O
compass	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pattern	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
a	O
remarkable	O
mark	O
.	O
)	O
Catherine	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
tore	O
it	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
of	O
wearing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
darned	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BAKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
stir	O
like	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
kick	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
halloo	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
snooze	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
half	O
past	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
clothes	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
drawers	O
were	O
stripped	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
MAYNARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
another	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
themorning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
says	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
WHITE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tash-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
offence	O
;	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
whole	O
week	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
a	O
sore	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
every	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
morning	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
morning	O
of	O
that	O
week	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
till	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
that	O
that	O
morning	O
and	O
every	O
morning	O
that	O
week	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
nights	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
lodging	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jury	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
acquit	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
plain	O
Ann	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
did	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
;	O
then	O
it	O
remains	O
to	O
consider	O
another	O
capital	O
charge	O
,	O
namely	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
stealing	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
above	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
upwards	O
of	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
759.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DALTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hay	O
sale's-man	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
hay-loft	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lost	O
with	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
sprung	O
his	O
rattle	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
dropped	O
the	O
hay	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
day	O
light	O
:	O
I	O
reached	O
rather	O
too	O
far	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
myself	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
HOLMES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
in	O
the	O
hay-loft	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
the	O
hay	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
the	O
hay-loft	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WARD	I-pers
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
hay	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
hay	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
JOHN	O
WARD	O
-	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GURNEY	I-pers
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
760.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
CONNOWAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Coke	I-pers
.	O
JACOB	B-pers
COKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
painter	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Thames-street	O
to	O
Mile-end	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crooked-lane	B-place
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
pushed	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
:	O
and	O
immediately	O
,	O
Meller	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
-	O
MELLER	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
EWEN	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Coke	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
our	O
return	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
croud	O
:	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Coke	O
pushed	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
fishmonger	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
761.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PAINTER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
ewe	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SHELTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
drover	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
ewe	O
sheep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pens	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
:	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Bennett	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
branded	O
with	O
a	O
B.	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
side	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
with	O
an	O
S.	O
and	O
a	O
dot	O
.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
BENNETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
ewe	O
sheep	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	O
John-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
sheep	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
sheep	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
drove	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
:	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Shelton	O
came	O
and	O
claimed	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DINMORE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shelton	O
came	O
for	O
two	O
search	O
warrants	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sheep	O
at	O
Esther	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
,	O
but	O
three	O
were	O
Mrs.	O
Bennett	O
's	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hundred	O
sheep	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
drawing	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
sheep	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
two	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
shop	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
in	O
St.	O
John-street	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
762.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RUMBALD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
fifty	O
printed	O
paper	O
pamphlets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Woodfall	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
SARAH	B-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dorset-street	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
this	O
Christopher	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Pinchin	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Christopher	O
by	O
using	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
waste	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
the	O
warehouse-man	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
as	O
waste	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
it	O
as	O
such	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sheridan	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
paper	O
consist	O
of	O
pamphlets	O
that	O
were	O
saleable	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
them	O
as	O
waste	O
paper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
by	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
pamphlets	O
that	O
were	O
unbound	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
state	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
press	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
certainly	O
looked	O
upon	O
them	O
as	O
waste	O
paper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
news	O
papers	O
with	O
a	O
stamp	O
,	O
sold	O
for	O
waste	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
connection	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOODFALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Eight	O
months	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
state	O
the	O
leading	O
circumstances	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
throw	O
light	O
on	O
the	O
transaction	O
,	O
though	O
they	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
immediate	O
evidence	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
my	O
overseer	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
something	O
alarming	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
facts	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
overseer	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
Wright	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
magistrates	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
wait	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
or	O
discharge	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
extort	O
from	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
stated	O
by	O
the	O
counsel	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Pinchin	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stated	O
his	O
suspicions	O
against	O
Pinchin	O
;	O
who	O
declared	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
sweepings	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
and	O
make	O
any	O
enquiry	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hardly	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
private	O
office	O
tenminutes	O
before	O
my	O
clerk	O
came	O
over	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
directed	O
my	O
overseer	O
to	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
;	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
produced	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
Rogers	B-pers
the	O
overseer	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
bundles	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
not	O
a	O
single	O
word	O
of	O
menace	O
or	O
promise	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
considered	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
perquisite	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
up	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
Morning	O
Chronicles	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
stamp	O
on	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
return	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
are	O
these	O
waste	O
papers	O
?	O
he	O
looked	O
blank	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
entire	O
pamphlets	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
fifties	O
and	O
twenty	O
fives	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
nine	O
pence	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
freely	O
,	O
Christopher	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
Pinchin	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
stated	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
them	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
pretence	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
for	O
such	O
perquisites	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
printer	O
for	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
the	O
very	O
appearance	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
stated	O
them	O
considerably	O
under	O
the	O
value	O
at	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
and	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
CHRISTOPHER	B-pers
PINCHIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Woodfall	O
's	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
these	O
books	O
and	O
papers	O
to	O
Atkinson	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rumbald	I-pers
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
weighed	O
in	O
three	O
different	O
parcels	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
waste	O
paper	O
round	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
one	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
received	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sheridan	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
property	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Woodfall	O
?	O
-	O
Certainly	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
premises	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
claimed	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
overseer	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
as	O
waste	O
paper	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
concealed	O
as	O
waste	O
paper	O
;	O
and	O
tied	O
up	O
with	O
brown	O
paper	O
round	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
contents	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
lump	O
,	O
without	O
ever	O
undoing	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Woodfall	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
authority	O
to	O
sell	O
any	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
further	O
than	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ROGERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
overseer	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Woodfall	O
's	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
till	O
this	O
day	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
insinuated	O
such	O
a	O
liberty	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
applied	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
fetched	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
really	O
a	O
fair	O
perquisite	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
Pinchin	O
with	O
these	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
his	O
perquisite	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sheridan	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
perquisites	O
besides	O
his	O
salary	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
this	O
paper	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
up	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
further	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
than	O
this	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
service	O
I	O
had	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
before	O
as	O
a	O
book	O
binder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
supposed	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
it	O
worth	O
my	O
while	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
one	O
single	O
article	O
of	O
property	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
one	O
single	O
part	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
never	O
locked	O
;	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
the	O
windows	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
down	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
person	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
this	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
consent	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
great	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
at	O
various	O
times	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Woodfall	O
's	O
service	O
;	O
never	O
a	O
daywithout	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
pounds	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
any	O
one	O
could	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
clerk	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
times	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
and	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
appeal	O
to	O
you	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
;	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
never	O
be	O
thought	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
ill	O
use	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
here	O
pretended	O
;	O
I	O
declare	O
to	O
God	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
there	O
before	O
you	O
,	O
