TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
,	O
1790	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
EIGHTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Pickett	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Islington	O
;	O
Sold	O
also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
MARSOM	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
183	O
,	O
High	O
Holborn	O
.	O
MDCCXC	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PICKETT	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Beaumont	B-pers
Hotham	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	O
HEATH	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buxton	I-pers
Thorne	I-pers
William	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Hobdale	I-pers
William	B-pers
Paton	I-pers
Felton	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
John	B-pers
Heaps	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sykes	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Danbykin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Caney	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
Matthew	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Jollands	I-pers
George	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Moakes	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Punderson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Wardel	I-pers
James	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cochran	I-pers
James	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
George	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
David	B-pers
Goughly	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hartshorne	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
George	B-pers
Brandy	I-pers
John	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Gateskill	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
689.	O
MARY	B-pers
WHITTLE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
woollen	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
an	O
iron	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
WILLIAM	O
GRACE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
they	O
paid	O
half-a-crown	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
constantly	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
unnecessary	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
because	O
if	O
the	O
husband	O
was	O
constantly	O
with	O
the	O
wife	O
,	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
being	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
presumption	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
husband	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
the	O
wife	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
coercion	O
and	O
command	O
of	O
the	O
husband	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
690.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
691.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GRIFFITHS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
three	O
pounds	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Willats	I-pers
.	O
Frederic	O
Willats	O
and	O
Walter	O
Drury	O
called	O
on	O
their	O
recognizances	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
their	O
recognizances	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
692.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
STOREY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
one	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
and	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
BRIGGS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Jeffry-square	O
,	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Colney-hatch	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
's	O
carriage	O
;	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
at	O
Colney-hatch	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
on	O
Finchley	B-place
Common	I-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
carriage	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
holding	O
the	O
bridle	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
's	O
chariot	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
clear	O
moonlight	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
ten	O
minutes	O
or	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
from	O
our	O
setting	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
force	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
held	O
it	O
tight	O
;	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
with	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
our	O
watches	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
very	O
violent	O
threats	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
being	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
to	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
delivered	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
finger	O
violently	O
cut	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
drew	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
leaped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
scuffle	O
insued	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
quitted	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
leaped	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
immediately	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
violent	O
blows	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
had	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
blow	O
given	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
blow	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
fell	O
;	O
that	O
blow	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
cutlass	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
opened	O
thedoor	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
arm	O
raised	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
back-handed	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
neck	O
with	O
the	O
cutlass	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
then	O
called	O
out	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
horsemen	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
all	O
be	O
seized	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
expected	O
friends	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
transaction	O
took	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
less	O
than	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
observing	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
whom	O
you	O
suppose	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
face	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
under	O
any	O
alarm	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
under	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
alarm	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
under	O
considerable	O
alarm	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
came	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
observing	O
any	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
on	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
opportunity	O
you	O
had	O
of	O
observing	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
light	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
conscientiously	O
take	O
upon	O
yourself	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
commission	O
of	O
that	O
robbery	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
smallest	O
doubt	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
give	O
any	O
alarm	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
circumstance	O
I	O
mentioned	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
loudly	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
cutlass	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
with	O
oaths	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
meaning	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
not	O
enough	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Monday	O
week	O
following	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
observing	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
appearance	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
observe	O
enough	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
opportunity	O
of	O
observing	O
the	O
other	O
as	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
mine	O
was	O
a	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
double	O
metal	O
cases	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
moon	O
then	O
shining	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
the	O
moon	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
carriage	O
was	O
perfectly	O
clear	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
:	O
the	O
moon	O
shone	O
into	O
the	O
carriage	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
shine	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
perfectly	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
enough	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hair	O
about	O
his	O
ears	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
dark	O
clothes	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
to	O
Dawson	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
cutlass	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
thin	O
man	O
,	O
shorter	O
than	O
myself	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
thin	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
nose	O
,	O
rather	O
bent	O
,	O
and	O
dressed	O
in	O
dark	O
clothes	O
,	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hair	O
about	O
his	O
ears	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
cutlass	O
as	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
cut	O
and	O
thrust	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paisley	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
wounds	O
he	O
has	O
received	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
sire	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
no	O
cutlass	O
;	O
Mayne	O
and	O
Bewe	O
accompanied	O
me	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
apprehended	O
was	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
all	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
dinner	O
:	O
my	O
mother	O
being	O
frightened	O
,	O
fainted	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
they	O
drove	O
to	O
Jeffery-square	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
;	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
Dawson	O
immediately	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Jeffery's-square	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
hearing	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
coachman	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
robbery	O
:	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
Maine	O
and	O
me	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
Maine	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
spice	O
that	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
sell	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
Bill	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
;	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
just	O
then	O
executed	O
;	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
now	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
certainly	O
would	O
apprehend	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
forget	O
you	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Jeffery-square	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
Dawson	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
to	O
Dawson	O
,	O
on	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
hearing	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
cutlass	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Dawson	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
lives	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Paislays	O
,	O
in	O
Jeffery-square	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
mother	O
fainted	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
warrant	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
square	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Briggs	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
cutlass	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
BARON	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
693.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COOPER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
27th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Luke	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
marry	O
and	O
take	O
to	O
husband	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
12th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
so	O
married	O
,	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
27th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
marry	O
and	O
take	O
to	O
husband	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
GEORGE	B-pers
FLEMING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
parish	O
clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
register	O
book	O
.	O
``	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1772	O
,	O
William	O
Cooper	O
,	O
``	O
batchelor	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
by	O
``	O
banns	O
.	O
Witness	O
William	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
''	O
He	O
is	O
dead	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
who	O
subscribed	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
handwriting	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
that	O
marriage	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
parties	O
sign	O
the	O
register	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
letters	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
first	O
husband	O
is	O
now	O
living	O
and	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
NICHOLSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
I	O
nursed	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
by	O
Cooper	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
living	O
;	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
lived	O
together	O
since	O
she	O
went	O
wet	O
nurse	O
to	O
Lady	O
Bathurst	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
England	O
;	O
but	O
lived	O
principally	O
in	O
London	O
:	O
she	O
lived	O
some	O
where	O
in	O
Kent	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
she	O
in	O
Ireland	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
with	O
Lady	O
Bathurst	O
:	O
she	O
never	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
:	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
while	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
:	O
she	O
lived	O
there	O
as	O
housekeeper	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BROOKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1787	O
,	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
acquainted	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
:	O
it	O
was	O
reported	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
Prior	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
three	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
two	O
children	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
courted	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
sister	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
mother	O
and	O
brother	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
church	O
:	O
Prior	O
is	O
a	O
gardener	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
lived	O
together	O
since	O
the	O
marriage	O
on	O
very	O
comfortable	O
terms	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
GOODYERE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
parish	O
clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1787	O
,	O
I	O
find	O
a	O
marriage	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
widower	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
by	O
licence	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
subscribing	O
witnesses	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
marriage	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
writing	O
.	O
WALTER	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
related	O
by	O
marriage	O
to	O
the	O
husband	O
,	O
Cooper	O
;	O
I	O
married	O
his	O
sister	O
:	O
during	O
the	O
seven	O
years	O
preceding	O
May	O
,	O
1787	O
,	O
Cooper	O
was	O
sometimes	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Leicestershire	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
frequently	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Aldridge	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
maintained	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
marriage	O
for	O
nine	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
very	O
often	O
visited	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
doing	O
so	O
till	O
May	O
,	O
1787	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
frequently	O
to	O
the	O
mother	O
and	O
grandmother	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
lived	O
then	O
at	O
Burrows	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Plumsted	O
,	O
in	O
Kent	O
:	O
the	O
son	O
knew	O
the	O
father	O
was	O
living	O
;	O
because	O
when	O
the	O
father	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
our	O
chambers	O
,	O
in	O
Lincoln's-inn	O
:	O
he	O
knew	O
all	O
the	O
seven	O
years	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
alive	O
;	O
they	O
corresponded	O
together	O
by	O
letter	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
father	O
's	O
death	O
till	O
after	O
this	O
marriage	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
can	O
Cooper	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
his	O
son	O
Cooper	O
was	O
;	O
Cooper	O
himself	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
letter	O
now	O
in	O
your	O
possession	O
that	O
ever	O
came	O
from	O
Cooper	O
to	O
his	O
son	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
produce	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
With	O
Colonel	O
Skeffington	B-pers
,	O
at	O
Skeffington-hall	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Tattersa	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
twelvemonth	O
before	O
this	O
marriage	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Emmerson	O
,	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
there	O
now	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
hear	O
of	O
this	O
second	O
marriage	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Recollect	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
boy	O
himself	O
informed	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
carry	O
on	O
this	O
prosecution	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
carry	O
on	O
this	O
prosecution	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
communicate	O
it	O
to	O
Cooper	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
remain	O
silent	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
fancy	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
silent	O
;	O
I	O
fancy	O
some	O
business	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
ago	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
first	O
active	O
step	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
finding	O
a	O
bill	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
step	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
step	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
now	O
of	O
any	O
step	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
further	O
than	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
of	O
Gray's-inn	O
sent	O
his	O
clerk	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
thing	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
for	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
husband	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
children	O
enough	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
was	O
any	O
steps	O
taken	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
What	O
step	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
session	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
any	O
step	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
children	O
has	O
this	O
woman	O
had	O
by	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
second	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
one	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
two	O
children	O
while	O
the	O
first	O
husband	O
has	O
been	O
laying	O
by	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
and	O
she	O
ever	O
meet	O
to	O
your	O
knowledge	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
only	O
hearsay	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
prosecution	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
woman	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
identify	O
her	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
did	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
really	O
married	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
time	O
was	O
consumed	O
in	O
finding	O
out	O
where	O
the	O
second	O
marriage	O
was	O
had	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
You	O
concluded	O
that	O
the	O
connection	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
with	O
Prior	O
as	O
with	O
Burrows	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
meant	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
steps	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
give	O
the	O
second	O
husband	O
notice	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
employ	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
myself	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
for	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
two	O
years	O
next	O
November	O
.	O
Now	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
take	O
any	O
steps	O
on	O
the	O
subject	O
of	O
a	O
second	O
marriage	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
maintain	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
strongest	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
the	O
husband	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
stated	O
as	O
a	O
widow	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
marriage	O
.	O
JANE	O
ALDRIDGE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
married	O
perfectly	O
well	O
with	O
Cooper	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
quarter	O
old	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
together	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Ireland	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
nor	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
once	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
demand	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Ireland	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
great	O
part	O
of	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
several	O
families	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
a	O
safe	O
oath	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
my	O
consent	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Kent	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Kent	O
:	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Kent	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
:	O
Prior	O
courted	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
had	O
that	O
woman	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
Cooper	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
nothing	O
but	O
her	O
own	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
before	O
she	O
married	O
Prior	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
;	O
justly	O
say	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
father	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
nor	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
?	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
dead	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
mourning	O
;	O
oh	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
father	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
mourning	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
aunt	O
and	O
my	O
uncle	O
are	O
in	O
mourning	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
child	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
communicated	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
death	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
father	O
had	O
supported	O
this	O
child	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
said	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
theprisoner	O
ever	O
did	O
hear	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
confident	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
among	O
those	O
who	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Cooper	O
,	O
reported	O
among	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
Sir	O
;	O
it	O
became	O
a	O
common	O
talk	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
believe	O
so	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
my	O
consent	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
marriage	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
she	O
and	O
Prior	O
lived	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
Three	O
years	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
children	O
have	O
they	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
children	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ask	O
your	O
consent	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
?	O
-	O
That	O
was	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
doing	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
she	O
went	O
as	O
a	O
visitor	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
wanted	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
keep	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
was	O
this	O
boy	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
messenger	O
of	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
death	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
fourteen	O
.	O
He	O
accompanied	O
the	O
news	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
your	O
son-in-law	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
observation	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
worthless	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
going	O
into	O
mourning	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Now	O
was	O
there	O
ever	O
the	O
least	O
pretence	O
for	O
supposing	O
or	O
stating	O
the	O
father	O
to	O
be	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
conversation	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
grounds	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
instructed	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
:	O
who	O
was	O
this	O
uncle	O
and	O
aunt	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
mourning	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
to	O
enquire	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
buried	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
off	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
frequently	O
see	O
Cooper	O
at	O
your	O
son	O
's	O
repository	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
never	O
since	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
nor	O
before	O
.	O
How	O
lately	O
before	O
this	O
woman	O
married	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
Cooper	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
for	O
eleven	O
years	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
eleven	O
years	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
it	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
was	O
an	O
hostler	O
at	O
Skeffington	O
park	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
daughter	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
those	O
that	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
this	O
second	O
marriage	O
,	O
ever	O
make	O
the	O
least	O
enquiry	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
means	O
of	O
communication	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
between	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
except	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
the	O
son	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
only	O
go-between	O
the	O
husband	O
and	O
the	O
wife	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
informed	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
husband	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
believed	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
that	O
this	O
woman	O
should	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
on	O
improper	O
terms	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
as	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
as	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
PEATT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
her	O
marriage	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
exactly	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
separated	O
from	O
Cooper	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
servant	O
in	O
several	O
families	O
:	O
Prior	O
courted	O
her	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
child	O
say	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
report	O
:	O
I	O
approved	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
marriage	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
but	O
for	O
that	O
report	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
pains	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
because	O
they	O
behaved	O
very	O
abruptly	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Alderidge	O
's	O
repository	O
during	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
preceeding	O
May	O
,	O
1787	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
during	O
this	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
how	O
often	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Cooper	O
bringing	O
horses	O
to	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
repository	O
?	O
-	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
seeing	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
sister	O
was	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
has	O
asked	O
you	O
whether	O
it	O
wasnot	O
generally	O
believed	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
that	O
Cooper	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
was	O
not	O
it	O
stated	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
Alderidge	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
frequently	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
year	O
1780	O
to	O
1787	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
it	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
this	O
boy	O
was	O
the	O
messenger	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
care	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
more	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
Prior	O
began	O
courting	O
your	O
sister	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
court	O
her	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Plumsted	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
that	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
did	O
Prior	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
propose	O
to	O
marry	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
your	O
knowledge	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
and	O
Williams	O
on	O
good	O
terms	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
communication	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
JANE	B-pers
SUDBURY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
son	O
,	O
by	O
Cooper	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
sister	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
her	O
marriage	O
with	O
Prior	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
courtship	O
:	O
I	O
recollect	O
the	O
boy	O
saying	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
that	O
watch	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
;	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
report	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
mourning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
master	O
that	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
wear	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
that	O
conversation	O
by	O
other	O
people	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
generally	O
understood	O
among	O
them	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Your	O
little	O
circle	O
believed	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
took	O
very	O
little	O
pains	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
enquiry	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
the	O
least	O
reason	O
,	O
except	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
stated	O
,	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
this	O
boy	O
told	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
.	O
He	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
pains	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
this	O
story	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
lived	O
In	O
Crown-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
I	O
frequently	O
saw	O
Aldridge	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Aldridge	O
tell	O
you	O
it	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
coming	O
frequently	O
to	O
his	O
stables	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
:	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
possible	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
approved	O
of	O
that	O
second	O
marriage	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
ever	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
boy	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
nobody	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
good	O
terms	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
builder	O
,	O
at	O
Paddington	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
family	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
Cooper	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
marriage	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
spoke	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
much	O
by	O
the	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
generally	O
spoke	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
marriage	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
before	O
the	O
marriage	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
doubted	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
marriage	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
positively	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
thought	O
herself	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
An	O
independent	O
person	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Prior	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
some	O
measure	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
believe	O
this	O
report	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
your	O
consent	O
to	O
the	O
marriage	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
consulted	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
trustee	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
you	O
was	O
consulted	O
?	O
-	O
How	O
it	O
might	O
suit	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
family	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
husband	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burrows	O
wished	O
to	O
protect	O
his	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
state	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
lawfully	O
protect	O
her	O
:	O
Mr	O
.	O
Prior	O
is	O
a	O
tenant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
bears	O
an	O
undeniable	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
theworld	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
it	O
of	O
several	O
people	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
married	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
conferred	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
withdrew	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
a	O
verdict	O
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
694.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
GARDNER	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gillingham	I-pers
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
dimity	O
waistcoats	O
.	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velveret	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
gauze	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
half	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
caddy	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
GILLINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
was	O
broken	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
23	B-place
,	I-place
Crown-street	I-place
,	I-place
Moor-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
where	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
past	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
lodgings	O
from	O
top	O
to	O
bottom	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
wife	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
William	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
there	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
since	O
.	O
LUCY	B-pers
GILLINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
rooms	O
;	O
their	O
name	O
is	O
Stokes	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
William	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
or	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
were	O
within	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
by	O
finding	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
property	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Mary	O
Parker	O
frequently	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
our	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
their	O
name	O
was	O
Woodhouse	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Edward	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
;	O
but	O
our	O
property	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
his	O
premises	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
take	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
shirt	O
off	O
Gardener	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
that	O
shirt	O
is	O
here	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
VALE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
at	O
Union-hall	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
some	O
lodgings	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
was	O
Parker	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
lodgings	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CAVE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
their	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
Vale	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
together	O
about	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
and	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
's	O
arm-pits	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
duplicates	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
Gardener	O
's	O
back	O
;	O
Gardener	O
said	O
immediately	O
,	O
Parker	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
duplicates	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
Mary	O
Parker	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
GRAYSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
slit	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
laying-inn	O
gown	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
GRAYSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Grayson	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
petticoat	O
and	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
laying-inn	O
gown	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
Bermondsey-street	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
dimity	O
gown	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
passed	O
his	O
word	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Here	O
are	O
my	O
gloves	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
tea-caddy	O
with	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
MARTHA	B-pers
BRIANT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
on	O
the	O
step	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
apron	O
as	O
full	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
hold	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
chuck	O
full	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BAGGIT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
winder	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
the	O
20th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
apron	O
full	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
PARKER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
never	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Grayson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Parker	O
took	O
a	O
caddy	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
the	O
scissars	O
;	O
the	O
caddy	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Vale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Vale	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
and	O
landlady	O
brought	O
this	O
tea-caddy	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
property	O
before	O
I	O
make	O
my	O
defence	O
on	O
my	O
trial	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
with	O
eight	O
shillings	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gardener	O
's	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
shirts	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
fair	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Grayson	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tea-caddy	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
key	O
would	O
open	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Grayson	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
scissars	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Grayson	O
took	O
the	O
lock	O
under	O
her	O
care	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
fetched	O
it	O
away	O
for	O
six-pence	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
tea	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Grayson	O
:	O
Edward	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
is	O
really	O
innocent	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
transacted	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
work	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
GARDENER	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
695.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
TYLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
falsely	O
make	O
,	O
forge	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
cause	O
to	O
be	O
falsely	O
made	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
andcounterfeited	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
act	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
false	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
drawn	O
by	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
directed	O
to	O
William	O
Fielder	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
Gun-street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
merchant	O
,	O
requesting	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
seventeen	O
days	O
after	O
sight	O
,	O
as	O
per	O
advice	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Lindsey	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
as	O
true	O
the	O
same	O
bill	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
an	O
indorsement	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
bill	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
A	O
fourth	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
said	O
indorsement	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
A	O
fifth	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
forging	O
an	O
acceptance	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
bill	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
written	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
words	O
and	O
figures	O
following	O
``	O
accepted	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
``	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
``	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
A	O
sixth	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
particular	O
witnesses	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
with	O
safety	O
proceed	O
to	O
trial	O
without	O
;	O
I	O
expect	O
them	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
this	O
evening	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
can	O
not	O
wait	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
COCKBURN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
academy	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
education	O
of	O
young	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
at	O
Newington-green	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
son	O
to	O
place	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
academy	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
terms	O
of	O
the	O
school	O
;	O
I	O
likewise	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
the	O
terms	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
twenty-five	O
guineas	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
entrance	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
son	O
should	O
dance	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
guinea	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
suit	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
school	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
we	O
opened	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Weymouth	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
send	O
his	O
sister	O
with	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
entrance	O
then	O
:	O
he	O
produced	O
me	O
this	O
bill	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
concerning	O
the	O
bill	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
bill	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
indorsed	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
:	O
the	O
entrance	O
for	O
the	O
education	O
was	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
entrance	O
for	O
dancing	O
was	O
one	O
guinea	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
apply	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
rather	O
fearful	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Foreman	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
this	O
transaction	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
You	O
asked	O
him	O
no	O
questions	O
about	O
the	O
bill	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
FOREMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Cockburn	O
to	O
make	O
enquiries	O
concerning	O
William	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
;	O
I	O
did	O
enquire	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Gun-street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
25	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
empty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
shut	O
;	O
I	O
enquired	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
present	O
the	O
bill	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
who	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
present	O
a	O
bill	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Fielder	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
tenant	O
that	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
enquiries	O
made	O
but	O
about	O
this	O
Fielder	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
no	O
other	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
asked	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
enquiry	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Addington	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
bill	O
became	O
due	O
that	O
you	O
made	O
this	O
enquiry	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
recollection	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
bill	O
became	O
due	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
payment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cockburn	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
negotiated	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
and	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
No	O
.	O
479	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
Bristol	O
,	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
``	O
1790	O
.	O
Seventeen	O
days	O
after	O
sight	O
,	O
please	O
``	O
to	O
pay	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
or	O
``	O
order	O
,	O
10	O
l.	O
James	B-pers
Lindsay	I-pers
.	O
Accepted	O
``	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
.	O
Value	O
``	O
received	O
as	O
per	O
advice	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	O
``	O
Fielder	O
,	O
merchant	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
Gun-street	O
,	O
``	O
Spital-fields	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
no	O
enquiry	O
about	O
the	O
indorsement	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
draft	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
indorser	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Gun-street	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
accepted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fielder	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
I	O
passed	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
lady	O
,	O
and	O
indorsed	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Now	O
shew	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
person	O
was	O
arrested	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bailed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
him	O
forward	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
the	O
nurse	O
that	O
nursed	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
that	O
assisted	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
prepared	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
might	O
have	O
called	O
people	O
enough	O
if	O
this	O
man	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
696.	O
MARIA	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
COOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
night	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
black	O
queens	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
check	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Swinchurch	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
SWINCHURCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catherine's-lane	I-place
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
small	O
house	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
repeating	O
them	O
)	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
lame	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
weeks	O
and	O
three	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
compassion	O
on	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
sprained	O
her	O
foot	O
;	O
I	O
hired	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
robbed	O
me	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
GOLDBURN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
in	O
Angel-alley	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
:	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
want	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
on	O
the	O
black	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
?	O
(	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
black	O
bonnet	O
,	O
cap	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
JONATHAN	B-pers
MURRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
her	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
cloak	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
drawer	O
by	O
itself	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
shift	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
petticoat	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
Idid	O
not	O
bring	O
home	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
every	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
be	O
buried	O
alive	O
:	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
three	O
girls	O
as	O
naked	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
born	O
:	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
men	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
right	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
nobody	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
has	O
done	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
697.	O
MORRIS	B-pers
HALEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
printed	O
bound	O
book	O
,	O
in	O
folio	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
first	O
volume	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
work	O
entitled	O
,	O
a	O
Compleat	O
Body	O
of	O
Heraldry	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
and	O
Basnett	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
COLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
and	O
Basnett	O
Lee	O
,	O
coachmaker	O
s	O
,	O
in	O
High	B-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
they	O
lost	O
the	O
book	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
book	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
moment	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
walking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Going	O
down	O
Holborn	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
for	O
eight	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
698.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PEARSON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
and	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
half-a-crown	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
REBECCA	B-pers
BROOKS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
widow	O
with	O
eight	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Marybone	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
Marybone-street	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
on	O
quarter	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
spring	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
;	O
the	O
leaves	O
were	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
one	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
purse	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
half	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
benches	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
just	O
right	O
facing	O
the	O
clock	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
well	O
dressed	O
man	O
,	O
very	O
genteel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
obedience	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
paper	O
bill	O
of	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
read	O
this	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
eyes	O
to	O
read	O
;	O
so	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
calls	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
after	O
his	O
horses	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
much	O
the	O
diamond	O
was	O
worth	O
:	O
Morgan	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
jobber	O
in	O
Smith-field	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
Morgan	O
stayed	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
returned	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Bank	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
half-a-crown	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
dodging	O
me	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
offeredto	O
give	O
me	O
three	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
is	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
for	O
the	O
six	O
guineas	O
?	O
-	O
Upwards	O
of	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
fetched	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
seven	O
weeks	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Bird	O
Cage	O
Walk	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
this	O
paper	O
away	O
;	O
a	O
soldier	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
watch	O
back	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
delivered	O
your	O
watch	O
to	O
them	O
did	O
they	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
to	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
them	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
proposed	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
your	O
watch	O
finally	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
:	O
my	O
son	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
abroad	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
day	O
did	O
this	O
happen	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
quarter	O
day	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
.	O
To	O
whom	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
your	O
watch	O
and	O
half-crown	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
Morgan	O
,	O
while	O
you	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
To	O
whom	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
the	O
six	O
guineas	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
present	O
when	O
you	O
delivered	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
half-crown	O
to	O
Morgan	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
present	O
when	O
you	O
gave	O
Morgan	O
the	O
six	O
guineas	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
talk	O
about	O
delivering	O
the	O
watch	O
or	O
money	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
;	O
because	O
,	O
though	O
very	O
probably	O
they	O
both	O
set	O
out	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
fraud	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
larceny	O
,	O
yet	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
699.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
HOLIMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
700.	O
SARAH	B-pers
DAGLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
velveret	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wasing	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
WASING	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Glass-house-yard	B-place
:	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wasing	I-pers
:	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
nobody	O
else	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
threshold	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
from	O
four	O
till	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
there	O
above	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
an	O
elderly	O
gentlewoman	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
my	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
much	O
about	O
eight	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
servants	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
no	O
visitors	O
;	O
nor	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
warning	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
warning	O
last	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
shirt	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
bed	O
loose	O
,	O
inthree	O
pieces	O
,	O
by	O
Winder	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
her	O
room	O
was	O
searched	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Do	O
the	O
three	O
parts	O
make	O
one	O
shirt	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
collar	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O
William	O
Winder	O
called	O
on	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
She	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
swearing	O
and	O
blasting	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
such	O
a	O
blasphemous	O
noise	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
701.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DUNKLEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
one	O
earthen	O
milk	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
goods	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
servant	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
when	O
the	O
gates	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
gates	O
were	O
double	O
locked	O
and	O
bolted	O
:	O
Benjamin	O
Bartholomew	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
locked	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
gates	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
;	O
the	O
gates	O
lead	O
into	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
gates	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
the	O
playground	O
,	O
which	O
adjoins	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
milk	O
pan	O
that	O
stood	O
opposite	O
the	O
dairy	O
door	O
,	O
was	O
removed	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
wheel-barrow	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
dairy	O
door	O
about	O
eleven	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
twelve	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
removed	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
ladies	O
boarding-school	O
;	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
family	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
HUGH	B-pers
CAMERON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Silver-street	B-place
,	I-place
Enfield	I-place
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
back	O
yard	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fellows	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
paling	O
about	O
ten	O
feet	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
incloses	O
the	O
whole	O
yard	O
;	O
at	O
both	O
ends	O
is	O
a	O
high	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
front	O
a	O
wooden	O
paling	O
.	O
Can	O
any	O
body	O
get	O
in	O
without	O
going	O
through	O
a	O
gate	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
hedge	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
close	O
gate	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
paling	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
BARTHOLOMEW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cameron	O
's	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
I	O
continued	O
there	O
till	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
a	O
small	O
yard	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
walking	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
dust	O
hole	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
wash-house	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
yard	O
towards	O
the	O
gate	O
that	O
leads	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
lane	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
before	O
he	O
pitched	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
then	O
Paul	O
Roe	O
came	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
also	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
both	O
before	O
I	O
let	O
you	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
us	O
both	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
one	O
with	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
with	O
the	O
left	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
PAUL	B-pers
ROE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
of	O
Enfield	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cameron	O
's	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
continued	O
there	O
till	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
cats	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
nobody	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
play	O
ground	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
BenjaminBartholomew	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
hand	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
heaved	O
the	O
latch	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
then	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
's	O
assistance	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
scuffle	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
searched	O
;	O
they	O
must	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
bolts	O
withinside	O
the	O
double	O
lock	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
this	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
and	O
bolted	O
at	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
nobody	O
was	O
nigh	O
the	O
door	O
afterwards	O
;	O
the	O
pan	O
stood	O
opposite	O
the	O
dairy	O
door	O
,	O
right	O
opposite	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
moved	O
to	O
the	O
barrow	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
gate	O
did	O
the	O
butcher	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
front	O
gate	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
back	O
gate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
COMMON	O
SERJEANT	O
.	O
702.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
COLBORNE	I-pers
and	O
MARY	B-pers
HIPWELL	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
sauceboats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
coffee-pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
nine	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
seven	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
cellars	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
an	O
ink-stand	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
seven	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
waiters	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
plated	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
plated	O
candlestick	O
,	O
extinguisher	O
,	O
and	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
plated	O
cream	O
jug	O
,	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
muffinet	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cruet	O
stand	O
,	O
plated	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
chain	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
hoop	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
green	O
etwee	O
case	O
,	O
mounted	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
gold	O
instruments	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
rouge	O
box	O
,	O
wrought	O
and	O
mounted	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
beads	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
paste	O
buckles	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
garnet	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
twelve	O
real	O
pearls	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
twelve	O
Roman	O
pearls	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Roman	O
drops	O
,	O
for	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
antique	O
Chinese	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
other	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
mourning	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
twelve	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
callico	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
mode	O
cloak	O
,	O
trimmed	O
with	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
wrought	O
bed	O
furniture	O
of	O
India	O
dimity	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
one	O
India	O
dimity	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
one	O
muslin	O
petticoat	O
,	O
flounced	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
jacket	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
bed-gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
callico	O
chemise	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
twelve	O
agate	O
handled	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
bed-gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
gilt	O
metal	O
,	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
paper	O
machee	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
blue	O
and	O
gold	O
smelling	O
bottle	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gilt	O
stopper	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
pillow-biers	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
sixty	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
a	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
eighty	O
silver	O
medals	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tyndall	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
who	O
informed	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
that	O
strong	O
as	O
the	O
suspicions	O
were	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
at	O
all	O
against	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
against	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
capital	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
TINDALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Bolton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Hipwell	I-pers
was	O
left	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
strict	O
charge	O
never	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
town	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
fastenings	O
are	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
no	O
person	O
could	O
get	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
without	O
being	O
let	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
haveno	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
servant	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
quitting	O
her	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
basely	O
going	O
to	O
Sadler	O
's	O
Wells	O
:	O
the	O
plate	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
winter	O
clothes	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
not	O
half	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
these	O
gloves	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
patrol	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
yours	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
pair	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Mary	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
mine	O
most	O
certainly	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
were	O
worn	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
initials	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
cabinet	O
,	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pillow-case	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
belief	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gloves	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
-	O
GRANT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
patrol	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tyndall	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
nothing	O
was	O
lost	O
but	O
plate	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
and	O
the	O
pillow-case	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Hipwell	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
my	O
mistress	O
three	O
honest	O
characters	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
COLBORNE	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HIPWELL	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
703.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ALLWRIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
forty-eight	O
table	O
knives	O
,	O
with	O
black	O
ebony	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
forty-eight	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
other	O
knives	O
,	O
with	O
black	O
ebony	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
forks	O
,	O
called	O
three-prong	O
forks	O
,	O
with	O
black	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four-carving	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
other	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
other	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
carving	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
twenty-four	O
other	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
14	O
s	O
,	O
twenty-four	O
other	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
six	O
other	O
carving	O
forks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
MOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Falcon	O
,	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
town	O
when	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Cloak-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
directly	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Dowgate-hill	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
-	O
JONES	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
,	O
Dowgate-hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
:	O
coming	O
towards	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
cart	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Dowgate-hill	O
,	O
into	O
Cloak-lane	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
me	O
towards	O
Dowgate-hill	O
;	O
the	O
cart	O
went	O
towards	O
Cannon-street	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
stolen	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
porter	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Crowns	O
door	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
expected	O
a	O
box	O
from	O
Birmingham	O
onthat	O
day	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
received	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
orders	O
for	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
on	O
Dowgate-hill	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
NEWMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
the	O
other	O
constable	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
thumb	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
;	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
escape	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
officer	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tried	O
to	O
stab	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
side	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
Jones	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
directed	O
,	O
``	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Cannon-street	O
;	O
''	O
it	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
opened	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
box	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
the	O
direction	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
writing	O
of	O
my	O
correspondent	O
,	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
into	O
Yorkshire	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
box	O
opened	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mott	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
these	O
goods	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
Certainly	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
letter	O
into	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Walbrook	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
coat	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
into	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
agreeable	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
when	O
Jones	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
halloo	O
,	O
cock	O
,	O
does	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
704.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PATRICK	I-pers
and	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PEARCY	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
goblets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Armiger	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
coming	O
through	O
Checquer-yard	O
,	O
Dowgate-hill	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Elbow-lane	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
till	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
two	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
conversing	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Hand-court	O
;	O
they	O
stopped	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
biggest	O
,	O
Patrick	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
across	O
the	O
nose	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
goblets	O
fell	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
into	O
Checquer-yard	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Patrick	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
goblet	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
goblet	O
that	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
myself	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
goblet	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Hand-court	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Patrick	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
goblets	O
ever	O
since	O
:	O
(	O
produces	O
them	O
)	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Armiger	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DICKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
green-grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Little	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Apostle	O
's	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
fortnight	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Patrick	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Armiger	O
's	O
back	O
gate	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
apron	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
two	O
fists	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Little	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Apostle	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ARMIGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
goblets	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
off	O
the	O
sideboard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
half	O
past	O
three	O
;	O
they	O
usually	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
side-board	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
goblets	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Five	O
pounds	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
forty	O
shillings	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
judge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Patrick	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Pearcey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Patrick	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PATRICK	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PEARCEY	I-pers
,	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
705.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
LOWE	I-pers
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JOBBINS	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
did	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
and	O
burn	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Gilding	I-pers
,	O
there	O
situate	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
peace	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gascoigne	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lawes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pardon	O
of	O
James	O
Flindall	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
FLINDALL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
convicted	O
in	O
May	O
sessions	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Now	O
recollect	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
state	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
only	O
to	O
confine	O
yourself	O
to	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Lowe	O
and	O
Jobbins	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Lowe	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Jobbins	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
months	O
.	O
What	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
was	O
Lowe	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
a	O
turner	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Jobbins	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
hearsay	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
chymist	O
or	O
apothecary	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
fire	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
me	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
Lowe	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
State	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
jury	O
whether	O
that	O
fire	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
wilful	O
act	O
of	O
any	O
persons	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
set	O
fire	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Edward	O
Lowe	O
and	O
William	O
Jobbins	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
first	O
proposed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
's	O
house	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Edward	O
Lowe	O
and	O
William	O
Jobbins	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
Lowe	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Hartshorn-court	O
,	O
Golden-lane	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jobbins	I-pers
then	O
proposed	O
to	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pitched	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Gilding	O
's	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
proper	O
places	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
were	O
they	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
?	O
-	O
With	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
and	O
plunder	O
the	O
inhabitants	O
,	O
while	O
in	O
confusion	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
and	O
Lowe	O
agree	O
to	O
that	O
proposal	O
of	O
Jobbins	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
ale-house	O
,	O
Cow-cross	O
;	O
Timothy	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
was	O
there	O
likewise	O
.	O
We	O
acquainted	O
Barnard	O
with	O
the	O
proposal	O
,	O
and	O
Barnard	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Aldersgate-street	O
:	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
?	O
-	O
With	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
shew	O
Barnard	B-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
Gilding	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion-yard	O
,	O
which	O
goes	O
through	O
into	O
Carthusian-street	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
inn-yard	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
cart	O
unloading	O
trussesof	O
clover	O
into	O
a	O
hay	O
loft	O
,	O
which	O
adjoined	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gilding	O
's	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
with	O
very	O
extensive	O
premises	O
;	O
Timothy	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
then	O
proposed	O
this	O
hay-loft	O
as	O
a	O
proper	O
place	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
soon	O
communicate	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gilding	O
's	O
dwelling-house	O
and	O
warehouses	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
clover	O
not	O
being	O
bound	O
so	O
tight	O
as	O
hay	O
,	O
would	O
catch	O
fire	O
sooner	O
,	O
and	O
blaze	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
Barnard	O
and	O
me	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
ale-house	O
,	O
Cow-cross	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Lowe	O
and	O
Jobbins	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Barnard	O
had	O
pitched	O
on	O
the	O
hay-loft	O
as	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
Barnard	O
proposed	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
turpentine	O
wood	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
among	O
the	O
clover	O
would	O
soon	O
blaze	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
Barnard	O
at	O
ten	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Pear-tree-court	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
:	O
we	O
accordingly	O
met	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
directed	O
Mrs.	O
Lowe	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
spirits	O
of	O
turpentine	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
me	O
went	O
to	O
Lowe	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Barnard	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
thieving	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Barnard	O
's	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
:	O
before	O
