TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1790	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
SIXTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Pickett	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
.	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
PART	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Islington	O
;	O
Sold	O
also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
,	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
;	O
and	O
J.	O
MARSOM	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
183	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
opposite	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
MDCCXC	O
.	O
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
UPON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
PICKETT	I-pers
,	O
LORD	O
MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
BULLER	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
John	B-pers
Janneway	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Beardmore	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Sangster	I-pers
James	B-pers
Sansom	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
George	B-pers
Henser	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Veno	I-pers
William	B-pers
Tavenor	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
James	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
Frederick	B-pers
Flading	I-pers
John	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Churton	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Berks	I-pers
William	B-pers
Parminter	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pincent	I-pers
Solomon	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
George	B-pers
Burrowston	I-pers
William	B-pers
Winlow	I-pers
Second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
John	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
Abel	B-pers
Panchard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hooke	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Mayle	I-pers
William	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Alderton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Sheperdson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Stoddart	I-pers
Percy	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Naylor	I-pers
538.	O
MORDECAI	B-pers
PASS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
hundred	O
and	O
sixty-four	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
NASH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
woollen	O
draper	O
and	O
salesman	O
,	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
30	I-place
,	I-place
Ludgate-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
half	O
after	O
nine	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
putthem	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
myself	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
bales	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
to	O
the	O
carman	O
and	O
my	O
lad	O
;	O
the	O
lad	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
packed	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
JESSUP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
carman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holyland	O
,	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Nash	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
last	O
seen	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
packed	O
them	O
up	O
myself	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
nailed	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
Jessup	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jessup	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
yard	I-place
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
cart	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
in	O
little	O
Carter-lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
hands	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
any	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
Nash	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
now	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jessup	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
?	O
-	O
Into	O
Little	O
Carter-lane	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
gentleman	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
box	O
off	O
my	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
THURGOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
following	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
box	O
opposite	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Paul	O
's	O
Chain	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
two	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
companions	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Paul	O
's	O
Chain	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
the	O
carman	O
went	O
on	O
about	O
twelve	O
rods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
carman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Nash	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
box	O
yours	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Conway	O
,	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
thieves	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Thurgood	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Salmon-lane	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
539.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RUGLASS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Letch	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LETCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Temple-bar	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
horse	O
chaise	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
behind	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
some	O
gentleman	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
the	O
coat	O
again	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
get	O
up	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Letch	O
's	O
chaise	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
companion	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
toSt	O
.	O
Mary-Axe	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
called	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopped	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
coach	O
behind	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
slipped	O
under	O
the	O
horses	O
heads	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
what	O
he	O
stopped	O
me	O
for	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
croud	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
Aged	O
17	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
640.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GORE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sattin	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
ATKINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
serjeant	O
at	O
mace	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Lawrence-lane	B-place
,	I-place
No	I-place
.	I-place
2	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
bed-room	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
a	O
peg	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
breeches	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scaffold	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
a	O
man	O
get	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
from	O
that	O
scaffold	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pledged	O
for	O
one	O
pound	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MATTHEWS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
clothes	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
one	O
pound	O
five	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
ATKINS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
property	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
acquit	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
other	O
men	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Atkins	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
true	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
:	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
25	O
s.	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
publicly	O
whipt	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
541.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
NEWTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
ROWLAND	B-pers
PUGH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
week	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
procession	O
of	O
the	O
Free	O
British	O
Society	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Red	B-place
Cross-street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Barbican	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
is	O
here	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
GABRIEL	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket-porter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Red	O
Cross-street	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
myself	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
committed	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
said	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
had	O
you	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
542.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
BUCKLE	I-pers
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
HIGHLAND	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Seagoe	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
stick	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Highland	I-pers
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Highland	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
witnesses	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SEAGOE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
evening	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
Just	O
past	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Plumb-tree-street	O
,	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Buckle	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Dyot-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
pull	O
at	O
my	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
prevented	O
him	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
turning	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
time	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
before	O
Highland	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
Highland	O
follow	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Dyot-street	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
provocation	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
conversation	O
between	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
Highland	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
made	O
the	O
attempt	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
knocked	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
retreat	O
into	O
a	O
coal-shed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
hallooed	O
,	O
blast	O
him	O
,	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
secure	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
other	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
struck	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beth	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Westminster	O
election	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
men	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
riot	O
at	O
the	O
Westminster	O
election	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
people	O
took	O
you	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
opposite	O
party	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
many	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
pick	O
pockets	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
pick	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
-	O
Buckle	O
attempted	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
riot	O
at	O
the	O
election	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
BENJAMIN	B-pers
POWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
night	O
Mr.	O
Seagoe	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
Highland	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
and	O
Buckle	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
speaking	O
to	O
Highland	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
detained	O
him	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TREADWAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HARPER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
BUCKLE	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seethis	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Justice	O
Walker	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sea	O
?	O
and	O
we	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
officers	O
put	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
prosecute	O
us	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
HIGHLAND	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
at	O
the	O
Cat	O
,	O
in	O
Newton-street	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Magnificent	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Justice	O
Walker	O
's	O
the	O
officers	O
persuaded	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
prosecute	O
us	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Treadway	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
reward	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
none	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beth	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
reward	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Highland	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
COFFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milk-carrier	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
for	O
Highland	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
night	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
say	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
till	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cat	O
,	O
in	O
Newton-street	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
Hendon	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
hay	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
else	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
were	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
taproom	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
join	O
your	O
company	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nor	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
supper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
single	O
,	O
or	O
married	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
married	O
.	O
Who	O
served	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
-	O
Sometimes	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
the	O
servant	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
watchman	O
went	O
half	O
past	O
ten	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
come	O
away	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
-	O
Just	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
first	O
;	O
Highland	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
followed	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
your	O
husband	O
and	O
Highland	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
sleeps	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newton-street	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Powell	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
Highland	O
?	O
-	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
.	O
Treadway	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
too	O
well	O
.	O
Harper	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
Powell	O
first	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
BUCKLE	I-pers
(	O
aged	O
20	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
HIGLAND	I-pers
(	O
aged	O
21	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
543.	O
MARY	B-pers
SLIGHT	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
desert	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
shawl	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Noray	I-pers
;	O
one	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
.	O
AUGUSTA	B-pers
CUMBERLAND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
44	O
,	O
Norton-street	O
,	O
Mary-le-bone	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
there	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
livelihood	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
.	O
Does	O
your	O
husband	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
abroad	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Noray	O
?	O
-	O
His	O
wife	O
lives	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
5	I-place
,	I-place
North-street	I-place
,	I-place
Charlotte-street	I-place
;	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
North-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
some	O
littletime	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
things	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
Justice	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
on	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beth	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
married	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
Charles	B-pers
Cumberland	I-pers
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
leave	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
About	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
who	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
there	O
a	O
man	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
besides	O
your	O
sister	O
and	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
.	O
What	O
man	O
lived	O
where	O
you	O
lodged	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
landlord	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Hicks	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Newman-street	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
allowed	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
desire	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
to	O
employ	O
this	O
girl	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Hicks	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
Noray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Noray	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
desire	O
Noray	O
to	O
tell	O
this	O
girl	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Norton-street	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
Hicks	O
's	O
house	O
last	O
Saturday	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
breakfasted	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Noray	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
your	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
prosecute	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
Noray	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
discharged	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
receipt	O
to	O
shew	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beth	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
NORAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
,	O
North-street	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
father	O
lose	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
your	O
knowledge	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Cumberland	O
brought	O
her	O
there	O
to	O
sleep	O
two	O
nights	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
stay	O
two	O
nights	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
leave	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
afterwards	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beth	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
mother	O
a	O
lodger	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
taylor	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Cumberland	O
ever	O
lodge	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
this	O
girl	O
behave	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
civil	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Cumberland	O
send	O
any	O
messages	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
call	O
on	O
her	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
no	O
servant	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HARTLOP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cutler	O
:	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Noray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
property	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
evening	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
detected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
in	O
a	O
checked	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Noray	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
care	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beth	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Cumberland	O
had	O
any	O
goods	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
she	O
have	O
put	O
up	O
these	O
things	O
accidentally	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
Mrs.	O
Cumberland	O
have	O
lent	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Noray	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Noray	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
peep	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
drawer	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Noray	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
on	O
Monday	O
evening	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Noray	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
kitchen	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Noray	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
daughter	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
sorted	O
out	O
Noray	O
's	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
things	O
are	O
here	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
duplicates	O
;	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
this	O
charge	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
rotation-office	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Noray	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
Hartlop	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
throw	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
them	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
(	O
Deposes	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Noray	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
(	O
aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
544.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
DIGHTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
stuff	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Walter	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
WALTER	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
8	I-place
,	I-place
Woodbridge-street	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
.	O
In	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
about	O
six	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
lodgers	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
ours	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
as	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
;	O
she	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
opposite	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
about	O
half	O
past	O
six	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
slam	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
back	O
window	O
sash	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
up	O
;	O
a	O
door	O
opened	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
that	O
bolted	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
left	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
searched	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
cuffs	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
gowns	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
since	O
for	O
another	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
March	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
belonging	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
duplicate	O
of	O
a	O
petticoat	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
out	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
afterwards	O
came	O
again	O
tomy	O
lodgers	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
accused	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
she	O
abused	O
us	O
for	O
taking	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
a	O
duplicate	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
petticoat	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
of	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
gowns	O
cost	O
me	O
twenty-seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
;	O
the	O
petticoats	O
were	O
good	O
ones	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
the	O
petticoat	O
at	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Hart	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
person	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
a	O
back	O
window	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
that	O
left	O
open	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
left	O
up	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
fastened	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
fasten	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
leave	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
not	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
drawn	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
petticoat	O
;	O
Justice	O
Blackborough	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
abused	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
the	O
petticoat	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
duplicates	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
petticoat	O
:	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Hart	O
,	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1790	O
.	O
Black	O
petticoat	O
,	O
1	O
s.	O
''	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
nobody	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
petticoat	O
:	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
come	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
545.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
DIGHTON	I-pers
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
BRICE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
seven	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
people	O
below	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
further	O
notice	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
cloak	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartments	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
bonnet	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
remnants	O
of	O
silk	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
edging	O
off	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
work	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
else	O
but	O
the	O
cloak	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
other	O
mark	O
but	O
this	O
cut	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
HART	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COLLINS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
silk	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
cloak	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
long	O
before	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
take	O
warning	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
you	O
are	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
546.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
DAVIS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sattinet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
body	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
twelve	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
mustard	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
bottle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
money	O
scale	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
BROWN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
children	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
sixpence	O
and	O
some	O
victuals	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
child	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
play	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Nelly	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
(	O
enumerates	O
the	O
things	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
flurried	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
crowd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
:	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
East-smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HURN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
things	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Staples	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
eighteen-pence	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Harn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
woman	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
child	O
again	O
directly	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
LACEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
duplicates	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
duplicates	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PENTELOW	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
duplicates	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
was	O
playing	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
547.	O
MARY	B-pers
ANN	I-pers
KIRKHAM	I-pers
and	O
ANN	B-pers
MADDEN	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
called	O
upon	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
KIRKHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
these	O
prisoner	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
this	O
property	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
them	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
man	O
naked	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
STEVENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
fighting	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
said	O
as	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
nominated	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
nobody	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
548.	O
JOHN	B-pers
DYER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
a	O
certain	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
wherein	O
was	O
contained	O
a	O
certain	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
acceptance	O
,	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
Joseph	O
Chaplin	O
Hankey	O
,	O
for	O
Thomas	O
Hankey	O
,	O
Stephen	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
said	O
bill	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
words	O
and	O
figures	O
following	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
``	O
No	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Richmond	O
,	O
``	O
Surry	O
,	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1790	O
.	O
Fourteen	O
``	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
``	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
``	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
as	O
advised.	O
``	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Accepted	O
for	O
Self	O
and	O
``	O
Co.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
.	O
''	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
feloniously	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
acceptance	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
as	O
true	O
the	O
said	O
forged	O
acceptance	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
A	O
fourth	O
count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Messrs.	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Silvester	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
PERDIE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
,	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Bond-street	I-place
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
wax-chandler	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
had	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
that	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
to	O
order	O
some	O
candles	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
thirty-six	O
pounds	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
for	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
Mrs.	O
Vernon	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
order	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
me	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
the	O
candles	O
she	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
the	O
bill	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
first	O
the	O
bill	O
should	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
then	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
change	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bill	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
:	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
for	O
ten	O
pounds	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
took	O
any	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
same	O
bill	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
VERNON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
conduct	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
,	O
the	O
wax-chandler	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
for	O
the	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
brought	O
this	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
out	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
for	O
thirty-six	O
pounds	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
for	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
;	O
and	O
this	O
bill	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
out	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
,	O
the	O
banker	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
had	O
to	O
run	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
yesterday	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
indorsers	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Conran	O
,	O
of	O
Berkley-square	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
received	O
that	O
bill	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Conran	O
,	O
of	O
Berkley-square	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
otherwise	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
indorse	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
certainly	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
;	O
he	O
then	O
returned	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
of	O
having	O
wrote	O
a	O
fictitious	O
name	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Lambridge	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
aman	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
resembled	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
wrote	O
a	O
fictitious	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
accomplices	O
in	O
other	O
forgeries	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
bill	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
has	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mark	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
marked	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
bill	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CROSS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
in	O
Messrs.	O
Hankeys	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
partners	O
are	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
acceptance	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
our	O
acceptance	O
.	O
Does	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Richmond	O
,	O
keep	O
cash	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
no	O
such	O
account	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
clerks	O
that	O
accept	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
partners	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
do	O
sometimes	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
seldom	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
undertake	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
acceptance	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
such	O
firm	O
as	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
;	O
whoever	O
accepts	O
the	O
bills	O
puts	O
the	O
two	O
letters	O
of	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
name	O
written	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chaplain	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
other	O
house	O
in	O
London	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hankey	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note-read	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
No	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Richmond	O
,	O
Surry	O
,	O
``	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
90	O
.	O
Fourteen	O
days	O
after	O
``	O
date	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
``	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
value	O
``	O
received	O
as	O
advised	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
To	O
``	O
Messrs.	O
Hankeys	O
,	O
bankers	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
accepted	O
``	O
for	O
Self	O
and	O
Co.	O
Joseph	O
Chaplain	O
``	O
Hankey	O
.	O
''	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMALLWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Conran	O
of	O
Berkley-square	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
writing	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
bill	O
,	O
G.	O
B.	O
Conran	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
writing	O
he	O
puts	O
to	O
his	O
drafts	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
he	O
writes	O
,	O
as	O
many	O
persons	O
do	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
character	O
when	O
he	O
draws	O
,	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
in	O
common	O
?	O
-	O
Very	O
generally	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
drawing	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
drawing	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
on	O
any	O
other	O
occasion	O
than	O
his	O
drawing	O
drafts	O
on	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
other	O
than	O
writing	O
the	O
checks	O
that	O
he	O
draws	O
on	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
other	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
to	O
a	O
draft	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
paying	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forged	O
one	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Kelsey	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
this	O
order	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
to	O
indorse	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
it	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
being	O
unacquainted	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Conran	O
:	O
the	O
order	O
I	O
gave	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
;	O
Sir	O
William	O
was	O
never	O
mentioned	O
:	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
acted	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
fifteen	O
respectable	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
most	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
within	O
the	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
humbly	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
549.	O
MARY	B-pers
CROSS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
twenty-nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
part	O
of	O
certain	O
lead	O
feloniously	O
stolen	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
and	O
whereof	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kensington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
builder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
from	O
some	O
carcases	O
of	O
houses	O
,	O
in	O
Manchester-square	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
houses	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
middle	O
gutters	O
:	O
information	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
4th	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
lad	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watchman	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
:	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
compared	O
,	O
and	O
matched	O
exactly	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
circumstance	O
but	O
the	O
matching	O
;	O
it	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
removed	O
ready	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
lead	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ROBSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
John	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
into	O
custody	O
:	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
KELLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
apprehended	O
Merchant	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
into	O
custody	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
lead	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gale	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cheeseman	O
present	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Cross	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
himself	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
went	O
without	O
your	O
consent	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
my	O
consent	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
Cross	O
's	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
trap	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
induce	O
them	O
to	O
buy	O
this	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prosecute	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
pardon	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
wrong	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
already	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
moved	O
from	O
the	O
premises	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
any	O
consent	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
refuse	O
the	O
consent	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
allow	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
trap	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
spring	O
on	O
the	O
game	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
your	O
cramp	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
nobody	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
this	O
boy	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
farthing	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
promised	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
trap	O
for	O
somebody	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Was	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
's	O
husband	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CHEESEMAN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
any	O
lead	O
of	O
that	O
boy	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
immediately	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
:	O
they	O
tried	O
to	O
put	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kelly	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
told	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
presence	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
marked	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
and	O
two	O
lads	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
publick-house	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
honest	O
man	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
boy	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Whose	O
scheme	O
was	O
it	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
boy	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
,	O
an	O
iron-monger	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
agreed	O
among	O
you	O
all	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
passed	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
thought	O
Mrs.	O
Cross	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
originally	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
convicted	O
of	O
felony	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
lead	O
actually	O
gets	O
to	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
scheme	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
this	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
party	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
lead	O
should	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
stolen	O
goods	O
:	O
you	O
must	O
acquit	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
morality	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
550.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BULL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
some	O
carpenters	O
tools	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CARRINGTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
tools	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
shillings	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
building	O
,	O
behind	O
some	O
doors	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
moved	O
down	O
below	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
SHARP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
tools	O
laying	O
in	O
an	O
unfinished	O
house	O
in	O
Finsbury-street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
plow	O
,	O
a	O
stock	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
,	O
an	O
adze	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dove	O
tail	O
saw	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
floor	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
working	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
building	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
not	O
fastened	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fence	O
seven	O
feet	O
high	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
must	O
get	O
over	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
hard	O
by	O
this	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
about	O
for	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
in	O
one	O
posture	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
walked	O
round	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
get	O
over	O
a	O
place	O
seven	O
feet	O
high	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
an	O
alarm	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
caught	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
PORTER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
board	O
crack	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
:	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
551.	O
JOHN	B-pers
REEVES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cambrick	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
VAUGHAN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grafton-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
fifteen	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
some	O
cotton	O
and	O
some	O
neck	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
various	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Crouch	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
at	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
's	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CROUCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
neck	O
handkerchief	O
for	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
care	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
552.	O
BAKER	B-pers
WALLER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
eight	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jeremy	I-pers
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
553.	O
MARY	B-pers
WALKER	I-pers
and	O
HANNAH	B-pers
LOUT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
witnesses	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
)	O
ANN	B-pers
HALES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blue	B-place
Anchor-court	I-place
,	I-place
Cable-street	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
lately	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
service	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Mark-lane	O
.	O
With	O
whom	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
(	O
No	O
answer	O
.	O
)	O
Why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
answer	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
woman	O
;	O
who	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
rent	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
rented	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Blue	O
Anchor-court	O
.	O
Did	O
Murphy	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
live	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
your	O
room	O
in	O
:	O
how	O
many	O
rooms	O
did	O
the	O
house	O
consist	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
Only	O
one	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoners	O
Counsel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
had	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
service	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
She	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
got	O
,	O
andfurnished	O
you	O
this	O
place	O
to	O
receive	O
men	O
in	O
:	O
we	O
all	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
very	O
well	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
only	O
paid	O
half-a-crown	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pay	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
houses	O
were	O
there	O
consisting	O
of	O
one	O
room	O
each	O
only	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
only	O
one	O
room	O
.	O
Who	O
rented	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
rooms	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
one	O
door	O
or	O
two	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
doors	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
entry	O
:	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Jury	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
trying	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
for	O
their	O
lives	O
;	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
convicted	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
reward	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
make	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
-	O
Out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
off	O
the	O
tea	O
table	O
;	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
candle	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
her	O
own	O
information	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
rents	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
,	O
in	O
Blue	O
Anchor-yard	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
abed	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
:	O
where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
see	O
my	O
friends	O
:	O
my	O
stays	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
back	O
by	O
ten	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
from	O
ten	O
till	O
eleven	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
front	O
door	O
,	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
green	O
stall	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
your	O
stays	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
stays	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
one	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
girls	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
the	O
thief-taker	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
tried	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Dawson	O
tell	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
rented	O
a	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
to	O
be	O
divided	O
among	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
hanged	O
these	O
girls	O
?	O
-	O
Nobody	O
.	O
These	O
girls	O
lived	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
court	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
you	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
man	O
stole	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
you	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
girls	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
left	O
your	O
stays	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lout	I-pers
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
within	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
DAWSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Moses	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Who	O
advised	O
this	O
indictment	O
for	O
burglary	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
committed	O
for	O
burglary	O
.	O
ABRAHAM	B-pers
MOSES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Walker	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Idelivered	O
them	O
to	O
Dawson	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
stays	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
Five	O
shillings	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
clothes	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
here	O
?	O
-	O
Once	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
accused	O
of	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stays	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
cost	O
me	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
MURPHY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
about	O
eight	O
days	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
girls	O
have	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
only	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
twelve	O
tenements	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
girl	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
place	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
HERITAGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
girl	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
bl	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
coast	O
was	O
clear	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
knock	O
the	O
staple	O
in	O
fast	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
say	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
Hannah	B-pers
Lout	I-pers
;	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
voice	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Walker	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lout	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
BOTH	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
554.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NORMAN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Bush	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
Staines	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
my	O
watch	O
on	O
a	O
nail	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
quartered	O
there	O
;	O
several	O
people	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
five	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
on	O
duty	O
at	O
Kensington	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
waiters	O
that	O
is	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Bush	O
,	O
gave	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
nail	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Staines	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
smiled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
serjeant	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Taylor	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
W.	O
S.	O
a	O
cypher	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
;	O
the	O
witness	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
Staines	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
promised	O
forgiveness	O
,	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
garden	O
gate	O
;	O
and	O
behind	O
that	O
gate	O
,	O
under	O
some	O
straw	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
more	O
,	O
only	O
begged	O
for	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
marked	O
W.	O
S.	O
)	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Strange	I-pers
's	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
seen	O
laying	O
at	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
tub	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
that	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Judgment	O
respited	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
555.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BATTERS	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
BATHURST	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
26th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Hanover	O
square	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Probyn	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
28th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
marry	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
to	O
wife	O
,	O
one	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Jemmitt	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
full	O
health	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
JULIANA	B-pers
HAYNES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bolsover-street	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Susannah	B-pers
Probyn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
was	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Probyn	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
of	O
age	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
older	O
than	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
-	O
GREVILLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
deputy	O
parish	O
clerk	O
at	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
:	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
register	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
entry	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
FRANCIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jemmitt	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
at	O
Bloomsbury-church	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
was	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
JEMMITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
courted	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Near	O
seven	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
family	O
;	O
he	O
represented	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
single	O
man	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
after	O
marriage	O
,	O
I	O
discovered	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HARRISON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
parish	O
clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
register	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
entry	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Batters	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Jemmitt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
556.	O
JAMES	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
quanty	O
of	O
carpenters	O
tools	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Owens	I-pers
;	O
and	O
other	O
tools	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hocking	I-pers
.	O
PETER	B-pers
OWENS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
Sloane-street	B-place
,	I-place
Chelsea	I-place
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
almost	O
finished	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
belonging	O
to	O
Hocking	O
:	O
(	O
repeats	O
them	O
)	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
basket	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
HOCKING	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
tools	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
Imissed	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
RICHARD	B-pers
MORRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
two	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
by	O
with	O
these	O
tools	O
:	O
we	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
at	O
Brompton-row	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
the	O
tools	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
tools	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tools	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WOOLLET	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
very	O
true	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
557.	O
JAMES	B-pers
CONWAY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
JACKSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
from	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
person	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
distress	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
redeemed	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoons	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Miss	O
Jackson	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
a	O
cloak	O
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
NOT	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
558.	O
BARNARD	B-pers
KING	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
furnace	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
THORTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
copper	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
Oxford-street	B-place
,	O
exposed	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
stove	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lurking	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
son	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
THORNTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stoop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Imprisoned	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
559.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
FLOCKTON	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
ofJune	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Reuben	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
.	O
REUBEN	B-pers
CLARE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
4	I-place
,	I-place
Coppice-row	I-place
,	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
sought	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
a	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
brought	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
suspected	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
hat	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
Whipped	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
560.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BRAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Blewitt	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
HOGGITT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blewitt	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
dined	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
carriage	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
or	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
when	O
the	O
carriage	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BRAMBLE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
on	O
sixteen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
to	O
pledge	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
box	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
box	O
coat	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
damned	O
good	O
box	O
coat	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
pledged	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
Mews	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
owner	O
,	O
I	O
pledged	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
561.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
ROOKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
ELISHA	B-pers
RAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morrett	O
,	O
of	O
Rose-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
on	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
twenty-two	O
shillings	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
claimed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Allman	O
,	O
son-in-law	O
to	O
Christiana	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
watch	O
.	O
CHRISTIANA	B-pers
HOWELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
afterwards	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
frequently	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
.	O
BRIDGET	B-pers
CANE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
at	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
if	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
comb	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
watch	O
till	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
nobody	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
her	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
six	O
years	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
lived	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
with	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
she	O
never	O
missed	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nobody	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
wrapped	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
stable-yard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
owner	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
bads	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
uses	O
bad	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
owes	O
me	O
a	O
spite	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Christiana	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
She	O
did	O
work	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
honest	O
before	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
her	O
be	O
privately	O
whipped	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
punishment	O
I	O
inflict	O
on	O
you	O
,	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
character	O
your	O
mistress	O
has	O
given	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
you	O
may	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
such	O
scrapes	O
again	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BULLER	O
.	O
562.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
LINCOLN	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thickset	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckeloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
KELLY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
watchman	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
and	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Cross-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
called	O
on	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILSON	O
.	O
563.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
WALL	I-pers
,	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WELLING	I-pers
,	O
and	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MILLINGTON	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cotton	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
hempen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
bird	O
cage	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
tame	O
canary	O
bird	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
ELEANOR	B-pers
GORDON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Harrow	B-place
Road	I-place
,	I-place
Paddington	I-place
.	O
Our	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
town	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
bonnet	O
into	O
the	O
front	O
room	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
cupboard	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
windows	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
beads	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
flower-pots	O
pushed	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
daisies	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
stocks	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
three	O
bonnets	O
,	O
the	O
canary	O
bird	O
and	O
cage	O
,	O
a	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
bonnets	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
canary	O
bird	O
and	O
cage	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bird	O
cage	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
four	O
bottom	O
knobbs	O
.	O
HENRY	B-pers
EMMETT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
Three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
labour	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Welling	O
's	O
field	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
farther	O
than	O
her	O
house	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
lay	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
bonnets	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
a	O
bird	O
cage	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
canary	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
across	O
a	O
field	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Croker	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoners	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Welling	O
's	O
yard	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Croker	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
met	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
field	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
Croker	O
drew	O
his	O
cutlass	O
;	O
and	O
Wall	O
threw	O
away	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
Wall	O
walking	O
or	O
talking	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Croker	O
stop	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
had	O
the	O
bird	O
cage	O
and	O
the	O
canary	O
,	O
and	O
Welling	O
had	O
three	O
bonnets	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
anda	O
boy	O
's	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
besides	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Croker	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
bird	O
cage	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
:	O
Croker	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
bird	O
cage	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bonnet	O
and	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoners	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Gordon	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Croker	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
while	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Wall	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
three	O
weeks	O
we	O
met	O
Welling	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
WELLING	O
's	O
and	O
MILLINGTON	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
.	O
ALL	O
THREE	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Each	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
564.	O
HANNAH	B-pers
CAVENOR	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
bed-quilt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Stockford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ACQUITTED	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
565.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FISHER	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
one	O
watch	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crutchfield	I-pers
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CRUTCHFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
wound	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
Lumley	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
