TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ALSO	O
The	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE	O
HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD	O
BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1791	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
following	O
Days	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
FOURTH	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Boydell	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
OF	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
TAKEN	O
IN	O
SHORT-HAND	O
BY	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
,	O
PROFESSOR	O
OF	O
SHORT-HAND	O
;	O
And	O
Published	O
by	O
Authority	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
PART	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
E.	O
HODGSON	O
(	O
the	O
Proprietor	O
)	O
;	O
And	O
Sold	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
White	O
Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Islington	O
;	O
Sold	O
also	O
by	O
J.	O
WALMSLAY	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
;	O
S.	O
BLADON	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXCI	O
.	O
THE	O
TRIALS	O
AT	O
LARGE	O
,	O
OF	O
THE	O
CAPITAL	O
and	O
other	O
CONVICTS	O
,	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BOYDELL	I-pers
,	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
LLOYD	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
KENYON	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
BEAUMONT	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
HEATH	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAM	I-pers
ROSE	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
JOHN	B-pers
SILVESTER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Common	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
First	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Curzon	I-pers
Addis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Axtell	I-pers
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Adamthwaite	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Norville	I-pers
James	B-pers
Farthing	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Peirsey	I-pers
Dudley	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
James	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Champney	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Frederic	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bingley	I-pers
Harry	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Arnett	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Strout	I-pers
John	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Harriott	I-pers
William	B-pers
French	I-pers
Matthew	O
Hellier	O
Henry	B-pers
Tedder	I-pers
Phillip	B-pers
Day	I-pers
*	O
*	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
served	O
some	O
time	O
on	O
this	O
Jury	O
.	O
First	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Holby	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Foresyght	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Greentree	I-pers
Leonard	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
James	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Lawrance	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
David	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Second	O
Mid	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
Evan	B-pers
David	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
William	B-pers
West	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Lambley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
John	B-pers
Boon	I-pers
+	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Dyson	I-pers
served	O
on	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boon	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quintil	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Gillies	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Tuck	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mayo	I-pers
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
London	O
Jury	O
was	O
sworn	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
First	O
discharged	O
.	O
144.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SIMMONDS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Levison	I-pers
Gower	I-pers
.	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
HARRIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Admiral	O
Gower	B-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
up	O
a	O
differentname	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
sent	O
his	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
few	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
and	O
called	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
just	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
shuffling	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
or	O
breeches	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
out	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
to	O
the	O
back-parlour	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
laid	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
STALEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
spoon	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
The	O
parlour-door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gower	O
's	O
hat	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
on	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
cleaned	O
these	O
spoons	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
once	O
lived	O
a	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
knows	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
supported	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
's	O
election	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
two	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
145.	O
JEREMIAH	B-pers
BOWERS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
school-boy	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cold	O
Bath-fields	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
coach-master	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
,	O
Grace-church-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Smithfield	B-place
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
it	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
be	O
off	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
box	O
;	O
Frances	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
across	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
after	O
striking	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
boy	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
was	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
struck	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
hand	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
goods	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
FRANCES	B-pers
GRAY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
;	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
through	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
Smith	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
box	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
should	O
he	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
upp	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wooden	O
box	O
.	O
MARY	B-pers
PAGE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
on	O
coming	O
through	O
Smithfield	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
behind	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knocked	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
arm	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
pushed	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
upon	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
Gray	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
thebox	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scuffle	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
Gray	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
Frances	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
hit	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
ran	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
LUCY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
packed	O
it	O
up	O
myself	O
at	O
Chatham	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
articles	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Chatham	O
coach	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
box	O
till	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
screwed	O
down	O
with	O
two	O
screws	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
violently	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
146.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ANGUS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dudley	B-pers
Hyett	I-pers
.	O
DUDLEY	O
HYETT	O
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	O
while	O
a	O
cart	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
it	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
RYCROFT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
book	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
FENNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
book	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
147.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
and	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
cutting	O
and	O
ripping	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
TANNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
Grubb-street	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
copper	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nine	O
houses	O
at	O
Pimlico	O
.	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
PENNY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
has	O
nine	O
houses	O
at	O
Pimlico	O
on	O
last	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Hatchett	O
who	O
lives	O
opposite	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
rang	O
my	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
on	O
the	O
houses	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
nine	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sheet	O
of	O
copper	O
rolled	O
up	O
ready	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
:	O
Holt	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
GARRARD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
last	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
alarm	O
of	O
thieves	O
on	O
the	O
houses	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
escape	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
somebody	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Wright	O
comeout	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
Lady	O
Dacres	O
's	O
Alms-houses	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
SIMPSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
copper	O
from	O
the	O
building	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
gutter	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
ripped	O
off	O
the	O
biggest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
gutter	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
moved	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
ripped	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
gutter	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
fitted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
matched	O
exactly	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
EDWARDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
former	O
witnesses	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Holt	O
coming	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
copper	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hat	O
which	O
had	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
Wright	O
owned	O
as	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
ZEAL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
James	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
assisted	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
LOWERY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
only	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
with	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
Edins	O
appeared	O
for	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Serjeant	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
appeared	O
for	O
James	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
HOLT	I-pers
,	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
,	O
BOTH	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
148.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hammond	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
ANN	B-pers
PAIN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
twelve	O
years	O
next	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Park-lane	B-place
,	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
swear	O
wrong	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
devil	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
swear	O
right	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
tap-room	O
,	O
making	O
shirts	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Park-lane	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
nobody	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
plate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
marking	O
of	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
to	O
thread	O
my	O
needle	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
shirt	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
caught	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
WATERFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
caught	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
crying	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirt	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
shirt	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
for	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
shirt	O
on	O
the	O
tap-room	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
walked	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
149.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ALLET	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
order	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
dated	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1790	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
,	O
thereto	O
subscribed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
signed	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
directed	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Prescott	O
,	O
Grote	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
William	I-pers
Prescott	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
for	O
uttering	O
a	O
like	O
forged	O
order	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
like	O
intent	O
.	O
A	O
third	O
and	O
fourth	O
counts	O
for	O
feloniouslyforging	O
and	O
uttering	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
,	O
to	O
defraud	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
indictment	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
case	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Enfield	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
in	O
Waltham	O
fair	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
,	O
or	O
twenty-five	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
horse	O
rode	O
;	O
we	O
parted	O
without	O
agreeing	O
for	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
my	O
return	O
from	O
the	O
fair	O
home	O
to	O
Enfield	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
about	O
other	O
business	O
,	O
not	O
particularly	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
introduced	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
twenty-four	O
pounds	O
five	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
note	O
(	O
the	O
note	O
produced	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
change	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
morning	O
I	O
presented	O
it	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
refused	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
until	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
ever	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
dealt	O
in	O
the	O
wholesale	O
way	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
what	O
part	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
written	O
direction	O
as	O
his	O
address	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
direction	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
else	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
horse	O
home	O
with	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spurs	O
and	O
a	O
bridle	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
refused	O
at	O
Mess	O
.	O
Prescotts	O
and	O
Co.	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
New-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
had	O
a	O
conversation	O
of	O
some	O
length	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Waltham-abbey	O
fair	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
bargained	O
very	O
hard	O
about	O
this	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
He	O
offered	O
at	O
first	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
price	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
informed	O
you	O
before	O
.	O
You	O
asked	O
him	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
you	O
be	O
settling	O
,	O
or	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
settle	O
at	O
the	O
fair	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Enfield	O
we	O
settled	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
First	O
of	O
all	O
answer	O
my	O
question	O
;	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
at	O
all	O
at	O
Waltham-abbey	O
fair	O
?	O
-	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
offer	O
you	O
as	O
low	O
as	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
at	O
that	O
fair	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
offer	O
you	O
something	O
less	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
him	O
your	O
address	O
at	O
Enfield	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
you	O
could	O
agree	O
at	O
Enfield	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
returned	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
conversations	O
about	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
agreed	O
together	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
this	O
draft	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
price	O
unless	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
draft	O
he	O
received	O
at	O
the	O
fair	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
fair	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
cash	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
creditable	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
note	O
would	O
be	O
equally	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
draft	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
New-street	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
?	O
-	O
From	O
the	O
directions	O
he	O
gave	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
New-street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Prescott	O
has	O
a	O
considerable	O
seat	O
in	O
your	O
neighbourhood	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
the	O
credit	O
of	O
that	O
note	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
of	O
your	O
saddle	O
and	O
bridle	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
burnt	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
where	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
lodged	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
learn	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
himself	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
some	O
stable	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
deposited	O
this	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
learn	O
that	O
as	O
a	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
learn	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
fire	O
at	O
the	O
stable	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
deposited	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
learn	O
,	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
fact	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
stable	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
deposited	O
the	O
horse	O
had	O
been	O
burned	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
learned	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
at	O
Enfield	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
fire	O
happen	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
draft	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
No	O
62	O
,	O
Threadneedle-street	O
,	O
May	O
3	O
,	O
``	O
1790	O
.	O
``	O
Mess	O
.	O
Prescott	O
,	O
Grote	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
pay	O
``	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rice	O
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
25	O
l.	O
``	O
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Junior	O
.	O
''	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PARRY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Prescott	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
keeping	O
cash	O
as	O
James	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
recollect	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
By	O
the	O
books	O
.	O
Only	O
by	O
the	O
books	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
customers	O
we	O
have	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
it	O
makes	O
me	O
more	O
certain	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
customers	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Long	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
directions	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
``	O
George	B-pers
Allett	I-pers
,	O
New-street	O
,	O
Covent	O
``	O
Garden	O
.	O
''	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
give	O
checks	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
that	O
asks	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
To	O
customers	O
we	O
do	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
draft	O
at	O
the	O
fair	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cruthers	O
,	O
of	O
Stepney-fields	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
place	O
,	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
my	O
address	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
street	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
confused	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
notorious	O
facts	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
be	O
proved	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
?	O
-	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
not	O
appeared	O
,	O
was	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
on	O
purpose	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
This	O
trial	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
last	O
sessions	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
witnesses	O
not	O
being	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
by	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
of	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
KENYON	O
.	O
150.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DRUCE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dresser	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
burglariously	O
stealing	O
,	O
nine	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
DRESSER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
we	O
were	O
violently	O
alarmed	O
by	O
a	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
string	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
caught	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
glove	O
inside	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
cut	O
above	O
the	O
glove	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
one	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
ATKINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
talking	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
cut	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
light	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Dresser	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
distinguished	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
under	O
my	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
them	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
them	O
down	O
myself	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
CRISP	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
on	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directly	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
making	O
any	O
observations	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
man	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
those	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
prentice	O
to	O
a	O
fishing-smack	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
she	O
failed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
aunt	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
12	O
.	O
)	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
youth	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
151.	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYAN	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
called	I-pers
GEORGE	I-pers
KING	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
made	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
steel	O
bed-hook	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
TANNER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
privately	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
watch	O
upon	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
Hare	B-place
court	I-place
,	I-place
Aldersgate-street	I-place
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Edward	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
following	O
me	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
to	O
dress	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hair-dresser	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
dressed	O
me	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
immediately	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Tottenham-court-road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
Sir	O
Sampson	O
's	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
a	O
metal	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
steel	O
bed-hook	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHAFFINCH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
three	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
he	O
dressed	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
7482	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Freake	I-pers
.	O
)	O
(	O
Watch	O
banded	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
MARY	B-pers
MANSFIELD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
his	O
watch	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
valueof	O
the	O
watch	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
the	O
hall	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
shop-mate	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Woodward	O
that	O
morning	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
152.	O
JOHN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
found	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
his	O
sentence	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
OWEN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
certificate	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shelton	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
conviction	O
.	O
(	O
Read	O
.	O
)	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
February	O
Session	O
,	O
1784	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
highway	O
robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pardoned	O
on	O
condition	O
of	O
being	O
transported	O
to	O
America	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penderry	I-pers
called	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
ROBINSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1787	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
some	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
out	O
six	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
1787	O
,	O
until	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
!	O
why	O
this	O
was	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
can	O
you	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
counsel	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
lunar	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
callendar	O
months	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
153.	O
ISAAC	B-pers
REGUS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Tennant	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
eight	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
MARY	B-pers
JOHNSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hare-court	B-place
,	O
and	O
only	O
rent	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Tennant	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
lets	O
his	O
house	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
with	O
two	O
padlocks	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
lock	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tub	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
the	O
linen	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
ANN	B-pers
RUTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
SHAKESHAFT	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
Produces	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
)	O
Ihave	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
ever	O
since	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Phillips	O
.	O
-	O
PHILLIPS	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Shakeshaft	O
.	O
To	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Phillips	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
bundles	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Spitalfields-market	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
respectable	O
people	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
five	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Of	O
stealing	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
HEATH	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
154.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TAYLOR	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	B-place
Hampshire	I-place
Hog	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
awoke	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
began	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
escaped	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
woman	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
patrole	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
flush	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
him	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
LEWIS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
tin	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
left-hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
back-door	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
Taylor	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
Dudley-court	O
,	O
in	O
Crown	O
street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
Taylor	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
Milk-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
before	O
that	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
mulled	O
raspberry	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
asleep	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Lewis	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Dudley-court	O
,	O
Crown	O
street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
and	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
some	O
gin	O
and	O
raspberry	O
.	O
The	O
PATROLE	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
patrole	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	B-pers
the	O
next	O
evening	O
dressed	O
in	O
another	O
garb	O
than	O
usual	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
under	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
you	O
these	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
heel	O
of	O
his	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
18	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
KENYON	O
.	O
155.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHASELAND	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Copps	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
hundredand	O
thirty	O
new	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
COPPS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
7	I-place
,	I-place
Ratcliffe-row	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
five	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
thieves	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
WYNN	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Copps	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
there	O
weekly	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back-parlour	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
front	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
bundles	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
missed	O
one	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
Rigbey	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
space	O
.	O
MARY-ANN	O
JACKSON	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
,	O
I	O
just	O
let	O
my	O
young	O
mistress	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
immediately	O
,	O
it	O
opens	O
with	O
a	O
spring	O
latch	O
inside	O
and	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
nobody	O
answered	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
apron	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
one	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
apron	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
tie	O
up	O
the	O
bundles	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
but	O
himself	O
and	O
us	O
two	O
women	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
RIGBEY	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
garden	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
bundles	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
through	O
the	O
garden	O
fence	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
tie	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
girls	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
fence	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Spiller	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Copps	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
seal	O
upon	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
opened	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Not	O
of	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
value	O
above	O
40	O
s.	O
Recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
19	O
.	O
)	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
first	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
156.	O
ROBERT	B-pers
JONES	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
and	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Whitewood	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
SARAH	B-pers
WHITEWOOD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Whitewood	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fisher-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
servant	O
maid	O
who	O
went	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
husband	O
fasten	O
the	O
house	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
a	O
lodger	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
being	O
very	O
poorly	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
which	O
comes	O
intothe	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bladder	O
with	O
some	O
gin	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
suppose	O
whoever	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
cellar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
lets	O
the	O
light	O
in	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
beer	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
place	O
bolted	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
bolted	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
gin	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
steps	O
that	O
come	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
cellar	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Winch	O
has	O
the	O
gin	O
.	O
CHARLES	B-pers
NEWTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
some	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
dog	O
laying	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
on	O
other	O
suspicious	O
occasions	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
seize	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
distant	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlady	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Whitewood	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
this	O
cellar	O
window	O
fastened	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
husband	O
fasten	O
and	O
bolt	O
it	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
near	O
Red	O
Lion-square	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
examined	O
and	O
stripped	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
157.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
duffel	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
.	O
JAMES	B-pers
GRAINGER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
68	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-market	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
duffel	O
jacket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
at	O
twelve	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
saw	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
jacket	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
ORTON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
jacket	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Grainger	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unpin	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
is	O
almost	O
opposite	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
back-door	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
jacket	O
upon	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
it	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
JOLDS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Orton	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
unpin	O
the	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
master	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
jacket	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
SINGLETON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
produce	O
the	O
jacket	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lad	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
this	O
jacket	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Whipped	O
,	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
158.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
sixbushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wylde	I-pers
.	O
And	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YOSTUS	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
coals	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
WYLDE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
coal-wharf	O
in	O
Town-lane	O
,	O
Upper	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
servants	O
load	O
sixty-three	O
sacks	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kinloth	O
's	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
;	O
John	O
Hill	O
was	O
to	O
drive	O
one	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
the	O
other	O
.	O
-	O
SHARP	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
two	O
men	O
standing	O
opposite	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
and	O
Still	O
,	O
loaded	O
with	O
coals	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
Barker	O
,	O
take	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
towards	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Yostus	O
conduct	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
sacks	O
empty	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
Yostus	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
lodge	O
there	O
;	O
Yostus	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
carmen	O
walked	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
Yostus	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
,	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Bond-street	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
joined	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
both	O
the	O
empty	O
sacks	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
waggon	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wylde	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Tyburn-turnpike	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kinloth	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
men	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coals	O
all	O
shot	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wylde	O
These	O
coals	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
speaking	O
of	O
were	O
loaded	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
from	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
how	O
many	O
number	O
of	O
sacks	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
all	O
the	O
coals	O
put	O
into	O
those	O
waggons	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Wylde	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
count	O
the	O
sacks	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
waggons	O
were	O
they	O
put	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
my	O
waggons	O
.	O
Hath	O
Mr.	O
Wylde	O
any	O
partners	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
these	O
coals	O
loaded	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
loaded	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
,	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
all	O
day	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
until	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
were	O
added	O
to	O
that	O
number	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
coals	O
put	O
into	O
these	O
waggons	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
to	O
Sharp	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
some	O
waggons	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
wrote	O
on	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
pretty	O
near	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wylde	I-pers
,	O
Crown-lane	O
,	O
Upper	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
might	O
you	O
be	O
from	O
Yostus	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
carmen	O
?	O
-	O
Half	O
the	O
width	O
of	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
It	O
so	O
happened	O
,	O
that	O
Yostus	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
with	O
the	O
coals	O
on	O
their	O
backs	O
,	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
;	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
men	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
coals	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
any	O
conversation	O
took	O
place	O
between	O
Yostus	O
and	O
the	O
bearer	O
of	O
the	O
coals	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
simply	O
Will	O
with	O
the	O
Whisp	O
walking	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
different	O
direction	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
happened	O
to	O
know	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
different	O
direction	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Because	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
being	O
confused	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
,	O
you	O
imagine	O
so	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
external	O
appearance	O
to	O
judge	O
of	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
.	O
They	O
joined	O
again	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
did	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
Yostus	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
whatever	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
fact	O
is	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
those	O
coals	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
them	O
carried	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
conducted	O
by	O
Yostus	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
those	O
coals	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wylde	I-pers
told	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
for	O
aught	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
waggons	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
some	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Wylde	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
serve	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
coals	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
gentleman	O
describes	O
the	O
two	O
sacks	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LEVI	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Yostus	O
lodges	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
done	O
for	O
this	O
half	O
year	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
order	O
coals	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
any	O
coals	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
brought	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
put	O
you	O
in	O
mind	O
of	O
your	O
situation	O
:	O
a	O
man	O
lodges	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
stands	O
charged	O
here	O
with	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
evidently	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wylde	O
;	O
remember	O
you	O
stand	O
here	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
intricate	O
situation	O
yourself	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
early	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
what	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
lodgers	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
not	O
all	O
separate	O
places	O
for	O
their	O
coals	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
generally	O
keep	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
rooms	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
vault	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Levi	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
first	O
informed	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Sharpe	O
informed	O
me	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
coals	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
coals	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
you	O
the	O
curiosity	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
if	O
any	O
coals	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
in	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
bring	O
myself	O
into	O
trouble	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
went	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
to	O
bring	O
yourself	O
into	O
trouble	O
;	O
is	O
this	O
man	O
a	O
lodger	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
finds	O
his	O
own	O
goods	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
does	O
he	O
lodge	O
in	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Sharp	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
whether	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
coals	O
fresh	O
put	O
down	O
into	O
that	O
cellar	O
?	O
-	O
Between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
Mr.	O
Wyldes	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
coals	O
fresh	O
shot	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
particularly	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Peatt	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Yostus	O
's	O
apartments	O
where	O
the	O
coals	O
were	O
seen	O
?	O
-	O
His	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
coals	O
.	O
Now	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
shewn	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
without	O
this	O
information	O
,	O
should	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
sacks	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
used	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
HILL	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
loaded	O
with	O
five	O
chaldron	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
near	O
Ball-street	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
a	O
sack	O
and	O
follow	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
certainly	O
did	O
unadvisedly	O
take	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
received	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
YOSTUS	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Barker	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
coal	O
in	O
.	O
Hill	O
called	O
three	O
witnesses	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Wylde	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
this	O
action	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Yostus	O
called	O
one	O
witness	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HILL	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
YOSTUS	I-pers
,	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
Transported	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
159.	O
ANN	B-pers
SMITH	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
two	O
pounds	O
nine	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
an	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
;	O
and	O
nine	O
ounces	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
SUSANNAH	B-pers
YORK	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
my	O
silk	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
's	O
room	O
for	O
safety	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pounds	O
nine	O
ounces	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ball's-alley	O
,	O
Wheeler-street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
this	O
silk	O
along	O
with	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
for	O
safety	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
moved	O
my	O
goods	O
in	O
Wheeler-street	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
MARGARET	B-pers
SHEPHERD	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Did	O
Susannah	B-pers
York	I-pers
leave	O
some	O
silk	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
black	O
silk	O
myself	O
,	O
eight	O
knots	O
and	O
six	O
skains	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
court	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
Susannah	O
York	O
's	O
silk	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
black	O
silk	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
silk	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
has	O
them	O
now	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
headborough	O
produced	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
me	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
my	O
apron	O
to	O
treat	O
her	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
29	O
.	O
)	O
Fined	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
imprisoned	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
RECORDER	O
.	O
160.	O
JAMES	B-pers
KELSEY	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
forged	O
paper	O
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1790	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
Richard	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
thereto	O
subscribed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
for	O
Bromfield	O
and	O
Harvey	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
directed	O
to	O
Mess	B-pers
.	I-pers
Child	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
Bankers	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
said	O
note	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
``	O
No	O
.	O
48	O
.	O
30	O
l.	O
Plymouth	O
Bank	O
,	O
``	O
Sep.	O
14	O
,	O
1790	O
.	O
``	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Thomas	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
``	O
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
on	O
demand	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
``	O
received	O
,	O
for	O
``	O
Bromfield	O
and	O
Harvey	O
.	O
''	O
``	O
Entered	O
G.	O
H.	O
July	O
15th	O
.	O
''	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
and	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Mess	O
.	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
A	O
second	O
count	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
the	O
same	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
an	O
indorsement	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
assignment	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
note	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
indorsing	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
''	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Mess	O
.	O
Child	O
and	O
Co.	O
A	O
third	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
uttering	O
the	O
said	O
note	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
indorsement	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
A	O
fourth	O
Count	O
,	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
said	O
note	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
indorsement	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Isaac	B-pers
Swainson	I-pers
.	O
And	O
a	O
fifth	O
Count	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
counterfeit	O
note	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
intention	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
opened	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
the	O
case	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WHITTINGHAM	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
superintendant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Swainson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
proprietor	O
of	O
Velno	O
's	O
vegetable	O
syrup	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
year	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Swainson	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
shewn	O
into	O
my	O
office	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
vegetable	O
syrup	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
medicine	O
for	O
exportation	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
allowance	O
of	O
the	O
medicine	O
,	O
when	O
exported	O
,	O
reduced	O
it	O
to	O
eight	O
shillings	O
a	O
bottle	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
demanded	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
two	O
dozen	O
when	O
packed	O
up	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
nine	O
pounds	O
,	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
paused	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
a	O
considerable	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
twice	O
tha	O
quantity	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
nineteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
two	O
bottles	O
left	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
lady	O
who	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
paralytic	O
stroke	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
following	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
precisely	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
carriage	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
address	O
?	O
his	O
reply	O
was	O
,	O
Captain	O
Simmons	B-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
18	O
,	O
Hartford-street	O
,	O
May	O
Fair	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
note	O
inclosed	O
;	O
on	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
I	O
hesitated	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
reply	O
was	O
,	O
``	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
signify	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
evening	O
at	O
the	O
Cocoa-tree	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
get	O
change	O
directly	O
.	O
''	O
From	O
the	O
mention	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
none	O
but	O
real	O
gentlemen	O
could	O
resort	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
removed	O
in	O
some	O
measure	O
the	O
doubts	O
of	O
my	O
mind	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
previously	O
entertained	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
farther	O
convince	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
his	O
advice	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
change	O
for	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
first	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
difference	O
,	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
banker	O
's	O
the	O
following	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
a	O
forgery	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Schoen	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
This	O
transaction	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
when	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
first	O
called	O
on	O
this	O
business	O
came	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
compting-house	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
that	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
situated	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
passage	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
compting-house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
practice	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
any	O
one	O
that	O
comes	O
,	O
in	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
person	O
came	O
then	O
in	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
drab-coloured	O
coat	O
,	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
round	O
hat	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
candles	O
do	O
you	O
usually	O
sit	O
with	O
in	O
this	O
compting-house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
imagine	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
;	O
sometimes	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
.	O
This	O
transaction	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
long	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
might	O
take	O
up	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
And	O
during	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
above	O
two	O
minutes	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
in	O
course	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
whoever	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
above	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
from	O
this	O
transient	O
view	O
you	O
had	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
candlelight	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
long	O
view	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
it	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
conscience	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
FULLER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
clerks	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mess	O
.	O
Child	O
and	O
Co.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
was	O
any	O
Plymouth	O
bank	O
correspondent	O
with	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
persons	O
whose	O
names	O
appear	O
on	O
this	O
promisory	O
note	O
,	O
have	O
any	O
account	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
that	O
note	O
professes	O
to	O
bear	O
date	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
HAWKER	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Plymouth	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
a	O
house	O
as	O
Bromfield	O
and	O
Harvey	O
,	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
Plymouth	O
bank	O
of	O
that	O
firm	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
certainly	O
have	O
known	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Schoen	O
.	O
You	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
you	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
situation	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
certainly	O
have	O
known	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
SCOTT	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knows	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
on	O
nineteen	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
;	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
at	O
school	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
TOWNSEND	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
officers	O
of	O
Bow-street	O
:	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
the	O
apprehension	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Macmanus	O
,	O
and	O
Jealous	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
Road	O
,	O
Islington	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
45	O
;	O
Jealous	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
Jealous	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Charles	O
,	O
seize	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
breeches-pocket	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
seven	O
notes	O
:	O
(	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Five	O
of	O
Plymouth	O
bank	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
Worcester	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
key	O
off	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
hanging	O
to	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
key	O
opened	O
two	O
trunks	O
which	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
JOHN	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
produce	O
a	O
trunk	O
with	O
its	O
contents	O
,	O
as	O
found	O
at	O
Esther	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
's	O
,	O
Warner-street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
ESTHER	B-pers
SAUNDERS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
Warner-street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
.	O
This	O
trunk	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
what	O
goods	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
this	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
A	O
paper	O
produced	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
purport	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
read	O
.	O
``	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
``	O
March	O
28th	O
,	O
1790	O
.	O
``	O
I	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
,	O
will	O
and	O
impower	O
``	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
,	O
``	O
to	O
proceed	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
``	O
in	O
Great	O
Warner	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
serve	O
``	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
public	O
notice	O
,	O
before	O
two	O
``	O
sufficient	O
witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
``	O
part	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
or	O
deliver	O
to	O
any	O
``	O
person	O
whatever	O
,	O
one	O
article	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
``	O
on	O
his	O
second	O
floor	O
,	O
formerly	O
the	O
``	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
before	O
he	O
``	O
receive	O
sufficient	O
authority	O
from	O
Mr.	O
``	O
James	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
,	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
those	O
impowered	O
``	O
by	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
.	O
Should	O
``	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
act	O
contrary	O
to	O
this	O
public	O
``	O
notice	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
the	O
consequence.	O
``	O
James	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
received	O
this	O
,	O
ever	O
apply	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
he	O
sent	O
this	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
prison	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
respecting	O
this	O
note	O
?	O
-	O
Nothing	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Two	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
paper	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
padlock	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
had	O
taken	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
gentleman	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prison	O
,	O
what	O
passed	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kelsey	O
?	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Kelsey	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
padlock	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
plainest	O
objection	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
the	O
doing	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
I	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
door	O
did	O
he	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
padlock	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
which	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
had	O
taken	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
?	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Never	O
enquired	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
received	O
this	O
paper	O
?	O
-	O
Never	O
,	O
only	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
might	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
prison	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
then	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
room	O
?	O
-	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
trunk	O
that	O
stands	O
before	O
you	O
:	O
did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
that	O
trunk	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
At	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
these	O
papers	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
about	O
these	O
papers	O
;	O
what	O
passed	O
about	O
them	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
these	O
papers	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Kelsey	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
understood	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
,	O
make	O
any	O
answer	O
or	O
observation	O
on	O
your	O
saying	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
it	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
your	O
papers	O
?	O
-	O
On	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
read	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
any	O
observations	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
your	O
apartments	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
apartments	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
has	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
some	O
broker	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
moved	O
the	O
last	O
week	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
lady	O
lived	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
removed	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
the	O
witness	O
was	O
speaking	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
paper	O
produced	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
speaking	O
of	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
attended	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
witness	O
might	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
paper	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Kelsey	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
a	O
padlock	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
might	O
be	O
moved	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
notice	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
E.	O
Saunders	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
examination	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
you	O
;	O
now	O
be	O
careful	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
about	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
imprudent	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wished	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
for	O
himself	O
andher	O
?	O
-	O
If	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
some	O
woman	O
left	O
goods	O
at	O
your	O
lodgings	O
;	O
did	O
that	O
observation	O
apply	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
left	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
imagine	O
it	O
applied	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
talking	O
about	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Schoen	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
trunk	O
opened	O
by	O
Townsend	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Schoen	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
.	O
That	O
trunk	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Warner-street	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
?	O
-	O
In	O
Warner-street	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
wife	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartments	O
in	O
Warner-street	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
(	O
Some	O
copper-plates	O
produced	O
from	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
)	O
JAMES	B-pers
BARTELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
engraver	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
this	O
print	O
has	O
been	O
worked	O
off	O
that	O
plate	O
?	O
(	O
A	O
plate	O
and	O
a	O
print	O
handed	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
examine	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
judgment	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
five	O
?	O
(	O
Five	O
other	O
prints	O
shewn	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
.	O
MATTHEW	B-pers
STANDWICH	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
18	O
,	O
Hartford-street	O
,	O
May	O
Fair	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Simmons	O
lives	O
there	O
.	O
PRISONER	O
's	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
wish	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
notes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
name	O
signed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
second	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
before	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
KENYON	O
.	O
161.	O
JOHN	B-pers
BELASCA	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
forty-four	O
pounds	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
called	O
Scotch	O
thread	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
.	O
GEORGE	B-pers
WILSON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hore	O
,	O
a	O
wharfinger	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Armitage	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Scotch	O
thread	O
was	O
delivered	O
at	O
the	O
wharf	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
quantity	O
delivered	O
before	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
unpacked	O
at	O
the	O
wharf	O
?	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
loaded	O
it	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
articles	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
the	O
carman	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
cart	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
marked	O
with	O
initials	O
,	O
I.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
72	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
articles	O
upon	O
this	O
wharf	O
?	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
putting	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
.	O
ROBERT	O
M'NABB	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
cart	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
taking	O
a	O
load	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
cart	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
I.	O
L.	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
delivering	O
a	O
parcel	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
44	O
,	O
Watling-street	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
thread	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Little	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
Apostle	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
thread	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
EVANS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
I	O
saw	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
bale	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
carman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
bale	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
touched	O
the	O
carman	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
bale	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
hewas	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
except	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DIXON	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
cordwainer	O
's	O
ward	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
bale	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wyman	O
,	O
at	O
71	O
,	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
court	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
begged	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wyman	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
]	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Wilson	O
,	O
marked	O
I.	B-pers
L	I-pers
.	I-pers
72	O
.	O
The	O
bale	O
opened	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
CHARLES	B-pers
REVELL	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wyman	O
,	O
callender	O
,	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bale	O
that	O
was	O
pitched	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
while	O
the	O
carman	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
At	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
turning	O
between	O
two	O
streets	O
in	O
Bow-lane	O
;	O
of	O
course	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
turning	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
?	O
-	O
Not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
MOSES	B-pers
MENDOZA	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bevis	O
Marks	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Portugueze	O
synagogue	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
JOSEPH	B-pers
SEALES	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
the	O
last	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
while	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
GUILTY	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
21	O
.	O
)	O
Transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Tried	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
Jury	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
HOTHAM	I-pers
.	O
162.	O
EDWARD	B-pers
PRITCHARD	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Martha	B-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
our	O
lord	O
the	O
king	O
then	O
being	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
willfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
wooden	O
stick	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
face	O
,	O
back	O
,	O
sides	O
,	O
belly	O
,	O
groin	O
,	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
legs	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
feloniously	O
,	O
willfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
did	O
divers	O
times	O
smite	O
,	O
strike	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
,	O
giving	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	O
,	O
by	O
such	O
smiting	O
,	O
striking	O
,	O
and	O
beating	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
fracture	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
mortal	O
fracture	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
head	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
fractures	O
and	O
bruises	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
of	O
the	O
bruises	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
sides	O
,	O
belly	O
,	O
groin	O
,	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
legs	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
to	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
did	O
languish	O
,	O
and	O
languishing	O
did	O
live	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
said	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
mortal	O
fractures	O
,	O
wounds	O
,	O
and	O
bruises	O
,	O
did	O
die	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
jurors	O
say	O
that	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Martha	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
willfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
above	O
murder	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
case	O
was	O
opened	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
)	O
JOHN	B-pers
SIMS	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
in	O
Hosier-lane	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
to	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
-	O
The	O
door	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
into	O
their	O
premises	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
;	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
particular	O
happening	O
on	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
andheard	O
a	O
monstrous	O
beating	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
some	O
time	O
listening	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
voice	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
dear	O
!	O
O	O
dear	O
!	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
deserve	O
it	O
,	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
voice	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
suppose	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Pritchard	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
head	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
very	O
near	O
spent	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
gasp	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
some	O
assistance	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
either	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
her	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
away	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
several	O
journeymen	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
several	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
judge	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
judge	O
it	O
any	O
thing	O
uncommon	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
them	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garrow	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
heard	O
?	O
-	O
Beating	O
and	O
disputing	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
You	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
near	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
habits	O
of	O
drinking	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
civil	O
whenever	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	B-pers
PAINE	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
keeps	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
in	O
Hosier-lane	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
called	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
Pritchard	O
was	O
beating	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
apartment	O
,	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Pritchard	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
deserve	O
my	O
beating	O
,	O
pray	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
beat	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
into	O
the	O
shuffle-board	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
window	O
was	O
nigher	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
so	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
beating	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
swear	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
this	O
continue	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
it	O
ceased	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
began	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
there	O
pass	O
between	O
the	O
beating	O
ceasing	O
and	O
its	O
beginning	O
again	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
between	O
the	O
beatings	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
distinguish	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
word	O
child	O
mentioned	O
once	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
These	O
unfortunate	O
people	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
-	O
Yes	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
her	O
voice	O
grew	O
so	O
faint	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
ceasing	O
of	O
the	O
beating	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
upper	O
room	O
was	O
left	O
dark	O
.	O
What	O
more	O
past	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
declare	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frightened	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
a	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
quiet	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
past	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Friday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knowlys	O
.	O
In	O
answer	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
say	O
she	O
deserved	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
ELIZABETH	O
AXTELL	O
sworn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
beating	O
another	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
and	O
listened	O
a	O
bit	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
sound	O
as	O
though	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
's	O
back	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
answered	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
from	O
myback	O
window	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
my	O
window	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
say	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
deserve	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
swearing	O
at	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
down	O
stairs	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
where	O
they	O
shoe	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
damning	O
and	O
swearing	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
back	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
to	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
round	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Pritchard	O
lay	O
all	O
along	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
ground	O
where	O
they	O
shoe	O
their	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
face	O
till	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
move	O
her	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
was	O
trying	O
to	O
lift	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
drinking	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
that	O
that	O
has	O
made	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
dying	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
die	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sad	O
situation	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
